Greetings everyone and welcome to Uncommon Radio.
And if you don't like what's being said here, you're probably not welcome, but I'm just joking.
And I would say, by the way, we always kind of date this.
Now, this is the 11th solo, and I just want to bring up lawful timekeeping again.
And it's something, whether you can do it or not, or whether you can't do it or not, it doesn't matter.
Are you aware that there is a lawful timekeeping precedent?
Are you aware that there's lawful money?
Are you aware that there are lawful things to eat?
Are you aware that there's, you know, basically something called law?
I'm not talking about natural law. That's kind of moronic.
It's kind of a pagan excuse.
I'm not talking about pagans where they'd let their hair grow long,
wear dark sunglasses at night and paint their toenails black.
No, that's just a fashion statement.
I'm not talking about just being plain dumb.
But anyway, welcome to Uncommon Radio.
This is American Freedom Radio.
And you are listening to this live on what they call May 11th, 2017, on that ridiculous thing they call the Pope's work schedule,
which all of you follow, by the way.
Not follow, but, you know, the entire society is using that as its corpus diem stuff.
But I would suggest it's already the third month and around the third day.
Yeah, because day starts at noon. Look it up.
Well, no, I don't do that.
By the way, this kind of stuff doesn't make people happy.
Well, it should, actually.
Have you ever heard of – it's better to have love and loss than to never have loved at all.
Isn't it better to have known the truth and be just a little dismayed at the idiots around you than to have never known it at all?
But anyway, when I use words like moron and idiot, by the way, that is just an accurate medical term.
You know, there are other things.
I mean, there's people around that use other stuff, but, you know, that seems to be accurate, I think.
So just for the sake of considering this sonic episode, feel free to call in if you like.
It's 218-339-8525.
Again, it's 218-339-8525.
It is on the left side in a red box on the AFR homepage.
If you don't see it on the left, it's probably on your other left,
and you'll see it in a red box, call in number 218-339-8525.
And if you do prefer the fidelity of Skype, you can use the Uncommon Sense Radio or the Uncommon Radio website email.
You can go on the www.uncommonradio.com and you scroll down.
There will be an email there.
It is a Gmail.
That is also the Skype contact, and I'll just give that out.
It's uncommonsenseradio1 at gmail.com.
That's a numeric one, and hopefully I'll be able to bring you in.
In the meantime, I will just take a momentary pause here because walking and chewing gum is sometimes a little complicated,
and I will bring up the conference manager.
Let's see if we have the phones accessible, and yes, they are.
So here we are.
It is roughly the first week, well, most likely the first week of the third month,
and how many people really even think of anything lawful anymore?
Now, I just wanted to bring up a few things.
One thing I want to bring up is, well, let's say firstly, this is the bell lap, for those that know, one to go of solo episodes.
I think we'll wrap it up around 12 episodes.
I appreciate AFR giving me the ability to do this.
Most of you folks might have heard of Greek Speak or not, but this is around the 11th time.
There will be just the 12th.
I don't think there's going to be a baker dozen.
What you've heard is basically the solo Greek effort, no interference, no co-hosts, very few people calling in,
and just gave a go at it, and I hope it's given some useful information to people.
If you have a program or an operating system to use the files, by the way, or what's known as information.
Secondly, I want to bring up the concept of donations and things like that.
If you folks remember when the solo thing came around, so let's do a four-week experiment on,
let's see how much financial support can be garnered or credit can be sent to AFR regarding the Greek being on.
We set a goal and we exceeded that goal by 30% or 40%.
The people that are tuning in using the old radio vernacular or listening to Greek Speak were very generous.
We met the goal, like I said, over 30% or 40%, and then it kind of went away because it was an experiment.
I just want to bring up this is in terms of the actual needs of AFR.
You also have to keep in mind, let's be honest, I'm not going to be on AFR anymore or any other internet thing.
I'm doing a project that will be more in private.
But AFR is looking for a computer.
If anyone would like to donate a computer or send them or give them or present to them for keeps a computer for archiving,
it just needs to have memory and things like that, please do so.
You can contact them, I guess, on the homepage.
There's contact information and hopefully the email and all that you guys can hook up.
Otherwise, I would just suggest give a donation if you can.
If you have liked the Greek as a going away present, send them some funds of some sort, some credit, just whatever it might be,
just to say thank you.
This was for having the Greek on because folks, I didn't want to say this, but I'll say it.
When I'm gone, you're condemned to stupidity.
Did I just say that?
Yes, sorry, to a certain degree.
Now, most people just like listening to music and radio.
By the way, friends don't let friends listen to bad music.
Why would friends let friends listen to bad, well, you know what I mean.
The thing is, be perceptive, be objective.
I don't want to tout this, but no one's really talking about what's lawful or really how things work.
Sorry, it's kind of sad, but I just want to bring this in because this is real talk.
People don't want real talk.
They don't want real wheat.
They want puffed wheat.
They want puffed rice.
They want free speech, man.
They want, oh, bad vaccines, oh, bad Illuminati.
It runs out of steam.
I mean you do have a little bit of people interviewing people with their own experiences
and whatever stuff, but they come out and it's like, oh, it's typical human stuff.
Yeah, you had a really bad experience, but the way you're explaining it is just not so.
Anyway, I just want to throw this in.
I kind of mentioned it before.
I recently did an interview with Freeman again for you folks,
so I think about 90% of the people that make sense have come over from that group,
but I just wanted to throw that in as a plug or whatever, not necessarily for Freeman,
but his listeners tend to be of a pretty high caliber in terms of asking questions.
Fortunately, I haven't been getting anyone saying, well, Greek, I really like you.
I like what you're saying.
It's like, well, what do you like about it?
I don't know.
I just like it.
Fortunately, I don't get any of that because that will be quickly just dispatched away to somewhere else.
But at this point, fortunately, the majority of the people that have been making contact
and asking the right questions, meaning, well, let's just say,
I couldn't say they were really wrong or right, but they're definitely not wrong,
meaning they're on the right track, meaning what are things based on?
You guys are not a really good lot as a human condition right now,
meaning you guys, meaning all of humanity is in really, really bad shape.
Now, you are obviously tempered and controlled by certain cultural aspects,
which society and traditions and things like that, and I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the true aspect of humanity right now,
where you are, let's say.
Things do change, so things have changed quite a bit, but yet they seem the same.
So I guess the things I wanted to cover, I guess, were, yeah, AFR could use a computer.
They could also, why not send them a going away thank you for the Greek?
You got one more week as well.
Just go ahead and dig in and dig out or go ahead and use that allegorical credit thing,
which, whatever, and send something over.
I just want to thank everyone, especially for the first four weeks.
It was a monumental achievement to actually meet the goal,
because how many times do people actually meet goals and exceed them,
at least in this kind of venue?
So I would just suggest a little bit of thank you and appreciation to AFR,
and even if you are hearing this live
and if you wanted to send them something that would be more than excellent.
So I wanted to just, you know, I have nothing planned out or outlined,
and, of course, I'm going to go to the e-mails there.
I have gotten some e-mails that are really noteworthy.
I will bring up the points and topics on there.
Also, I would like to bring up a topic that is reoccurring, and it's very contemporary,
and I want to just tie it in to the condition of where you are listening now.
You're listening on what's called alternative media platform, internet radio.
I'm sure you could tell if you don't know, if you listen to the adverts,
that it's not mainstream.
Now, I don't endorse anything or anyone or any of that stuff.
I just happen to be here, but because I'm here, it's fine.
I might as well make the best of it, but I want to just bring up a point,
especially for the people that are in internet or alternative media.
What you will notice, and I've been saying this for a while,
is this is the time right now where you're going where you're all going to be hurting.
Hosts, radio platforms, you're all going to catch a hurting because the paradigm is changing.
Of course, you don't know because you don't know what day it is or anything like that.
You're stuck on the dummy load, which is fine because that's just the way things are,
and I want to get into why you're all stuck on the dummy load.
What you will see now with alternative media, and actually all media,
all communications is they're hurting, and they're hurting through accessibility
and especially finances and attention.
Less people are paying.
They are losing the relevancy they once had.
Can you fault them for procuring dummy loads?
Yes and no because it's all dummy loading, even university.
At least you're not paying $50,000 a year to be dummy loaded on alternative media,
but across the board, they're all hurting because they don't know what's going on
and you don't know what's going on.
The gods kind of go after those that are providing the stuff more than those
that are accepting it if they're going to look for change.
There's a paradigm shift that's happening, and that's all you're experiencing.
You're all struggling with your donations and your YouTube monetizations
and your subscriptions and all that.
I say pretty much, even the AJ, the great Alex, you know who,
has been subject to some turmoil lately.
This is a sign of the times.
I'm just going to loosely refer to something ancient about a certain time period
that you've been in and are going in where the common man's actual income
or intake will be equivalent to a pretty modest equivalent of grain,
but it also states that do not harm the oil and the wine.
What that means is the oil and the wine would be the more of the wealthy
because in order to do oil and wine, you need infrastructure.
I just want to mention that the caste system that you folks are always discussing,
have you ever heard of middle class?
Oh, the middle class is suffering.
That's a caste system, by the way.
Shame on you.
I shouldn't say that because it does exist,
but if you ask any of these morons that use the middle class terminology,
upper class, and whatever, they don't know that they're actually using a caste system.
You're not supposed to know what's going on because that's the nature of the cosmic censorship,
and that was the point that I was leading to.
There's something called cosmic censorship I've been giving up,
and even though others have discussed it with me on air,
they don't seem to get a grasp on it.
How do you get a grasp on it?
Well, let's just not say it's a problem,
but the situation with most things that people conceptualize or are cognizant of
is on the typical surface-dwelling, earth-inhabitant mentality,
which is equivalent to tic-tac-toe or checkers.
By the way, what I mean by that is there's a chicken in New York City, Chinatown,
that will beat you in checkers.
Yes, you put in a couple of bucks or something and a slide thing,
the chicken is on the other side of the window,
and you push some buttons and the chicken will beat you at checkers.
The reality of it is more like chess,
but the problem is when you get from that tic-tac-toe checkers mentality,
which you see everywhere, when I mean everywhere,
let me just say it again, everywhere,
the most people that enter into that reality forget that by the rules of the game
that a pawn can take a king.
Now, that sounds kind of, you know, anyone who knows chess says,
yes, I guess Greek it can, but that never happens.
That's right, it doesn't.
Because usually when you sit down at a chess game,
you kind of like have a strategy or a tactic,
and right now you're sitting in a position where you're still so heavily censored
that you couldn't pour piss out of a boot even if you had instructions on the heel,
if you heard me use that before,
or you could think of other metaphors that might come out of Texas.
This is the condition of all humanity,
and obviously the ones that are bringing you information are under the same condition
because it is a cosmic censorship.
When I say information, it's all of it.
Mainstream, alternative, all of it.
Now, not here and there, all of it, even university, you know,
and even your gurus and your spiritual people, these morons.
But anyway, you're under censorship, man.
And here's the thing, it's like, well, aren't you too Greek?
Well, it's irrelevant.
No one else is reporting it.
If you think I'm censored, I'm censored.
If you don't think I am, then I'm not.
How's that?
Here's the thing I wanted to bring up.
If you're stuck in this mentality of checkers and chess,
especially where a chicken will beat you at it,
or you get into checkers or tic-tac-toe,
and you get into chess and you let your king being taken by a pawn,
this is not what I'm talking about.
There are many levels, like Star Trek 3D chess.
That's really what's going on.
But unfortunately, those that are on the game board,
meaning the people and the leaders and the other institutions
aren't aware of what's going on because of the censorship.
Okay, Greek, you've mentioned censorship so much.
So what's going on?
It is not a simple thing.
But once you are made aware of the context of the censorship,
you can very well get an idea of what is being censored.
And sometimes when something makes a statement
or there is a statement made somewhere,
it actually gives a lot of information not also by what it's discussing
or mentioning in the information but what it's not discussing by omission.
So the thing about the censorship, I just want to get back to it,
it's put on humanity by the gods.
Let's just say imagine the mindset or the perception or consciousness of humanity
and what they are aware of being bound in a book or a scroll.
The censorship would represent a seal on that or a lock.
Now you know it exists.
You just don't know.
You can't see it.
Now if you bring that to someone and they say,
well, I can't see what's in there because it's sealed.
Well, then you bring it to someone else and they say,
well, I can't read it anyway because I'm illiterate.
And then you bring it to someone else and they say,
well, I can't see, I'm blind, so it wouldn't matter anyway.
You see, there's the three levels of the censorship.
So what you're going to be seeing soon, and this is because,
well, this is metaphor, is the blind are going to begin to see
and the illiterate are going to be more literate
and the seal finally will be open
and you folks will see what was there all along.
And what is it all along?
In subject or in context, all along there's been a parallel world
known as the gods or the unseen,
and it's also transferred over as things that you know nothing about
but are aware of that exist.
Like, for example, years ago when people put hot coals in a room
to keep the room warm and they had the windows and doors shut,
the next morning, knock, knock, no one's there.
Yes, they are.
They're all dead.
They went to sleep and woke up dead.
There's some kind of ether or something coming out of the charcoal.
See, they didn't have a carbon monoxide detector then, did they?
They knew that you shouldn't do that because when you do that, people died.
So you folks are kind of operating as a whole now, at large,
as a wholesale group on that level.
You know if certain things happen, something bad is going to happen,
but you're always kind of always going in that direction anyway.
Now one of the things, one of the directions,
we've got roughly another hour and a half or so.
There's much to say but much won't be said publicly.
I keep bringing this up because you ever notice when the more people
that are being addressed, the more superficial the address.
Why?
It's just the way things are.
If you look at just how it's been, just think about that for a minute.
Okay, the more people that are being addressed,
the more superficial the matters.
Just think of it even reduced down to a small group.
You're addressing someone over here and you say,
Tom, can I speak to you outside?
Ooh, he's going to speak to him outside in private.
You think it's a little more critical, the information, isn't it?
So as the group gets smaller and smaller,
and when I say group I'm not talking about the group mentality,
but the information can be conveyed more.
That's why I've suggested that I'm done with internet radio for now,
for a while actually.
I'm going to be doing a more private podcast type thing
that is not open to the public.
So more can be discussed and more rational, more helpful information,
let's say unabated by knowing that you're speaking publicly.
Because I assure you folks, what is being said right now is everywhere.
It's amazing you guys can even see straight from the dummy loads,
but this is the thing.
There's things that are going to be happening.
This is the last year of the seven-year period
where I personally just bring this up.
I don't want to be near the internet or the news.
The last thing I want to do is have an internet show
and have people calling me in about all the carnage that is going on in the future,
in the near future in a certain place.
And I'm going to get into that a little bit
because there's a lot of hypocrisy there and there's just a lot of perception.
There's a lack of maturity.
There's just not much good to say about what's going on.
Now, the other thing you have to remember,
when you offer anything publicly, you have to be accommodating the audience.
Otherwise, no one comes or no one buys or no one listens or whatever.
Well, that's the interesting catch right there.
Most people hear things, but they don't listen.
Unfortunately, I don't get much of it,
but I've had people message me privately and say,
hey, a lot of the stuff you've said is coming to fruition.
Like they were having a discussion with someone else.
I said, well, can you mention like what?
They're like, well, I don't know.
And I'm like, well, how do you know the stuff that I mentioned?
And sometimes I catch a little flack about that being a low-hanging fruit.
Now, the best of the best is low-hanging fruit right now with humanity.
Most of them are falling off the tree and are on the floor rotting.
So anyway, and the top of the tree has been cut off.
So at this point, this is not something I want to get into
because if you listen to Greek speak, you've known about this already.
It's not a surprise to you.
The aspect of what's coming and how things are going to be
goes into the realm of the future, doesn't it?
And I do want to address some of the things.
I don't think there's anything in chat and anything in e-mail
that we can probably open up another form of subject matter.
And someone, let me just say here before we get into any kind of a thing here.
It appears to be the second day of the third month.
Yeah, it could be.
I suggest the third at noon.
It started at noon, so and even beyond for others.
Okay.
There's certain discussions that will be had regarding events that will be coming.
And a lot of them are also going to be more enriching.
I just want to, in terms of enriching, I want to bring up the point that
I want to also give a shout out.
Let's see if someone wants to come in on Skype.
That there are things, yes, let's just see.
I have someone that would like to call, and we'll just say yes.
And let's see if I can get Skype to work.
Because there's also a correction I'd like to make
regarding the types of humans on the planet.
And recently, because of a listener, I have been under the discovery,
through paying more attention to what is going on,
there are actually four types of humanoid creatures on the planet.
And I want to thank that one.
And let's see if we can, he might be the one that might want to come on.
So let's just see.
Oh, this sounds kind of like a delay.
Should I put on some?
Skype is not cooperating.
Ah, here we go.
Let's see if it, add to group.
Let's see if it, okay.
Greetings.
Ah, greetings.
Are you on?
Is this Sam?
Yes, I'm on.
Hello, can you hear me?
Greetings, yes, I can hear you.
I just started bringing up a little bit of the conversation we've had
regarding the four types of creatures that are on the planet,
and you wanted to come on.
I mean, talk about riding the telepathic superhighway.
So how are you?
I'm doing well.
I'm sorry I didn't catch that tail end of the discussion,
because the Skype feed, I think, is a bit behind the live feed.
Yeah, yeah.
We're about a minute or so.
So what's on your mind, and thanks for coming aboard.
Well, thank you for having me.
Well, I had certain things on my mind that I think are not in line with what you were talking about,
so please excuse that I changed the subject.
Please, that's okay.
We are allowed to do that.
Walk and chew gum, I call it.
Go ahead.
Well, I wanted to ask about two or three different things,
and the first being connected to sort of food and biology.
I think when you examine the back of fruit juices, yogurts, packaged non-water fluids in general,
there's a reoccurring ingredient that has a widespread use that you see often
to the point where you start to scratch your head and wonder why that seems to be everywhere,
whether it's something that you would consider to be organic at a fruit vendor's stall at a farmer's market,
or whether it's something that's clearly processed food, and that is ascorbic acid.
It's frequently marketed as natural vitamin C, and it's added to foods as an alleged natural preservative,
and a lot of people are being sort of fooled by the misleading semantics,
but we do know that vitamins are not individual molecular compounds,
but rather biochemical interactions and complexes that consist of different things, nutrients, enzymes, and so on.
So when isolated into these artificial commercial forms, like what they call ascorbic acid,
I sort of feel like they're synthetics that act as drugs rather than what we call vitamins.
So we know that a lot of so-called vitamin C is synthesized corn, and it has nothing to do with citrus fruits,
and I've read a few articles about it being linked to cancer and thickened arteries and such,
although I don't know how much weight to place on that.
But I wanted to ask you, why such an insistence on this use of ascorbic acid in drinks, and what are the health effects?
Okay, you've heard of the concept of fashion. It's fashionable now, right?
The scientific, industrial, nutrition, whatever community has fashion as well.
Think about that for a minute. They have their own fashions and their own trends.
Think about how they almost – they are the true terrorists, by the way, I should say,
because terror is to bring fear and terror onto the public.
How many times have you heard them talk about the little critters that cause diseases
and what you should eat and shouldn't eat?
That harkens back to what is lawful and what is not lawful, which I go into a lot.
And I'll tell you the misgivings of any of it or all of it.
We can either address – addressing solely the ascorbic acid aspect, I believe,
is demure from the real stuff that's going on.
They have a false premise that the body absorbs things.
And also, when all of their research is done on dead things,
don't they research things when they're under a slide and separated from the living host?
So unfortunately, yeah.
Basically, let me just say it like this.
At this point, what your question is about is about trust, isn't it?
And I would say the entire group is untrustworthy at large, every single one of them,
except for those that have figured out what's going on in the scientific medical community
and are looking for an exit strategy.
You always got to give a little bit of a leeway for this.
There might be some good people left there.
Essentially, what they have gained their trust on, the scientific and medical community,
when it comes to the human body, is they have repackaged battlefield medicine as healthcare.
Let me just say that again.
The reason why people think doctors and nurses and all these people are important
is because they have repackaged battlefield medicine as healthcare.
They are a miserable failure everywhere else, and they are going down the wrong path.
Now, this can be garnered.
Well, it's actually easier than the flat earth versus the round earth argument.
You've heard that brought up recently, right?
Some people want to talk about the extolled virtues of the medical society,
and I'll tell you that you just want to walk away from that because there is none.
Because reality of what they are doing, again, I'm repeating it again,
is they have repackaged battlefield medicine.
And if you want to understand what battlefield medicine is,
then that's a whole other discussion.
I think you get the point.
Their massive failure is the way that they're training, actually,
and what they are doing to the public at large is based on death,
studying dead organisms and chemicals that are synthesized or whatever for economic purposes.
Now, it doesn't mean that humans cannot have a good, let's say, medical society emerge.
Yeah, you will in the future.
But the one right now is really bad.
It's just like telling someone, you know, go to church to learn about the gods.
You're not going to learn anything about it.
It's ridiculous.
I'm glad you brought it up because it just shows one of the veritable symptoms of what's going on.
There are many aspects to it, but I would suggest if you want to get more critical into it,
how much of a percentage, how much ascorbic acid are they adding in there,
and then again you might say, well, if you understand homeopathy,
you may not need much of the substance at all to actually have maximum efficacy anyway.
So interestingly enough, let's just say it this way.
You know, Rudolf Hoschka is one of the fathers of vitamins, and he coined –
I'm not sure if he coined the phrase, but he was trying to search what gave food its vitality,
and ultimately he found out that these substances, these extracts that later became vitamins,
only had efficacy for a few days.
So that adds another – so even in industry, if you're making drinks or whatever
and you buy a truckload of ascorbic acid, you're probably – even if you use it within a few days,
it's probably not going to go to the end user.
So it's kind of like another dummy load to the body.
The body only reproduces things that it recognizes.
That's why if you eat a piece of plastic, it comes out just like a piece of plastic,
even though there's thousands of calories in a piece of plastic if you burn it.
You don't get anything out of it, do you?
It's undigestible. It's not recognized.
You see, that's what makes a poison a poison.
The body recognizes it as something it can reproduce.
There are many substances that can be chemically considered toxic,
but you can take them and they won't kill you because the body doesn't recognize it.
I'll give you another example.
You ever heard of something called margarine?
That's something the body does not recognize.
It's foreign.
It's just like putting lube on a gear and it gets all messy.
So there are many things like that.
Industrial synthetic – when you say ascorbic acid,
when you bring up the vitamin C, then there's a qualitative issue.
Ultimately, if you continue with that thought, you'd say,
well, then we should have citrus for it.
But there's another problem there.
We really don't know what's in citrus until –
to communicate it the way people are used to having it communicated
because in order to do that, they have to assay the material,
which is bring it into the lab, squeeze the juice out
or whatever other component they're going to use an extract from,
and they usually torch it and combine it with other chemicals
to see what they can derive as being its constituents,
and all those processes change it.
So if I tell you something that might sound ridiculous on its face,
like no one knows what's in an orange, we really don't,
other than it's wet and squishy and juicy and orange in color and smells good
because the way we define what's in it, the process that it goes through
to define it, let's say clinically or academically, also changes it.
So in essence, if you're having a food question or anyone is, it's very simple.
Well, if you want to go more exacting, it would be eat lawful,
and that comes from your god, by the way.
And secondly, you will find out that we are integrated into the environment
so much that the environment provides us with what we need,
whether it's abundant or not.
Even if you were in the desert, something like the Sahara or Gobi,
where it's really kind of barren, and you had enough know-how,
you could still survive.
You would still figure out how to garner nutrition out of that environment,
even though it's hostile.
So I would suggest that there is a rhythm in seasons,
there is a rhythm in agricultural growth that is by the seasons,
and when you eat seasonally and you eat locally or cross-latitude, I should say,
you will probably benefit the most.
In terms of things called healing diets, I always tell people,
if you're going to want to heal something,
never eat anything that comes sealed in a package or has ingredients on it.
If it has writing on it, don't eat it.
Well, what does that mean?
Well, what do we do then?
Well, you receive some of these markets where they offer things in bulk.
You kind of scoop it out of a large container and put it in a smaller container
and have it weighed out or measured,
and then you finish the transaction and bring it home.
Have you ever heard of like a bakery where you walk in
and it smells like bread has just been baked and it's just right there cooling off?
And when I said that, it was really ironic.
When I started saying this a long time ago,
I started noticing a lot of produce had little stickers on it with writing on it and barcodes.
I said, oh, this is a cosmic joke, isn't it?
Because I used to tell people, don't eat anything that has any writing on it.
And here you buy a tomato and it has a sticker on it with writing on it.
I'm like, okay.
Now I'm like fighting with some cosmic force on this.
Now I'm going to leave it alone.
So you would say that because these vitamins, in this case ascorbic acid,
because a lot of what is useful in them is rendered inactive or sterile after a certain period of time,
it's not a health hazard as far as consuming it in excess amounts?
Anything in excess.
Well, nothing exceeds success and everything in moderation, I should say.
But I would say that all these things, no matter if it's okay.
Let me just say it this way.
The premise of it is poor, what they're doing and why they're putting it in there.
It's a very poor premise.
It's like Santa Claus, Easter Bunny premise type stuff.
Everyone does it.
No one knows why and they don't care.
This is ultimately the thing.
This is a religion, by the way, that we're discussing now, if you know what I mean.
The other aspect of it is it's a testament.
Even if it was really nasty stuff, it's a testament to the robustness of the human organism.
Think about that for a minute.
The other thing is I was speaking with someone even on another Internet thing for an hour and a half a few days ago.
I was saying there's a perception of how we interact with the material world.
For example, an average adult, male or female, man or woman, requires about half a kilo or a pound of food a day.
Going by the Pope's work schedule, let's say that would be 365 pounds of food or 180 kilos or so.
Now, if I said to you, this is the food you need for the whole day,
can you pick that up and carry it around all the time?
No, but you will consume it in a year one bit at a time because it's a very large burdensome load.
Most people couldn't pick up something that weighs twice as much as they do.
This is how the information about food can be too.
You want to really get into the finite and the massive amount of information.
It will just bury anyone.
They'll say, I need to take a break from the food discussion because I'm hungry right now.
A little bit at a time.
If you're going to parcel out a large body, something that could be burdensome one piece at a time,
wouldn't you want to just give the more important things in the beginning?
Because if you didn't continue that process, at least they got the most important stuff.
That's what I tend to do regarding food matters.
That is eat seasonally and eat locally.
In other words, if it's hot out, don't eat food that was grown in a cold climate.
If it's cold out, don't eat food that was grown in a hot climate
because obviously, look at the food as being an input to the body
and it will change it according to the environment.
That's why, have you heard people that live up and near the North Pole,
they eat blubber, pure fat to survive.
Things like that.
In the tropics, the variety of the diet is typically hot chilies and more tropically grown,
sugary stuff or water-based, quite the opposite.
Very little fiber in it.
Let me just bring up, this is like a loose conversation now,
but there is something that is counterintuitive.
For example, when someone eats hot and spicy food,
they think it is warming them up.
I've seen this with people here in America that have come from Asia.
When it's cold outside, they say, oh, I want it spicy to warm me up.
I'm like, no, actually, that's going to do the opposite.
It's going to open your pores and thin out your blood
and you might feel hot at the moment, but you will feel worse tomorrow.
Some of it is unintuitive.
Some of it you really do have to rationalize what is really going on.
Right.
In this case, back to that, would you say the question about ascorbic acid or vitamin C
and all that is very similar to anything else that they're putting in there,
whether it's mysterious or not as a vitamin?
I would say so, but it's nice to have specifics
because those things would have very particular effects on the consumer of them.
Yeah, it would, but here's the thing.
They don't want you to drop dead from it right away, do they?
Because then you won't come back.
Right.
When you mentioned that the ability for humans to consume certain things
is a testament to their robustness, I mean, if you get bitten by a snake,
you'll probably die if it's a poisonous snake of a certain variety.
Unless you drink your urine within the first 30 seconds or a minute.
That's where the antidote is, but go ahead.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I thought that was just a myth, but no.
Well, I mean, if they really wanted to kill you,
there are ways to go about doing that in a very concrete, effective way.
So obviously the agenda as far as food is concerned
is deliberate to sort of kill you slowly.
Yeah, but the thing is, if it was really so,
I think people would protest and have them hung
like at the end of the Frankenstein movie, you know, the villagers come.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
I would suggest from firsthand experience being around people
that are captains of industry that they don't know what's going on.
They are just as intellectually humbled or as ignorant as everyone else.
Now, it's kind of hard to say that because they have access to many more means
because of their wealth and stature in society than others,
but I would suggest that they have drank their own urine, I should say,
or their own Kool-Aid for too long.
So, yeah, they're not – you're all – it's like no one's at the wheel.
No one's – yeah.
I'll touch on one more food point if that's okay.
Sure.
I guess mindset-wise it's probably in line with the previous question,
but just to hone in on another specific,
there's another overt agenda in the food world
which is that of these estrogen, estrogen-heavy foods
and endocrine disruptors that are contained in synthetic foods,
whether through government subsidies for certain crops
or widespread injection of farm animals with hormones
or the ingestion of xenoestrogens through plastics,
it's kind of clear that that's a situation that is artificially maintained,
whether one wants to see it as a chemical warfare operation
or whether it's just a misguided move on the part of certain whole food fanatics
and new age enthusiasts who push every soy product under the planet.
What are the effects of estrogen imbalances in the body of males and females,
or men and women, rather?
Well, a short way to say it without really getting into it,
again, the body has to recognize it to reproduce it, right?
So that shows that the male can reproduce the estrogen
once there's a stimulus in the intestine or the stomach,
and it actually starts in the mouth.
I think I've mentioned before,
this is one of the agendas of the unknown goddess religion.
And I think the teaching, I'll reiterate it again,
the teaching of the ancient goddess religion which has been revived,
which is not known, by the way, but you could research this painstakingly,
and start piecing it together,
is that mankind was in a godlike state at one point.
In order to return a society of people back into a godlike state,
you promote male with male union.
The males become effeminate and sterile.
You promote a female with female union,
and the females retain sterility and procreate without the male.
And hopefully the females then will have asexual or hermaphroditic creatures.
And when everyone is now either asexual or hermaphroditic,
both sexes or no sex, you have a godlike society on earth.
And this really started at the turn of the 20th century.
That's why, and by the way, the scientific community, the legal community,
the religious community is all on board with this, and they don't know it.
The scientific community, let's say the medical community is on board with it
with the in vitro fertilization and their obsession about fertility.
And obviously all the other things that they're doing.
The scientific community is up on it also for, again, similar reasons.
The legal community is up on it by saying that if you want male with male union
or female with female union, you have legal rights now, right?
On and on and on.
And the religious community is on board with it because, well, I should say,
not directly but indirectly, the patriarchal aspect of it is being challenged.
And when you look at the patriarchal aspect of the religions,
they are actually just a male aspect still under the female goddess religion.
So anyway, because she has priests that are men,
because if you actually look at the writ of ancient texts,
women are held in very high regard.
Right.
But Christianity, Islam, Judaism, and other places don't hold women in high regard
because they're not adherence to their text.
So this is, would you say, cosmic reason?
And that's why when you know the cause,
do you want to maybe garner a sense of spiritual protection or the divine from it?
I would say that's a good place to start, right, because that's the cause of it.
And then the second aspect of it is to get protection or insulate yourself
from the beings on this planet who have legitimized the savagery.
Because, you know, when savagery is legitimized, it seems normal, doesn't it?
Yeah.
So this is a cross, this is a multifaceted thing that's going on.
But again, you know, let me just fast forward.
You know, in the amount of time that is left for human society on the planet,
if it was not, let's say, interrupted, let me just say this as a presumption,
because we won't get there as a society,
but if society is not interrupted, 50 or 100 years from now,
if a woman gets pregnant, she won't even have a fetus or an embryo.
It'll just be a cancerous lump.
I hope that sinks in to people.
This is the agenda, folks, from, you know, the influence of what's going on.
So the interruption, fortunately, you will be interrupted,
but unfortunately, you will be interrupted.
So either way, it's all right.
So at the same time, I would just guard oneself.
I mean, most people don't really care about what they eat,
and if you happen to care about what you eat,
it'll take a lot of time out of your life finding good food.
Now, if you think of that statement for a moment,
if you go back and look at, let's say, much older cultures,
don't you think they spent a greater percentage of their waking hours
thinking about how they're going to get food or making food to eat than they do now?
Yeah, they would.
It seems to be a revival in that direction.
Right now, the prepackaged food, ready to eat, heat it electronically or whatever,
well, you might want to contrast that and be more like the ancients,
you know, making fresh food from more raw ingredients.
And now you end up spending, I'd say, at one-tenth of your day at least
for just preparing food.
So let's say most people are up 16 hours or so, so an hour and a half a day.
There's shopping, buying, preparing.
That's normal.
I mean, in some places it could be all of your waking hours is getting food in some places, right?
So there's a contrast.
Right.
I kind of do understand more of the male effect as far as the estrogen imbalance would go as a male
and sort of seeing it overtly being displayed on people's bodies.
But on the female side, I guess it's a bit more under the hood
as far as if you already are somebody that has that disposition
to have more estrogen than a man, what exactly would that imbalance do to you?
Yeah, but let's just go back to the vitamin C perception.
Let's just keep it really simple and raw, so to speak.
Do we even know what estrogen is other than extracting, you know,
hormones and fluids from a living thing and segregating them through fire
and other chemicals to isolate them?
And is it possible that we're creating estrogen in the laboratory?
It doesn't really exist, but it's a form of communication.
How many times has the scientific community, medical community, even legal community
produced an aspect of something chemical or physical in physics,
but they never talk about how they separated it and got it?
They always just tell you, this is estrogen that does it.
Everyone agrees, but no one ever discusses how they were able to isolate it to estrogen.
And even the most rational, quote, unquote, uneducated mind,
if you look at the entire process of how they separated or segregated estrogen
from a living being, you're like, that doesn't sound right
because all those things they did to separate it could have actually created it
or changed it, you see?
One other way to think of it is the consistent appearance
or presence of something called estrogen consistently, you know,
through certain diagnostic processes or scientific processes,
showing up in many other things, you see?
Because how would you test something for having one?
Now, here's the thing.
Even when they – let's say they isolate or synthesize that hormone
and put it into a subject, now it's a completely different thing all of a sudden, isn't it?
You see, now it's like another – now it's just a different story again
because, you know, I'm sure they've done – they've isolated estrogen-type hormones
or what they could classify as mostly estrogen and inject it into rats or people
or monkeys or dogs and cats and looked at the effects of those that haven't.
And they might find consistently, yes, their genetic – meaning, should I say,
what is it, male or female differences that are accentuated or diminished?
So the storyline continues, you see?
But again, you know, really good science is based on knowledge,
and that's all the word means.
I would suggest that, you know, when we start discussing the effects of very specific chemicals,
it starts to get into what's called fractional thinking, you know?
And again, you brought up the soy aspect of it.
You know, there are so many varieties of soy,
and what most people are getting as soy products are the ones that are the least expensive to produce.
In other words, require the least irrigation, the most resistant to bugs, and are –
and grow the fastest, and that is not always the best soy for human consumption, let's say, you see.
I've been saying for years and years and years, a lot of people say,
well, I have – I'm allergic to gluten.
I need – who told you that?
Well, the doctor told me.
I said, okay, wait a second.
There's no such thing.
This is moronic again.
The reason people have, for example, gluten intolerance or whatever
is because of the quality of the wheat at this point.
And of course, you know, there's also been the lactose, they call intolerance,
for certain people with dairy.
Again, that's kind of spurious.
Again, it's a very personal thing.
But this whole thing about gluten-free right now is because you basically have a substandard wheat crop
that's been sprayed and modified.
But this is okay because this is a planet of M-O-R-O-N-S.
But with regards to the lactose thing, I mean, I do kind of hear a lot of people profess that,
and I guess what they're trying to hint at or point in the direction of
is that something along the lines of the lactic acid doesn't fully digest
and sort of leaves some kind of residue in the intestines,
and that causes flatulence and gas and things of that nature.
And I wouldn't claim to understand the specifics of it at this point,
but I've had some kind of experience where I consume dairy products,
and there is that kind of an after effect, which is undesirable.
And the question is, have you consumed dairy products that are less tainted,
like directly, you know, direct whole milk,
or products that are made from direct whole milk that haven't been packaged
or let's say affected by industry and had the same effect?
Well, the best I can say on a sort of layman level
is that I went into what they would call an organic food store,
and I bought the milk that was there thinking that, well, this is more reliable,
and the effect was still the same.
Okay. All right.
So then there's something to be done there based on your tendency,
your personal constitution regarding that, or others like you, which is fine.
Because it goes all the way from the palate also.
You know, like for example, someone might like Brussels sprouts and someone else doesn't.
And when they try to like them and eat them, they don't feel good.
They might get nauseous.
You know, it doesn't mean that they're bad.
It just means that this particular, you know.
Because here's the other thing I'd like to suggest.
There's only, I wouldn't say a small handful,
but several handfuls of genetic types on the earth.
You ever heard of like, you know, look-alikes?
You know, people that are cartoonists actually get into the forms of people,
but there's only a few handfuls of maybe 100 or so genotypes that everyone sort of fits into.
You know, this guy looks like this, or this person looks like that,
or this lady looks like this person.
You know, there's a limited amount of genotypes.
And even with intermarriage and, you know, when I mean intermarriage,
I mean not marrying someone who's in your own family.
But, you know, there's still, it seems to be recurring.
So the more we know, the more we learn about how we were,
and the more as we go into the future we're going to learn more about the ancient past,
I think a lot of these things will be answered a little more readily.
Okay. Moving on to sort of another topic that's not too far off in another realm of what they call science.
You've often stated your unwillingness to give credence to prevailing orthodoxy of physics
regarding electrons and protons, what they call those things.
But you seem not to be railing with similar vehemence against other bodies of knowledge within that field,
like the periodic table, although you sometimes comment on that with regards to water,
but you're more, I feel like you're more using it to explain a point
and actually giving it some kind of credence by using it in that way.
And you don't also seem to have anything against the existence of molecules or the phenomena of ionization.
So there's certain things that you seem to be fine with and other things that you feel is part of the cosmic censorship or the dummy load.
So I wanted to ask what is the nature,
what is the nature of the information that constitutes subatomic particles that make up matter?
What is it in an atom if it's not protons and electrons?
Well, there's, OK, I'm not OK with any of it.
But is all this information come from a group that has done a lot of heavy lifting for many years?
Yes. They've done a lot of grunt work, meaning that if you want to go into industry,
the majority of their physics and chemistry is that it's available,
is workable for what is now industrially and commercially available.
You know, cars, planes, whatever, you know, and all that medicines and all these other things.
Right. But are they are they beneficial now? Are they wasteful?
Yeah, very. And they're inefficient. Very inefficient.
I would suggest that even within the mainstream orthodoxy, once they start looking at things as known as an atom.
OK, even the densest material, as they get down atomic level, they find out it's all space.
Mostly in terms of the the volume that it takes up and what is there and what it can be measured as being material.
There's almost no material within the atom itself.
It's mostly all space. Yeah. So there was something in the atom.
Yeah, they they're beginning to to notice that they're not really they don't really have a handle on the material world.
Because essentially, if you go back to the sub sensible, if you go back to the aspect of.
OK, well, I want to go to an email also where it's all external input.
You know, let's just say we're censored from that right now for obvious reasons.
You don't want to give you know how you tell children not to play with matches.
So if you want to hold on, we're going to the break right now and we'll continue the subject about the atom.
Cool. Greetings and welcome back to the second hour of Uncommon Radio.
We are still on with Sam, I believe.
And we were bringing up the concept of the atom and how nothing is really there.
I think, Sam, right? Yes. We're kind of finished off.
Yeah. What is really there is the point right now, I would say, is we lack the maturity to truly know directly.
And it sounds like might be a cop out. I feel like it's a cop out for myself because sometimes I sometimes I say to myself,
you know, I'm going to take some time and figure this out.
And guess what? It just a lot of time goes by and you don't figure much out.
But you're always working with it and you're made up of it.
So it's one of those things that you kind of like set aside.
And again, go and look at all the heavy lifting that these grunts have done.
That's what they are. The intellectual elite of humankind right now, the doctors, the PhDs,
the researchers are operating on a grunt level, at least institutionally,
because those that do make what you might call incredible, fantastic or, you know,
paradigm shifting discoveries are shunned because it's like not disturbing the convention at this point.
The other thing the other thing I want people to consider and consider this,
if you're going to take anything to heart from Greek speak, is this.
Currently, the most surface dwelling earthen habits and think that everything sprang into creation.
Everything I think is important less than 100 years ago.
Like if you look at the scientific field or the medical field or even the legal field
or any other important fields that are important in society,
how many of them actually go back and really use what was accumulated up until the 1890s?
Very little. Things were done very, very differently back then.
And so in essence, there's this pride of being modern and being so technologically advanced.
I think there's the topic of discovering, let's say, empirically what's in an atom is something that is unpopular
to discuss because it's really different from the convention.
And the only reason the convention is there is so industry can keep working.
Look at university training. It's for industrial purposes.
And I've also spoke about the society in darkness.
They're in the dark, you see, by the time the way they keep time and the way they garner their main materials,
you know, being petroleum based products.
So they're very dark in terms of spiritually.
And their religions, of course, are, you know, nothing to say much about.
So spiritually, they're void or into worthlessness.
Scientifically, it's dark. Medically, it's dark. Dead, medically.
Cadaver study and all that.
But we do know that there's a certain functional efficiency and results from the use of the knowledge, as you've mentioned.
In industry?
Yes, in industry.
And yet, if so, something is being practically applied or used to create or give results,
then we know that there has to be a body of knowledge that underpins that that can be validated.
So if you've expressed that, you know, in your talks about water or engineering or other things,
that ionization is, for example, something that actually happens, and we know that that's a process, allegedly, anyway,
by which an atom or a molecule acquires a negative or positive charge by gaining or losing electrons, if that's what they say,
then how can we also then turn around in the same breath and say that there are no electrons?
No, the electron is a form of communication that was put on the world substantially by Walt Disney, by the way.
Prior to that, it was the charge and nature of that charge was what was considered.
And positive has a little bit of negative in it, and negative has a little bit of positive in it.
It's kind of like the yin-yang symbol.
The black field has a little white, and the white field has a little bit of black.
Everything has a little bit of its opposite in there.
Okay.
But electricity is – here's a simple antidote for electricity.
I think I've given – do you remember the one I gave, what you learn about electricity when you go to college, right?
You get zero for university.
You learn about how to work with it.
The other one that I want to suggest is it takes roughly 2,000 or 3,000 volts to send an arc a few millimeters, okay?
So if you set up a 12-volt device or a 9-volt device,
you ever notice sometimes when you hit the switch or a wall switch, you'll see sparking and arcing in there, right?
And sometimes it's more than a couple of millimeters.
Well, the entire thing is rigged up to only 9 or 12 volts.
How can you bridge a gap that requires 2,000 or 3,000 volts?
Where is it coming from?
Think about that for a minute.
And also, just for those that are listening for the first time on this respect,
where you learn about electricity formally or in the orthodox way in university is the physics department or the electrical engineering department.
Those are two general areas where that is studied or physical parts of the university.
And they're usually across the street from each other.
So if you walk into the physics department, they're always studying the negative path or the negative charge,
and they always mark the positive as a source.
So we'll put a negative 1 on that building.
When you go to electrical engineering, they send the negative to ground.
They always mark it as ground, and they're always studying the positive side of the circuit.
So we'll put a plus 1 on that building.
So what do you get when you put plus 1 and negative 1 together?
You get zero.
And that's where you're going to learn about electricity,
but you're going to learn a lot about electrical engineering and a lot about physics.
Now, that sounds convoluted, doesn't it?
A tiny bit.
Because what they do is they hide under the rug a lot of the anomalies and a lot of the things.
I mean, for example, in religion you do that a lot.
Certain religions have certain precepts, and when they come across something in the text that doesn't agree with it,
they kind of shove it away.
They don't want to look at it or they say, well, this is how this should be interpreted, you see.
So the same thing happens in the – if you even talk to anyone in the medical community that is at the top of their field,
ultimately when it comes down to how the human body works, you know what they all say?
They all say, well, the body heals itself no matter how well –
I just love that.
Yeah, but even the orthodox medical people say, well, hopefully he'll heal himself.
Hopefully he'll heal.
Well, what do you know about healing and how the process works?
Nothing other than time and, well, rest and hygiene.
That's what it boils down to, but there's a lot more to know about that, and that's one of the things.
Actually, I'm glad you mentioned this, and I don't feel pressed to answer it,
but it will be answered through the future endeavors.
I'll go into several hours and giving a little bit of history, practical knowledge,
just like, for example, a 9 or 12-volt DC circuit.
How can flipping the switch send a several-millimeter arc which requires 2,000 or 3,000 volts
when you only have a 9-volt source?
How can that be?
What's going on, you see?
We're going to talk about that in more detail, and there's a concept –
this is, again, a level of chess that most people don't understand
where one aspect of society overlaps into the other.
When you're discussing physics, science, medicine, or whatever,
guess who are the gatekeepers to what gets flooded, poured out into society regarding that?
It's the legal society.
They're the gatekeepers of that information.
I've personally known an attorney from Europe, and I said, what do you do?
He says, I edit university medical textbooks.
I said, oh, what do you know about medicine?
He says, absolutely nothing.
So how are you qualified to edit?
He doesn't answer because he's an attorney.
He doesn't need to know anything about it.
He just needs to see and make sure that everything is presumptuous,
if you know what I mean.
That's why when you look at a gray's anatomy, it never says a kidney looks like this.
It says a kidney usually appears this way, doesn't it?
Right.
So you just have to keep everything in the presumption.
Academic can be defined as theoretical, impractical, never leading to a conclusion.
You could look it up etymologically.
That's what it means, being of the academy.
The ancient Greek schools were basically teaching young people parlor tricks
on how to take what someone said and turn it and use it for their favor,
you know, the one who has the socratic charm.
Right, right.
Yeah, there's not much part of the dummy load in the cosmic censorship.
I get that.
I kind of have to take off in ten minutes, so I will ask one more question,
and then I might have to drop out.
So changing subjects a bit to something completely different.
You mentioned attorneys, and I think of laws and sovereignty
and things like that in connection with it.
When we look at certain countries,
one comes across what initially seems to be an anomaly of sovereignty
pertaining to small areas of land within a nation
that seem to be operating under its own laws,
whether it's financial districts, religious institutions,
or seats of government that we see with the city of London and England,
Washington, D.C., and U.S.A., and the Vatican in Italy.
They pop up as examples of places with their own constitutions
and exclusive self-government.
So what other sovereign districts within countries do you know of
that could be pointed to as similar, aside from the ones that I've mentioned?
Because I feel like they're the more overt ones.
All of them.
Yeah.
All of the federal districts in the world, whether it's in Russia,
let's say Mexico, the capital of Mexico is called Mexico City DF,
District Federal.
That is not part of Mexico.
The same with Moscow.
Every federal district is not part of that country.
It's under what's called federalism when you study what federalism is.
You have to understand the ancient commercial codes,
how it was all put together.
Now, in the sense of sovereignty and freedoms and things like that,
it's super, hyper, ultra convoluted because most jurisdictions in the world,
sovereign or not, are under what's called a credit-based economy.
And when you have a credit-based economy, the actual resident, citizen,
slave, or participant, anyone who has a credit line,
meaning a social security number, birth certificate,
is the one that holds all of the credit.
But you can't let them know that they have it.
And then there are organizations, agencies, institutions like the legal society.
When I say legal society, it's everyone, the clerks, the attorneys, the police,
the judges, the bankers that are involved with them.
So, in other words, the legal society, the financial banking society,
the medical society, all of the government agencies, for example,
and a lot of the religious societies also know that the people are the ones with the credit
and they have to get it from them without them letting them know that they have it,
and that's what they're giving up.
So it's a very twisted, convoluted thing in what's going on.
So, again, you cannot escape the –
what should be in the forefront of anyone's mind is it's a credit-based economy.
It's a credit-based economy.
What does that mean?
It doesn't mean debt.
Debt is just an option that you can go into if you like,
but that's what they tell people because they're always going to give you the Santa Claus Easter bunny myth.
So the thing is, ultimately, it's really frowned upon to go into a lawful –
if you're discussing sovereignty, it's irrelevant if it's sovereign or is sovereign.
What's relevant, I would suggest, is is it lawful or unlawful.
That's why there's lawful money.
Can credit be done lawfully?
Yes, it can be.
But is it being done lawfully?
No, it's not because people are told that they have debt.
How can you have debt in a credit-based economy?
It doesn't make any sense.
But I guess if you have attorneys, I mean anything is possible.
Right.
But with regards to something like the – you say that the federal government or the federal –
Districts.
Districts usually tend to be sovereign, but I guess the City of London is an exemption
because that's a financial district.
It's generally classed as such, although it has religious overtones.
Yes.
Well, they all do.
They're either – most of the federal or governments of – or centralized –
federalism is just centralized, you know.
It would be like the ruler of thousands, right?
They tend to be necropolises, you know, or they tend to have a patron or matron deity.
So they all have – we recently did an interview with someone,
and he brought up American government buildings.
I said, those are temples.
I mean, if you go look at the inscription on the building itself,
and I pulled an inscription of a building, let's say the Lincoln Memorial,
and on the – cut into the marble itself, this government building says,
this temple, yada, yada, yada, yada.
And I'm like, okay, there you go.
It says it right on the building, you know, the capital buildings,
the various monuments are called temples.
Yeah, it sounds archaic, doesn't it, or ancient, doesn't it?
And not much – doesn't it harken back to think that not much has changed,
just the perception of it has changed?
Right, yeah.
So do you have a –
Yeah, the credit-based economy needs to be considered first, you know,
and then is it lawful or unlawful?
And I would say that is the credit-based economy considered?
No.
Are all the societies on earth right now lawful or unlawful?
I would definitely say unlawful.
So what are you going to do?
So if you have, for example, Scandinavian countries like Sweden
or even other European countries like the Netherlands that have monarchies,
what would you point to as being their version of that?
Is it the monarchy that tends to be the self-governing thing,
or is it the judicial system where the prime minister works?
Sure.
The judicial system would be if they have a separate one set up,
and also if they have a credit-based economy,
you will see there's an adjunct or something operating next to them that has a presidency
and is also not part of that country.
It's considered some kind of a district.
Okay.
Yeah.
You'll find that if you research it.
It could even just be a building.
Just like – it used to be online, but if someone wants to research it, let me know.
There's the Vatican in Rome, Vatican City,
and there's another building called the Vatican.
It's a very nondescript four- or five-story brick building about 600 years old.
What they do is if you have a state department, they subscribe to them,
and they dictate the policy of all the state departments of the world.
Once you join and they dictate policy for you, it's unappealable.
So let's say they make a policy for, let's say, Ghana or Switzerland or the U.S.
Once they make a decision and you've joined them, you cannot appeal it.
It makes you wonder why sometimes you see certain politicians get up
and try to make a poor excuse why they're passing a law or doing something.
It's like you know they're just up front as a front person.
I'm not giving too much credence to the –
I'm not talking about the Vatican where they have all those columns
and the fish hat and the big penis in the middle, you know, the spire,
and the guy with the fish hat and all that.
I'm not talking about that.
There's another building called the Vatican there in Vatican City.
It's very close to it.
Maybe we'll get into that on the podcast a little bit,
but it's really irrelevant stuff on the grand scheme of things
because if we had a lot of time to go,
it would be something to keep and start edifying,
educating people about how things really work, but I don't think it really matters.
I think it's going to be put into irrelevancy here in a minute, let's say,
in the next less than a decade.
Right. I get you.
All right.
Thank you.
This has been a nice conversation.
I have to take off unfortunately.
Thanks for dropping by and dropping in and calling in.
It was a pleasure.
Good luck with the rest of the broadcast.
Thank you.
Take care.
Have a great day.
All right.
Later, Greek.
Bye.
There you go, and thank you for calling in.
I hope you folks got something out of that.
I sure got me thinking.
So, okay, we're back.
Anyone else have anything they want to contribute?
Otherwise, what I was thinking of doing in certain fashion is going back to some of the relevant comments
that I've gotten, let's say, either in the Greek-speak chat,
which there does exist just Greek-speak chatango, I believe, or the emails.
The most recent email I was going to bring it up, I'll read it anonymously here.
It harkens back to much of the discussion, and I think it's pertinent
because we only have one more Sonic solo episode to go.
I think making this available to most people because most people tend to dream and things like that.
Okay, it says, Hello, Greek.
I want to thank you for, let's say, teaching on dreams, and I hope you continue to speak on that.
Our thoughts are not our own.
Are they?
Question mark.
Many times something comes into the mind, and one might say to themselves,
What?
Where did that thought come from?
That's not me.
I didn't think like that, or that's crazy thinking.
So are one's thoughts, whether sleeping or awake, our own?
It seems to be.
You have stated the scriptural men.
Okay.
All right, so let's just change this up, get into a little Book of Daniel things,
but I just want to get back into the – there's a certain nomenclature to apply here maybe.
If you remember being very young, you can only go back to a certain point.
Like you don't remember coming out of the womb.
You don't remember suckling.
I mean, you might because believe it or not, lawfully, in certain, let's say, what's called biblical law,
someone was suckled until about weaned off at five years old.
That's why the value of a male child increased after five because – well, anyway,
that's just another thing here, and five also comes before number six, which is man.
So when you go back to a time period when you are very, very young,
you notice that your thoughts are scant or minimal or nonexistent,
and you have thoughts of being very young.
You probably don't remember taking your first step or something like that,
but you are walking for the first time.
But you might remember, let's say, riding a bike for the first time.
And I want to go into the riding the bike metaphor because once you learn how to ride it,
you never forget and you never tend to experience that similar struggle.
Actually, you could if you've been injured a certain way,
but I just want to say that you take walking, speaking, like learning how to speak and all that for granted.
You don't think about these things.
So, okay, well, where are the memories?
Now, I want to go back, maybe just refresh a little bit of the conversation we had with Sam.
It was just on about science.
If you actually look into the nether regions of what the scientists say is we don't know where memory is.
Now, obviously, they talk about lobotomies and things like that and the brain being damaged.
But in terms of harm being done to the mechanism, they can't see the memory.
Now, even if you were to look at the way things are codified digitally, they need to be interpreted.
Or this is just a matter of another way you might say it's just signals.
Now, the word mem means water and or means light in a certain language.
And I would beckon anyone to meditate on this.
Meditate means think on it over and over and over.
There are how many different ways to think about it is when it's all external input.
Can you imagine going, let's say, walking in a park or the beach or someone's house
and they have a table set radio playing and they're playing jazz music?
How many people said let's take this radio apart because there's a little tiny jazz band in there?
You know, we better get them out.
That sounds kind of ridiculous on its face.
But that's how it sounds eventually when you start discussing about memories being your own
and thoughts being your own.
Could it be, let's just keep it framed this way, that you are receiving and you are transmitting.
And what makes you you, by the way, the spirit, your personality,
what makes you you is your spirit, by the way.
The soul is interchangeable.
That's just the breath.
The spirit, there is a place where, let's say, for example,
it's been memorialized in ancient texts when man dies, meaning woman as well,
the spirit returns back to the heavenly realm.
Now, what's interesting is, well, in animation, disanimation, it's like being asleep.
There is no animation because at this point it requires the body to be animated.
What's interesting about that is you also hear about a lot of other contacts on the other side,
like a guardian angel type thing or thoughts being put in or thoughts plucked out of people's minds.
Could it be that what is really going on,
we are receiving and transmitting through a certain frequency that makes us us?
You know how certain, let's say a cell phone or most devices have a very specific frequency.
You know you have cell phone towers that accommodate all of the cell phones, let's say,
somewhere in an area locale.
But when you make a phone call or receive one, it doesn't ring all the phones
because there's a way to discern the different components in the entire system,
all the various phones, and there could be millions or billions of them that seem to be discernible.
I would suggest there is a major hard drive or a source somewhere,
and it's in a longitudinal way, I would say counter-spatial way,
not measurable as we know how to measure things, meaning humans,
and that is where everything comes from.
So you are not on your own.
That's why it's very easy to be messed with,
and having those things now with psychotronics and other things like that,
there is research on how you can actually intercept this longitudinal-type communication
and pump thoughts and sounds and things into people's minds.
I'm not going to talk about that.
In the future, I will talk more about how that is done, and it's very counterintuitive.
It's being done using a longitudinal technology, not transverse, which means it's instant.
There is no wave as such.
There's still a measurable, discerning energy field we can call a wave,
but it's not like a sine wave where it takes time to travel.
It happens instantly.
So one of the most difficult things to, I mean, of course, because no one really thinks that way,
that their thoughts are not their own, but we might, let's say, rest assured we'll know in the future,
and at this point, I find it to be very plausible and to be so plausible that once you use that methodology,
that your thoughts are not your own, your memories are not your own, they're not stored in the head.
They're actually stored just like on computers, on a cloud, on a network.
You have a more usable perspective of your, quote-unquote, consciousness,
and of course, just like you have the various perspectives of reality,
and it seems like the more ignorant the people are, the more emphatic they are about what they think it is.
So having an open discussion in a calm fashion is difficult,
because that's what is required for each one coming with their own experiences in a rational way,
explaining what they see is going on technically,
so you can put it together to advance the idea of how our thoughts and what we really are made of.
But again, you're dealing with an irrational society.
What I mean by that, you have all these groups of people talking about reincarnation
or when you die you go to heaven or hell or they can travel astrally and do all this other stuff.
So there's no, you're not going to, that's fine to consider all of that,
but it has to be rationalized in a very cool, calm, let's say educated way.
And unfortunately, most people are bound up by these beliefs
and it's almost impossible to have a rational discussion,
including what I'm being said will actually be poo-pooed or viewed as,
oh, that's what he says, I don't believe in that.
This is almost, this is not the time yet for it.
But those that consider that your thoughts are not your own
and the memories are sort of uploaded and downloaded from a cloud, a virtual cloud,
and it's all instant, forget about the Einsteinian rubbish of speed of light and all this other stuff.
And dreams are actually not your own either.
You're being plugged by other entities that have been created to make dreams for people.
You will find that, by the way, in every culture.
But of course, if you believe that everything was created 100 years ago, you're at a loss.
So with getting down this road, the most rational explanation, I would say,
and the most founded explanation that can be memorialized by the ancients
is that our thoughts are not our own, but our personality is.
We are granted a certain personality and unique quality,
but yet everything else that we do is interactive.
And just to throw something in that might make it helpful,
what's interesting is you're never really alone spiritually because of that.
Imagine however you want to imagine it, somewhere up on a cloud, somewhere,
and when I mean a cloud, meaning not the cloud in the sky,
but like the computer cloud network somewhere, a server somewhere.
Why don't you ask for help when you're looking for someone?
Just ask someone there to go and maybe pull a switch
or patch you on to a body of knowledge or an ability.
Have you ever done that? It's called prayer, folks.
Yeah, and you don't want to do it in public because it's not that effective.
Now, there are entities, quote unquote, and demons and lower-level gods
that do thrive upon public prayer. That's their MO, modus operandi.
But when you start getting into the much higher realms,
these things of associating with them on the conscious level by making requests
and things like that is done in private.
And I know this is contrary to the cultural means
and the way that you've been taught,
but that's something you're going to have to figure out.
But what I can do is rationalize what is going on simply by the performance
of what is going on. Just think about how things perform.
This is performance-based information.
In other words, if you're getting an idea or a quote unquote belief,
which is even worse, I should say even worse meaning because belief is based
on something temporal that will be achieved later.
If you're getting these concepts of what the mind is and how it works
and all this, and it's not performance-based, in other words,
you cannot increase your performance, meaning your specific attributes
or benefit you, it is known as worthless information.
Yes, so has anyone been on the Internet lately?
Most of you, anyway, get it, or turned on mainstream media
or gone to church or university.
You get it. It's pretty worthless.
Unless you are, again, looking for a specific performance
and you need to gain this bit of information to work as such.
Now, in terms of the dreams, this is a reoccurring theme.
Yes, dreams are not your own, but the thing is most people are so casual
about them, and dreams have a lot of weight in tradition and in culture.
Think about it. When I mean a lot of weight,
I mean people like to discuss them.
It's kind of like from the old wives' tales all the way to the psychiatrists,
the spiritualists, PSY prefects, and all this.
They hold a lot of weight when you bring up the dream world
and interpreting dreams and what they are and all this,
but no one really gets down to the nitty-gritty that when you get a dream,
you're being plugged.
Basically, plug doesn't sound good, but it's usually not very good.
The reason why I'm saying they're not very good is because the level of quality
of those delivering the dream and the dream itself is so low
that in contrast to when there is a high-quality dream,
especially when you start getting up the ranks in the realm of the gods,
they typically identify that you are being plugged with a dream, basically,
on the more benevolent higher ranking.
But unfortunately, if you do get a dream from one of that level,
you may not survive it to tell everyone else that you did.
Just imagine having a thumb drive or a disc, using the computer analogy,
and walking up to a machine and just putting it in,
and the information kind of lights up when the thing was asleep
or the screen was black.
That's what dreams are, essentially.
But typically, at this point, most people's dreams
and most people's interaction with these lower-level entities
is for entertainment purposes, I think, both for the people
and those plugging the people.
But they're coming into a time period where the dreams will get more serious
and there will be some identifiable markers behind them.
So, yeah, that is an interesting aspect.
But those that are experiencing dreams in a negative way,
where they can't sleep or rest because the body does require a certain amount
of rest to rehabilitate physically, the dreams can be malevolent in that case,
or if not just being an outright nightmare, which, you know, whatever.
But I believe I found discussing this with myself and others for years,
meaning with myself actually trying it,
is that the more proper knowledge you gain of what is going on regarding dreams
and thoughts, you will benefit.
You will actually, let me just say it this way,
when you start getting to a point where your knowledge base is proper, okay,
your dreams will stop and you will actually have a very restful sleep
or they will be at an absolute minimum,
almost as if you were aware that a dream could have been coming but it didn't,
kind of thing, or maybe there was a dream and there wasn't,
or, you see, almost like a residue of a dream.
But, you know, some people enjoy having dreams and they'll have at it, you know.
However, you know, it's like the vitamin C.
There are people out there screaming about vitamin Cs curing everything.
Even putting it in your car maybe gives you better gas mileage.
Who knows?
But, well, I know, I'm just poking fun at the way people think and talk,
what I hear out there, both mainstream and alternative.
So I just wanted to bring this up.
This is a reoccurring theme.
Thank you, V, for sending that.
And that was a reoccurring thing because people have reoccurring dreams
and reoccurring thoughts.
I'm presuming most people are thinking, even though it's a – anyway.
So I would say that regarding the biblical questions here, yeah,
there's a time coming here, folks, where – I don't even like to use the word
because the Bible comes from Biblos in what's known as modern-day Lebanon.
You folks don't really have a lot of really good information,
at least what you've stored up in your heads about any of this stuff about the gods.
Why? Because it's come from religious circles, whether it's Christian, Judaic, Babylon, whatever,
any of these religions.
What it shows you is how the several levels.
First of all, the fact that humankind has been fractionalized and fractured
and broken up into various religions is not good.
Okay, now just hear me out because I'm not a proponent for a one-world religion
because that can't really happen because every group of people have to behave differently
in different parts of the world.
But you're fractionalized there and also you're fractionalized within each division,
within each group, whether it's the very fact that there are many different religions
and then within those religions there are other fractures and groups there.
I believe somewhere it was written that all of the institutions on the planet right now
or mankind's world are controlled by the adversary or Satan.
It didn't say except for religions, so we have to include those as well.
The other thing I would like to include is that another thing that was said
was that Satan's kingdom is divided.
So now we're actually, when you look at the religious beliefs, not some religion,
I'm talking about all religions now, there are several proofs in ancient texts
that actually explain them very, very specifically as being not good.
So anyway, that was the question.
I didn't get into it.
It was regarding the Book of Daniel and other things
because you're coming into a time period here where these things are starting to open up.
But the blind will have to be able to see and the illiterate will become more literate
and the seals will be loosened up in the future.
And I just want to reiterate, that's why people that are, let's say, venues,
whether it's alternative media, mainstream, written, print, university, new religious recruits,
you know, all these things, places where people go to get something
that is spiritual information-based or whatever are all not doing well right now.
The ones that are still just stringing along, just giving you the same old stuff
or, you know, let's just see what happened yesterday and talk about that,
they're not doing well.
The readership is down in newspapers.
Just about everyone in alternative media is hurting.
Mainstream media is hurting and there's a reason for it.
You are being sidetracked by the gods because what you are saying means nothing at this point.
Sorry, I said it that way, but because it's all the same stuff over and over.
It's the same dummy load over and over.
Or it's just so inaccurate that, man, okay.
Anyway, yeah, so now you know how I feel about what's going on in the planet
because knowledge is also based on communication
and communication is basically knowing what letters and words mean,
you know, having a sense of communication.
And what you can see being communicated is not very good
and it looks like there might be a call.
Wow, okay.
Someone has been waiting, not for very long.
Let's try them out and see if they are there.
Greetings.
I agree.
Sorry to hear that you are getting ready to cut it off here on the FRM.
It's been a real educational endeavor for me.
Sorry.
I just wanted to tell you thanks.
And also you mentioned about the goddess religions.
I didn't write that down.
I was trying to keep up with what you were talking about,
but I'll certainly go back in the archives and do my homework later.
But I just wanted to mention this fact, a little factoid for you
or whoever may be listening.
I live here near Nashville, Tennessee,
which according to the power that be is a hot city here.
Many people in the states are coming here for whatever reason.
I'm sure that has to do with sheep herding effect.
But concerning the – you mentioned repeatedly in your past conversations
about the revival of the goddess religions.
And as I go back in your old conversations a couple of years ago
and I'm trying to catch up and educate myself about things that I suspected in my own mind
but I didn't know how to articulate until I came across these talks that you provided,
and that's why I appreciate you so much.
You're welcome.
There is a revival of the goddess religions.
And I noticed this because I work in the legal field here in Nashville,
and I spend a lot of time in the local courthouses here.
And I never really paid attention to the buildings until as of recently.
As I come across your talks and I started doing homework,
and I'm looking at the building, one of the particular buildings,
if I give you the address and the name of the building,
that engraved on this building, which is an actual courthouse here in Nashville,
is Justitia.
That's right.
And I've been living here in Nashville since I served in the military prior to moving to Tennessee,
active duty back during the first Gulf War when I got out of the Army,
and I moved here in 1992.
And I've been here since for the most part because I've settled down and married and raised a family.
But just to give you some background on how long I've been here,
but it's now 2017,
and I've never even realized that engraved on this building is Justitia.
Which is a straight-up ancient goddess, yeah.
Yeah.
And I've been doing my own homework as I go through your previous talks
and creating notes for my private library for myself and my family.
And studying Justitia and looking back at the history of her,
not only in the Internet but going through local libraries here
and universities that I've attended here and so forth.
And as I go into this building, which is the building is the ñ
I'll give the name and the location.
It's the Justice General Sessions Court Building,
the Justice A. A. Berkshire Building here in Nashville.
And anybody can Google it, but you may not find photographs of it
because I've looked for photographs on the Internet myself,
but I can't find photographs.
But engraved all around this building are like 30, 40-foot-tall personifications of Justitia.
And I'm like, holy crap!
Yeah, yeah, it's right there.
This stuff that this guy's talking about is not some fabric,
the fabrications of someone's imagination.
This stuff is real because I've been ñ
myself, I've traveled through many places around the world.
And, you know, it's ironic that I've really never paid attention to these things.
Obviously, in the past, I had no idea of how ñ of the history of where things evolved from.
And it's only recently that I began to question where things evolved from.
I mean, because I've been around long enough in the world to realize that, okay, you know,
things that I see, things that I experience, and what I interact with in the world that I live in,
there's no way that this stuff could have evolved just, you know, 10, 50, 100 years ago.
Right.
And as I've come across your talks, which I believe are absolutely timely in my life and my experiences,
I've come to realize that, yeah, that is absolutely true.
And that you have simply articulated what truly is reality concerning all these matters.
Even when it comes to the scriptures, which I myself have ñ and when I say scriptures,
obviously living in the United States, the primary scripture from which all these versions of the so-called Bible come from
is King James 1611 Version.
Right.
And I have questioned that, which is what I want you to elaborate on, and then I'll hang up and let you continue.
You know, you mentioned in one of your previous talks, I believe it was the Rosetta Stone Part 2 with Ochoa,
about the Paleo-Hebrew, which is what I want you to elaborate on,
because I'm trying to figure out what was the original language that those so-calledÖ
Okay, I'm going to stop you right there.
You don't have to hang up.
Stay on, because I want to hear your comment on this.
Because, you know, the reason I'm speaking, by the way, is because nobody else is saying anything like this.
Right.
So the thing is, you want to say it once, you want to say it twice.
When you're satisfied that people get it, then you can like, you know, bow down and go away, because you achieved something.
That's why I'm speaking, you see.
So what I want to say is simply this.
It's important to be able to know the original language, only to see what the source is, right?
And anything, you want the original, right?
Because that shows you the reference.
And anything else that comes after that, that's not like that, is not the original, or a poor copy, or a fake.
Okay.
Now, when you look at something known as the scriptures, what is it?
Now, we're not talking in the pagan reality where they tell you to swear on it, or it's a talisman, or it's got some magic power.
We're not talking about that.
What it is, it's a communication, is it not?
Right?
You've got to read it, you've got to speak it, whether it's audio or you read it or not.
There's information there that needs to be communicated.
Now, if the information that was in the original language, or let's say the original communication was memorialized in a certain language,
it really doesn't matter what language you get it in as long as the communication or the information is preserved.
Another example of that would be, like, let's say somebody has an Apple computer back in the days, and they had a file.
Now, they put that file on a disk.
You go to Microsoft, it doesn't seem to work.
It doesn't recognize it, or you don't get the communication.
But if you have a program or a way to go from Apple, let's say, to Microsoft, a different operating system,
and all of the information comes through, then it doesn't matter if it's Apple or Microsoft.
It doesn't matter if it's paleo-Hebrew or English or whatever.
You see my point?
So ultimately, whenever you've heard me discuss anything about what's called the Bible or the word of the gods or the Most High God,
I'll have the people gotten a clear, concise, accurate communication of what the gods want to communicate to us.
And you know what the answer to that is?
No.
You still do not have that.
You don't have that information.
And then what we do is we could just backtrack and show you how.
You know when you go to the shops and they have these things, they've got ultraviolet light or a yellow marker,
when you hand them a 20 or a 50 or a 100 to see if it's counterfeit or not?
Yeah.
Okay, so at this point, if you took a King James Bible or any of the other Bibles and you ran that yellow marker,
it won't show that it's good.
It's not the communication.
If the gods gave you one of those markers, you could do that.
You say, no, this is not what we're saying.
You see my point?
And the only way to do that now is by using forensics.
What does that mean?
You need to go back and find evidence.
Forensics just means evidence.
So my point here is being aware of it.
Now, is it the time now where people will actually get the message?
No, not yet.
But is it coming?
Yes.
And is it going to be surprising the most?
Yeah.
Well, if you know about it now, it's surprising.
But one thing about the gods is when the information is opened up so every man and every woman and child can understand it,
it's not going to be a surprise to them.
It's not going to shock them.
It's going to be like, oh, okay.
You see?
And what I'm doing is just giving a heads up right now about what's going on.
And I appreciate that you appreciate it because here's the thing.
If half the people just helped one person, that takes care of everybody, doesn't it?
Right?
So if someone like yourself calling in and saying that it's helped you in just one thing, that's great.
I don't have to speak anymore.
I'm pretty much done.
Right?
That's the altruistic way of doing it.
But I think what you bring up about regarding going back to the paleo Hebrew,
which was actually in Israelite cuneiform writing, I would suggest that even if you found it, how helpful.
You still have to translate it into English, French, or German, or Chinese.
And then when you translate it, are you going to be able to communicate what's there?
And that hasn't been done yet.
You don't have that yet.
You have a general idea, but enough specifics are left out and enough mistakes are made
that people's idea of what is going on regarding the reality of the gods is still not known.
So this time is coming, and it's going to be interesting.
Just being aware of that is a big plus, you see.
That's why I didn't want you to hang up, because it's not about the original language.
It's about do we have a delivery of the communication, and the answer to that is no.
The information held within has not been communicated clearly or concisely.
Just how many times have you heard me say if someone says do you believe in God,
just walk away shaking your head, because there's no such thing.
There's a plurality.
If you say the word army, do you just think of one guy just standing there,
or is it a plurality of beings, you see?
I mean, that's how far off people are from reality of that.
Now, this has nothing to do with belief.
This just has to do with the information.
So we're at a point right now where these things are going to be changing.
But remember, the information that's going to be coming in the future
is going to come at the right time, which is not going to make people freak out.
If you push this information at the wrong time, you'll get people freaking out
and going wild on you, right?
So you have to understand the right time for things, and understanding time.
I mean, have you ever considered also the Pope's work schedule,
the Gregorian calendar not being a timepiece?
You know, when you celebrate a day every year, recognize observance,
a day, one year, it's a different day of the week the next year.
I'm sure you've noticed that as well.
Yes.
Yeah, and that means that it's not really, you can't keep time with that thing.
It's just a work schedule.
That's why they call it work week weekend, you know?
Sure.
As a child growing up, that was something that always confused me.
I didn't understand, okay, why would this, or my birthday, for example,
would be on a different day the next year and a different day the next year.
It's like it didn't, and I had no idea because I didn't grow up in a,
I guess you could say for lack of a better word, educated home.
My mom grew up in a home.
And I didn't understand.
I was like, it doesn't make sense.
But I had no way to question it.
I had no foundation upon which to question it.
But I just, in the recesses of my mind, I was like, it didn't make sense to me.
It didn't make sense that all these days of the year,
all these celebrated so-called holidays would be on different days of the year,
the next year, and it's just like something's just not right.
I didn't know what it was or how to articulate that it's not right.
There was just an intrinsic anomaly in the back of my mind that just said,
this doesn't make sense.
But it's not supposed to make sense.
You're not supposed to think about it.
You're just supposed to do it.
You ever hear about that, just do what you're told, right?
That's what I tell people.
Sometimes I might be critical.
I say, look, just do what you're told and you'll be fine.
Yeah.
Because it takes, you know, this is, when people figure out,
I mean, you said you were in the military.
You know, I've communicated with people in the military, family members,
those in the military, especially those in the field.
I've seen letters of officers, officers write back to their families,
and they say, listen, my own people or my own troops
and my own people are more dangerous than the enemy.
They shoot each other.
They kill each other.
I'm afraid for my life here, not from, let's say, the Iraqis, but my own guys.
You know what?
It's ironic you bring that up because I almost ended up in the Middle East
some years after I'd been in the military.
And long story short, I didn't go.
But in the back of my mind, if I had gone, that was my primary concern
because of the mentality of the guy.
And I was an officer, mind you.
And the mentality of the officers that I trained with was like,
are you kidding me?
These guys are freaking morons.
Do you not question what the hell they're trying to get up to try to do?
And I was in the armor.
I was in armor, M1s, you know, these 80-ton vehicles
shooting 120-millimeter rounds downrange.
And, you know, as an officer, you get to see before you go to command your guys,
because, you know, anyone, any branch of the military can attest to an officer,
whatever branch they're in, they can attest to their training that they have to be,
before they go out and command guys, they have to go through similar training
of what these guys that come in are going to do.
And I've seen the destruction that these tanks can do.
And as I was going through this training, in the back of my mind, I'm like,
how can you do this to another fellow man?
Well, because it's just the way it's where humanity is.
The earth is a very violent place.
Yeah, it is, it is.
I understand that.
But anyway, I just wanted to, from my own personal experience,
I get exactly what you're trying to articulate to others,
from my own personal experience as a military officer.
It didn't make sense to me.
And that was just something I couldn't do.
And I didn't end up going.
I just, it didn't happen.
I couldn't let it go.
I couldn't let it happen.
And that was kind of a turning point for me, you know,
towards trying to figure out, you know, okay,
I'm missing a lot of information in my life.
There's a lot that I don't know.
But I'm willing to just sit back and be taught what the destruction is.
Yeah, and the more obvious it is, the easier it is to learn.
Well, the harder it is to learn.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
So that's what I appreciate you appreciating the episodes and all that.
But I'm not going away.
You can go to Uncommon Radio, and I will be doing a podcast.
So you could dig into that.
And also, feel free to send an email or whatever.
It's on the site.
And I appreciate you appreciating what's being said,
because I think as the times change, more and more will be discussed.
And if you've noticed, the thing about I call Greek speak,
it's all the obvious stuff that no one's looking at.
Yeah, it certainly is.
But, you know, even, I mean,
repeatedly I have to listen to podcasts and study and take notes
and do homework and listen again and again and again to break through the
Pavlovian conditioning all of the years of my life to sometimes get one little tidbit.
Right.
And then it opens up Pandora's box to another bit, another bit, another bit.
Yeah.
I mean, your efforts are not futile in any way.
And I really believe that you've got some divine intervention that's placed you in this position
to be able to impart this information.
So thank you.
Thank you very much.
And that wraps it up for Solo 11.
We have one more to go.
This is Bell Lap.
And we will see you folks, everything being willing, next week.