Greetings everyone and welcome and this is a voice you might have heard before and it might be the only voice you hear for the
Next two hours on American Freedom Radio, and it's the Greek and if you heard me before it's with others
And which are greatly appreciated by the way, and we're gonna give it a shot. I'm flying solo here on American Freedom Radio and
Perhaps maybe without a co-host maybe the listener can be co-hosted on this as well
We'll see you we're also going to consider
Having some sonic input from whoever is listening, so we will somehow
Give you a Skype convention and a telephone convention, but this is also known as uncommon radio, so
Anyone out there. Thank you for coming, and this is also going to be archived on American Freedom Radio
and we will see how this project flies and
Perhaps you've heard Greek speak before perhaps you have not but either way we're going to be giving it a
solo kind of thing
Here on American Freedom Radio and also a courtesy website where you can get archives and other ways of getting in touch with the Greek would
be
uncommon radio
calm
so let's let's maybe get into it before we
Discuss anything or bring up anything for discussion perhaps. We're going to do
Give out the call-in numbers for those who might be curious just from the beginning and the call-in number would be
218 area code three three nine
eight five two five and for a Skype convention you would pretty much use the
Uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com
the whole thing
As the contact or you could put in the Greek and Skype and scroll down until you see uncommon radio
And that would be the one so for the Skype it would be uncommon sense radio one
that's a numeric one at gmail.com for Skype and
You could send a contact request if you would like to participate so just getting that
Idea that this is still open for anyone to call in
Because this is radio folks, and this is not a podcast as some might refer to it
It is just what we call radio, and it's live radio, and that's what makes it exciting so
with that out of the way
Again greetings everyone, and I will be looking at the chat room as well for any other input if it's so available
And I have emails open which you can contact the Greek through uncommon radio.com
So and here we are this is the solo flight
sort of an impromptu very
Or not introduced pretty much said let's keep the same time slot as Ocelli and the Greek was and we'll pretty much
Keep this sonic. Let's say event going I've gotten quite a few emails all positive by the way
people
Pretty much stating what they've gotten from listening to Greek speak or what the Greek has been reporting on over the years
And it's all been very positive
And and when I say it's been positive in no way is it ad hominem like well Greek
I really like the way you're saying it or I like you or whatever none of that stuff
it's all been very objective very straightforward based on the quality of the report and
Why why give a good report?
You know that's that's another we're probably get into discussions about
Things like that and if I'm monologuing it's not going to be much of a discussion unless you folks want to participate
But on the in the inside thinking of this of doing uncommon radio and continue it on AFR was
pretty much spurred on by
the end of the last
project with Chuck Ocelli there was a
Pole sort of taken by the Greek I'm speaking a third person here about perhaps
Having a project like a members area or something more private, and this is just a convention that I've noticed
Throughout internet world or internet or in a net world where people are offering things
On a merchant level
I've also stated
Directly and indirectly I find it to be somewhat distasteful
Not because it is but personally I find that and one of the things is not to share up too many personal
opinions or ideas
But the reason why is because these reports and the reason why they've been done and the Greek has been let's say calling in
years ago into radio shows and participating in let's say public forums about
not necessarily questioning things, but actually just bringing up a point of view and a mindset and
this this point of view in this mindset perhaps should continue and and
There was a desire for it to be done perhaps in the convention that people see on the web
Many hosts and many other venues do a certain paid members area or something
And and the thing is that there's nothing wrong, and there's it's actually very apropos to have good and fair exchange now
Let me just share this
What's going on behind the scenes in terms of evaluating that?
What the evaluation was is
Pretty much setting up a members area on uncommon radio where people now can go and access more like in-depth information
things that maybe were
Considered not to be set on a public forum and all these other things etc. Etc
And I actually started
Procuring something like that
I realized there was a massive amount of time to do and it should be done in audio format by the way
I mean treatises and white papers and reports can be given
But really it's best to have things that are written read out loud and what a better way other than audio format
So just not to get into any more detail. It seems like to be more of a project than the Greek wanted to get into so
Why why why not just continue let's continue perhaps on AFR as we are now and on common radio
At this time slot and consider it a members area and just as an example
I really do appreciate by the way all of the private emails about people
Wanting to do some kind of an exchange or send something this way, you know
Monetarily quote-unquote, you know their credits and their efforts, but we're gonna do a little experiment because this is a
an experiment before the experiment I mean
Before
Uncommon radio develops a private members area or or something like that that people are used to seeing and quote-unquote paying for using that
common terminology
Before that we're gonna try it just an AFR. So anyone that's listening that was pretty much inquiring
About a special project, you know things that are special, you know members area or something that they can buy into
What I am asking and
Suggesting and requesting is to buy into AFR right now
if here's the thing guys, and this is a private conversation done in public if the Greek comes on and
like tonight and there appears to be
Donations being made to AFR because of this request or let's say consider this the members area then it might be worth it
For the Greeks actually shell out whatever credits and you're needed and actually get into the supplies meaning manpower
people power woman power and all that other stuff to actually assemble a more elaborate section on uncommon radio, but
just as a litmus test if
not really holding anyone to their desire what they've expressed on joining or
But but indirectly, yes
If you hear this even on an archive go ahead and send a donation of some sort
To American Freedom Radio you will find how to do that on the home page and put a little mark on there that it was
Because of the Greek or whatever. It doesn't matter that you that you actually put in that was for the Greek or whatever
but I'm gonna use it and communicate with AFR if there has been an
Influx of some sort then
Everyone who stated they would like to join something that is more in-depth or something that is more in the convention that they're used to
Seeing on the Internet
Then it might be done. Otherwise
If there isn't a lot of action that way
But would just be clear monetary action towards AFR something being sent in
To AFR to just see how much of an effort can be made even indirectly
Because if there isn't then this will be the members area this particular show
Uncommon Radio open for all to hear now the wonderful thing about it. Is that when people join these members?
Areas or they feel like a sense of exclusivity
Okay. Well, you know, it's like I'm getting it because I'm paying for this or something, right? That's that's all well and good
but to do it openly right now just to see what kind of a
Feedback week is gotten from this particular
Show on Common Radio on AFR if there is an influx and then then it shows that there could be an investment behind the scenes
So actually develop that because I'm really not going to want to develop it
Turnkey, like everyone else does it's going to be something very interesting
But in the meantime folks if you're listening even on an archive send a donation to a farm
We will evaluate what the the listening public
Okay is capable of throwing towards a sonic project known as Greek speak or
something like uncommon radio or this type of venue this type of
Discussion where things are discussed
Well dummy load free perhaps should we say and we'll get into more of the mindset and the and what?
Quality of discussion and things are how things are evaluated and discerned on this planet
But in the meantime just to kind of throw this out to everyone listening in a private way that this is going to be
Sort of the quote-unquote members area for the Greek right now
and then you might say well that sounds kind of like an oxymoron because the private area you get a
Password and you go in and then you know
You get this sense of exclusivity and wait a second. This guy's just talking on air. Anyone can hear it
Yeah, but the interesting part of that is the best way to keep a secret is to put it in public
Right. So if you believe that you're comprehending what is being said here and actually listening and not just hearing
You're going to get more out of it than anyone. That's just hearing what's being said because the whole idea is about mindset
so we're gonna do this little experiment and I'm inviting you guys and gals out there that if
based on the responses again that the Greek has gotten an uncommon radio about perhaps doing
More exclusive project or a quote-unquote members area or private area or a project like that where it's quote-unquote paid as a
Term is used for an exchange of something right now. Let's see what can be done
by sending it to AFR and
Okay, is this a beg of fun for AFR? Is this a fundraiser for AFR?
No, it's not but on the other hand it is because they can use it and here's the thing. I
always
Kind of like give a little disclaimer the disclaimer for it this
Particular sonic project would be clearly this that the views expressed expressed by the Greek are not
Expressed by AFR or the hosts and they used to put that in quotes not even close. This is very very very unique
The reason I'm at AFR is because I'm at AFR and it's it's a really really looking at it objectively
It's you know, it's it's fine. It's great. It's a it's easygoing and
It's a it's kind of a cool place. You know, it's it's simple
It's it's not pretentious
So that's you know, I'm just happening to be here
So again just to tie things back
Let's do this little experiment with all the requests again about somehow
Supporting the Greeks efforts in a private or more private exclusive area go ahead
Let's see. What kind of support can be garnered with just uncommon radio on in public right now on this same time slot as you
as you hear so we'll see how that
proceeds or if it doesn't because to actually put any project together it takes an effort and quite a bit of
How would you say?
Expense and the expenses, you know that the time as well
so
Let's just see how that pans out and again feel free if anyone this is a
Feel-free if anyone so desires to call in
Again on the Skype, it would be uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com
Is the contact it's the email as well and the one is numeric and perhaps let's see on the call-in number
It would be two one eight area code three three nine eight five two five
And let me tell you folks when you get over about a half a century or so the body
No matter how good your vision is it starts to kind of you know
Peter out a little a little unfocused. So I get the little cheaters on and also there's an email where I could be directly responded to because
basically
Whenever you typically heard the Greek speak before it was either at a roundtable or a co-host and doing little
Joint venture sonic projects and this one is going to be solo. So and there's nothing planned
Basically
I'm talking to the monitor talking to whatever's in the room. I'm here alone and and to you folks
So the any requests of any topics or a or any subject matter can be brought up. Of course
This is AFR there. There is no limitation on that
So, please consider that just to reiterate again. I want to thank everyone that has supported at least, you know
So the support being garnered
Spiritually meaning by the mind or through intent and spirit by the way is intangible, but it's just a pure information
Was all very positive and it has been so far
Because the the people I think get a sense I've had discussions with people in there
Even those that are not familiar with what the Greek speak is about a Greek speaks about typically
when they kind of
hear the point of view
They say people are ready for that, right? And I'm like, well, it doesn't really matter
Does it I mean if they are or not?
The thing is you have to discern is it the time to say it because sometimes it might be the right time to say something
But the people are not ready to hear it and I believe that that's still the time period
one thing you'll see on the uncommon radio site is
Basically discussing the obvious of things that were things that are and things to come
That kind of sounds you know, you know, how do you how do you place that how do you figure out what that means?
well, you just sit back and and use some discernment and listen now one thing that uh
If you've heard the Greek speak before is one of the main things is discernment. Can you discern?
So can you discern the times, you know the times that you're living in, you know, the fashions the culture the trend
Can you discern things in the material world the natural world, can you discern?
Conversation, can you discern relationships? Can you discern basically?
On a qualitative level and that has always been the point or the crux or the crossing point between the quantity and the quality
You know, you ever notice how things are mentioned whether they're in positive or negative light a quantitative figure is given
Like for example when Hollywood does a film, oh this film made a hundred million this weekend, right? Okay
What is it? So there's that doesn't say anything about the quality of the film, right or you know this particular, you know
Lecture only ten people showed up, you know, it's like that doesn't tell you if it was a good lecture or not, you know
So the see these things are being done
Maybe they're out of time and out of place where people still have not really prioritized
What what level of discernment they should be operating on and it seems like the default in the universe is
materialistic or numeric
Whenever there is a lack of discernment. It seems that
You fall back on numbers big numbers mean it's good small numbers means it's not very good
In one of the things I used to do in terms of big numbers and small numbers
Here's a little discernment thing. I was on before I think about a year ago doing another project on AFR and
Coming on repeatedly
one of the things I want to do is like bust biblical cliches a lot of cliches that people use that you will find in
in the various
Versions that you have but it was not in the original language of preservation
So one of them was that you know
the I'll paraphrase here the road to destruction is wide and the road a certain road a good road is very narrow and
Straight narrow as they say so, you know that has never really been explained. It just gets kicked around
That is by the way, if you if you read that in context
If a big if you will find that is a point of discernment based on quality
Not on really a big road just being a big road where it's easy
Well, what you might state it was and there's the narrow road being difficult
That's not the context that it's in the context that it's in is how the how the quality of the road
Exists and say and how its travelers travel on it. For example a very large wide road
Let's just think of these big metropolises that have these superhighways with six lanes in each direction
You've got a lot of litter pollution they may or may not be well-maintained it's dirty
Uncourteous so on right you get the picture now
That's from an engineering perspective. Let's say a very large road will end up having that kind of condition now from an engineering perspective
If you're going to design a road that is very small or short
or a narrow road
That will because it's going to be traveled by very few you have time now to plant roses, okay
You have time to make it well manicured pave it really well
Maybe have maybe have a scenic view and have it well maintained
So the whole thing about the road being narrow and straight as it's translated
Or the version it doesn't mean that it's rigid and unpleasant. It actually means that it's more pleasant. You see so
One one that is perhaps maybe giving an example of
Things that maybe should be discussed because it seems like the easiest way
To pretty much get into the mindset and discern the mindset is to start by looking at the things that you're used to
What are you used to hearing and saying and there's a lot of cliches?
That are you know biblical. Let's say I'll just use that term because it's easy or scriptural and
But by the way folks there I've said many years ago that what you will see is going to be an increase of interest in
What's called spirituality?
whether it's a
mainstream conventional religion matters biblical matters
Of any what's called really even even in the New Age II
Stuff you know there's just I don't even know what to call that
I mean like the light people and the psychic people and all this there's going to be a less
Drive towards materialism and more of a drive towards the things spiritual or of the mind now not because
People are materialistic and have mastered that in any way not at all because people that are dubbed
materialistic are hardly masters at that at all because if you were truly materialistic and
That means you would be perhaps on a mastership level
Why aren't you complaining that you liquids are being stored in flat-bottom boxes?
Where it's pretty obvious in the material world that all liquids are in an ovoid shape so and it goes on and on and on
So being dubbed spiritual or materialistic that again doesn't give you the quality of that particular category
But to go back to the aspect of the mind
The discernment and the mindset
there's a
Tremendous lacking in a qualitative way. Yeah, I'll give you folks an example since this is radio
And you might not just be listening to the Greek you listen to other radio
Have you ever put on either mainstream or to alternative radio podcast videos and a certain subject comes up?
and it's usually
Typically with the big subjects regarding spirituality the universe of the gods or God they usually say all this other stuff
You ever hear them when they say well, you know God or the universe or whatever
Or hey, you know, it's it's your soul your spirit or whatever or it's this or that or whatever or you know
or okay, whatever you hear a discussion where a description or a point is being made whether you know, it's
somehow
Something that can be defined and is being conveyed in the conversation and the whatever is thrown in there. Guess what?
Guess what?
That person is just very happy to have the mic and you don't and that's about it
And you could you know read into it or read out of it what that means?
You know like whatever dude, you know, whatever, you know God or universe or whatever people say the universe
I'm like the universe empty space mostly we talking about or the soul the spirit whatever. What are you talking about?
Those are two different things
You know, it's like grab the car keys in the orange or whatever
What are you talking about?
The thing is now that
Nothing much has changed what's it what is truly amazing from an objective point of view is the stability
the stability of
The the level of how things are and yet people feel insecure which which rightfully they should
So, you know, we'll see how that
Pans out in the future because I've many times said there is about a another year left of this particular time period as it's known
So here is someone stated perhaps in a chat. There might be a question
Oh
Perhaps mentioning would talk about the universe any chance perhaps. Yeah, of course
Now the universe is something that is one condition supposedly, but there's many conditions of it
Meaning that there is the scene and the unseen here. Here's the mindset aspect of it when it whatever
Anyone is going to approach any information
Okay, there's a mindset that's involved. How many times have you heard someone in passing or someone?
You know, you start bringing up like, you know, how many eggs are in a basket or like? Oh, man, you know, I'm not mathematical
I'm not into math, right? They've already decided
On a mindset that you know, they can convey to other people communicate. Oh, I don't like math. Well, what's wrong with math?
Well, I'm not mathematical or if you bring up something regarding spiritual. Oh, I'm not religious, right?
So what does that mean? What does that have to do with you see it's there's there's a category for mindsets, right?
If you've ever imagined that you know, yeah, like I'm not mathematical or I'm not religious or whatever
What does that mean is so right away people are using that as a block or a shield?
Or it could be used for its advantage. Like someone says yeah, I like electronics, right?
So I have the mindset to look at circuits and rational things and logic and things like that, you know circuit paths
You know, okay. So, all right fine. So it works both both ways
now there's an interesting thing about the mindset of humanity and
How can it be objective if though if one cannot discern things for their quality and it's again just for their numbers
But again, the main thing here regarding what's called the Sun in the universe and all that
Like I see here in chat. People are asking
Is it a heat source and you know
There's fun a heat source and all that the problem with this again having a discussion like this is what I've mentioned in the past
is I
Use the term moron, right?
That's a technical term and technically the term means someone who stopped developing at the age of 12, which is very lenient
most people that you will meet right if you are
Let's say on a path of discernment
You will notice that they're pretty much have their characters pretty much very much in common with what's called a nine to ten year old
Well know what I mean by that. This is not a put-down or pejorative of being condescending. Is that typically between?
when when the formative years begin
People pretty much have figured out that what it takes to know things and they stay on that path
When people hear new information
They pretty much attach it
They compare it to a filing cabinet that began developing around eight or nine years old and up until you know
Whatever time they decided to close that file cabinet. It was full
And whenever they hear information
They have to try to match it up with things that they've heard before
Right, and that's the biggest problem by the way with many researchers because if someone sets out to research something
Well, that's not really necessary in the state of affairs today
Why because research means to search it again to research it because most things have not been searched out once
anyway
so
This is a big problem for many people in in that field, you know, you hear about a lot of the you know
in the conspirology, for example
They're called researchers and scientific researchers and ancient document researchers or whatever
Archaeologists or you know, whatever is it being properly searched out the first time and
Once it has then it can be researched again
And I would suggest that things have not been searched out now going back to the
Questions about the universe and the Sun is it a heat source and all that? How can one have a discussion?
Regarding of what can be seen?
Right and what can be observed and objectified regarding these matters meaning looking up when someone you discuss
What is the universe or the Sun? It's like you're basically looking up
When the any information that's given is going to be compared to all the things that they've been
Taught already before it's the cognitive dissonance thing could kick in and all that. So the point here is can you see it clearly?
when when some let's say if you're asking a question regarding that how about
Maybe giving a little bit of an outline and what you've discovered that you can be known about it already
Right as a baseline, you know
You know, there's there's an example for of a trend that's been going on
Regarding the shape of the planet. Okay, if you want to call it a planet if it assumes one shape
Maybe it's not a planet if it assumes another and that is a moot point
For example, the reason I always bring that up. There's a moot point
I'll just say at the flat earth versus the globe or the round is because are you have you already mastered?
Being on the earth because to be a master on
Being on the earth. You have to master the movements of the Sun and the planets as such
When you're a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant, the Sun rises in the east and sets in the West. Have you mastered that?
Have you mastered that regarding?
Agriculture orientation of structures
So on and so forth, right? No because
perceptively
What you will see it's a geocentric universe, right?
That the everything is going around the earth and because of that perception
Well, if you for example understand or want to believe that the earth goes around the Sun
How does that help you? How does that information transfer back to?
What you see which is the Sun going around the earth, right and what's more important if you're going to master
The material aspect of being here in a body is the Sun rises in the east, you know
And sets in the West which gives the perception that it's going around the earth and it's important to master those movements now
Let's just throw this in because if you've heard Greek speak you've heard this again
Don't even know what day it is. Do you right and that's a question
Why because seems like everyone is operating under a modality that I call the Pope's work schedule
The Gregorian calendar as if it's a timepiece and it's not let me just throw this in there folks
We pretty much had a 13th moon this year and it appears to be the 22nd of the 13th moon
So about noon wherever you are, and by the way, just to throw this in again, you know
How if you are in the Western Convention, you know as you are the northern part of the world
Let's say and you discuss things. Let's see Europe in America. You discuss things with
People in New Zealand Australia, let's say they're in tomorrow
They're actually not lawfully they're behind and if we've done measurements on that to show it
So so what's going on? There's a convention that's been overlaid over mankind and just to throw this in again
I didn't give a time marker on the Pope's work schedule will be March 2nd
But lawful timekeeping, that's what the trees the birds the planets and all that
Operate on and in other words this day will be exactly the same day next year
It's the 22nd day of the 13th month and in fact of 13th month
And you may not have a 13th month next year, but you might have it in four or five
Let's say which is it's very interesting and I've never gotten into the 13th month
intercalation
So again, the question in the chat was regarding the Sun in the universe
That is a huge huge question
Okay, and actually missing okay being the question here perhaps is
Giving giving homework perhaps is the Sun a heat source, okay?
well
Yes, it is a heat source, but it's in a form of induction
It's not the type of heat that you imagine what let me just for the listeners that are listening to this in the future
an archive
It's it's a concept of induction. There's a glass stovetop by a few folks might have seen it's electrically powered
You have a pot of boiling water you move the pot of boiling water to the side you put your hand right on the
Stovetop it's room temperature. You put the pot of boiling water or actually the pot of water right on the induction top and it
Starts to boil almost immediately, so where is this heat coming from?
Most of the heat in the that we sense is coming from the Sun because it's directional when you feel it on the skin
It occurs roughly 150 miles outside of off the earth's surface, so I agree. How do you know that have you been there?
No, don't have to go there. You can pretty much see what's going on if you can see
Right now the thing is if the Sun is a heat source according to the laws of thermal thermodynamics
Which is the inverse square by the way if you understand the geometry of a circle and its radius you'll understand
They're the inverse square, but anyway and the surface of a circle or the sphere
You'll understand how the inverse square works. It has to do with a ratio a
Pythagorean ratio, let's say
but just to
Perhaps not answer because if you're they're asking the question or asking asking the answer if you're asking the answer
Another question might arise and that is why is it as you travel closer to the Sun?
Which is allegedly a heat source it gets colder and colder and colder
Right because what you're actually
Seeing when you see sunlight or heat is you're seeing the
Degenerative aspect of that source right just like electricity when you measure
Current and voltage that is a degenerative aspect the grounding aspect. It's the rubbish part of nature
Well, how can you say the Sun is rubbish? Well? It's not really rubbish
It's just the part that breaks down
into the material aspect
That is when I say material as we have the pressurized material aspect
now these are things that if there is inquiry we can get into it with a proper introduction because
Sometimes just looking at a chat and trying to answer a question is a pretty good
Way to keep a let's say a thought or interact with those that are listening
But you know another thing is perhaps is a light source well
Yes, it is a light source, but it is the moon a light source well
It seems that the moon is a light source is being written here of course, but it's secondary not primary. Uh-huh
right
There's a reflectivity there so again
There are so many things to discuss and folks there is a period of tension
I think I've explained in the past anyone's heard this kind of type of speak before
that will be ending in about a year and
And
To get off the universe in the Sun topic for a moment one of the things of discussion is that how man is agriculturally based
being agriculturally based agriculturally based doesn't mean you have to get dirt under your fingernails and
Wrangle a plow or a bull or an ox or work on a farm
It just means that your existence here is agriculturally based I once had a discussion with a computer programmer
He said Greece Greek. We're not agriculturally placed. I said, okay fine
I'll lock you in the room with the computers and see how long you can stay in there before you want to come out
For something that's agriculturally based now another way to perhaps state. You know earth inhabitants is
it's turned into a pig farm in a way a cross between a pig farm and an insane asylum and
this might be an interesting trough to come and feed off of because
Most people you'll notice by the way, don't really care unless someone's coming to take bacon off day back. So
Anyway, just thought I'd throw that in for you guys
Especially the you folks in the future that will be listening to this down the road
many of the questions by the way that are asked or
Require pondering and
There's a sitcom mentality or the light conversation
Basically that people are used to having amidst all the pranking that they've had already. But anyway, we'll get into that in the future as well
That quick things can be answered and decided
Concisely and quickly. Yes, they can be but again is the mindset there
How do you if someone has a mindset for example, like I'm not mathematical or I'm not religious
How can you bring up even a short discernible package regarding any of those topics if the mindset isn't there?
so the general mindset is
Not necessarily a problem
But it can be viewed at how it leads to the way people think and function on this planet, you know
so again, this is uncommon radio if anyone wants to
Call in we could we have someone running the board at AFR
And just to throw that number in again
Let's see, it's a 2 1 8 area code 3 3 9 8 5 2 5 and on the Skype convention
You would use the email for uncommon radio, which is
Uncommon sense radio 1 at gmail.com. It's kind of long and the number one is
Numeric so if you guys want to interact
But again, I want to thank AFR for you know, pretty much agreeing to
Continue some
Sonic let's say reports from the Greek
and continue this
At the same time slot as the previous venture went on or sonic adventure
I should say and for you folks that were not here in the beginning. I
Just wanted to mention a recap. I'm doing a little bit of an experiment. I've gotten a lot of emails and
let's just say correspondence regarding people taking interest in a members area and
Something more exclusive and the experiment in here is okay
let's see what happens if the Greek goes out solo and
Pretty much gives whatever he would give in a membership area for two hours a night once a week and just see how it goes
And if you folks think that it's worth anything
Should it be?
Let's just say fair exchange. I mean, are we merchants now? No, we're not merchants. Are we receiving a benefit? No, it's just credit folks
Send it over to AFR. You know how to do that
they have the the electronic conventions in place you go to the home page and if
If it can be gauged that those that are listening even not tonight, but even down down
Let's say in the future. Let's say on archives
I'm going to try to keep some
Accounting on what's being sent in and that will pretty much show the measurement of how much of an effort?
Can be made behind the scenes because there's a tremendous amount that can be discussed again. It's not the information
It's the mindset behind it and can you discern it, you know?
so
Perhaps doing a two-hour
let's say sonic event once a week on a minor Internet radio platform and
Calling it a members area and calling it exclusive sounds kind of asinine, right?
It doesn't doesn't make any sense because it doesn't look like the convention that everyone else or whoever everyone else that has an exclusive
or members area is using but
Let's just try it. Let's see. What kind of a response and this would be an equitable
Let's say monetary response towards AFR and if it seems to be
Let's say a measurable in any way there might be an effort done on this part here to develop uncommon radio
so
Just wanted to bring that up because we're about a half hour into it just to remind anyone that has heard it or has not
Heard it yet, but there are many things to be discussed
But again folks regardless of the subject matter the discernment has to be discussed, you know, there there's something
How would we say there's an emotional aspect to this as well?
You know how people feel like well, I really like that and you ask them why it's like I don't know
I just do you know, okay, so, you know, why all right, you know, okay
So all they can do again is describe are we getting any explanations or are we just getting descriptions?
If you're familiar with how the scientific
Society or community works lots of descriptions very little explanations the legal society medical society all the same way now people
Tend to have fallen into that model and when you ask them why they favor or disfavor something
They don't sense that they have to tell you why and really it might be I'm not talking about prying into the personal aspect
Or the private aspect of why but I think it could be packaged very neatly and given
The reason can be given or the sighting can be given as the you know
The the yay or nay is given also and you'll see that
That is one of the things that are lacking
Right now with people at large, you know everyone pretty much it doesn't matter where you're from
This has been going on for a very very long time and one thing you might have heard
Discussed in the past with other sonic events, especially let's say in the past year
I've been bringing up the concept that of the level of pranking on this planet
Yes, if you want to know what the Greek means by pranking just look up what their word means typically means a ludicrous trick
Right things are not as you have been told now
But some things really are see some of the pranks really are like for example
It starts when you're young when the parents might say something like you know
When you grow up you're gonna have to go to school like I did you're not gonna learn much
But you have to do it because I did it right and the other thing outside of the pranking would be
motivation through penalty
well you
so and
Speaking of motivation through penalty. We have someone who's motivated to perhaps call in so
Let's just see what they have to say caller if you are there, let's see if AFR can bring you in
Hello
Yes, greetings
Greetings
It's Chris in Tennessee. How's it going?
All right, Chris. All right. What's on your mind? You're on uncommon radio at AFR
Yeah, I got I got I was fortunate tonight. They will come across this I wasn't expecting this I didn't
Expect to hear you doing your own thing, but that's good
My I'll get to my question I'll express it right quick and then I'll ask him a question and I ain't got to let you elaborate
Take your time. Go ahead. Take your time. Go ahead
I've been
I've come across your your talks and just recently I should say that with this year
Whatever that might mean depending on who you talk to
And
It's ironic
From from some of the talks that I've dealt back into in the previous talks you've done
I've noticed you referred to
Well, I guess I get to my question
Maybe I haven't gotten to that point in my studies yet. I've gone back just recently into
Real ancient ancient historical studies of where a lot of things come from that we have in
practice today and
It's been a process for me for probably I guess since the mid 90s
So it's been it's been ongoing to get to this point to say, you know, this doesn't make sense
You know this, you know, this stuff didn't just appear in a vacuum say for instance, I give the example like
What quote the Bible?
And that could be I mean with all the different versions, you know
Don't figure but I refer to like the 1611 King James Version Bible. Okay. I say well 1611
Okay
Well all this stuff that you just didn't appear in a vacuum and even in those that Bible it refers back to stuff
That was going on. Well before
It's time
but
My question is now I'll get off and I'll let you elaborate
Because before it before you get to your question
I hope you got a grip on it because here's the other thing when you said the 1611 King James that was supposed to be a
Version or an English version of the scriptures that were pretty much finished being canonized around the first century AD and then you know
The the other stuff prior to that so we're looking at 1611
That's roughly 1,500 years after the fact of all these things that were memorialized
You see now, let me just throw in something for thought. It might might help you with the question or not
Is that even today one of the most prolific?
Validatable texts that are available to mankind to validate their time is the is the scriptural text preserved in Hebrew and Greek
in other words you see if you in other words
You've heard of the Dead Sea Scrolls when they got put together
It took about 30 40 years before they decided to sequester most of it and not have in public view most of it
And the reason why I've heard in private discussions with people that were loosely involved with it
Was it will ultimately the the last thing they want people to understand and comprehend and grasp is
That if you go online or get something called the Masoretic text in Hebrew, let's say language of preservation
It is word-for-word in space for space identical. What was really written?
2,500 years ago or 2,000 years ago and and that kind of confirmation seems to give it more importance now
I'm not talking King James. I'm talking about the language of preservation
How something I had still made it to this time?
So when we talk about King James, you know, if you could study the history
Which is very difficult on why that document was put together and by who and how?
Yeah, that's a whole other thing so I'm gonna I'm gonna just digress I mean I'm not gonna I'm gonna just sit back and go
ahead and
Continue either with the question
Yeah, what you just said this got me to this point. It's like okay if these guys had this information that 1611 supposedly
That was you know, the power that be that were
Authorizing these things to be written, you know, it makes me wonder
Did that come from and that's what got me to this point, but
I'm glad you brought you know, you the Masoretic text didn't know about that. That's what I'm taking notes
Well, well before you continue again
What did come from the 1611 came from just exactly that little time period that you just brought up right there
What's go what went on around that time in England is a period to study all on its own and you'll see how hastily it
Was done, but but go ahead. Yeah. Yeah
So, let me get to my question and I'll get off I'll let you elaborate
I'm having trouble. I've been going back and
I'm an I'm an infant at this
trying to locate
etymological dictionaries, I've been able to find some that were reasonably old but
Not as old as I like for them to be of course being here in the States
You know, we've got limited information
I've spent some time overseas in different places, but
At the time that I was overseeing in different places
I had no clue about reality and real history
So I didn't even have any idea that hey, I'm in a place that has a real long
History to going back well before the United States. I could do some digging while I'm here
But since then I've grown up and learn. Hey, maybe if I go back to the Swiss, I'll do that
but I have a question about
One of your talks previous talks you did with them Shelley. We've done some good work, by the way
You mentioned you guys you get you guys talked about
Soul and spirit and I'm having trouble reconciling
with
What I found thus far doesn't mean I'm not gonna try it but what I found thus far. It's only going back to about the 17th century
etymological dictionaries
Where the soul is what I've been finding. It's defined as
Actual spirit and not breath up. I'm having trouble finding where the soul
Sure, you might want to go a little further
Let me just cut a step on you just for a second
Then you can I want you to continue on on your experience discovering this because on
Previous events perhaps that you may not I may not have up on the uncommon radio site
Are you found on archive is that we're living the past 2,000 years in a time period where things are shut down
Okay, there was a cosmic censorship 2,500 years ago on things pretty much all all
Extensive knowledge and even when I say extensive knowledge was how man existed pre-flood. That's all been cut off around then
So now the soul in the spirit now, here's the thing about the soul in the spirit
Let's just say you're looking for it in English. Okay, I'm presuming you know, you're an English speaker. You said you travel
Okay. All right. Now English is is an agglomeration
It's a it's an interesting language. It's very verbose
It's not direct, you know, it can be no, but what well, you'll notice when it is direct their bar
They're using Greek technical terms are using Latin technical terms. So so here's the thing
Yeah
Our existence is dependent on the mind. Let's say us being as a spirit being animated in the physical sense
So that means that you've got you're made up of three things the soul the spirit
Let's just say the breath the mind and the body now, that's headquarters. That's HQ
That's what makes you you you know your mind your ability to be alive, you know
The life force and the physical flesh right now if you
obscure two two definitions out of those three
The vote is against you, isn't it two out of three against you? I mean to get right
Okay, so why not just keep the definition of those two other aspects obscured now
We I just threw in a bunch of stuff here for you. Now, let's go back
English is fairly recent if we go back to all older languages
We will always find that the word soul means breath
Simply it's a mechanical to pneumatic for example in Greek. It's pneuma PNU
that's where you get the in English the prefix whenever you see PNU that means movement of air and
Then the mind is
PSY where you hear psychic psychologists, I call that's the spirit, but you'll see Psyche, right?
So in English, it's it was very common to obscure it. Look, you know earlier you brought up the 1611, okay?
Do you know that prior to that not much prior to that around 1500 there before that there was no letter J
Okay
In my own studies just I mean just from the scriptural studies that I've had over the years
Even within that 1611
version of the Bible
That's delineated there. I mean, I can't when I when I found that I'm like, whoa, wait a minute
Yeah, it was an IE they use instead of a J. Yeah. Yeah, there's no J even during that
You know what that they had actually translated. So I'm like, okay
You know knowing that this was certainly not the original language
English being what back in history from what I've seen has been considered kind of like a dog language of
Yeah, like you should mention the conglomerate of a number of different
Like it's a sign of the times
right
Years in universal in universal aspect 500 years is nothing right in a big aspect, right?
Yeah, right
Let me just let me just consider consider one more thing when you're trying to find things in English a lot of these young
Folks right now. They don't know when you say telephone, you know, they reach for one of those silly phone things
You know with the screen on it, right?
Screen and whatever now, could you imagine giving one of these jokers a rotary phone and tell them to dial the number?
Think about that
Well, it's funny you say that because I worked at telecommunications for about 15 years
back when
In the mid 90s when they supposedly quote-unquote opened it up for competition
Okay, right right alleged competition, right? Yeah
But a competition that's another thing
It's like something's being hidden in plain sight if you ever been to a big city anywhere in the world
When you go to restaurant row, they got all these restaurants next to each other in one Street
You go to the garment district the diamond district. They got a hundred stores all right next to each other. Where's the competition?
They work together
Right. The reason they're telling you about competition perhaps is so you could give up 90% of your energy to whoever says you should and
Then stab each other in the back for the remaining 10% which you kind of see ever been in a parking lot of a big
box store, but anyway
Think about English now. Here's the thing the mindset. I was discussing earlier
Is that we're limited in a the 70 80 90 what a hundred year old, but you know existence
That is very very very short to determine things in the way that you just brought up for example now
what I would suggest is
If I said to you if you're pretty fluent in English or even if it's the only language
You know I can assure you you got about 50 words
Maybe 50 to 100 words in your vocabulary right now that are Greek, and you don't know it
In other words you're about one quarter fluent or one about maybe 20% fluent in Greek
And you don't know it if you speak English and probably five or ten percent fluent in Hebrew if you speak English you see
So a lot of these words have Greek and Hebrew origin and Latin origin so speaking English is
Actually making you well. I wouldn't say proficient, but semi
Workable in these other older languages you see what I mean by that
Okay, see if I if I lost him there, but anyway, maybe he jumped off
I don't know. Maybe someone at the board will tell me if we lost him or not or he's just taking a pause
Okay, great
So anyway the question there that
The the caller brought up was having difficulty with the soul and the spirit and I have brought that up many times before
Where if you look up a simple definition of the soul it means the breath
But it could also mean the spirit and then if you look up the spirit
They tell you well it means the mind and it's ethereal or whatever and it could also be the soul
Wait a second folks if that's not a scam. I don't know what is so
You have to also remember folks when he said said he was having a hard time finding etymological
References those are not popular what are popular dictionaries, and we'll get when we come back after the break
we will discuss the concept of why a
Dictionary is so popular and what that term means so we'll see you at the other part
Greetings
And this is uncommon radio with the Greek or it might be without the Greek
It depends on if you're just listening or hearing because if you're hearing things of course
It's the Greek, but if you're listening the Greek is irrelevant. It's what's being said think about that folks
It's not about what you like or if it's likable or not
Are you getting what it is and just to want to thank the caller who called in for the previous hour?
And one thing I want to just rolling around in the head. I want to just bring up
He says that he didn't know what reality was and actually it's kind of hard to say that because it is reality
It's just not a high-quality
Reality perhaps just want to throw that in there for anyone who thinks about saying that's not real or that's fake
No, it's pretty real. It's just not qualitative
Or qualitatively assessed and before we went to the break
I brought up the one trying to discuss what the caller brought up was about difficulty finding
etymological sources and
In print and of age, let's say and why did I brought up the concept of the dictionary?
really short without maybe elaborating on or maybe
elaborating on it
His diction is how things are pronounced
So when you are let's say a ruler or a lord over a group of people and after a while
You don't want to be known as a ruler over those who don't know how to pronounce things
So what you do is you give them a guide or a help known as a diction
Erie
that allows them to learn what how things are pronounced and it seems like
Definitions are ephemeral meaning they change right?
So that's why when you let's say get a dictionary and you look at it
Look up a word you will see how it is phonetically spelled next to the word
You know and sometimes, you know the upside-down ease and the little lines and things
That's how you pronounce it
Now the meaning of the word that is typically being given is the way that they who they are
Would like their subjects to pronounce it or
Uncomprehend or unless you got company or understand what that word means, but etymology
Etymology and
etymological dictionaries go a little bit beyond that they give you a little bit more of the history and the use a lot of them will
Describe that etymology is not necessarily empirical. It also is ephemeral it changes
What let's say what how words are defined to what they mean, but do they really folks, you know, is it possible?
Yes, it is. It's happening, but it gives a little bit more meaning
One of the things that always comes up is
Do you say what you mean and mean what you say and is that important and obviously it's not anymore
Why should it be?
One of the things I had always is discussed is the concept of cosmic censorship and I want to say always with me Greek-speak
There's you haven't missed anything in other words
It's not like missing the bus or an opportunity unless you're over
2,500 years old you have not missed anything
You've been born into this reality and based on the limited aspect of one's longevity, you know
you're you're pretty much either going to be engrossed in the times or you're pretty much gonna tune out and
Not know what's going on in either way. It doesn't matter because the human lifespan is too short. So
Again
Do you say what you mean and mean what you say and that's another concept, you know, it could be you know
It's taken from a pedantic point of view and say angry. That's pedantic. You know, that sounds like you're really having a hard time
You know, how are you gonna communicate and all this well, you know think about it
Let's just take the aspect of forgetting about what words mean and are we being accurate because there's some hypocrisy there
You know, if you're getting shoes or a door fixed by a carpenter or tires you want them to be accurate
But when it seems like there's communication the accuracy and precision tends to not be important
And it all it all falls apart, doesn't it to some extent and just to put that aside for a moment
If it's not just regarding words, let's say you're having a conversation with someone and it's about maybe associating with
Someone new someone you have not met yet, and you would say listen, you haven't met this person yet
But he doesn't say what he means or she doesn't say what she means and doesn't mean what she says
Is that someone you want to do business with is that someone you want to have as a friend?
Is that someone most of those are people say no
No, I don't want anyone that has that kind of quality
interesting
Okay. So where do you draw the line? Do you say what you mean and mean what you say if there's
No desire or very little desire to find out what words mean now. I've discussed in the past
The concept of is what's called the Democratic
World I've also said freedom is a concept once of course because if you're on this planet
You're really are not free and freedom by the way means to be free of dominion or free of a state
So it's really interesting when you see a politician say they want freedom because that pretty much
It's kind of like a shoemaker saying everyone should be barefoot. It's just don't know what it means either but
if you're if you're looking at
the state of affairs on this planet and you're looking at the way people are functioning and
You have come across terms of we say oh
I'm depressed or I know the world is not fair or I know this or this is not really great
I just do this, right? Okay
That's fine
But in order to be able to suss things out
Are you able to act with efficiency? Are you able to make a clear decision?
You're gonna have to set yourself apart from it
And once you understand what it means to be set apart from it like a third party
Then you can go back in with a cool head
You see this often
Hmm, let's say with people in the emergency
services
typically if there's a car accidents a real grotesque
Outcome the people the bystanders could be anywhere from screaming to throwing up to not wanting to look at it
But here come the paramedics and they are just cool as a cucumber. They go about
Whatever that needs to be done
Efficiently and they could also be you know be scooping up someone's guts and discussing
You know where they're gonna have lunch in an hour
Because they they already were exposed to all of this
Before it happened in through training. So when you hear people discussing things
Like for example the when the caller asked the question that he did
He and he said he's come across this type of let's say project recently
He's
He's even if it seems like he said this year, which would probably be a few months
He's fairly new at this and he's probably discovering how much work is involved
To do it on your own, even though all of the hints and all of this can be laid out. There really is no
complete advice or how to
ultimately, you're going to have to do your part and it's really slow in the beginning and
It seems laborious
But you know the work if it if it if it tips your ticket like they say do it
Otherwise, you know leave it alone, but I want to go back to
Being a third party if you look at
How most of the authorities by the way, whether you view them as being benevolent or benevolent is irrelevant
It's always done by third party. Now. How can you be a third party in your own existence?
Well simple if you're affected by actions and thoughts separate yourself from it for a moment
So you can see it clearly and then when you become engrossed in it again
You already had the time without being in it
You're you've had the time of being outside of it not without being apathetic or negligent
but you could see it more clearly and more rationally and this is something that you
You who is a listener or will come across throughout all media when I say all media, I mean all with a capital L
You will see discussions that are being
hmm
let's say sign of the times or this week's discussion or
you see what everyone is pretty much doing and
The interesting thing is in this democratic society
You're or what's called the Western part where the individual rights?
And all that are not to be tarnished. Let's say they tell you be individual, but whenever you're dealing with anyone of authority
Their agents or themselves. They always want everyone to be the same if you start bringing up your individual attributes or points
They'll say shut up. You have to be just like everyone else, right?
Inprivate but public they're giving a different
Message you see so there's there's a tremendous amount of hypocrisy in this
In this existence and it's not something that's going to change. So the only the only thing there is no solution
To it other than when your time is up
the thing to do perhaps is to can you
Objectify what's going on? Can you pull yourself out of it? And when you go back into it?
Be objective and rational and not get caught up into it because right now an all-media like I said with a capital L
They all tend to be swayed whether it's mainstream or alternative in a group think a crowd mentality
And right now if you're picking this up, this is what they
It's almost New Year, by the way lawfully a couple of weeks away meaning the first
The first day of the first month is soon approaching in a couple of weeks or a week or so I should say
But it's what they call March or the third month on the what I call the pagan or Gregorian calendar
and
what is being discussed now is still the American political scene and
I want to throw something in here because I
Spent quite a bit of time. I was told earlier a Greek you spent 13 minutes discussing, you know
the the experiment of
instead of having a private members area where people would do and listen come some kind of monetary exchange and like a
Convention like other people have just to send it to AFR to gauge
What kind of a response there is or what you know?
What kind of investment should be made behind the scenes to create such an area, you know?
so
The things that were perhaps will be said here little by little might be something that you would find in a second hour a
type of a
Second type, but let's say the premium or the more exclusive side of other other venues
And things like that and it would be interesting to those that want to
Donate to a cause or buy into something like that to pretty much do it publicly through AFR for this episode and perhaps the next
Just to gauge what it's like, but I assure you that
What could be said
Not saying it will be but what can be said here for the two hours on AFR with the Greek would probably much
We're probably say rival most of I'm gonna be high on the britches and things like that
But rival what you would get anywhere else, you know
And in terms of putting something together and throwing it out as an exclusive tidbit of information
let's say that you can see packaged and
You know doing good work or giving a good report
But you know, maybe something can be thrown in before let's say this night is over got up another 45 minutes
Maybe I could do it now or do it a little bit. I just want to maybe do it now. I don't know if you
Folks might agree with it or not, but I'll just throw in something a little tidbit. Have you folks ever heard of 9-eleven?
Researchers, okay, you know what what they all seem to miss. There's someone that kind of
Touted this will for a short time and that went away
But you know why bring that up it seems like anything that's being researched as well as such a conspiracy Greek and I'm not for or
Against anything that's being said whether it's the official story or not
But why isn't there any discussion on the level of complexity from an objective point of view?
I people really looked at everything. No, or do we grab on certain notions and concepts?
Do you know for example the way the buildings came down was very unusual and the methodologies that are being explained
Have always led, you know, the contrasting methodologies. Let's say have always led to contention amongst those discussing it. So
Why why isn't it possible to find video evidence of other things?
That have let's say
Disintegrated like that using a methodology that's been around since the early 60s and it's on YouTube folks
And it's it's funny how no one has found it
the other thing I wanted to bring up is
about 9-eleven because this was a short discussion recently on this and and
What what I do is I don't just I don't like discussing it publicly
But I do it in private because the public sorry folks
You don't deserve the truth regarding many of these matters because of your behavior and I'm talking about the public at large
You know, you don't pull your sister's hair
You don't kick your brother in the groin and you won't get any dessert, right?
So you're not going to get the truth of matters
You basically like arguing too much and forming little cliques and groups and look what I can do or whatever
So it ain't gonna happen in public, but let me just throw this other tidbit in here or this is the tidbit
Why isn't there any discussion on how let's say
Something that happened on that morning was really the result or the product of what you would see in a James Bond movie
Right. I mean what well, that doesn't make any sense and I'll just throw this out there
If you want to really understand one of the things that happened that morning not in New York City
But the other place is you're gonna have to look into a character a case called Victor boot VIK
Tor and boot B O U T what he's been charged with certain crimes, right? Well, what was his crime?
Really? What was what did the Justice Department need to satisfy in terms of case for me?
You're not going to find that in public
But what was interesting also when you tie that together with the American political scene right now
There's a lot of discussion about a place called Russia, right?
Right. Well, why do you think it's because of some kind of election or something of you? Are you doing your research here?
where's Victor boot from and
What was he being charged with that's going to be kind of difficult to see openly and
Tie all that together. Why is there still a discussion with Russia? Yeah, it's been 15 years or so
I mean, let me just throw one thing one more thing in and this is the most that I would do public
Do you want to curse class submarine is?
Okay, look it up. There's one that made it that imploded and went all the way to the bottom around
I think it was 2000 or something the sinking of one particular
Submarine, this is very technological submarine things like that don't happen. What was aboard that submarine?
So and it was Russian also, so if you think this talk about
Russians is has to do with what you are being told you have not looked at the whole picture
Let's say so that's just a little bit of that. I mean so much can be done
It's not a rabbit hole. By the way, it's pretty open to see if you want to prime one's thoughts in that direction. So
Perhaps maybe that would have been a long discussion for a members type area, but let's just start here folks
See if you can what you would send the Greeks sent to AFR and let's just see if it's worth it to do something like that
So again, I want to thank the caller the the called in the past hour because his point also shows many of the points that
If you've ever heard the Greeks speak before is it ties back to scripture now
I don't like to speak about it because it's not time yet. But on the other hand
There is going to be a time where those that understand these ancient things because they all tie together
They all come from the same mindset all of your ancient documents, by the way
Those that do have an advantage on comprehension or having a grasp of what is it has been memorialized
Will be in a clear advantage in the near future
All right, but at the time
Currently, it's not the time to discuss these things openly. I've have
perhaps in the past
but there's tremendous amount of detail but the details can only be discovered when the mindset is correct and the correct mindset is
Stop reading into it what you've been told and learn to read out of it be objective from a forensic point of view
All right, look at what is really being said the other thing is
Get a ladder
Why what I mean by get a ladder the Fox and the grapes
Aesop's fables
Fox couldn't reach the grapes. So I guess the Fox called them sour
So when what you'll typically hear is that when people can't well shouldn't say can't but yes can't because of the censorship
Understand something or comprehend it whether it's because of their laziness or because they're
Cosmically blocked from it. Guess what? It's no good. If I don't get it, it can't be good
Right. That's where the Fox and the grapes comes in
So if you can't reach those grapes get a ladder or make one so you're gonna have to elevate to get the grapes now
Another thing I want to throw in there
It's just a little bit of a help when you're approaching ancient stuff
Especially regarding the gods and if you've ever heard me speak before
It's the gods. Yes plural. It's not singular, right? The scripture mentioned 36 or I think 38 of them by name
There are many gods, but there's only one who is the highest form and what makes him the highest he is not subject to death
You know, so think about that for a minute
but the thing about
Looking at all of this
Stuff that you you look at don't read into it read out of it and if you can grasp
anything out of it is that it's not done in futility and
What you've been told about it is probably false and it doesn't matter what it is
If it's old because there is a mentality that's still pervasive
That the modern current contemporary society is so much better and so much more advanced
Right, and these ancients are ignorant and you know, okay. All right granted you want to go that way? Okay
Well, let's say we grant it that the modern and the contemporary man
Is far better and less ignorant. Okay, if we grant that point, how about consider this if these things still exist?
In memorial form where they can be accessed unchanged or seemingly unchanged
What kind of an effort do you think was made or how significant is it that they've made it to this point all of those years
Especially the ones not even written in stone because one concept a list in jest or joking around was the reason they carve things in stone
Is because if it was memorialized in paper or something less durable, it wouldn't be around for so long
We have things still that can be accessed that are not in stone and quite prolific
So there's an importance aspect here if something is that old
Unknown because of people's stubbornness and rejection of it because they don't want to do the work
Well, so be it
But what is going to happen in the future is there is going to be a desire
Towards that direction and those who have the advantage to look at it now
Before the questioning comes up
Right is where the clear advantage is, but you know, I say it's not time yet. But uh
Let's just share this
From a private context is that most of the messages that the Greek has gotten
through the website and emails has been about scripture go figure and
Typically, I don't come out wanting to discuss it because there's the discussion is very very difficult. I recently
Told someone and I'll tell you why it was difficult is because
Someone had said to me, you know Greek you're correct about the accuracy of the statement as time goes on
People will be interested in more of these matters of ancient things and
And I said yes, and actually the person actually finished the rest of it
Which was complete which is there'll be more discussion as time goes on, but what will be discussed will not be accurate
right, it will not be accurate, but the but the
Getting set up and looking in that direction is what is what to watch for
you see so there isn't going to be much accuracy in these topics and
Why why because it's just not time yet
There's a tremendous amount of work as the as the caller that in the first hour said he's been listening to this type of
mindset kind of discussion
information reporting
that is very different and he's
Trying to seek out things that are really where where one would start
You see and you have to experience them on your own, but the the timing is very important
and what is
Coming up for that timing is also very important
So if it's not time now for what well would be things ancient especially regarding the gods
It's not time yet. If if this kind of
Reporting what you hear me saying about that
Strikes you as something significant get started
Get familiar. I know it seems like a lot, but it does take a lot a lot of time and a long time
but it doesn't have to there are
things to
To look at and just to go back what I started saying before
was any I
Try to discuss this topic with anyone or any time without prefacing it correctly
Shows the quality of the discussion
What is the preface if any discussion you folks here any discussion no matter where it is regarding Scripture?
It has to be prefaced that even to this day
What is known as the scripture that's preserved in Hebrew and Greek has yet to be translated
Period
This is a preface you should be looking for there's a tremendous amount of discussion of things biblical people writing books about that book
People telling giving positive and negative commentary heck there even religions that are based on it go figure and none of it is accurate why?
Because what they fail to tell you is that they're reading a version now if you have
an unabridged version
They usually have a pretty substantial introduction, and they tell you why the version is inaccurate. I'm using that loosely
So one way to see if you're getting a good
hmm
Discussion is if the preface is correct, and why is it correct am I being dogmatic? I don't think so
I'm trying to be objective the the prep the correct preface is that even to this date or day?
These things have not been translated into the corresponding languages of the discussion being held about them
so if you pick up a biblical text that is in Chinese or Japanese or
English or Spanish or French or what have you it is a King James version
The scriptures have yet to be translated. Do you want to go a little further?
How many times have the Greek philosophers been touted as having revelatory work that can help mankind?
Well, I what I say to that is if they're so great
How well is it helped really you know think about it?
The other thing is what you're being told in all the other languages is still a version of that now Greek
Are we going to go and read ancient Greek or ancient Hebrew or again coin a Greek or any other ancient language or even?
Aramaic no, you're not you don't have to but what you'll understand
is that all languages are made up of a group of letters are usually 22 and
Usually these other languages the letters have definitions which help define the words
so I don't know how well you are memorizing things, but a phone number is
pretty much
Memorizing seven words isn't it when you say a phone number isn't each number also a word
It's not that difficult folks at one point. Maybe we'll get into discussing how to increase memory
Which one thing to think about mem
Means water and or means light
Think about it for a moment
So okay, I've just checked out a comment in the chat, and I want to thank anyone and everyone who's
Here on uncommon radio right now on the other side meaning the listening audience
Because this is a first go-around for an intended monologue type or solo Greek effort
Sands the possibility of someone calling in which you know could get interesting just as it did in the first hour
So again what what I would expect to see
being said for the let's say two hours here on AFR is
as an experiment
tonight and the next episode maybe the next one is
What you would like to hear in a members area or more of a members area type of con?
Let's say something more exclusive than that had happened prior to with prior sonic engagements
Where I had a co-host let's say
so
Is it possible to do something exclusive in public and charge for it now?
That's a crazy statement to make because there is no money. It's it's not about that. It's about is there an exchange
So at this point if you feel compelled that the Greek deserves
Some kind of exchange go ahead and send it to AFR
And we'll see if there's enough coming in for AFR on that it might be worth for the Greek to invest on
Developing something more if not
It will just continue these discussions openly because guess what it's probably not time yet still and when I say probably I know
It isn't we still have about another year of the way things have been since the past six years or so
I've always discussed how the the discussion is going to be kind of
Frustrating and full of tension, but not disabling and I've never discussed in public though. Why?
Why it is that way and let's just throw this in there this particular seven-year period is a time
Let's just say where it's part of the setup
For the next seven years and one of the setups that you are experiencing as a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant is
that you will be
Led into unbeknownst to you and very quite smoothly into what's called a Middle East Union
Well, let me take that back. It won't be called the Middle East Union. It can be described as such
by description
And it will be accepted not
Perhaps beginning in the next seven years by the end of the next seven year period it will be fully accepted
But this is the time where everything will be set in place
so why
the seven the past seven years of frustration and
Let's just say confusion, but not to the point where it disables the inhabitants on the planet
That is the time where let's just say a large portion
Maybe 30% or 33% of the spiritual entities or gods and angelic beings throughout the universe are being corralled
And sent down to the earth
Kind of like customs at an airport where you see immigrants coming in and they're all in line with their luggage
Well, this is the time where everyone, you know, you guys on this planet are being
given fed stories
about missing airplanes
corrupt politicians and
impending financial collapse
Which doesn't happen because it can't it's credit based economy and all the other stuff and the dummy loading that you've been getting for the past
Seven years is to keep you in a mellow enough agreeable state, but yet a little frustrated
so pretty much one-third of all of the
Entities in the unknown unseen world of the gods are descending upon the earth. Think about that for a minute
And you're all missing it. Why?
Because this is the grand final
Showdown that is you've got about another decade and a half on this planet that everyone pretty much
Is going to follow through and be about as agreeable as anyone can be
About what is going to be happening here starting in the next few years on this time period. It doesn't mean there's going to be
You know, everything's gonna be honky-dory and peachy keen
You're still gonna have all your attention and all this other stuff
but what it's going to lead to is a
Let's just say if you have a racetrack you have a starting line and a finishing line
Don't you or where is the starting line? You gotta draw a bead on it with your eye. Where is it?
Okay, and I want you to draw a bead on with your eye where the finishing line is
same place
Where did everything start?
Or is it all going to end?
The end just means this particular era
So I just wanted to throw that in there because that I have not discussed publicly prior to this
up until this time
so the other thing that I discuss is the agricultural aspect of how humanity is and
Folks that get it get it and just to give another way a loose way of saying it
It's spring it is a time for planting summer is a time for growth and fall as a harvest time for breaking down
Now everything that is a metaphor for everything that people experience in their private personal lives
Culturally socially on and on politically economically, but for example, there are people crying still
I have not really looked at the media very much
But I recently I did catch a little bit in this moron is
Saying that watch out for what they call March 15th or something for
Economic because of all these trillions or interest debt. I'm like, oh wow
I can't comment on that because that is just so bizarre and ridiculous
And the first thing that's bizarre and ridiculous is that all financial troubles happen in the fall
Breaking down event would happen in the fall
This is the time of planting where it's very dynamic and very quiet at a time of growth this summer
So, I mean there are people
Still that have microphones and shows and media
Outlets that are not aware of it. Now, I think
Even if they were made aware of it, I think they're accommodating the audience
so because people in general are not aware of it that there tends to be a
blame factor that people have
You know if you turn on that TV show, they call the news occasionally they'll say well this such-and-such happened
We don't know who to blame yet. Whoa
What what is this blame stuff the blame game, right?
You know why you know, oh, it's the globalist elite, you know, or it's the Illuminati's man
Illuminati's gonna get you or
It goes on and on and on
Why not set yourself apart from it at least in your mind start thinking about it, you know, what's going on here?
Is anyone paying attention?
You know, let's just I maybe instead of just dispelling cliches all the time I get a little bit of about the credit system
every so often
Think about it folks
Have you ever heard of?
Let's say two people standing there and they're gonna bet whether the third person is going to
Move to the left or move to the right. I've actually had your bet. Well, I bet ten bucks
He's gonna move to the left. I bet ten bucks. He's gonna move to the right. Well, and he moves to the left
Well, so one guy gets to ten bucks because that's the completion of the wager or the bet
That's how the credit system works when you hear about interest and debt and loans
And all this stuff. These are people within the financial market that are betting that once these transactions take place
They put a description on them and the description is oh, it's a loan
With interest or it's this with interest or it's debt or whatever
Description and they're betting on how they're gonna funnel it down the market who's gonna buy into it on a bet
But there is no debt because it's all credit
But the betting is very powerful. You know, have you heard of betting on sports and
you're shooting craps or
Casinos. Yeah. Okay, so it's all paid for
Because you're in a credit based economy. Yeah, and that's really kind of ironic
I might even say because in the beginning of this show
I pretty much said let's use AFR as an experiment for donations to see how much people wanted willing to put behind
Probably an exclusive project by the Greek
So we'll see that you know, what's really happening there folks is when you go ahead and donate through the electronic convention
That that credit is being created on AFR is financial institution instantly and you're being docked to give you the plausible
Deniability that it was transferred over when the whole time the institution that you're using is
Still holding on to it, but you can't have access to it anymore. It's a single awful
No, if you guys want to understand a little bit more about it's written an eighth grade reading level
Look up USC 12 section 411 United States Code title 12 section 411
Read it. What does it mean when no other no other use is authorized?
What does that mean?
Anyway, think about it a little bit talk about what's called money
Is it is it going to wake up anyone? Is anyone going to comprehend it? Yeah, very few
We'll see. I don't think it's a point of contention anymore
There are bigger fish to fry like your existence on this planet
So if you're if you're listening just to give a little marker here
This is uncommon radio and you're on American Freedom Radio, and this is the Greek. Yes flying solo. So
Let's uh, let's you know, pretty much continue
I would say it's a conversation but flying solo pretty much is I'm on I'm at the stick. I'm at the
I'm flying this thing. So and I just got a message here, but perhaps I'll share it with everyone
It says thanks for clarifying the quote-unquote versions of the Bible and elaborating on my question during your
First solo talk on AFR looking forward to listening taking those further studies understanding. Thank you, Chris from Tennessee
Yes, and he did identify himself as Chris. Thank you for
for calling in
and the thing is there really is
there really is
Nothing, that's not viable. I mean everything asked is viable because it'll be shown as such
When you're pursuing the the truth, you cannot be offended, right?
Because you just see it as it is and you can discern whether it's true or not
so
Thank you again caller
For calling in and that was a very good point because it tends to tie in
With all of the behind-the-scenes messages that I get and folks, you know, you're listening to this on AFR
This is something that could be archived. It's pretty much taking up two hours of
Time and on a minor internet radio platform
But the Greek gets a tremendous amount of message and inquiry
Regarding things scriptural and or quote-unquote biblical and you couldn't believe
How that is still?
considered a major turnoff by society at large
but privately on
Backdoor and but I say three-quarters if not 90% of the messages are regarding things spiritual and I'm kind of reserved
Holding back on discussion discussing things in more detail up until this point. So I believe that
Trying out more detail on it. We'll see if it'll satisfy the
The inquiry and it should be but like I said before you wouldn't believe how distasteful still
through the society at large
That subject matter is because the mindset they've already decided
You know, like I said, if you count how many eggs in a basket
Someone says well someone might say well, I'm not mathematical. I don't want to know what's wrong
We're not talking about being mathematical. This is can you take a small tidbit of information, you know?
Regarding a subject that might be contrary to a mindset. You've just you've discovered works for you as an excuse or whatever
But even now to this day typically
Throughout society when you bring up something known as quote-unquote the Bible or
Scripture or whatever people say well, that's a work of fiction
Oh, I don't believe in that or I'm not religious or or or they'll give you a million reasons
Why not to discuss it or how it shouldn't be discussed or how can anybody know what it's about?
Except for what one can discuss about it is actually what's in it, right?
Or what is trying to be conveyed another thing?
I wanted to share with folks is I've gotten quite a few messages regarding an interlinear, you know seeking one out
Yes, of course. It's the reference material, right? It's the base
But here's the thing, you know
Let's let's be even more practical
there are quite a few people out there that could read the languages of ancient the ancient languages of
Preservation and still don't understand what's being conveyed. So
But if you're approaching it through an interlinear, in other words using the languages of preservation
You are now technically accessing the information whole
So it's like saying I want water
Would like to drink some water do I drink off from the puddle in the street?
Or the river where all the fish are pooing or the spring that feeds the river where it's pristine
Right now you haven't drunk yet, right because you can make a you can bring a horse to water, but you can't make him think
so
The the only analogy that I can give that sustains a simple
Imparting of what is going on here is the concept of a jigsaw puzzle
If you have a 10,000 piece jigsaw puzzle
It really helps to look at the image that is cur as a form of courtesy given on the box
And then you dump out all the pieces and you look at the fielding of color and shapes
Let's say in the image and you start fielding loosely the pieces in
General areas before you start piecing them together and just like a jigsaw puzzle once the pieces are put together
They really interlock well where where if you've put a good jigsaw puzzle together
You'll notice that you can actually pick up the whole puzzle from one piece and it all grabs on really tight
And that's exactly what the scriptures are. The thing is that I've what I've discerned out of
Looking at it for over a decade and a half with what I would consider to be
Objectivity is that the picture at this point?
We are in history is are the people that can see it and explain it clearly and concisely
Right. So at finding someone that sees the picture has been given the picture through the hard work. They've done
It's not you're like you're hearing voices or have any kind of revelatory
Experience right or major download because it's pretty strict about doing the work
It's up to the people to show others the the general picture
That's why I believe in the past discussion. I've had the last one with Chuck O'Kelly and we had a caller
I said the scripture is about three things, right?
And it's not like, you know, there are three types of people in the world
Those who are good in math and those who aren't right that's not like that
But anyway, it's about three things. It's about life. It's about death and
everything in between
right
Think about it. No
What is law?
How you deal with your environment?
We are a type of in existence right now that we are in a physical environment
In other words, you can't write, you know, you can't really displace one
Thing that is physical for another without causing major movement, right when you are a non physical
You can pretty much move around and get about a little bit differently
so what is in in the environment can either assist or impede you and you need a really you need to grasp a
Good set of laws that allow you to work with this material world and they call them laws of physics and things like that
So engineers and mechanics use them but as a society as an individual
Whether it's corporate, you know, meaning a group of people coming together to do something or familial or
On national level the purpose of the law is how you interact with each other and with the environment. It's very very important
And one thing that the Greek has surmised and we've been reporting on for over a decade and a half is that your law comes?
from your God
Period that is part of the operating system
It sounds dogmatic because there are many people of course who do not know anything about the gods
And they'll say well, I don't believe in that in that well, that's fine
The gods never asked you to believe in them
Anyway, if there's anything regarding belief in in these ancient writs
It's that you're going to believe that there are things that have not
Come into fruition will come into fruition because they have stated so it's it's sure that that's the strange thing
I don't believe in God. That's not really something that you will find memorialized. It's that when the gods have actually
Said something will happen and those that understand the message will be able to talk about it before it happens
That is what belief is about so until someone tells you I believe in this or that
Well, it has to be attached to something that has not occurred yet
This is just a clear concise report what people do with that word is another thing
But if you run into someone who says Greek
I don't believe in God, you know, so your point that law comes from your God is moot
Well, not really because then you would ask them. Do you believe in the laws of the state and they typically say yes
Well, then the state is your God and April 1st is your holiday and the state supplies a God for your law
Anyway, it's a statue of a woman. It's called justicia or justice and you serve her
She has a personified in iconography and statuary, I mean how clear can it be and
All the language around it and the priesthood if you ever look at a typical lawsuit
the
Plaintiffs are praying for relief
Are you folks paying any attention?
The answer is no at large you're not
Because the the level of complaining let's just say the the level of activism complaining protesting
disheartened
Whatever individuals that that voice it through any form of media whether it be public or private
Are not paying attention to any of this and they don't want to because it's still unpopular
But what is going to happen in the future is that there will be more discussion regarding the gods
Why because it's this era is ending and it's not like not to be confused
With anything that you hear of any kind of messianic trippiness from various
Let's say overly reserved or overly conserved religious types
in the world talking about the return of someone or such and such because
That is a crowd Gustav Le Bon crowd type thing. You can't think
By the way, there is in the American fundamental movement
What's called the Bible Belt or the buckle of the Bible Belt or typically in the Western world a fervor?
Towards a particular religion and it's known as the Christian era
And if you bring up the erroneousness of what they're espousing they say it doesn't matter
Right, right. So what's interesting as they're espousing very definitively these things are going to happen next week and
Yet they don't know how to keep time
They're on the Pope's work schedule
They still haven't figured out that you can't keep time with what's called a calendar and they still haven't figured out that there is no
Pope's work schedule in the
text that they allegedly
Some say that subscribe to and if you bring up pretty much anything that they're discussing as being erroneous and being able to prove it
They come back and tell you it doesn't matter
So yours there's your discernment folks
And by the way, I just want to throw this in there people that tend to historically
Historically profess with fervor and great pleasure their beliefs and
When it was investigated that the fervor and belief that they have professed was based on nothing
They tend to not be so pleasant anymore. They tend to be the most violent types
And I'm just gonna throw something in here
this is from a personal experience where I'll keep it real short because
If you've ever learned if you ever learn about the scriptures and you go to one of these quote-unquote
Bible studies in their homes and stuff and they profess things about the King James Version
If you open your mouth about anything contrary to what they're saying you will discover
What a rotten
Vile and violent people I want to say rotten. I mean with a capital T can be
Yeah, I'm talking about like, you know 75 year old little grandmas, you know, they're gonna go they're gonna say you said something about that
I'm gonna go get the sawed-off shotgun
Okay, so this is this is the level of humanity and this is memorialized by the way
If you want to read something in the book of Kings there was I think
Ahab and Jezebel anyway, so I don't like to bring up a lot of specifics, but here we have a Greek
How did you uncover the truth objectively?
About scripture the container universe language most of
Us for me have been blocked and blinded by a conventional thought passed down through tradition
Schools pop culture aka the herd. How do we break that?
Well, stop looking at us something you have to break and something as you have to work, you know
And also when the time is right just asking that question you already began, you know, here's the thing
it comes
When you have a very large picture
Something like I mentioned 500 years in a cosmic sense is not a long time
When you start looking at how long people live that's even shorter, right?
When you look at what your desires are on a cruise ship, right?
It's it's insignificant compared to the the entire group on the cruise ship going. Let's say from London to New York
Right, so just understanding that the captain's job
Let's say or the ship being safe through its journey or coming to its completion is important
That gives you a little more peace about wondering. What am I going to do on this cruise ship?
Should I go to the theater? Should I go into the cabin and sleep or should I go whatever so many things to do?
Think about it in way that way just the very fact that
People recognize a certain report and want to act on it
and you know what the action is in action and
It's actually a trick. This is the thing
When you set yourself apart
It takes a tremendous amount of action to do that meaning set yourself apart from it pull yourself out of it
But to the observer who is not aware of what you're doing, they will you will appear to them as being inactive
So I'm actually when I say being inactive or do nothing
This is what you will be observed as right like for example, someone knocks on your door and says hey man tomorrow
You know, we're gonna go downtown and with a bull horn protest this dirty politician
Okay, sounds good
But you learn a little bit more what the political system in the state of your country is, you know
Like wait a second. This is all you know irrelevant the next day they
Knock on the door and they say hey, you said you're gonna let's go. We're gonna protest
No, I decided not to go because you know what I found out the country was bankrupted is in receivership. There is no money
This is all just a show and oh, oh, okay. So you want to be inactive?
You want to be inactive? Okay, I get it and they walk away
So when you set yourself apart and pursue higher, let's say choir by the way, man's kingdom is vertical
You have the king of the top Street sweeper at the bottom better or worse
You know betters at the top horses at the bottom the kingdom of the gods is their realm is lateral
You're either in or out you're on the left or the right you're in the inner circle outer circle, right?
So that's another little
Hint for that
But you will seem when you do all of the work that it takes to learn the truth
And there is truth by the way
Now if you speak to people in the legal society that been influenced by it, they're very careful to tell you
Oh, whatever you want it to be or it's your opinion, right? That is the work of the adversary
But anyway, you've that that could be another discussion because when you hear of the God of this world, that is the adversary
so
I
Will see here
Maybe another question here is looking for a way out of the mold of the past and reshape the future. Is it possible?
of course
Lido Jack for the shuffleboard. Yes, the interesting thing here is when you understand
Like I think I mentioned earlier with the caller you're made up of basically three things
You're you're the life force, which is a soul
Breathing is not I try to stress that it's mechanical and chemical which it is, but there's a pulsing
Action that is considered the life force behind it. You're made up of that. You're made up of the physical
Chemical constituents, let's just say and then you're a spirit which is a mind those three things you see
That's that's what you're made of. So once you understand you have to satisfy all three of them
Yeah, that's a handful
But there's a lot of distraction in the meantime. So be discerning
Be set yourself apart be discerning
Look for quality. This is this is not advice like I think that was one of the things that was mentioned
On the previous sonic episodes. This is not advice, but it actually is when you think about it
One thing that I always look forward to just to discuss with people is something that they are severely lacking in
Especially in the Western world and I call it. Let me just do it this way back at you perk up
I call it white people food
There's nothing to do with the color of your skin because if you read ancient stuff
Back in the ancient days when something was called white it meant bland
No flavor not really good for you. And what I mean by white people food is for example when I was somewhere in the Midwest
Traveling around saying with people, you know, it's like they brought out lunch and what's that?
You know, that's hot pockets man, or that's what if you know, I think that's a brand
I shouldn't say that but all this frozen food that was pre-packaged full of chemicals that resembled an Italian dish or resembled this
Resemble that and you would eat that stuff and feel sick
and the thing that is really lacking that I've noticed is really good food preparation and
discerning of food preparation
Because you are still in a physical state where food
Nutrition has to pass through the body and that determines the state of affairs of the character in other words
Good food good drink promotes good character
Bad food bad drink promotes poor character. You ever wonder why people are talking politics all the time
Anyway, think of I don't think these
these types of discussions mix well with those that are interested in politics because don't you know that
We're gonna have a big financial meltdown on March 15th. Oh boy. How can that be?
Is anyone paying attention? No, so maybe one place to start
I find it personally that I
speaking out to the listener
One of the most important things that you can do is increase the quality of the intake of the food and drink that you have
Of course of the mind as well things that you hear there you take in
You know, if you think there's going to be a financial meltdown in the middle of or the beginning of spring
You're a moron. I hope that whisper came through. So this is the convention. So start off by
Clarifying a level of quality of discernment and food preparation. I had previous sonic event
I think we did roughly four hours on food preparation
I think they were called the perfect rice was the name of one of them and it was about certain dishes
We even had a simple preparation that are official. We even had someone call in
Stating how well it worked for them. So again, thanks
donate to AFR so we could see if the Greeks should do a private project and
This is episode one was uncommon radio, thank you everyone. We'll see you again next week