Greetings, everyone, and this we could call the second installment of Uncommon Sense with
the Greek.
And what you might see that is different than the last time is that the Greek is solo now.
So we're going to keep trying to try to have the word failure built into it, but we're
going to see what kind of success can be gotten.
And that's always the question.
What is success?
So maybe we'll talk a little bit about that, but let's just give a little bit of a time
marker.
And I want to talk about that as well, because it's around the significant time of the year.
It's what they call the third month of the ninth day, 2017, or March 9th, 2017, according
to the Pope's work schedule.
Yes, you heard me correct.
And if you've heard Greek speak before, this is one of the key points that is always discussed.
It is not a time piece, no matter how much you believe in it or whatever faith you are
or technical knowledge of it.
It is a work schedule.
And that if you ever heard of something called the sun, if you've ever heard of anything
called the moon, well, guess what?
The sun reckons a day and the moon reckons a month.
And the year gets a little more complex, which involves the movements of the earth, the sun
and the moon together.
But with that said, guess what?
What's coming up with the next full moon?
Well, let's not guess too much, but let's just say it.
The next full moon is going to be the first day of the first month.
OK, boys and girls, you've always been told something is called a certain thing when
it's the first day of the first month.
Yes, I won't say it.
And there ain't no ball dropping in Times Square and anything like that, because this
has to do with being in the light, not in the dark.
Now, how many times have you heard something like that?
Probably none.
So thank you and welcome all to Greek speak.
And it's actually uncommon sense.
But yes, you are going to be welcomed or unwelcomed by the Greek speak itself.
So before we continue on tonight, I'd just like to say that this is also participatory
on your end. So if you have what is called a telephone, there is a telephone number at
AFR that you can call and join and participate.
And that would be 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5.
I'm going to say it a little slower and one more time, which also it can be gotten on
the American home page.
It is there on the left.
Yes, your other left in a red box.
It is on the left.
So it will say call a number with a border on it in red.
And that number one more time is 2 1 8 3 3 9 8 5 2 5.
Now, if you like using the Skype convention, you have to consider also there is a
website called Uncommon Radio dot com and the email on that website, which is a
courtesy site.
The email for that site is Uncommon Sense Radio one at Gmail dot com.
And the number one is a numeric one.
And that is also what you would type into the search query box for contacts in the
Skype. So if you're interested in coming on using the Skype search for contacts and
put in Uncommon Sense Radio one at Gmail dot com.
And when you search, you will see Uncommon Radio, the Greek and the request for that
convention. So please, if anyone does feel like they have a voice and want to
participate, that is open.
Now, one of the things that we used to discuss with previous Sonic episodes when we
decided to do the reload with Ocelli and the Greek, it was in jest, of course, you
know, but all in jest, half in earnest, the two the two things about calling in.
And I think it's just an interesting reflection on the human consciousness.
Well, the first one, let's do it backwards.
The second thing we used to say is if you're under the influence, you may not think
like you sound that you are, but everyone else knows that you do sound that you are
under the influence. So if you're under the influence, whatever that might be, refrain
from calling. And the other thing is when you call in, impart and share things that
can apply to anyone, pretty much use it as an open platform of communication.
Typically, when people discuss their own personal matters, you're sort of raised in a
culture where it's polite to act like you're listening.
But when you're discussing your own personal stuff with other people, they're
basically wondering when you're going to shut up so they can tell you what they want to
say. So the thing is about, you know, when you do things in public, make it publicly
applicable. So those are the two things, perhaps, and not and not just the only two
about calling us. Let's make it participatory if you so choose.
And speaking of being participatory, I want to thank everyone who has been sending some
form of exchange or some contribution slash donation, let's say in accordance with
the, well, let's just use the common word, the plea, the asking, the mini beg-a-thon,
perhaps, maybe not, that the Greek did last week about seeing what kind of support can
be garnered for this kind of a project.
And the reason why is because ending the last sonic event, there was a contemplation of
perhaps starting a member's area.
And when I looked into what it took to do something like that, it was quite an
undertaking in terms of time and all that.
So many people always say they want to participate, but essentially when it comes down
to doing it, very few appear to do so.
So but I wanted to thank everyone who has sent a donation to AFR and the concept here of
a member's area is perhaps a concept of exclusivity, you know, but I think that if
you're tuning in to this and you're listening to Uncommon Radio and what's dubbed as
Greek speak, there is a sense of exclusivity on its own there, because what you will hear
are things that are not being said anywhere else.
And as a matter of fact, that's one of the reasons why the Greek is speaking.
I don't consider myself to be in any way a public figure or want to be a public figure,
but for years I've been contemplating the things that I have been emanating sonically on
various platforms or especially this one.
And no one else is saying anything even close.
So the point is, if it can be said, it should be said responsibly, of course, and
accurately and with precision.
So I'm kind of dubbing, like, let's say perhaps the next this time around and the next
two, which would be the first four of Uncommon Radio, the members area open.
And again, I want to thank everyone who has contributed based on what was mentioned last
week regarding this.
And I would like to see perhaps even more, because as it is so far, would it would it
actually deem setting up a separate area, an endeavor as such, what is called the
members area on someone's platform?
Let's say no, it wouldn't be at this point, but pretty close.
So if support can be garnered for AFR regarding at least what's being said on
Uncommon Radio, that would still be appreciated and still needs to be seen.
And so let's just dub the next three, including this one, let's say would be the
next two. So four, let's do four weeks of pretty much answering questions.
I'm going to be going back to emails and pretty much discussing things a little more
openly than you're used to hearing.
And unlike many, many, let's say, groups or sonic figures that do provide a members or
exclusive area to their sites, I do find it to be somewhat distasteful.
I mean, there's no need for exclusivity.
So if there is a need for it, that will be communicated to some extent.
And there is, for example, a right time and a place to say things.
And right now, clearly, is still not the time.
But it is fast approaching, meaning in about a year's time or this would be the last year
of this seven year period that you folks have been experiencing.
So let's just make this the members, the open members area on AFR.
And again, send some support.
Let's just see what can be done about this.
You know, years ago, a brick and mortar facility was a place where people gathered and
shared things. But, you know, here's something to consider.
Universities have been around for, let's say, an eon or two, and they still operate under
the Greek Convention.
But people were supposedly going to learn things, real knowledge and real information
was actually shared at the open market, the Agora, the Agora, which is a Greek
pronunciation. That's why, for example, you've heard like the soapbox concept, you
know, soapbox where it was typically political views, but not always.
But in the open market, one of the first things to sell out was soap because it was
difficult to make, was sort of limited.
And all these empty soapboxes piled them up and spoke.
This was pretty much in a Western society type thing.
So that wouldn't say this is particularly a soapbox, but it is a place to impart things
that are just not being imparted.
And I just put this out there.
If there are people out there, yes, I know there are, that can stay and keep and carry
these subjects forward.
Like what is lawful?
You know, what is real?
What do things really mean?
Please come forward and start speaking.
I'm sure here at AFR they will give you a time slot and or anywhere else.
Do a website, do something, please.
I would like to take a break from it, not that I need to be doing it, but actually
being able to bounce things off of someone else.
And I know you're out there.
In other words, if anyone approaches a topic, let's say the concept of religion.
You've heard the Greeks say there's not one religion on the planet, bar none, that
does anything or knows anything that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to.
Or comprehends it the same with science, the same with medicine, the same with the
financial industry, the same with what's called government agencies.
No one or the legal society, no one really seems to care or know about what they're
supposed to be doing.
Right. So, you know, there's pretty much an abandonment of accuracy and precision in
conversation, in communication, every social aspect.
If I send them a message and say the Greeks said I should call in or get into the with
AFR and perhaps do what's called a show or a sonic event of some sort, because I would
like to see that.
I would like to see that as well.
So I just this is the first time I've actually put something like that out there.
I also want to pretty much mention I do not partake much in what's called Internet radio
or the news or the show they call the news or websites they call the news and things
like that. But I do have to see or look at it to see what state because remember, folks,
it's all about mindset and it's still the same stuff, still the same rubbish talk,
rubbish mentality.
You ever heard of something called taxpayer dollars, right?
These people are like saying, oh, no, all this money was wasted and it's tax payers
dollars. Well, that's the mark of a moron.
Why? Because it's a credit based economy.
Everything is running under economic theory, you see.
So whatever is called taxes, excise law, that is still a theory.
None of that pays for anything.
What is called money is based on the monetization of hedging transactions.
That's all it is.
You know, we can get more into this about the credit system when I used to speak with
others before. I had to keep it limited because even they were limited in their ability
to relax into the subject.
You see, if you discuss anything, for example, with the legal society, they know no law.
You know, can there be precision and discussion to say to impart what is going on
regarding the legal society or the medical society?
And I'm not discussing, oh, vaccines are bad or this is a corrupt judge or anything
like that. Nothing in that capacity at all.
What are they supposed to be doing and is there any discussion on what they're supposed to
be doing? And the answer to that is no.
There might be some actually recently I've been discovering a few people that are
actually coming out of, quote unquote, the woodwork.
That's an old pagan term. Actually, I'll describe that maybe someday and bringing forth
what people are or these groups are supposed to be doing.
And that is basically the alignment of thought that is required to have clear, concise,
accurate and productive communication.
Let me just bring up a point.
I had an email recently.
And it was perhaps a greeting type email.
And this person supplied the information that they were in the art field.
They had gotten art training and pursued that and found it to be, let's just say
several paragraphs of the email, just to boil it down to saying they were sort of dismayed.
Everything from the training to the practice to how to proceed.
And the whole thing about this, for example, discussion that can be had about what art is
ultimately, what is it?
It is a communication.
It is visual.
It is audio.
It could be sense.
It could be touch.
Because whenever we look at things or people look at things that are considered artful, there
is a certain aesthetic that garners as such.
Now, for example, I'll give a quick personal quip on this.
You know, when we do some manufacturing or let's say prototyping, if it doesn't work
out and it's worth keeping around, we throw it in the back of the shed.
You don't want to throw it away, let's say if it's welded titanium or something.
So when it just sits there and that's called the art department, right?
There's a film by Stanley Kubrick.
I think it was Full Metal Jacket.
And one of the quips there was I think the drill sergeant called someone as ugly as a
modern art masterpiece.
So I can see how there's a lot of negative relation, but I see the positive relation
also being in the same category because everyone is missing the point.
It is a form of communication.
And just as an open thing here, whether you're an artist in terms of painting,
sculpture, writing, music, you're communicating something, right?
It is affecting the senses of the individual.
And that is ultimately a limiting factor as well, because these things are also considered
part of certain social conventions based on fashion and what's fashionable.
So a lot of the discussions and a lot of the things that are being discussed transcend
that. So.
So I'm told that the sound is cutting out every 20 seconds or so, I don't know if it's
on the receiving end of someone, but thank you for letting me know.
OK, so we took a little pause there in case the studio wanted to edit that out, if
there was any disturbance.
All right. So the again, being the second time around, so there's a lot of fat to chew,
as they say, and there are many things to be said, but most of it might sound like a
commentary on society.
And it's not necessarily a commentary.
Well, it could be garnered as such, but it's a commentary viewed on what is objective
and what can be seen.
So I just want to go back to tying things together.
You know, we kind of mentioned that it's the Pope's work schedule.
Yeah, you know, it's pretty obvious by now.
If you've heard any kind of Greek speak, you know that.
Well, you know, it's the calendar is pretty debunked as a timepiece, but it works well
as a work schedule or a timekeeping schedule.
But it is not lawful, just like very little is.
And what's the interesting thing?
I didn't say New Year because it's not really dubbed as New Year because it kind of
still is being the first day of the first month lawfully.
What is meant lawfully is, you know, well, lawfully it's based on something.
Right. It actually comes from the gods, believe it or not.
Yeah. Those imaginary friends again, that dumb people or crazy people are dubbed to
believe in. There's nothing to believe in regarding the gods.
The only thing that when you hear the word belief that should come up is that something
that has not happened yet, but you can't really believe in the gods.
You might believe that at one time you will be more, they will be more tangible, but
themselves an intangible society is quite different.
But when we bring up the concept of lawful timekeeping, it's just like anything else.
I recently was exposed to someone before I say what they said.
They pretty much have discussed anything mathematical and someone says, well, hold on.
I'm not really into math.
OK, fine. Or discuss something, let's say financial.
And the person would say, well, you know, I'm not into money or finances.
OK, well, you discuss law.
I recently discussed some lawful timekeeping with someone and I had to kind of have them
say it twice because what they said was, I'm not really into lawful timekeeping.
Think about that, folks, for a moment.
Yeah, if it sounds ridiculous, it is, but that's your typical human convention here.
It's ridiculousness. So let's just carry on.
And so I see some, I see again that maybe we'll clean up the audio somehow if there is any other way.
OK. Again, I'll bring up the call number again would be 218-339-8525.
And the Skype convention, if you'd like to join this, is UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com.
And you will find that is the email that you will find on the UncommonRadio.com site.
That is also the Skype contact.
OK, hopefully the audio is better.
So we shall see.
OK, I'm getting messages that it is.
All right. So again, folks, what is interesting here is there's many, many things to say and they all tie in together.
It's really difficult to pick a subject because there's something called a boundary layer effect, right?
You know, you've heard as a child, you know, the neck bone is attached to the arm bone and it's just attached to the back bones, attached to the hip bone and the leg bone.
You know, everything is sort of attached.
Even physically, you have a boundary layer.
You know, you have the body, let's say, and you're standing on the earth, which is also in the air.
You're part of your body is touching, you know, most of it is in the air.
And the air is a material, even though it's a gas, is touching the tree.
And so everything is connected and you have one membrane or a boundary layer where everything is touching.
And certain things transverse those boundary layers, like, for example, electricity can go through the air, right?
Lightning and sparks and things like that.
So when you're discussing one subject, there's a boundary layer to everything else.
You know, you imagine anything and everything that can be thought of or discussed in this big soup or this big tapestry.
And you just focus on one thing.
You can't deny that it's not on this in the soup or in the tapestry connected to the rest.
And the culture that has emerged in the past century or so, especially with the forms of entertainment and education, which has been dumbing up people and people like to call it dumbing down.
It's really dumbing up because the dumbness is going up.
It's actually censorship.
But to discuss, let's say, for example, the credit system or the legal society or the medical society and all these other things, it's not to be critical, but to discuss the fields that they should have been discussing or should have been imparting more properly and more accurately.
I just want to share with everyone that some of the private messaging that I've been getting, especially, let's say, on Skype groups or email.
The majority of the commentary has been regarding questions of scripture and questions regarding how the body works.
So let's just, in air quotes, say, well, if this is going to be done democratically, then, Greek, you have to do what the people that are communicating with you are requesting.
Yes. But when you're speaking publicly, you know, if you start discussing scripture, there is an attachment right away.
You know, it's called the Bible right away.
It's sort of a revolting subject to people because of what groups that allegedly are supposed to be subscribing to it have done with it and how they presented it.
It makes it very distasteful.
The same way when you discuss the human body, when you discuss how the body works or not just the human body, anything living.
Right. It ends up becoming very distasteful because if it sounds contrary to what the entitled classes are imparting, meaning universities, doctors, scientists and all that, it can't be true.
Even though you have a body that you can examine objectively, what is being said or heard by most people cannot be true because I have put so much, quote unquote, faith and trust into these semi superhuman demigods
known as doctors and universities and scientists with a language that I can't quite comprehend.
Right. So how can this, you know, even though you have a body, right, you cannot most people cannot delve into the subject matter objectively.
And to prove this recently, I was on a Skype group call and there are questions that were asked by people hadn't spoken to in about a year as if I had never said anything.
So I guess it might be the censorship aspect again.
But to just share with everyone democratically in their quotes again, demos is an interesting word and cross is another part of the word that needs to be examined.
But discussing scripture on on an open platform like this is will be found to be distasteful.
I'm saying, again, by many that do listen to it because it's very, very difficult to reckon what is being put in what is being and has been put into the into people's minds and what the truth of the matter is.
The truth of the matter means a rational information thing that you can access at any time that anyone can see.
Oh, I have a question, by the way, here just for everyone else.
I'm getting some feedback or something, but can you please explain the credit system and its tenants?
Well, that is, yes, it's very simple.
The simple way to explain that is very simple.
The credit system, let's just say not the way that the people are should be relating to it.
But the way that it's operating right now is that the behavior and the movement, the actual dynamic, the movement and the behavior of those that have a credit line is being monetized.
OK, another way to say it is that there imagine two people betting that the guy across the street is going to cross the street or not cross the street.
So it's ten bucks if he crosses for one guy and ten bucks for the other guy if he doesn't cross.
So he ends up crossing the street.
So now one guy has to give the other guy ten bucks.
And that's what the credit system is based on.
It's just betting on what's going to happen.
But the thing is, in a credit system, the ten bucks does not exist until the guy who's crossing the street signs his name on a piece of paper.
I don't know if it sounds confusing.
It's designed to be such.
And the tenants of the credit, the simple aspect of the credit system, it's based on faith, faith that something that everything that requires money needs to go on.
Even when there is no money.
All right. Think about it for a moment.
So essentially, the systems that have been put in place through most countries in the world since the 1930s up until the 1950s, is that most of what you call the government,
not the agencies, but the actual function of the government, which is another discussion.
I'm being told that I'm cutting out.
I don't know why.
And I'm stationary and everything is good.
Maybe we will try it after the break or right now, another type of headpiece or microphone.
But most of the country's folks are in receivership or which is what comes after bankruptcy.
So if anyone wants to look into what bankruptcy reorganization is, there's various chapters in it based on IMF conventions.
What you call it, say, America or Australia, Europe, Japan, all these are they're all in receivership of some kind.
All right. So if you want to study how that works, but the people still need to eat, things need to be made.
So you're given a credit line or actually it is a credit line, not a line of credit.
This is the legal community playing with words.
Again, the credit line and a line of credit are two different things.
Just by switching the words around slightly, just like the state of New Jersey is not New Jersey state, right?
It's one is an entity, right?
Like copywritten things sort of.
So when you're born and this goes counter to pretty much a lot of the, quote, unquote, radical law groups that talk about how bad the birth certificate is and it's a slave document and all this and the other.
Well, it doesn't say that it is.
So we have to take it that it's not.
What I would suggest is considering that when you are born into a jurisdiction or born, but naturalized or brought into that jurisdiction to function and by various ways of description, you're given a birth certificate.
And all that is, is a credit line, right?
That's all it is.
Now, what what the majority of the effort of all of the institutions in place and, you know, let's say churches, synagogues, mosques, government agencies, universities, the legal society, the Bar Association, let's say, from the smallest little petty attorney all the way up to the city of London, Hollywood TV radio, even alternative radio.
The entire purpose of all this regarding the credit system is that the people never find out that they're the ones with all the, quote, unquote, money and all of the governments and corporations have no money.
And what the governments and corporations want to do is get the money from the people without letting them know that they're the only ones that have it.
So it's kind of like a pickpocket tactic.
So you're being robbed if you catch someone picking your pocket, but if they pick it properly, you'll walk away and not know that it's gone until much later.
But to add insult to injury, the legal society now says that you actually owe them again.
So that's the pranking aspect of it.
So perhaps if anyone could message me if the audio is still good, that would be great, but it seems like it is.
Okay, which agents are primarily responsible for instituting and maintaining the credit system?
Also, who determined the world's countries are in receivership and how do they have the authority to do that?
They do it. Okay, the legal society is responsible for instituting and maintaining the credit system as a form of trusteeship.
And I would say that who and how do they have the authority to do that?
Well, they're in the seat of authority, but they have to garner the authority from the people and they do that through the administrative process.
Have you ever seen like someone post a notice and it's acted on after a certain amount of days, whether it's 72 hours or a month or so?
This is exactly what's been going on and no one realizes it.
The only thing, though, is that you're dealing with pranksters, right?
Imagine going to a planet where, okay, there was an entire industry with Kevlar underwear, okay?
And you're wondering, okay, why is this Kevlar underwear industry so big here?
Well, you found out that everyone was raised into believing that it was proper to put a thumbtack on a chair before you sat on it.
It sounds pretty ridiculous, but that is a metaphor of what is going on here with the legal medical societies and the informational societies that you call professionals and you always look up to or told to look up to.
And all of this has started with the parents, of course, because the parents are pranking the shit out of their children.
And I should say sometimes they do that.
But, you know, how many times have you heard a parent say, well, I know the education system isn't worth diddly squat, but, you know, you have to go because I went.
Right. I recently heard a young lady, a young, let's say more than a girl, less than a lady, about 14 or 15.
I want to get this car and drive it because, well, you can't drive.
Mom said you can't drive that without a driver's license.
Why do I need a driver's license?
The child asked because if you don't get one, you go to jail.
OK, so now we're having motivation through penalty.
We have to do things because if we don't do them, you get penalized.
Right. And that's the only reason to do them.
Right. So what does that do to your perception of nationalism, patriotism and all that other stuff?
If this is the norm, I don't know.
I think, by the way, if anyone thinks it's a good idea to start a factory producing Kevlar underwear, just send an email or so.
Maybe we can do an SEC filing of some kind and get some vulture capitalists and get that going.
No pun intended. That's kind of a joke.
So. Let's see how most countries of Federal Reserve.
So they in the same boat as us.
OK, us, U.S., perhaps.
Yeah, of course. Yeah. This has been going on.
You see, when people are in a in a in a position where they are, quote unquote, running and what's called a government, whether it's a monarchy or or dictatorship, let's say, or democracy, socialist or whatever.
The first thing you come into with having a corporate body like that is that you'll notice what kind of budget or what kind of access of wealth do you have to do what you want to do?
And anyone in that kind of position always wants unlimited access to what's called money.
You see, so that's why, for example, recently in the American administration with the, quote unquote, new president, he says he's going to increase the size of the military and everyone thinks that it's coming from taxes and it's not.
Let me just throw in something here.
Have you guys ever heard of the Miller process or Miller bonds?
You know where, you know, when you have a bid, let's say a construction company bids on building a bridge, there are three bonds.
They have to put in a bid bond, a performance bond and a surety bond.
And but no one ever asks, you know, the the institution that is putting out the idea to have this bridge built.
Where do they where did they get the money to pay the construction company to build it?
Right. No one ever asks that.
I mean, no one when, for example, a government says we're going to build a highway and we need it's going to cost a billion dollars.
They use the term and a construction company bids on that project.
They supply three bonds, a bid bond, performance bond and a surety bond, and each one will have the billion dollar value on it.
What happens is when the.
Well, before anything happens, there is the money to pay that construction company does not exist.
Where does that come from?
When the construction company enters the bid, the three bonds are taken and let's say the bid is awarded and they're deposited through the Federal Reserve and three billion is created based on what's on the bond.
And the three billions put aside and one billion that was created out of that was given to the construction company based on whatever schedule of payment to build that road.
Right. So the actual company that is bidding on the work is financing it itself.
But the people there think that we better win this bid because we need the money.
How twisted is that? I would recommend some Kevlar underwear.
But anyway, this is how the earth is functioning right now.
This is everywhere. This is in Iran.
This is in Russia.
This is in Italy.
This is in Canada.
This is in Bogota.
This is in Japan.
This is the same system all throughout.
Yes, it is.
This is what's going on because you are so heavily pranked.
You can't see straight.
And well, anyway, maybe that's why there's so many curves in the road.
But these are questions that I'm just throwing out little tidbits, trying to be poignant as possible that are in the chat right now, because I find that, you know, real time questioning can enrich the conversation or the, you know, the sonic event.
Then here we have another.
Who are the legal society acting as trustees on behalf of?
Well, that's the that's really funny to ask, because the legal society is pretty much a monopoly right now.
At least the one that has been given legitimacy is what's called the Bar Association, and they're pretty much started in ancient Greece on one of the previous sonic events.
I explained how they got started and they had gotten that from a book written by a retired judge that wrote it, I think, in the 70s or 80s.
And I sorry, folks, I didn't write down references or the author, but it was it was that part was interesting.
But anything that is written by these people, I kind of like feel like I have to take a shower after I just read it or touch it because it's a really nasty group.
And they did come out of ancient Greece, by the way, not out of England as well.
The contemporary aspect of it is out of England, as you can imagine.
And you will find a bar association in every country in the world.
And they still whatever corresponding language they have when you pronounce that particular title, it sounds like bar.
And I brought this up once to someone recently that names are exempt from language.
Right. So let's say if you say IBM or Microsoft or Bar Association or Tom or Jim or anything that is a name, regardless of what language it is spoken in or written, it sounds the same because names are exempt from language.
They do not change from language to language.
So this legal society has been pretty much installed.
And by the way, I have also mentioned many times before that law comes from your God.
This is one of the Greek maxims that someone mentioned to me a few days ago that they have a list of Greek maxims.
OK, like fine, that your law comes from your God.
It's very simple. And if you don't have a God, then if you follow the laws of the state, the state is your God.
And April 1st is your holiday.
It's very simple. This is just the way things are set up.
And no one is objectifying it.
Well, I mean, we are now, let's say it's very, very simple.
Now, if you look at what's called the Bar Association, they set up what's called justice departments everywhere.
Justicia, Justinian was the name of a lot of the later Roman emperors, early popes.
Let's say that comes from it's the goddess revived goddess religion from Greece known as D.K.
D.I.K.E. She didn't like men, by the way.
That's why women that don't like men today are still called D.I.K.E.
Anyway, keep going on and on from Mott.
This is the revived goddess religion.
And it's it's very cruel.
It's indifferent. And it but it tends to be it upholds its supporters quite well.
I mean, those that prescribe it, not those that ask for it.
It's kind of confusing. I think I have mentioned on previous sonic events again.
I shouldn't be doing that too much thing on previous sonic events.
But but if anyone I implore anyone to well, actually, if anyone wants to really get a background of what can be said there,
go to Uncommon Radio and you'll see there's about 80 hours of archives there.
But for those of you listening to this in real time, what is the problem with the revived goddess religion?
This particular goddess, not all goddesses, but this specific one, let's say that is not so specific in terms of persona yet.
But I assure you, it is what is put the spiritual cast over mankind right now.
She is anti-life.
Think about that for a moment.
That's why you wonder about chemicals and food, the encouraging of male with male unions and female with female unions,
this genetic thing, gender bending chemicals, the genetic thing.
What I mean is splicing and all this humanism stuff that you hear about.
And by the way, none of that's going to really take place as you're being told, by the way, the future stuff.
And, you know, one simple way to pretty much see that, folks, and I'm just going to divert here for a moment,
is if anyone does a little bit of a study, just do a cursory examination of the world's fairs in various nations from,
let's say, the turn of the century till the mid 20th century.
They had these things called the World's Fair, a world's fair.
And if you see around the 30s, 40s or so, you're going to have flying cars by the 1990s,
there's a hotel on the moon by 2000, right, and all this stuff.
Have you gotten any of it?
No, no, you still don't have, you still have a reciprocating engine that wastes 80% of all the fuel you put into it,
turns it into heat, right, and it's got, it runs on Satan's energy drink.
So anyway, and no one really cares because they, well, first of all, they still haven't figured out how to build them right.
If you go into a new car dealer, let's just say you're visiting this planet and you want to take notes,
and you've been watching this manufacturing process and design work of what's called an automobile,
which is not an automobile because it doesn't go on its own.
It's a engine driven wagon, right?
But if you ask them, you know, go to a car dealer and say, hey, this model year is different than the last model year, isn't it?
Oh, yeah, yeah, it is.
So I guess you made it different because you still haven't figured out how to make it right.
Isn't that why you have a different model every year?
Wouldn't that be the rational thing to say?
Well, you know, if you buy a hammer or a saw or a chair or a table, the design is,
and the efficiency of the design is essentially the same, is it not?
But these automobiles keep changing.
But maybe it has nothing to do with whether or not they figured out how to make them.
Maybe it has to do that someone who gets it says, ha, I have the newer one and you don't.
Hmm. OK, that's another level of human condition.
So again, we're about 40 minutes in.
If anyone would like to call and join this monologue, which can turn into a conversation,
it would be 218-339-8525.
And the Skype convention would be UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com.
And then one is numeric.
And that also happens to be the email for UncommonRadio.com.
But you see, there's there's much to do and how it's all connected.
And just to keep making the connections essentially is the is the way to relax into the subject.
So you don't get someone putting a ring into someone else's nose and dragging them around
with their methodology or what they think or forming some kind of group, of course,
which has some radical concept to it.
I just want to throw in again, since we were asking about the money here.
And so there's this another fellow or whoever it is still asking another question.
So the trustees are not banking dynasties.
Well, yeah, they are. But but no, they're not.
They have the attorneys do the work for them.
Right. Yeah, they are.
And here's the thing about the banking dynasties.
And that's their global, let's say, or world world based, let's say, you know, there's
multinational.
Recently, I've heard in many times in the past, I've heard people complaining about
globalists, you know, running their country or a globalist agenda.
How many times have you heard that?
You know, it's like some strange form of activism, because in case you folks haven't
noticed, you know, if you buy clothing, you know, you really like the clothing you wear
and you don't mind buying it again, but it's probably made somewhere across the planet.
Right. You know, many of the things, especially, for example, if you're functioning in
the information venue aspect of things, you might be getting your information from
someone on the Internet that's on the other side of the planet.
I mean, you like using browsers that are global.
You like using, you know, financial things that are global.
You know, all these other things, you know, but oh, we're going to have someone that's
going to run our country that is globalist.
OK. Yeah. Uh-huh.
Of course, they better be a globalist, they better understand how small the Earth is
right now. You know, the thing, the question of discussion that is never brought up is
that what is the quality of the rule and what is the quality of the character of this
individual based on their performance of their position?
I would actually prefer someone who is pretty much intent on and I should not do what I
prefer, but what can be preferred, let's say.
As someone who is intent on understanding how small things are on the planet right now
or things, meaning transactions and dealings and whatever, years ago, if you wanted to
go from one side of the planet to the other, it took months.
Now you can do it in less than a day.
So there's this not necessarily rapid, but it is rapid growth or connect connectivity
and it is good to have people that are familiar and even foreigners at this point
because it seems like all of your government's in receivership, if you know what that
means, as long as it is benevolent.
So the point here is, is any kind of rulership or leadership or guidance benevolent or
malevolent? Right.
And I would suggest that if if you did some research, you would find that it's
malevolent, pretty much all of it.
And is a terminal, yes, meaning it will come to a not a good end, of course, but the
thing is, it's it's termination is sometimes brought quickly, sometimes
multigenerational.
But what is going on on this planet with by, let's say, you folks, you know, humans
and myself included, is is not good.
It's terminal and it's malevolent.
And let's not forget, let's put the Hollywood and religious iconography and and
creative writing and stuff aside.
When something is truly malevolent, it always appears as being malevolent.
Right. Rat poison appears as a delicious meal.
Right. Counterfeit, let's say, notes always appear to be non-counterfeit notes.
Right. Things they tend to mimic what something of a better quality or
benevolence that people are typically pursuing.
So be aware of when when people say that these are the good guys and those are the
bad guys. You know, how many times have you seen that, by the way?
You know, good guys and bad guys.
And what are we like five years old?
Yes. Pretty much nine years old mentality right now.
Can can you imagine going to a planet where you see some anthropomorphic figures that
have been granted directly through external input, the ability to work with their
environment, how to work with stone, how to work with metal, how to weave fabrics, how
to actually build edifices and buildings and things like that and work on what's called
chemistry and other things and various forms of engineering.
And they tend to to make things that could be helpful and things that could be very
dangerous. But they're pretty much locked into a nine year old mentality.
I'm just going to say this once.
I rarely say it. But when you look at these people of great authority, because the
covenant that I live by, it's not to curse or badmouth the leadership because the
leadership is there. The gods put them in place based on what they think of you, the
people as a whole or as a group.
And it doesn't take much to spoil the whole bunch.
But anyway, when you look at these people, these multiple star generals or these old
captains of industry and all these tough looking guys, I assure you and gals.
No matter how many degrees they have after their name or how many stars on their
shoulder or whatever experience they've had, they have not matured beyond the nine
year old mentality.
Ten, if they're fortunate.
And this is the status of humanity right now.
And why do I say that? Because if you have the maturity of a 12 year old, you will be
fired. You will show up whatever institution you're working and you will say, what the
heck is going on here?
Let's do it the right way.
Right. So and by the way, folks, I don't discuss the military much, but there's no
need to discuss it because it's what the gods use also, by the way.
But what's interesting, I remember once very young getting a job at what they call a
job. It could have been a job also.
With a convenience type store 30 plus years ago, and the manager met me and he said,
you know, it's like $2.50 an hour and all you could steal.
And I looked at him, I was like, what?
OK, what's going on here?
That was like a taste of the real world, you know, it's all you could steal.
I see. So here's the here's someone who's supposedly minding the store, has a new
hire and says it's X amount per hour, you know, wage and all you could steal.
All right. OK, this is what's going on.
Right. When you're brought in to one of these institutions, military type, the
doesn't matter what country you're in.
It's basically that we have all these armaments, you know, you could do what you
want. Just don't get caught.
All right. I hope that gives a little bit of insight into what's called the news.
And whenever you hear the good guys and the bad guys and all that stuff, that
ridiculous crap, this is a human condition.
Doesn't matter if you're in the military, in the legal society, medical society or
prankster in the religious society.
When I say the religious society, it doesn't matter what religion, because none of
them know or do anything that's in any of the texts that they alleged to subscribe
to. So ultimately, I've been kind of going on here for almost an hour.
Well, what I'd like to say is that Greek, you know, you don't have any solutions.
You know, no one's ever really said that to me, by the way.
The solution is very simple.
It's set yourself apart from it.
First, you ever notice in certain conditions that could be a calm condition looking
for a solution. You take a little more time and then you might have more of an
emergency type condition, like let's say a really bad what's called a car accident.
And the people on the sidewalk are panicking or throwing up because of the
dismembered bodies. And here comes the emergency crew and they're as cool as a
cucumber. And they just, you know, put all the intestines in a bag and discuss what
they're going to have for lunch in an hour.
All right. You know, like emergent people that are have training in emergency
situations tend to keep their cool.
But there's always some kind of solution, you see.
And it's so simple.
You know, the problem is not how would you say, OK, institutionally, what is being
put out there regarding problem solution?
You're not going to get any solution because there's no way to monetize that kind
of behavior. We just spoke about how the credit system is monetizing behavior.
Right. The solution is time based.
It's a terminal one, meaning you are actually as a human group and animals as
well that are here to accompany humans in their environment.
You're in a terminal condition where you're going to go to the next level.
And essentially, based on all the questions that I get regarding scripture, this
might tie in for you guys, because I know you're thinking about it, at least, you
know, privately, the emails I've been getting in private conversations.
One of the qualities of the termination of this condition and leading to the next
condition, the main thing is the elimination and the existence of something
called death, entropy.
Yes. Can you imagine a world or a universe where there is none or very little or no
death? Yeah, I say, can you imagine?
Right. Or you notice I didn't say, would you or may you?
It's can you? And the answer to that is very difficult.
It's very difficult to imagine that.
Right. And that is the so, you know, why is it that there is no accurate discussion of
things to come? None whatsoever.
Why? You ever think about that?
Don't. Because you'll go nuts thinking about it.
Right. Because the only way to actually see that is when you're given.
Well, first of all, you have to be inspired to have the interest.
Second of all, you have to be given the information that satisfies that interest.
And you have to have the ability to validate and verify it.
But right now, perhaps the status of the mindset and it's all about mindset, not
information, by the way.
Right. The status of the mindset is so piss poor, qualitatively, that the quantity of
what is being discussed is absolute rubbish.
Absolutely. Now, just because everything that's being discussed is everything, mostly
in media and alternative media and university and the pulpit and underground and behind
closed doors is absolute rubbish.
Why? Why is it rubbish?
Think about it. Anyone want to answer why pretty much everything that is being discussed
and thought of is rubbish?
And I mean, absolute rubbish, total garbage.
Why? Think about it.
Sounds like a big, tall, arrogant, dogmatic statement.
But see if I could get an answer from someone in chat or call and we'll get let that
fly for about 30 seconds while I take a drink of some of this delicious water.
OK, why is everything that is being discussed garbage?
No answer yet. But before that, let someone think about it, perhaps if they can't reach
out, I will answer that.
Sounds like we need. Here's a question from Chad.
Sounds like we need to guard our loins against the circumstances.
Earth here. Now we can't escape.
Setting apart won't change the world.
But sounds like it'll change us.
Right. Well, no, it won't change you.
It'll change your mindset.
You'll still be the same, but your behavior will be different.
Remember, tying this into the credit based economy, they're betting on your behavior.
For example, we'll just go back to the credit just for a moment.
Banks don't loan. There is no such thing as a lending institution.
You show up, they have nothing.
You sign a piece of paper, they deposit it and the money, whatever funds were on the
paper with your signatures created out of thin air.
And they're betting on you believing that that is a debt and you have to pay it back.
And that's how they put it on the secondary market.
That's how they make their living.
The banksters were pretty, were pretty, were pretty smart.
They said in order for them to do the receivership, they have to get at least one third of the
population approaching half if they could to get on board.
In other words, they make their living by pranking everyone else.
One of one one indirect comment, I think it was JP Morgan or someone else.
He was asked later on in life, what are you going to do if the people find out the
let's say pranking and deceit that is involved in this banking system?
He says, oh, that's really easy.
I'll just print enough money to hire half of the people to kill the other half.
Right. So it's very simple.
Any any any government or institution, even corporate or whatever that is in
receivership, they try to get as many people as their employees as possible, because
once they got you as an employee, there's no way you're going to anyway.
So here I'm getting some answers on regarding why everything everyone is discussing is
rubbish. Is it rubbish because everyone is deceived?
Yeah, pretty much. But the deception can come only when you're there's lack of validation.
Right. And responsibility in this cosmic censorship.
Yes, that's tied into it's rubbish because it's based on the lies deception.
We're going to answer back why everything being discussed is rubbish.
And I think you will find it interesting.
Greetings, everyone, this is Uncommon Sense with the Greek, and it's also
Uncommon Radio at Uncommon Radio dot com.
But in terms of discussing Uncommon Sense, before we went to the break, I pretty
much made a statement, let's just say, however it could be described that pretty
much everything that is being discussed is rubbish and why.
And there were some pretty good answers actually coming around.
But this is going to be very, very simple.
Folks, I gave a little bit of a metaphor earlier about how one of the financial
moguls was asked if the deception of the money system were to be uncovered, what
would he do? He would hire half the people to just kill the other half of the
people simply by just printing, you know, fungible assets, right, or money, what
they call. So here's the interesting thing.
If you listen to people forming groups and by the way, there's something called
The Crowd. It's a book or you could it's the best way to engage with a book, by the
way, is through audio, because years ago people didn't read silently.
So anyway, that's perhaps something we can discuss again in the future.
An audio book is the way to go.
But Gustave Le Bon, L-E-B-O-N, is someone who wrote something called The Crowd.
And he tries to, let's say, objectify why these crowds form.
Right. And there's always an idea behind it.
Now, if you listen to the various groups and the various ideologies, whether they be
political, scientific, religious or whatever, the people treasure, treasure these
things. Right. And they blindly and wholeheartedly, they have to be wholeheartedly
into it, because if there's doubt, they don't really they're not consistent about
joining the group. So why is everything out there that's being said is rubbish?
Because one man's rubbish is another man's treasure.
And this is where the entire concept of disinformation and misinformation has evolved
and unraveled into being the state of affairs in human society today.
By the way, disinformation is done by or disinformant is done by someone who knows that
it is untrue, but they're putting it out in terms of false information because that's
their job. Misinformation or the misinformed are those that receive it and think that
it's true. So you have the disinformers, which are very few, and the misinformed, which
are the many. And what has been going on is that just about every subject that is being
sonically experienced and in writing pretty much in the past, don't know how long, but
a very long time. And if you want to look at your religions, it goes back thousands of
years is rubbish because it's rubbish on one end and treasured on the other, because
one person's rubbish is another person's treasure or one man's rubbish is another
man's treasure. Just like if you look at architecture, one man's floor is another
man's ceiling, unless you're on the top floor, of course.
So with that said, I just wanted to put that out as a loose commentary that strictly
applies to what is going on. What did he just say? That's half in jest, all in earnest,
perhaps. Start listening to what's going on, folks. Start listening to what you're
being dragged in spiritually, spiritually meaning of the mind. Right. So and with that
said, being dragged in, let's see if we can have, I think we might have someone coming
in via the Skype convention here and perhaps we will have him here momentarily. We have
someone that has joined us on Skype. Greetings. Greetings. Hello there.
Can you hear me? Yes, I can hear you. Yes. And you're on AFR,
Uncommon Sense. I believe this is Sam. Yes. Yes, it is. What's on your mind?
Well, forgive me for diverting a bit from what you were previously talking
about. I had a pre-written question that I wanted to throw out concerning some of the
things that you've said previously about deities and supreme beings and also certain
concepts connected to that. One of them was concerning this idea or this, what you would
probably call a truth or a fact, that the claims that are made by the supreme being
concerning creation and his supremacy have remained unbutted, sort of like a stop sign
that somebody's put up, that nobody's contested. And so it remains until further notice.
That's right. But what you will find when you discourse with people in society is that there
is this recurrence of people daily denying the existence of the supreme being or what they think
is a supreme being. And they craft theories and narratives and claims that are meant to discredit
him and keep afloat the persistence of other religions that make contrary claims of what
the nature of reality is. So don't doesn't this collective body of contrary information constitute
a rebuttal of some sort? No, it doesn't, because it has to be done in kind. Let's just use the
legal society, for example, when they have a court case and there are filings that are being done.
If you're going to rebut one of the filings, you have to do it in the form that the court accepts.
But doesn't that validate the court to begin with? Yes. Well, it validates the jurisdiction
and the procedure, because you can go into another thing now that a court can be held anywhere. Do you
know courts are being held in people's kitchens and living rooms and out in the street all the
time? Right. But this is this is a certain methodology here. And the methodology also
applies to those. Your question is very pertinent. But but the example you gave regarding is it being
rebutted? No, that is not being rebutted in like because no one is coming forward and directly
rebutting, for example, saying, no, you didn't create it. I did or no, you didn't create it.
It wasn't created. You see nothing in like against like saying that my God created it or my deity
created it. They can't give you specifics and they can't back it up. And how is it backed up,
by the way? That's an interesting question, isn't it? Because, again, I always like to preface
several things regarding what's called the biblical text. And one of them is it leaves a
bad taste in people's mouths, not after they hear it sometimes, but when the subject is brought
because most because of what the mainstream religions and the academics have done with it.
Right. And the other thing is that what's called the scripture or the or the Bible is not a
translation of what has been memorialized or preserved through time. It is a version.
Right. It would be like the yellow journalism versus a true account, let's say. Right.
So regarding all of these matters, it takes a lawful mind, you see, to take interest.
Most people don't have lawful thinking abilities. They just think everything is a joke and for
right reason. Right. Because they've been raised in a society that is full of pranks, pranksters
and prankster ease, let's say the pros doing the pranks and those accepting the pranks.
And also motivated through penalty where they can't see straight, just can't think clearly.
And anyone with a lawful mind will look at any claim and examine it.
And what makes the the claim just to tie back to the to the the crux of the matter is what
makes the claim within the document itself to validate the claim. It says that no one or no
else, nowhere else can you find such accuracy of things to come. Right. Other than here,
this is what's going to validate. It's one of the main validations of what's called the
scripture or the biblical text is that claims of things to come will happen. And that proves
the text. Right. Well, we're talking about specifics now. And the irony of that,
maybe throw in cosmic censorship on how, again, people are avoiding this is that it that would
be called prophecy. Right. Things to come. Right. How there is very little understanding
about, quote unquote, biblical prophecy. You'll hear a million reasons why there's prophecy is
real and other million reasons why it's not. But no one is addressing directly the prophecies that
are in scripture directly. You will hear people say there is antichrist everywhere.
Well, you know, so so go ahead. I sounded like you want to interject some. Yeah,
because once to come back to this idea of rebuttal, it does, at least what you're describing,
it does seem to require that the objector still validate the being in question or the scripture
in question by engaging it or perhaps even subjugating his will or understanding to it
in order to engage it lawfully or committing committing a certain part of their time to it.
Well, not this time, but also but also acquiescing to those laws, the laws under which that text
functions in order to rebut it in a way that's lawful to the being associated with that text.
And to me, that sort of feels like if I'm opposed to it or I'm an enemy of it, why would I
want to subject myself to what it claims is the ruling understanding or the sort of constant
understanding so that I can discredit it? Why not just try to blow it up from outside externally?
Right. I mean, if I'm going to war with you, I'm not going to come into your city and sit
in your courts and try and tell you why what you're doing is unlawful. I'm going to send
a missile into your city or I'm going to lay siege to the city. I don't want to discourse.
Right. Right. Right. In other words, extend to the other aspect. Right. But
OK, there's several levels to that. And here's a few of them. Let's just bounce them around. One
is you're dealing with a non tangible in the state that we are in right now, a spirit animated
through material. Their existence is not solely dependent on our existence. In other words,
we are solely dependent on being animated through flesh and material. They do not require that,
as we know. So lobbying the missile or doing the physical destruction and in reciprocation
doesn't work too well. Also, there is a big time difference. A thousand years for us is one day
for them. Right. So a seven thousand year reality on Earth is only seven days for them. So no matter
how much frustration or what is going on here doesn't seem like a long time on the other side,
you see. So there's that aspect to the other aspect of it. Perhaps is a commentary on the
piss poor evaluation of the information when you compare it to the level of quantity of people
that are on the planet. There are millions of people, if not billions, that have, I wouldn't
say directly examined it, but indirectly examined or know of it. And no one is putting it together
in a clear, concise way. And when I say no one, I mean, there are those, but they're not public.
Right. Because I'm saying it statistically, statistically, we don't know anyone who has
so openly. And there's a lot of pieces being put together, but it's not being holistically or
as a whole explained very simple. That's why one of the things I like to discuss is the purpose of
that. And but also keep it short and minimal, because the time for this is going to be coming.
Right. And the other interesting thing is you notice how much contention is brought. And even
those who don't know anything about it, which is the majority of the people on the planet,
meaning the document, the scripture or what's called the Bible and other things like that.
That is the main thing of contention. Other holy writs are not right as much. I mean, they might,
you know, depending on the fad, you know, like right now there's a big problem. A lot of
fundamental Westerners believe that Islam or the Koran and all this stuff is a problem because of
certain political issues. But throughout history, it's always been the biblical text. The other
thing about it is that regarding the time that's coming is the whole crux and the whole element of
time. Right now, we're talking about a mindset for conservatively and most rationally,
since the Popple Bowl in the 1500s, this Gregorian calendar, which is, you know,
modification of the Julian calendar, which is another five or fifteen hundred years before that
is the only way that people have been considering time as a convention
or some kind of twisted, indirect, unlawful way. Like, for example, Asia has their own timekeeping.
Certain other places have forms of timekeeping, but they're not cohesive and they don't know
why they're doing it. So when we look at how time is being measured and when these things are being
told to happen, that has been abandoned. That's why when you study, for example, things to come,
it's always events. When you see this, you see that, right? Not using the ridiculous Pope's
calendar or something else. It's always, and I think we might have had a discussion
off-air once about there's a lot of contention about something called the chosen people,
why Israel are called chosen. And most people are too immature and they think it's an elevation,
like they're better than everyone else. It's actually not the case. They're actually there
as a clock, right? Just like if you and I decide to have coffee somewhere tomorrow at 3 p.m.,
according to the wind-up toy known as the clock, we have chosen the clock. So when you hear about
Israel being the chosen, it is because of you watch them to see what's going to happen next,
you see. As a matter of fact, it's quite the opposite. When the gods choose you to do something,
it's going to rain trouble on you as a group. Go back to the original question, please.
Do you believe, let's just say at this point, it has been rebutted? Or are you stating this because
why the question? I don't feel like it's necessarily been rebutted from within,
as you seem to be describing it as having to be in order to be lawful. But I think that people
lobby critique and theories and narratives against the scriptures and the biblical text and that
understanding. I think they've been lobbying critique at it for a very long time. Some of
the critique is arbitrary, some of it is immature, but also some of it sounds to be thought out,
invalid. And granted, I would probably have to look into it a bit more to be able to ascertain
how valid it is. But it certainly does sound as if people have made cases against it for a very
long time, to the point where it's now culturally trendy to just turn away from it. And any mention
of religion whatsoever. Well, there's a double there's a double level to it. Yes, I do suggest
people turn away from it, because what it is right now is what's called the King James Version,
or the New International Version, or all these versions. Yes, they will turn away from it.
And they're going to go back to, you know, it's the same thing with the medical field,
the legal society, science, or whatever. What is being spoken of in circles or groups or in
the media or in university is not what's memorialized about that subject. And for example,
the King James Version is not a memorialization of the scriptures. It is a version that has been
bantied about for political reasons, obviously. But for the average layman, these things would
still be interchangeable. Yes, erroneously so. But they wouldn't be able to tell the difference
between the King James Version and the actual text. To them, it's the same thing. So yes,
the outwardness of their attitude is, to me, still the same. They don't have anything to
do with it, because they don't see how it's valid. They will in the future. But most of them,
when I say the average, this is one thing to consider. And this is what I've deduced this to,
and anyone can if they take their time. There's a simplicity. It's not really like Occam's razor,
but you can consider it along the same mindset. When you consider what we mentioned about the
gods do not require material to be animated as we do, and also the time difference,
1,000 years for us is just one day for them. OK, let me just give it another way. There is a ratio
of 360,000 to one, right? If there are 360 days in a year, do you see my point? I just gave a
little bit of a hint there. So if you're studying, you'll see the numbers divisible of 360,000 come
up quite often. It's a proportionate thing. Think about that for a moment. Recently, I had a call
with someone, and I said, look, have you ever heard of what is the meaning of life? What is
the purpose of this? And we have philosophers and academics and writers, and it's become an art to
describe the meaning of being here. It's very simple. And again, not to deduce it to oversimplify
it, but something simple enough that anyone can think. Let me give you an example. Sit down at
this table here, and I want you to sort out 7 billion of these handkerchiefs, and when you're
done, call me, and we'll go to the next level. It's very simple. We don't know what a bear is,
but we know enough about a bear that we can discuss we know what bears are. But we really
don't, unless you sit down and have an 8-hour conversation with one. But we do know enough
about them that commonly we refer to them as bears when we know what we're discussing.
When it comes up to the society of the gods, from the low tier up to the highest,
one thing regarding their product of creation is whenever they create,
they always create in very large numbers. Everything they do is in very large numbers.
Stop being impressed by the quantity. And I've said this many, many, many times before. I call
the earth right now as inhabited by space heaters. What I mean by that is this. And this is very high
value, space heaters, because the gods say that man has a very high value. But the crux of the
matter is this. People take up space. By displacement, you could use the Archimedean
method. You could dunk someone in a tank of water and make a line, and you could measure
how much volume they take up. So they do take up space. And also, when they're alive, they give off
heat. People, when it's cold, they huddle together to get warmth and all this, right?
The majority of people that have come to this planet are space heaters. They're smart space
heaters. You know how you have smartphones that do more than one thing? You'll have some
space heaters that sweep streets, others that put on uniforms and lead other very dangerous,
ignorant people. You have others that tell you to worship a Coke bottle or whatever.
You have others, right? These are intelligent space heaters. But ultimately, they're space
heaters. And a certain number of them have to come through before you go to the next level.
It's very, very simple. It's almost to the point where it sounds indifferent.
But many times I've said that all the gods are malevolent to humans or mankind in their
condition right now. All of them. There is no such thing as a benevolent god in itself,
because if any of them showed up, benevolent or malevolent, as they are, you will disintegrate.
So they have to go do it by proxy. And what makes them benevolent is they control the plan,
and they are high up on the tier, which is actually, again, I've described before that
the man's world is a vertical one. The street sweeper at the bottom and the king or the
president at the top. The world of the gods, their society is a lateral kingdom. It's in or out. It's
left or right. That's why you sit at the left hand or the right hand. When Solomon was asked to
whatever he wanted, he would be granted. He asked for wisdom. And the reason why was so he would
know how to go in and how to go out. He didn't say up or down. It's a very little, short,
little thing there. So the interesting thing here is, like I've always deduced it again,
this will tie it back to the original. You're here for three basic things. To fulfill a number
of bloodlines, right, of this family should come through, let's say. It's not what you believe or
your political affiliation or whatever. It's what's running through your blood that the gods
are concerned through your veins, where your hereditary is, right, that they're concerned with.
A certain amount of people have to come through here and animals, by the way,
in all of creation that you see alive. And that's pretty much it. So when you understand that,
the three most important things are food, clothing and shelter. And then when you have those things
qualitatively, let's say, put together, then you can assemble a lifestyle or a behavior pattern,
which then you see what's going on amongst the rest. And you have a choice to do what they do
or set yourself apart from it based on a law form. And this is very simple. This is the purpose of
life here on Earth. And it's very simple. Now, it's not easy because try to pursue the highest
form of food, clothing and shelter that you can. It's a very simple idea, but it's not easy, is it?
All right. And the same with your behavior. So I have to go in like ten minutes. I'll try
to squeeze in two more questions. Well, I'll start with the shorter one first. You mentioned
earlier death and it caused me to think about certain verses in what's called the Bible regarding
that. And I wanted to ask death and what is called Hades. Are these angelic beings? Are there entities
that are in charge of these things? Because it mentions that they will also be thrown into the
so-called lake of fire. Right. Well, death will. Yes. And it's agents. At that time, there was going
to be a slightly different manifestation of it, too. But Hades is the Greek word for meaning empty
audio, like like, for example, heresy is another word that's used in these circles. Heresy is a
Greek word meaning what you just personally prefer. Like if you were to go to an ice cream
shop and someone's what's your heresy? In other words, I like strawberry or I like chocolate or
vanilla. It's a personal liking. Right. Where Hades or if you go to the ice cream shop and there's
no ice cream, you say, well, the ice cream shop is Hades means it's empty. It's emptiness. That's
all that words that word means. But it's been a lot of poetic license has been granted to it,
hasn't it? Mm hmm. Right. And it's been turned into a thing or a place that's a terminal form
of existence. I assure you that. And let's just share this publicly. When when people die,
everyone goes to hell. Right. Which is Hades or it means the grave. There's several words, shale,
Tartarus, let's say. Hades, everyone goes there, you die, you know, unless you're cremated,
that gets a little more technical and no one goes to heaven. No one goes to heaven at all. Only one,
the prototype, the Christ and the rest. Why? Why does no one go to heaven? Because heaven is coming
here. It is a realm. The earth is going to be turned into, let's say, a Grand Central Station
or a central universal hub. Here's an interesting thing to consider for all the listeners as well.
Even these new age idiots, you know, that are into this love and light and intention and
the ETs are going to come and save us and all this stupid stuff. Right. They even talk about how
the earth is being focused on. Right. So the malevolent, low level entities that are pumping
these people with these thoughts are still explaining how important humanity is. I'm just
going as a far stretch there not to be berating of the new age people and all these other
quote unquote spiritual idiots is what they are. But but, you know, it's just they deserve it
because it's just so ridiculous. Even they are professing that the importance of the position
of the earth and all the other beings in the universe. Right. You know, I've many, many times
given examples of how all of these signs are around us, but no one's paying any attention to
them until until they're brought up, of course. So. So regarding the Hades and death, are they
can they be represented by singular angelic beings, spiritual beings? Yeah. So here's an
example in, I guess, in Western culture, you have the Grim Reaper. Right. Right. The character
personification. A lot of things in art, which is a form of communication, let's say,
are actually based on the truth. They could be a diversion or corruption of something or inaccuracy.
But very little is really. For example, I once did one of the first sonic things that I did
with Ocelli was 100 percent external input. We humanity has gotten to the point right now where
they think that their thoughts are their own, where everything is streaming in. You're actually
receiving and you're broadcasting. There's really nothing in you. And of course, there's the
misinterpretation of, you know, the kingdom of heaven is in you. It doesn't say that it says
it's beside you. So so the thing is, yeah, you should you should be enticed by the concept of
death because it's very difficult, difficult to imagine. Right. But if death can be, let's say
if there is a Grim Reaper or some version of that, if, as you've mentioned, if gods or spiritual
beings manifest physically and you kill them and that takes them out in the spiritual realm,
if death were to do that, would that mean that it's now no more death because you've destroyed
that being? Yes. Yes. Well, it's there's certain things, you know, how there's like double negatives,
you know, it works in mathematics to a certain degree. When death is put to death, there's no
more death. And and the supreme being is not subject to death. Death is subject to him.
Right. And he has another. He does everything by proxy. Right. Like imagine you were an emperor.
You know, he doesn't do he doesn't run the nation on his own. He's got a multitude of of agents to
do it. So this sounds, you know, what's interesting, Samuel, is having this discussion in an open
forum is like these guys are crazy. They're talking about, you know, unseen. These guys have
friends that they talk, you know, we don't talk, but, you know, they believe in things that we
can't see right now. Yeah, of course, because it's all information based at this point. And one thing
I've actually mentioned before that the entire what you everything in the universe. And by the
way, whenever you hear people say, well, the universe where there's nothing in the universe
is just the space part. But everything that you see, whether it's the table in the room, the floor
yourself, the through a telescope, the galaxies and all that is information based, not material
based. It's information that holds everything together. And it's a longitudinal, not transverse
form. It's all instant. You can travel any amount of time instantly. So so you see how the the
boundary layer on such a question how expansive it can be? Yeah. I'll try and squeeze in my last
question here. You've said previously also that people bear the guilt of their wrongdoing once
they've been made aware of it. Yes, that's right. Yeah. So that's the law aspect of it. So then
going off that, one could say that and this is kind of a popular phrase that ignorance of the law is
an excuse. Yes, it is. OK, but it doesn't sound a lot. Judging by, you know, and I'm I'm looking at
it perhaps from a superficial point of view, but judging by your tone and some of the criticism
that you love and mankind in general, it doesn't really sound that way. It almost sounds as if you
would find them guilty of their stubbornness and their ignorance. Sure. Sure. Because they
actually admit it. Have you ever run into someone and bring up something that is of importance,
not just because someone thinks about it, it is objectified as an important topic and say, well,
you know, I didn't know about that. And you know what? I don't want to know and I don't care.
Right. Now, the other reason, but this is shorthand for something else like you said
yourself, that people don't say what they mean and they don't mean what they say.
So when they say they're not interested, I don't think it's tantamount to a
to disinterest. It's still a part of that internal confusion. That's just an input.
Disorientation. Right. And they're also being influenced by an input that allows them to be
in that position. But the reason perhaps you would have heard the Greeks speak in such a tone and in
such context is because when they do find out later, there's going to be gnashing of teeth,
so to speak. There's going to be a very, very deep regret when everything is exposed.
Right. So it's right now it might sound like the tone of the Greek is kicking them in the shins,
but later they're going to be getting a little bit more than that. And of course,
it's all going to end up in a benevolent fashion. It's all going to end up beneficial for everyone.
By the way, folks, if you subscribe to any one of these ridiculous religions or whatever,
and you've been told to believe in an eternal, by the way, there is no eternity
or a very long time of torment, that is not true. You will not find that. And when you read,
when you hear about eternity or forever, you will not find that memorialized anywhere.
What they're translating into that word is the word a eon or Olam, right, which are given slots
of time. So, but yes, the thing isn't ages yet. Typically, they're chunks of 2000 years,
typically. And though I say typically, meaning it's typical to note that astronomically,
right, the the ages come around every 2000 years, every 1960 or so to 2100 years.
Okay, last question, and then I got to run because I need to get to work. But it's regarding this
input, this hundred percent input thing. And I wanted to ask, how can a person,
as you've described, be 100% external input or be animated by that when he has his own agency
and his own autonomy over the expression of his character and his personality, both of which seem
to be considered a part of an inner intangible being through which emotions and pros and
convictions are manifested? Yeah, on one hand, you have free will, which is harnessing an application
of one owns sovereignty in order to act. And you have the aforementioned mechanisms of self
government. And you seem to reside inside a person, but you feel yes, though, because we
have to receive the information and instruction that this constitutes 100% dependence on input.
What about imagination, you use imagination to transmit one piece of information into another,
but you own that imagination? Well, you own it, you own it as much as it is displayed,
that it is being emanated from you. Here's an archetype way to look at it. There's an archetype
for mankind, right? Meaning we have an anthropomorphic form, a spirit and a soul,
okay? That is the archetype, basically the three year, you know, the body's animated through the
mind and the soul keeps every, you know, it's the pulsing breath that keeps everything going.
And one day I'll keep repeating the definition of those things. But the archetype there,
it would be the same as the archetype, let's say, of a television or a radio. There are many,
let's say, radios, let's say, give some brands here, we don't have to give brands. They have
circuitry and form, right? And when you turn them on, they hiss, right? Unless they have a signal,
like a what's called a television or a monitor. They all have their little alien sequences,
meaning like, you know, you can have 1000 computer monitors built and run for 10 years,
but they're all going to break down a little differently, right? What these radios and monitors
and things are is they, to themselves, or let's say a computer doesn't have much,
they require input, right? A monitor is monitoring the video signal, a speaker or audio is monitoring
an analog projection of the sound. You know, it's the same thing that I've given the analogy,
imagine someone sitting at a beach with a portable radio listening to jazz and, you know,
the concept of opening up that radio and there's a little tiny jazz band in there that's being
amplified is ridiculous, isn't it? Now, the ridiculousness of thinking that there's stuff
in us is also, if you confide temporarily into the scientific community, what they keep kind of hush,
but can be discovered, is they have discovered with all of their devices that there's nothing
in the brain. They're trying to find memory, they're trying to find, there are impulses in
the neurons and things when there's speech and thought, but they don't see it and they can't.
Another example of it would be the Egyptians would mummify the bodies and various aspects
of the organs based on their importance, but the brain they threw away because it had no purpose,
you see. It's very interesting. What happens is we take it for granted. Like right now,
you could be speaking or walking or tying shoelaces, you don't think of it
very much. The thoughts, the imagination, and what makes us us, what comes out of us,
let's say, what we think, is all external. But what makes us us, our spirit,
like our fingerprint, things like that, that is unique to us, just like an archetype of
manufacturing a monitor. So you would say that the imagination and personality and character
and things of that nature are a product of the spirit. A product of the spirit that's been,
let's say, manufactured or the archetype of each individual. Like no two loaves of bread are baked
alike. No two radios or no two monitors are exactly the same. The tolerances that make humans
humans are still there. Like for example, everyone has the same intelligence. The discernment and
ability to project it and use it are different. So that's the functionality of it. And that's the
aspect of it. There's an archetype. See, if you start looking into archetypes, what is the base
aspect of things? All machines have archetypes. All living things have archetypes. What is the
basis of them? And this is something that is, because we're taking things for granted. For
example, I give this metaphor. If you were a spirit being and you were not familiar with the
anthropomorphic form and you were given anthropomorphic form as an adult, you would be
laying down on the floor wondering why you can't stand up because you have to learn how to walk.
Right, right. Okay, well, thank you, Samuel. Sounds like you're getting ready to get going.
I appreciate you calling in. Thank you. Thank you so much. Okay, thank you. We'll speak again.
Thank you. Definitely. Bye then. Bye. Okay, folks, so we had someone giving some input. Again,
hopefully it didn't labor anyone listening. But again, from most of the private messages that I
do get, there is a desire to discuss these matters. And one of the things that I've been saying for
years is that starting, let's say, about six or seven years ago, what I started saying with
there's going to be more and more interest on things, quote unquote, biblical or about the
scripture, increasing interest, none of it or very little of it will be accurate. But the focus
and the interest will start going there, you hear more of it being used metaphorically, and being
brought up, but none of it is accurate, that is being given, let's say, to the masses. So I'm
going to maybe look at the chat just for a minute here, because this is a way to interact live with
people here. When Okay, his question, what happens when you're cremated? Why? Why would it make any
difference? That's more of a cultural thing that nothing is too difficult for them to do. So if
you're cremated, they can still still reassemble you or assemble you. It's just that traditionally,
in older cultures, a garbage was burned, and people were buried, things that people loved
were buried. And if you look at, you know, very different cultures have their own views on that.
So that that's something that wouldn't be too difficult if you're cremated to be reincarnated,
let's say again. And when God's day do they reincarnate? Yes, possibly they could be granted
that but they could also be just left downloaded in the hard drive is from what I've gotten.
Let's see. I'm interested in your thoughts and insights concerning art. I'm an artist,
perhaps I will email. Okay. Yeah, well, art is a form of communication. Right? Think about it.
You know, there you have, let's just use music. For an example, you have many genres of music,
right? And why like quoting, I think it was Satchmo that once said, they asked him,
what music do you like? What's good music? And he says, if it sounds good, it is good.
Right? And that's like beauties in the eye of the beholder. It's not like a rose is a rose by any
other name. For example, if you listen to some of this music that just if you could call it music,
certain genres, you know, I usually criticize it, I call it Oh, that's a love song, you know,
or whatever, you know, it just kind of makes people rethink what they're listening to. But
there is an aspect to it. There are aspects to it, where some things can be destructive,
some things can be productive. But I would suggest that if you guys are familiar with
someone called Nikola Tesla, what he was discussing regarding electricity or electrical
fields in the universe and how man can use them, his counterpart in music would be JS Bach. And
I'll just leave that for now. Another couple of questions here is people stubborn rejection
of truth and valuable matters will be held accountable for the rejection future once
they've been told Yes, they will. But it won't be to a degree for those that know it and deny it
like the misinformed will not be held to the level that the disinformers are. Despite their saying
that they didn't know or don't care. Yeah, they will be held accountable. But on accordingly.
Another question is, I'm thinking they're responsible for what they're told despite
rejecting. Okay, it's pretty much a same kind of thing. I have no clue their mindset or
God standards. Yeah, it's about knowledge again. Sorry, I murmured that question out. But okay,
not at all. Okay. Okay, there's loud mystery booms and trumpet sounds. Are they written about? Yes,
but not yet. And Wilhelm Reich, and armoring. Yeah, okay. That could that could be discussed
also. This is the thing, folks. Some of these questions here were about holding people
accountable for what they say. Do you know that in certain cultures, for example,
if you profess publicly, and it was memorialized that you said this, for example, this being like
something's going to happen, and you gave a specific and it didn't happen. Do you know it
was like off with your head or you were thrown into a muddy pit to die or something like that?
You know that these things were taken very, very seriously. In previous and other cultures,
let's say of previous days right now, what I've noticed and one of the reasons why abstain from
the media, all media is that given example of financial moron, we'll make some financial
moron as he says that he's a consultant. But anyway, he says, Oh, yeah, there's going to be
a financial collapse in March 15. Okay. All right. This idiot doesn't know that all financial
collapses happen in the fall. Oh, boy. All right. So there's a, you know, people's espousing days
and dates and things like that. And none of it happens. And they're not being held accountable,
which shows that there is no quote, unquote, form of policing, or the people just don't care,
right? Why? Because they're being censored. They really, here's the thing, you shouldn't do
anything at this point. Because if you're setting yourself apart, you're watching it from from afar,
you just want to pray that their violence is not brought on their foulness and their violence is
not put upon you, which is quite easily done. And I tell people, look, if you're complaining
about this, this or the other, you're really not paying attention, because you should be
appreciative that you're able to speak right now. And they're like, Well, why do you say that? I
said, because you should be appreciative that no one came in to where you were sleeping last night
and rip the liver out of your body. And they spared you then. So what do you mean? That sounds
kind of harsh. Yes. Are you? The earth is a very violent and harsh place. And by the way, if
someone tried to come in, where you were sleeping last night and try to rip out an organ out of the
body, and you ask them why they were doing that, they say, I don't need any reason, I just feel
like it. And this is basically the concept of what it means to be on this planet, folks, think about
it. You know, that's why perhaps maybe getting into details on sort of criticizing what is being
said out there. One thing that I've never really gone into is discussing current events, whether
it's a scientific current event, or a political one, or what have you, other than the main mass
nations and the big thing, the big things that are coming, and actually being you're being set up
for right now, as we speak. But anyway, you know, you know, we're, who are you going to address with
things rational, that's, that's the thing, maybe the best way to do it is with a, maybe some kind
of two hour show on a minor internet radio platform. So, yeah, let's get back to the
thank you, I guess, again, and I'm grateful for for people participating. And folks,
I just want to recap here, for the purpose of doing this,
uncommon sense is that two hours a week, you could come and be dummy load free. And the thing about,
well, it's two hours, it takes about an hour to undo the dummy load that that's been put on you
from all the other stuff. And it is not a criticism directly, but indirectly to everything
else out there. One way to discern what is being said is to just see where liability is being shed.
Folks, you ever hear people say, you know, they're critical about a subject, whether it's
whatever, and say, well, our banks are doing this, our military, our courts, and this is just,
you know, we're not talking about, you know, the person speaking that you're hearing this from now
is either a host or a guest or writing an article or has a website or something or even on mainstream
or in the movies. These are not people that are in that society, and they're still calling it
theirs. Be careful with that. But by the way, other than that being the mark of a moron,
that is the mark of, there's a spiritual, let's say, quote, unquote, karmic
evolution. When you become part of that and you agree with that, now you're taking liability
for that. So, for example, I've heard recently someone say, our military. I'm like, oh,
wait a second. Okay, this person is not in the military, you know, whatever, you know,
and they profess not being, but they're calling it our military. What they are doing when they do
that is that anything that the military does, they now attach the liability to them or whoever
says it's ours. You see, liability meaning you take the hit spiritually, and you see, our banks,
our government, our this, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second. So, be careful and listen
to whenever you hear liability being put on you, the listener. That is an initial mark that this
is a lazy, spiritual, lazy, sonic emanation, and it's just blazing, lazy goop, but I just want to
go back to the idea of doing a two-hour, presumably dummy load free for whoever's tuning in,
and especially down the stream with archives as well, is that there is still the possibility of
the Greek doing other projects that are on the inane net or internet. Discussing many of these
matters. It seems like two hours is just a matter of getting, you know, warmed up before you run
around the block or something, but the idea of a members area, the idea of getting into more detail
or the idea of just showing up here two hours a week solo and speaking. What kind of input can
you folks give to AFR? What kind of input can you folks just send? Send whatever you think,
whatever you deem is worthy to AFR, and just go to the home page and donate something
and put in the subject line, this is for uncommon sense, so we kind of know what kind of input
can be brought and what kind of resources can be gathered.
What's interesting is discussing how the credit system works and based on whatever law you live
by, it could be viewed as I don't care or it's really deceptive, evil practice, which is most
likely the latter. This is what we've got, and if there's any other way, I mean if you want to
send a pound of corn or some potatoes or a live goat or whatever, I don't think the live goat works
well, but the easiest way to do it now is electronic convention and there are ways, by the
way, of doing it conditionally. If you folks understand unconditional and conditional, that's
a whole other discussion, but if anyone wants to understand the money system a little bit more and
how topsy-turvy and how crazy this world is, all the countries have a similar code or tend to.
Go into a browser and type in USC12 section 411. It's just one paragraph. It would be United
States Code section 411, Title 12 section 411. It basically tells you that these Federal Reserve
notes are only to be used by Federal Reserve agents and no other use is authorized.
So, we're kind of like in this screwy kind of, really, it's a dirty system. Now, whether it's the
money system or whether it's the religious system, all of them, whether it's the medical system,
the legal system, even sports. By the way, when you watch something like the Stupid Bowl,
that is completely fixed. All the stuff is fixed. Not everyone in there knows it, but the key people
do. All the systems right now are just to keep everything going because a certain number of
space eaters have to come through. Sorry, folks. You know, there was something interesting to be
garnered from all the popularity that's gone to the movie known as The Matrix and the series there.
There's some interesting points there and most of it, I would say, the gist is true,
but the interesting thing is if you're killed in The Matrix, you're killed in real life,
and I like to use that metaphor because that's also a commentary on the realm of the gods and how
they exist also when they manifest. If anyone is familiar with the Mahabharata, there's a story
there about a prince shooting, I believe it was an antelope or a deer that was a god that had
been manifest and he's in big trouble. You know, you can see how these films somehow do copy and
do project the sense of what is going on, but I don't like to use them as references like many
people do because I think there are things that have been memorialized of higher significance that
can be. So again, things of higher significance, I just wanted to say that it's best to discuss
what can be discussed and of course, I am still curious and we're probably going to make it a
project here for the next two weeks, so it's four weeks total of Uncommon Sense to see how much
public support can be garnered from the quote-unquote public and it would be towards AFR
to see if Uncommon Radio, which is put together by the Greeks, should assemble a members area or
someplace where things can be just a little bit more in depth based on different matters. And
again, I just want to thank everyone who has reached out and sent emails and also in the
chat or anything else because coming here for two hours a week and just openly discussing anything
is great, but it also requires some feedback and I want to thank whoever calls in or even anyone
in the chat because especially what I have found out at the public at large is just ridiculous and
vile and just however you want to comment on people and what they have their hope in
is completely fruitless. Their desires are completely just off the mark. I mean, they're
just existing, but what I have found out is that when this type of conversation is instigated,
the feedback that I get is always very positive and very pertinent and it comes from almost
every aspect of young, old, international. It seems like there is an interest and
something to look for that I've been saying for over a decade is that if you just study
what things should be based on, like the lawful pretext of something, and I'm not talking about
the legal society because there's not one attorney that knows any law because if he did study law
in context, he would go to work or his friends in the bar association would have him disbarred,
period. That is the truth of the matter. Now, there might be some of them that do it privately,
but I'm sure they're grinding and they're trying to figure out how to get out of that field and
a lot of them do, but there are no attorneys that know law because if they profess to know law
and operate lawfully, they will lose their position. When I say law or lawful, it means
what things should be based on by the way that we exist. For example, if you go somewhere and buy
mashed potatoes to consume as food and you look at what's called the ingredients and you see a list
of 50 items there and it's hard to find where the potatoes are, can you say those are lawfully
mashed potatoes or are they in name only? Anyone that is pursuing anything than just beyond what
is in name only and what is it based on, you're going to have an advantage in this society whether
you're set apart or not in the future because people are going to start going back and all
of these things that you're being influenced with, political or however they are, are always
temporary and fall by the wayside, but once you get a grip on what is the foundation and what is
lawful and what is tangible, that stays and you use that as a judgment or a ruler to see the
quality of what's being discussed or what's being presented and that is ultimately where mankind
should be or will be. So again, let's just consider this sonic event, the next and the
next two episodes to be what would pretty much be presented in a member's area and also
as an experiment again to see how much support can be garnered from Greek speak or
Uncommon Sense and I'm sure it will be appreciated at AFR because also they've been providing the
platform for the Greek to come consistently and do sonic events with others or just
solo as he is right now. So in essence, it is sort of an experiment to see how much
support can be garnered for both, but at this point I want to also thank everyone who has
sent some support and because obviously you deserve it and thank you and again as time
goes on we'll see what kind of projects can be in garnered but to be developed, but as it
stands so far not much support has been sent for creating a member's area or something too
specific. So we'd like to see a little more in number if possible or a quantity of some kind of
something because it takes quite a bit of effort to do a more of an exclusive information
informational base. Otherwise we'll just keep showing up and discussing what can be done here
every week for two hours. So let's see if there's anything else here that anyone wants to
ask. Not really. We just have a few more minutes left and I just want everyone to consider
that no matter where you are in the world, if you get up early enough and you notice the sun
is rising, you notice that the past few days and perhaps tomorrow it is going to be rising
cardinal east and I mean due east. If you look at how the light comes into a room or a house,
notice how much different it is if you can. So it'll be the first week of the first month the
next time we come around and I want to thank everyone for coming around this time
and thank you again and for Uncommon Sense.