Greetings, everyone, and welcome to Uncommon Radio.
This is the Greek with Greek speak speaking at you.
Yes, it is the second month.
I would propose it is the beginning of the second week or more into the second week.
I'd say about the middle, I'm reckoning around the twelfth day after noon.
And I think giving the lawful timekeeping should take precedent over the ridiculous pagan papal stuff.
And I guess I said it, you heard me.
And when I say pagan, I'm not talking about the fashion where people, you know, I'm a
pagan. Well, what they do is let their hair grow.
They wear sunglasses and get all these tattoos and wear, you know, whatever, you know, the
look, paint their toenails black.
That's just a ridiculous fashion.
I'm talking about the mindset that is on prevailing this planet.
Now, that just means however you want to take it.
Is it a pejorative term?
Is it kind of bad?
I wouldn't say it's bad, but it ain't good.
And later on, you'll find that it ain't it's pretty bad, but you'll have to find out.
See, I don't want to talk about what's really bad because I think people need to find that out on
their own. But at the same time, it's around what they call April 20th, 2017, for that
ridiculous mindset, which everyone tends to have at some point in their life till they
discover that they've been caught out there.
But here's the thing, folks.
I hope you're sucker free for the next two hours because I don't know what we're going to be
talking about. Basically, I've been keeping a sort of a numeric sequence coming around here.
And remember, this is speaking in public.
So, you know, if I ride the public bus or use the public bathroom, I was speaking to
someone, a forest like, I don't know what to say tonight, and I hope the audience isn't like
who I see in public.
It's just deplorable.
But anyway, and when I say that, I don't mean just, you know, some dark alleyway or
something, which I've never really been down.
But I just mean the public at large.
And really, if you want to discern the public, you don't look at them or a mass of
people. By the way, when they take a cancer out of a body, they call it a mass.
So anyway, when they decide this, the suspect society is to be viewed.
Do you folks remember the 1950s propaganda films about UFOs and all that?
You know, the little green man lands and says, what?
Take me to your leader.
Well, why don't I? What is it?
Why does he talk to just whoever he ran into?
Well, think about it, you know.
OK, anyway, well, the leader's got the power and also he represents the people.
That's what I want to just maybe talk a little bit about.
You hear a lot of, I don't know, I'm laughing because it's like I really just I
mean, it's not even worth bringing up.
I'll bring it up just for about maybe 10 seconds.
You've been thoroughly dummy loaded all week.
I don't need to know what you've listened to, what you like, what you don't like.
If you've turned on any alternative media, any mainstream media, go to university,
read the newspaper, even talk to someone next to you.
You have been dummy loaded.
That is the condition on this planet, folks.
And, you know, showing up here for two hours a week to kind of rationalize is
insane. One of the things you might have discovered from especially the archives,
this is sort of cumulative, by the way, when you hear Greek speak, it's
cumulative. When you when you listen to the archives, there's a long chain of
descriptions and explanations on why humanity is in such bad shape.
And an idiot with a microphone telling you things are going to be better or an
idiot with a printing press saying the same or telling you that some warships
are going to end the world is ridiculous.
I mean, on and on and on and on.
I mean, it just there is no rationale whatsoever.
I mean, you won't find it.
Now, speaking of finding some rationale, why don't we just say for a moment that
this is also a forum that is kind of open?
I've just been the phones are ready and I will give that and I will give out the
information, meaning that you can participate.
And the call in number is 218-339-8525, 218-339-8525.
And I will bring up the phones here momentarily.
The other thing to consider is if you like the Skype convention, you could always
go to Skype and that would be the email for Uncommon Radio, which is
UncommonSenseRadio1, numeric one, that is, at gmail.com.
And that is also the Skype request contact.
So if you'd like to join somehow, you may.
All right.
And I'll keep an eye on what's called the chat at American Freedom Radio and perhaps
have the emails available as well.
Many people have been emailing all positive, but positive in a sense that it
shows that they're listening.
The questions and the comments are very specific.
The worst thing you could do is email, oh, I really like you.
It's like, you know, I very often, you know, well, what's what do you like
listening or what do you like reading or what do you like?
I really like it.
Well, what's about it?
Just like it.
Right.
It's just I get none of that, thankfully.
And by the way, when I also gotten some private comments about, well, you know,
when you give descriptions of humanity or religious types or scientific types,
you're discussing the low hanging fruit.
Well, perhaps perhaps commenting on the low hanging fruit, because the majority
of all of it is not even on the tree.
It has fallen off the tree and it is rotten.
The best of the best is the low hanging fruit.
There is the top of the tree has been cut off.
So anyway, well, let's let's just see if I could bring up the phones and just
make those available in case someone would like to make themselves available
to speak at everyone else.
So we'll see now it's just a conference manager.
Let's see.
We are on.
OK, so the caller network is open.
Please call if you want to just voice something.
That's fine.
Used to give several criteria about calling in and one was if you're intoxicated
or under the influence, please don't do it because you might think you're fine,
but you're not.
The rest is don't speak about yourself too much because you know what?
People might act politely, socially, that they care, but no one really cares.
They're waiting for you to shut up so they could tell you what they want to tell you.
So if you call in, be edifying, share something, give us some good testimony
and provoke some thought.
So with that said, let's just see what's going on over here.
OK, I don't know.
I don't see much happening in chat.
Well, there's always something happening in chat other than cobwebs and tumbleweeds.
Whatever.
OK, not much that I could discuss.
Let's see.
Check the emails right now.
OK, so basically, if anyone's noticed through archives that there's been a
successive solo progression and this would be the eighth one coming around and
suggesting that eight is a number of completions, suggesting the eight is
infinity sign, you know, for the you know, the eighth the eight year old mentality
thing because it looks like an infinity sign or whatever.
That is another another approach.
If one is going to discuss this from, let's say, a cosmic perspective, we don't
really have a lot of information or how it can be attributed to something.
You know, it's too specific.
The specifics is that this particular epoch of humankind will be finished,
thankfully. Now, what does that mean?
Well, it means that life as as is known will not will not exist the way it is
now, which which is something else to to discuss.
You know, some people say, well, you know, Greek talking about the end all the
time, you know, this and that.
And some people, a couple of people would say.
And it's not about the end.
It's about the end of this condition.
Here's the thing.
Let's just let's just give a little bit of a preface on the condition.
For those of you that are have a pulse and can walk and I know you get I know
you're taking up space and giving off heat, but it might be considered a smart
space heater. You know how they have smartphones anyway.
There's a pun on that, by the way.
And it's not a pun like you can say, well, I'm waiting for people to be smart
phones to be dumb again, because, you know, are you waiting for space here is
to be smart and whatever, you know, I don't know, or dumb or so people can be
smart. People are space heaters.
You take up space, you give off heat.
What are you going to do with the rest of the time?
Now, one thing that, you know, cutting to the chase is very simple.
You know, there's a lot of you can go to art.
Art is the best way to maybe think about this or philosophy is another good way to
think about it. Not that philosophy and art is good, necessarily.
It just happens to be an expression.
The meaning of this is so simple, just like what's the meaning of two?
And people tend to illustrate it.
Or what's the meaning of this?
You have to have a very simple meaning, not oversimplifying it for the dumb crowd.
You know, or to dummy load anyone.
But it's very simple. If you're looking around for answers, you are it.
What I mean by that is very simple.
If you start seeing the infrastructure of how society cosmically has been set up and
how things are going to take place and why, right, the key why is the key word there
or the key aspect, you will discover that a certain amount of time and a certain
amount of people need to come through here.
So if you've shown up, if you are born into this reality, even if you've died within
the first 30 seconds, it doesn't matter.
If you have lived even a short life, it doesn't matter.
You have showed up. You have taken a place number.
Yes, the gods are into numbers and you will find that out later.
You have taken up a place and your job is finished.
All you have to do is show up.
Once I give the metaphor, and this is true, where a project had to be done, need a lot
of bodies, a crane situation type thing, get the picture, heavy lifting, rigging.
And you need a lot of people around in case something goes wrong.
And I called a lot of people and they said, well, describe what I should show up for.
And I described, I said, I know nothing about that.
And I said, well, you don't have to.
If you show up, it's 90 percent to show up at the time and you'll be fine.
And guess what? You're 90 percent done if you're in this world.
Now, think about that for a minute.
Actually, don't think for a minute.
Well, OK. All right.
Think about it for a minute.
Why should you think about it?
Because doesn't it start to put all of this into a different perspective?
You know, when you hear about things like fate, I'm not talking about just from the
Greek mythological point where there are three aspects and even the gods are subject
to that. By the way, if anyone wants to look into Greek mythology, look at it
specifically. Don't look at it based on what you think you know about it.
And don't read something that someone wrote about someone else with someone else
wrote about it. Get a little more functional.
You'll see even because there's the aspect of the gods, it's brought up there.
But this is a concept of fate.
OK. And then there's the concept of free will.
And you will see there's no there is no difficulty with that.
You see, there is no how would you say, well, is it a paradox?
What about free will? What about it?
Everything ties together very, very neatly.
What about this? What about that?
Now, if you understand that you are here, your job is done when you show up and
you're functional. Even if you're not functional, you came, you came, you saw, you
did nothing. That's pretty much what it's about.
There's a saga. There's a story.
There's like I said earlier, there's art, there's philosophy, there's works, there's
war, there's growing, all this other stuff.
Now, when you consider the growth aspect, you're an agricultural based society,
period. Right.
And here's the other aspect to it.
You probably walked around today and didn't didn't mind that very much being called a
filter bag, did you?
What do I mean by that? You know, how many times have you heard?
Well, you know, tying this with the agricultural aspect that you absorb things like
you're a sponge or a filter bag.
This is what you've been told now.
Why tying this back together, if you show up, you're just you're done, you've pretty
much accomplished most of what you should accomplish.
It's because everything around you has been indirectly and directly designed
indirectly, meaning it's not the exact meaning from here on out, but it is what
you've got right now as a deception.
It's a deception to keep you in a place where you have what's called culture,
tradition, society, your aspirations, your desires, your perceptions have all been
pre-planted or preset for you.
So basically, right now, if you are in any culture, in any society, there's really
very little you can think about that you cannot find that either someone has written
a book about or a cult of a society, a culture or tradition that has something to do
with it. Even these new emerging technologies tend to fit within that realm or that
realm, meaning the earthly realm of what's in the world right now.
So, again, back to the filter bag.
You folks believe at this point still that what you are being told and what you are
happy with hearing and being in agreement and believing tends to supersede your
ability to perceive what's going on with your own body, with your own body.
I'm not talking about stupid stuff that is put in front of you by the scientific
society, the medical society or the legal society or the religious society, anything
else. It's just you and yourself.
When you put your feet and your hands in water, do they shrivel up when the membrane
softens or do they expand like a frog?
Think about it. When a soft membrane shrivels up, that means that it's under a slight
vacuum. Put a slab of meat in a plastic bag and put a little suction on it.
Does that plastic bag expand or does it shrivel up around that slab of meat and bone or
whatever you got in the bag?
Think about it. Notice how plants dry out, how they shrivel up.
Well, you have something called a biological vacuum.
Biology just means life.
OK, how can one start to define life, right?
Because if you're not alive, you're not here and if you're not here, nothing matters,
does it? By the way, I just want to throw in a little dig to you older guys out there and
women. You know, very often I do make a comment about how the older people have rendered
themselves useless, especially in the past half century.
I recently had someone, this has happened many, many times.
It's just been reoccurring.
If you don't just say it on radio, I just thought about it again, is when you speak to an
old person or older, meaning older than 50 typically, and you start, let's say,
mentioning things that are coming in the future because it's not difficult to know what's
coming in the future. You've just been trained that you shouldn't.
Basically, when you start going 5, 10, 20 years beyond, when you hear an answer like,
well, I'm not going to be around then, so it doesn't matter.
Think about the fatalism there.
Here you have an elder in society that actually professes with their own mouth that
because they will not be here, they are apathetic and don't care.
Isn't that the same thing as saying that you don't care right now?
And if you actually look at their behavior, you guessed it.
Yep, that's right. That's why they slap diapers on them, throw them in nursing homes and
pump them up with drugs.
You see, it's not pretty, but it's true.
Not all the old people, but the majority.
If you're around any elders, go ahead and ask them, try to discuss anything that's beyond a
cereal box or what's in the newspaper or whatever kind of indoctrination or pranking
they've suffered. What are you going to get?
Pretty much nothing. And this is the condition of society.
Now, look, if you're just visiting this planet, taking notes, it's not going to be really
hard to come back wherever you came from and describe it.
It's very, very simple.
There isn't much going on other than what you are doing.
Think about it for a moment, what you are doing, because the purpose behind it, I just
hopefully illustrated and demonstrated, has been wiped away because your purpose is to
show up. If you were born into this reality and you are functioning even now, your job
is done because there is a big plan.
There is a big infrastructure.
I'll give you another example, perhaps.
I always discuss the infrastructure, not always, but tend to.
Remember, this is all cumulative.
A lot of the things that were brought up, let's say I maybe did a couple of talk shows and
did a few things, did a project with Chuck O'Chelly and whatever, all those things I
tend to repeat, but not really get into things too much.
It's cumulative. If you want to go into archives and hear other stuff, elaborate on other
topics. But essentially, just being here.
And showing up is it.
So how do you tie it all together?
What's there to tie together?
What do you want to tie together?
What do you see, what do you perceive?
Coming to this planet, let's say coming into this existence and realizing that your life
is as short as it is, is going to require a little bit of effort for you to understand
the infrastructure, which is whatever.
Just thinking of how else can this be explained?
The infrastructure example that I give, for example, is someone riding a commuter train
and this commuter train, you know, whatever, however long they ride it, you know, it's
not built for them. It's built for society at large or wherever it wants to buy a
ticket or whatever, gain access to it.
There's a tremendous infrastructure there, all the tracks being laid down, all the
planning, the actual manufacture of the equipment, on and on and on and on.
And the maintenance, it's massive infrastructure.
Most people that commute and ride that are not aware of what went into it.
Yes, let's say, you know, maybe there's some civil engineers or whatever that might
be to a degree.
You see, so when do you actually appreciate what has been done so you could just take
a simple, you know, train ride to your slave job and get a piece of paper that you think
is being paid? You see how everything ties together.
So when you look at the infrastructure and how everything is put in place cosmically,
right? You're done.
You showed up. You're pretty much.
Think about it, you know, if you're here.
So what does this do?
Well, it's not it's actually the opposite of it should be very optimistic, not
fatalistic. I would suggest that it would be the most probably one of the most
enlightening things and one of the most inspirational things that could be said to
anyone. If you're here, you've done 90 percent of it.
Why? Because now you can start filtering and start thinking objectively of what's
going on around you. Well, what's going on around you?
Well, at large, if you anyone in general, if you are dealing with
any type of, let's say, crowd, this goes all the way from
the most loosely assembled or figured social groups,
meaning like, you know, movie clubs, music clubs or whatever, all the way
into political stuff, activists, activists.
Anyway. OK, I'm not going to lie.
All right. So then then you then you go up into other more structures and industry
and what's called government.
Those cannot exist without many of the outlines set forth.
And this is not a recommendation.
Take it as you will. But I mention it because it's quick and easy and it's a good
reference. Gustav Le Bon's The Crowd.
He actually wrote about about 1895 or something,
the technical aspects of how a crowd forms.
Let me just reiterate that real quick.
In order to form a crowd of people, they do come together under a thought and
idea, religious, technical, political, whatever.
Now, in order to get the common masses to form that crowd,
that idea has to be made so simple.
That when you examine the idea, once it's been adjusted for the crowd mentality,
it hardly represents its original form anymore.
Right. You ever. OK, let's pick on the activists a little bit.
I mean, I shouldn't because they're in really bad shape.
You know, they're very sensitive in their act, whatever.
Ask them what they're protesting about.
But their activism is about it's not even skin deep, it's paper thin,
paper, paper thin, not even to have no clue, but it's a crowd.
OK, the same, you know, the arts might be interesting because that's so subjective.
Fine. You want to go into industry, look at the compartmentalization.
You want to get into more directive institutions, perhaps what's called
government or whatever. I mean, that's when you get up to that level,
by the way, when you're actually ruling the ignorant masses.
You know, I think that the ones that are in what's called government are a
different species.
Almost so.
So the situation is very, very, very clear.
Now, who it's clear to?
Well, I guess that's up to whoever it's clear to and who it's not.
But it's really simple, folks.
One of the simplest maxims is food, clothing, shelter and find out what the
soul, the spirit and the body is.
I'll just keep plugging that away.
And it all ties back together.
You know, you think you're a filter bag.
Now, calories matter, don't they?
Huh?
The definition of a calorie, by the way, is, you know, the amount of heat given
off in a certain thermal unit.
Versus the amount that's being tested, you know, in weight compared to how
much heat it takes to raise given amount of water, one degree.
That's basically OK.
That's the definition of it without using too many technical terms.
So when that experiment is given and in order to determine the caloric value,
it is carbonized, is burned until it can't burn anymore.
So if you eat a piece of toast or a banana or whatever, when you pass it
through the body, is it charcoal briquette?
Or is it, you see, so what do calories have to do with food?
And vitamins and all this other stuff, what do you where you how come your
references are so screwed up?
Could it be because you are?
Well, I mean, you not meaning you, but, you know, I'm not talking about the
furry animal called you.
Yeah, well, they're accommodating you.
It's very, very, very simple.
Now, it's easy to sound rantish about this, but how about discussing the
simplicity of it?
Right. You don't even know how the body works.
Now, you have these idiots called doctors or whatever.
They're entitled classes and they're very stupid, by the way.
I mean, because, OK, here's the thing.
I recently did an experiment more than once.
And fortunately, I try to avoid this type.
They're called academics, people with degrees.
And I'm not saying you should, but I do.
I avoid them.
And with anyone, any one of them just have a discussion, discussion regarding
information and education and just bring up that anyone with more than an eighth
grade education has almost irreparable damage done to them by the system, whether
it's private or public school.
And they always agree.
The academics always agree.
And I'm talking about the Ph.D.
professor types.
And they say, yes, that's true.
And the idiot just didn't realize that they have double that and they haven't
noticed. I mean, it's amazing what people will say.
Now, I'm not saying the lawyer, these morons, a lawyer, meaning, you know,
attorneys like, for example, here, let's just get a little bit into legal
society, because people still are and rightfully so afraid of them.
And you should be to a certain degree if you encounter them, because if just
like if you're a hunter in the forest and you see a big grizzly bear, there's a
sense of fear because they're not there to be your friend.
But what the attorneys do is they don't don't know, especially bar members, they
know nothing about law.
I assure you that because if they did and they spoke about it, which usually they
do when they find out because they're so excited, they get disbarred across the
board. Now, there might be some of them that do know some law, but they don't
talk about it or exhibit it because, again, they will lose their position
because they are actually boots on the ground representation of the malevolent
spirits that are ruling the earth, meaning all of your religions.
Yes, all of them, some of them, all of your sciences, all of your arts, right?
All of your medicine is ruled by malevolent inspiration.
Now, in order to pull it off, they have to appear as benevolent.
Because it is quite well known that if you consider yourself human or man or
woman or however surface dwelling earth inhabitant, you're easily deceived and
easily accept the prank.
This has been going on.
It's almost it's been going on for so long that it's inherent within the
quality of the species at this point.
Now, why am I bringing this up?
Because if you showed up, your job is done.
But at the same time, you need food, clothing and shelter.
Now, most of the time, people engage in what's called commercial activity
commerce. I need a job or I need to buy stuff or whatever.
The entire world is pretty much under a credit based economy.
And yes, some people like to hear more.
Some people hear it and they don't know what's being said.
That's fine because you have the censorship against certain information is
very, very thick. But if you realize that there is no debt.
Now, if you have someone emphatically suggesting because all they could do is
they can't prove it. Notice I didn't say speaking, whatever they're suggesting
that it's all based on debt, which is a perception at this point, because no
material substance lawful or even unlawful has been exchanged.
That is the mark of a moron with a capital R and it doesn't matter who they
are. This is explicit in terms of the description of the people and what is
going on on this planet right now.
Now, of course, the concept of debt within a credit based economy can only
be hatched and propagated by the legal society, of course.
So there's many, many.
And by the way, when I say legal side, I mean, these are the head pranksters
and then it's the medical society and, of course, the academic society, because
that's where the pranks are structured, packaged and distributed from all
meaning in your within your social, tangible realm, discussing the
entities, let's say, behind it.
What inspiration means is coming from out there somewhere.
Right. So for many, many aspects, if you're here, you're already done.
You've showed up. You've done everything.
OK, so now in terms of the from a cosmic point of view.
So what do you do while you're here?
Because, you know, you're susceptible to being pranked pretty much every day of
your life. And it starts when you're an infant by the parents.
Now, it's very rare that parents don't prank the children.
You know, basically tell them something that's untrue deliberately.
Now, I don't mean like they don't know.
And because they don't know, they're just saying what they know, which is what
they don't know about.
I'm talking about deliberately pranking the children, for example, here.
Fortunately, it's tapered down right now a little bit, but there's a lot of talk
about vaccines and being mandatory.
And I'm like, oh, wait a second. If you read the codes and laws, you have to be
part of the administration or whatever.
You know, you don't want to talk about law in public because it really is scary.
What's what is memorialized and documented in terms of code, statutes and
laws that are written by men, for example, are almost not known by anyone, even
though anyone can access them.
Again, don't don't try to make sense of crazy people.
But for example, the vaccines came up quite a while and I'm like, oh, wait a
second. Why is vaccine vaccination in the child an issue?
Well, I went to the doctor and he said, I have to vaccinate the law.
Well, you go to a doctor.
What did the child fall off a roof or get hit by a car?
Do you have an emergency?
Why are you going to them?
Because they have not evaluated what they're doing, see, or they can't go to
school to get a vaccine.
You mean you mean you're sending the child to school?
The vaccines are not the problem.
Oh, boy, do you see the point?
It's so simple.
I mean, the idiocy is just to reach the point.
Well, here's the thing.
It's not this is not a rant, it might sound like a rant to the unaware,
obviously, but it's just a discussion or maybe I'm just talking at you because no
one's called in yet.
So here's the thing.
Well, there are many things, of course, but the level of pranking, the level of
malevancy and all these things that are packaged as being good or the way we do
things need to be discerned by those that are able to discern them.
And you can't go out and change it because it's not there for you.
Once you figure out it's a prank or malevolent, you get it.
You see, when you don't know that it's a prank and you don't know that it's
malevolent and you don't know that it's a lie, you think it's directed at you.
And it is.
So is there's a voluntary aspect to this somewhat, I would say, but do you really
have a choice?
You know, again, there's something called cosmic censorship that is filtering
pretty much everyone, but it's not difficult to look through it once you're
made aware of it to a certain degree.
Now, it's possible to ponder these things on your own.
But anyway, so if you're here, you've accomplished the place marker, you mean
the number, you know, like the World Bank, you know, is the one that keeps the
stats allegedly and how many people are on the planet, seven and a half billion,
they say, whatever, right?
Why is it the World Bank?
You know, because the credit system, everyone, you know, it's like if you go
and you want to figure out how many people are in a casino, well, it's the
cashier. And that part needs to know how many people are out there because of the
chips, you know, but well, OK, so the various aspects of it are very simple.
Why are you going to stress things, be worried about things?
For example, some recall ancient writ says, don't worry about anything, of
course. Think about it for a moment.
Why would you worry if you've already taken place, your highest achievement in
life, which is showing up on this miserable society and miserable condition right now
has been taken place and done the rest of just filler.
And it could be wonderful filler.
It could be just blah, blank filler like most people, or it could be real torturous,
arduous and tormenting filler.
That's what we're talking about, the events known as life.
So once you're aware of pretty much everything around you is set up to either
prank you or deceive you just to take up your time.
And if you fall for it or let's say if you're going with it, accepting it or don't
know, it's still OK.
But if you do know what's going on, it makes life a little more adventurous, doesn't
it? All right, think about it.
You ever hear someone say I'm bored?
Well, I always suggest could think about it this way.
Could boredom be a form of anger?
Can it? Well, all right, something to ponder.
But how can you be bored?
You know, you have a lot of choices, but you also have to determine the position that
you are. You know, you're in this, you know, plastic is great, by the way, you wrap
yourself in plastic, someone throws dog poo at you, you just peel the plastic off.
It's you see, insulation can be good.
Distance can be good.
Certain things have a range, and if you're beyond the range, you might be in the
clear. So it is quite interesting to see things from a very basic, almost like a
maxim. A maxim is something that is not discussed, doesn't have to be written.
People know it like don't harm.
Right. You can't be a borrower and a lender at the same time.
You know, all the stuff that the legal society, medical society tells you is real is
anti-maxim positions kind of.
But it doesn't make sense.
And there's a certain fear that underlying fear people have simply tried to define
fear as a weak spirit or a weak mind combined with lack of skill.
You know, so when you hear a lot of this again on this what's called alternative
radio, and I think it's everywhere, sort of the private discussions that have been
done in cafes on the streets and within bedrooms and closets and living rooms or
wherever have now reached a proportion or a level where you have what's called
Internet radio podcasts and the like.
And people start voicing and littering the entire population with just more of the
same. Inaccurate, loosely fitting and less than paper thin.
So what is one to do?
Well, you have a lot of choices.
First suggestion would be don't worry if you're here.
Yeah. If you're and you're conscious to whatever degree you've accomplished most
of the purpose while you're here and the rest of it, you'll get over it, man.
Think about it. That's really, really simple, isn't it?
There are things in place that are lawful that you might find lawful in certain
cultures and certain societies.
I think every society tends to have the concept of lawfulness or whatever.
You have things known as inheritance to a certain degree.
You have things known as a family unit to a certain degree or a social unit based on
religion and other similarities.
Yeah, that's fine. You know, all these things are here in place.
So your movements on this in this world world is the way the society structure has
nothing to do with the Earth or the planet.
If by the way, if everyone was put on a big mothership and taken and just floating
out in space, that's still the world.
And just the planet is just barren, you see, just man's society on Earth.
But you have all of these things put in place for thousands of years that you can
choose from. Now, here's the other thing, folks.
I've noticed this by listening to people and watching them and also watching what
they watch and what they listen to.
And if you were to walk away with an outline of it in terms of placement in
history or time, the morons in this planet right now think that everything was
created about 100 to 150 years ago.
Now, obviously, if you ask them, they will know they won't say that, but their
behavior and their perception of information and agreement and acceptance of
information around them is definitely so.
And they're not asking any questions about anything or you get some ridiculous
stuff like, oh, this civilization was around 70,000 years ago, what does it
matter? Or diners around 60 million years ago, or you want to hear a real
ridiculous thing about time or really ridiculous.
They're God created everything 6,000 years ago.
That's the creationist crap that they want to put in school.
By the way, there's certain places in the world that want to start teaching
creation. Well, listen, if you knew enough about creation to teach it, you
wouldn't be here. Think about it.
This is idiocy.
And this is just to bring it up in terms of time, the evolutionists and the
creationists are both wrong.
And you don't even have to go outside to prove it.
Just look at what they're saying, what they're referencing.
So anyway, who wants to explain the insane?
Does it take an insane mind to explain the insane?
No, I wouldn't say so.
Right, because it doesn't.
There are a couple of idiots that sometimes get around, they have like a
certain group or following or whatever, like it takes one to know one.
I'm like, not really, because if you got a horse and he's sick, do you need
another horse to tell you what's wrong with him?
No, take him to a vet, someone who's competent.
You always have to see things from a human perspective because that's all you
got. Once you got one of those fish eyeball cameras, those are fun to look at
or, you know, photos kind of warp everything around.
They call it a fish eye.
Who knows what a fish sees?
Have you ever asked him? You can get through to him or her.
So the point here is that there is no point.
The thing is, are you taking time to not worry and to not be pranked and to not
fall for the deception?
No, probably not, because you're probably working on what's called heresy.
Heresy is just a Greek word that means what you like.
Like, for example, if you went with a bunch of friends to an ice cream shop and
they were to ask you, like, what flavor do you like?
It's like, well, what what is your heresy?
Right. Heresy means what you like, personal, personally, subjective liking.
So and then I've also mentioned this before.
And then you have this thing being brought up, a cliche.
Well, you know, Hades, you're going to Hades.
You know, people think it's hell or something like that word just means
emptiness.
So if the ice cream store was empty, you couldn't get your heresy because it was
Hades.
Are we communicating here?
Probably not. That's fine.
Do you see how the technological aspects of communication known as language and
words have been abandoned?
What hasn't been abandoned?
Now, there's going to be a discovery of things that's coming in the near future.
And these things are just going to be part of the setup, of course.
But it's going to be more interesting and more interesting.
And I just wanted to bring up for those that are paying attention to some degree.
Have you ever noticed that whether you're turning on the television, Internet,
newspaper, university, that people are getting dumber, not dumber, but are doing
stupid things and saying stupid things and being irrational?
For example, this week, I was kind of going around a little bit, these news
agencies and such.
And the stuff that they're reporting on is just really, really, really.
Yeah, you guessed it. It's a dummy load.
So I'm thinking in the future to offer a dummy load filter.
And it goes in between the device that you're using.
It's visual and audio.
And we tested it recently and I had someone spend about 10 hours on the Internet.
And they said, I don't think it works because every time, every time I try to hear
something, I didn't hear anything at all.
And I said, well, that's right. It works just fine.
It's a dummy load filter.
Anyway, you get it.
So if you want to be dummy loaded, you can.
Dummy load is just a technical term, meaning putting a load on something to test it
and see if you can handle it before you put it into its proper use.
So by the way, let's just see.
We're about 40 minutes into this sonic event.
And oh, good.
Now I know the meaning of life.
That's a load off my mind.
Yeah, I'm just reading something out of chat here.
OK, well, that's brilliant.
I don't know about that, but that's fine.
Is that brilliant?
Is it like a 20 watt light bulb in total pitch dark?
Because that'll be real bright.
Or is it a thousand watt light bulb during the day?
So anyway, there's many things to consider.
So but the thing to consider is this.
There are disciplines out there, by the way, folks.
There's a lot of discipline that's been put.
Like one discipline is martial arts.
And, you know, unfortunately, when you say that, it goes.
People are like, oh, Bruce Lee, you know, the Asian karate, Aikido.
Well, every society, every culture had that form of discipline.
It's just that you don't know about it.
You know, have you ever heard of Pankration?
That would have been known in the ancient world by the Greeks.
Yeah. Capoeira in Brazil today.
You have very various disciplines and they're not just for fighting folks.
It's how to move the body in within the medium
known as the air and solid material and maybe greeting space
heaters with it sometimes.
So these disciplines that have been put out discern those as well.
There are disciplines that help one move the body with
economy of movement, let's just say.
So you're more efficient.
I would suggest learning some disciplines, whether they are,
you know, this is the physical side, of course.
But when you get into what's called martial arts of various disciplines,
even a sport would be a discipline.
You notice that it also is not purely physical,
that it has to do with the mind or the spirit.
It's not a discipline, like, for example, even, let's say,
bodybuilding or powerlifting, where you have a limited movement.
But even there, there's technique.
So the aspect of gaining a discipline
while you're here makes life a lot easier.
It can and it should, especially even if you're not doing it properly.
You're aware that there is more of a proper way to do things.
Or let's say if you're not good at it, you're aware that something takes skill.
That's the other thing.
If people tend to shy away with things that they find that they do not have
a natural talent to gravitate towards or excel in,
the most common one that you hear spiritually or mentally is I'm not good at math.
Now, maybe we should do some quick math primers one day.
But what will happen is even if you encounter a particular discipline
that you may not have, quote unquote, personal interest or find that you're good at
or whatever, whatever, whatever, at least you realize
that there is a higher form to it that you may not want to partake or just can't do.
So it gives you a little bit more of an appreciation of what you can do.
So when you are accepting a discipline and you're doing well with it,
well, then you might say, hey, this is this is a sign that I am getting
a little bit closer to finding, let's say, what's called a natural calling.
Yeah. So having appreciation for what you don't find a liking to or not good at
will lead you to more appreciate what you are good at.
You know. Now, by the way, whenever a suggestion is given to anyone,
and I just want to say this because the old people are just you suck.
Sorry about that. You do.
I feel bad for the younger people.
But whenever you're giving suggestions, you have to consider,
you know, who you're speaking to and where you are and is it appropriate.
Now, I wouldn't say this is really appropriate.
It's a public venue. It's a minor Internet platform.
It's an uncommon radio. I mean, what does that have to do?
You know, it doesn't mean much, does it?
But at least it's being said.
I know you're not getting much anywhere else and I don't even have to look anymore.
I stopped looking. You know, I mean, like if you spend a couple,
you know, a couple of years or so with horses and you haven't seen a horse in 20
years, you don't have to know that it's still going to want to eat.
Pee and poop while it's standing up and what it looks like and what it does.
Horses haven't changed much. People haven't changed much.
Your information streams haven't changed much.
Your academic streams haven't changed much.
Your religious streams haven't changed much.
Your legal streams haven't changed much.
Governmental streams get it.
Medical streams. It's all the same.
You don't have to stay.
You don't have to stay and listen and see what's going on today or what medical
development or what the government's going to do or what the legal society
is going to do or the scientific society, religious society.
It's all the same, slightly rehashed.
So, yeah, there's been no surprises there.
Yeah, you might get a little surprise, something out of place.
You know, things do happen.
You know, things do shock people or whatever.
And by the way, speaking of shocking people, it's still around springtime on the,
let's say, the latitude that's considered the central part of the earth.
You know, of course, the friends down below, down under and other places like that,
they're experiencing colder weather.
Well, it's too bad.
So, but you're up here where it's still springtime.
What's spring about?
Mostly quiet.
Planting.
There's a little bit of noise when they're planting.
You don't see a lot of growth yet, but things are planted to grow in summer and
harvested in the fall.
By the way, I just want to throw this in there.
If you guys know anything about the corporate culture, if you know anyone, you
know, that might be in the corporate culture, even you could do research on your
own.
Isn't it interesting that typically, not always, but most typically CEOs of
corporations or let's say let go or their contracts terminate around the fall and
they're typically hired around the springtime.
Yeah.
Think about that.
You'll start noticing things like that.
Especially things that matter.
Why?
Because things that are planted in the spring tend to matter more because
agriculture works that way and you're agriculturally based.
Like for example, if you think about water, you know, it's when you're thirsty
or you want to wash, hopefully you do, and other things like that.
But when you're a fish, water has a different meaning to you, doesn't it?
Because it's the ambient environment you partake in.
And by the way, I just want to throw this out there because I've been known a
little bit to know a little bit about water.
And you know, fish drink water also.
Yeah, Greek, you're funny.
Yeah, fish drink water.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah, they do.
Just because they're in the water doesn't mean they're drinking water.
I mean, having it pass through their body for nourishment, you know, to reproduce
the water inside the body because when you drink water, it doesn't get absorbed.
But anyway, there was something, if you look at some previous sonic events, I
did one called The Container.
I think it was the second one.
I might get into that again in a future project that is being put together.
But yeah, fish drink water.
So when poison, when let's say a lake is poisoned or a river is poisoned or an
aquarium, you'll notice that not all the fish die right away.
Well, it's the ones that were thirsty that died first.
You know, ones that are just swimming around, not in taking it through certain
parts of the body, tend to last a little longer.
Yeah, because fish get thirsty too.
So yeah, what a concept.
So I just wanted to, there's not much to hint anymore other than suggesting when
the time is right, there is a new project that has been going on.
It will be in the form of a podcast.
You will not have the allure and the mysticism and the excitement of live
radio as you do right now, even though there's only five people listening.
It will be informational.
It will be very much more in depth.
It will be solo most likely if there's anyone that would like to pair and do a
sonic event with the Greek in the future, let me know.
We can arrange that.
And there will be things spoken of more in depth and you'll have to access it
somehow and it might be expensive.
So just letting you know up ahead, it's not going to be cheap.
It's not just to filter out the riffraff.
It's just because it's worth a lot.
And for quote unquote, for every credit you give, you'll get ten times back
worth in information and at least in whatever you consider to be valuable.
Hopefully you will find it as valuable as it is and to come with an objective mind.
So there's not much to hint at that's been hinted at before and until it's
finally ready, the only thing I would suggest is stay abreast on the Uncommon
Radio site for the Greek.
It's www.uncommonradio.com and that will let you know where more stuff is coming
around because there is a lot to discuss and there is a lot to think about and
there's a lot to think about and discuss that will actually help you.
Yes, concepts about water, not only concepts, but what is water?
How does it work?
Well, you know, people don't know what water is when they're putting it in flat
bottom containers and in the light and at room temperature, obviously, you don't
have to ask usually, well, sometimes you do, but usually, especially through
industry or commerce or in the crowd, what they know.
They typically exhibit it through their behavior and their wares.
So if you are in a society and you see, for example, water or fluids that are to
be taken by the body or considered important fluids in flat bottom
containers that are exposed to the light at room temperature, typically, that
society does not understand the purpose of fluids in biology.
That's quite simple.
Now you can go to a university idiot, meaning the professors and morons there
and the scientists and all that, and they will show you reams and volumes of just
rubbish to talk about things that have nothing to do.
With reality, and they still can't explain it, obviously.
Right.
So you just look around, things like that.
You talk to someone in the medical society, you know, they don't know what
they're doing.
If you spend, let's say you want a particular thing done, a process, a
procedure with someone in the medical society, go research right now.
What's great about the internet is you might get a little bit of access to what
they did when in their, let's say, consider part of their training.
And you look at the proper way to do that procedure and then approach this
medical moron about the procedure.
And he'll say, well, I know about which, yeah, that's interesting that you know
about that.
I haven't really, I haven't heard about that since I was in college.
No, wait a second.
How many of these procedures have you done in the last 20 years?
And you're not sure about what's going on here.
It goes on and on and on in every field.
Now, by the way, in private more than public, I'll be crashing the religious
societies also.
They, they're the worst, um, see, because the, well, the legal society ties
into it also, cause they're representing a God known as justice, but the medical
society, uh, and all these other societies or whatever, they're, they're
not claiming to represent any of the gods.
And they're, they've really screwed up big time.
The religious societies, because they stepped in, um, a really, really, really
high level of responsibility.
Not, not the way people think about it, because the common idiot on this planet,
you know, that when they say religion, um, it's just a box that they check on a
form, like, you know, a form of you, male, female, you know, how to, what color
your eyes, what religion is check a box.
Yeah.
I'm this, you know, and forget about what they profess.
You just watch what they do.
But, uh, crashing the religious societies, um, is going to be a lot of fun.
Um, informationally, informationally and the contrast I've done this before
in previous sonic events, if anyone wants to consider, for example, um, uh,
any of any religion at all, uh, you're, you will find that, uh, typically they
have a text that they subscribe to or alleged to subscribe to that is the
basis that they're in that holy writ that they have there in contains and
memorializes the purpose of their quote unquote faith, right?
This is what they say with their mouth.
Okay.
And that's all.
And, and you go look into it a little bit, right?
Just a little, not much.
And you will see that they know nothing or do anything that is in there
that is on the positive side.
Actually, very often I've said, I'm not really, this is not a correction, but
there's not a religion on the planet that does or knows anything in the text
that they allegedly subscribe to.
That is not exactly wholly true.
And I mean that from an optimistic perspective, because what they are
actually doing is in the don't do or the abominations, the things that the
gods find repugnant is what these religions are doing according to their,
each to each one of their, uh, let's say relative, uh, text.
So, so those are going to be very, very simple to, to go through.
But the thing is, um, why do that?
Because it's going to give people a good preface on what's coming in the future.
Um, and I think I've mentioned this before that, uh, the gods are surely
going to tear down and piss on everything that you consider sacred or believe in
or think about it, because what the majority of the people have as their
faith, quote unquote, and they actually kill other people for it.
This is, you can get into that, why, how that's been done.
Um, yeah, they will kill other people.
As you see, it doesn't matter that, you know, it's a cross versus cross, uh,
Muslim versus Muslim, Buddhist versus Buddhist.
They do it because that's just the way people are there.
They have legitimized savagery.
But when you go through the aspects of, uh, what is going on from a religious
perspective, there's only one way, only one description, uh, to give on why this
is happening, the way it's happening is because again, the world is under a, uh,
very heavily malevolent control.
And in order to be successful as a malevolent, you must present yourself as
being benevolent every time you get away from the Hollywood mentality, get away
from all this stuff that you've been told because really bad people don't
look like really bad people.
I mean, you know, I mean, if they do, they don't last very long.
Right.
So, and when I am saying that on a very base level, um, uh, you know, can you
say that people are bad?
No, but can you say that they're good?
Definitely not.
You see?
So again, this, this is not clear cut, but we have just a few more minutes
before the end of this first hour.
Uh, I appreciate anyone who's listening.
Uh, let's see in the chat, we have just a handful and maybe we'll have
another handful for the second hour.
We will see you after the break folks.
So, uh, I just want to, uh, just the first hour is got a comment.
Oh, you're a little scattered or whatever, but you know, welcome to the world.
Uh, how can you say everything at the same time?
But, uh, you know, one thing that I do mention, uh, coming on is Colin Skype
in right in, uh, try to look at the chat.
Um, but I just want to, uh, also give a little bit more of a hint of what
will be discussed in the future because the mindset of the people that are
communicating, uh, through emails and other messaging, uh, has been all very
much in common now, now I just wanted to, they very uncommon, but the theme
seems to be the same and I'm going to read this, um, Email, uh, anonymously.
And, and it, it, it's going to reflect, I'd say 90%, if not a hundred percent
of the emails, uh, that are gotten.
And this is going to be the direction, which I believe, uh, uh, it will be.
Future presentations should go into, because again, when I think Sarah Vaughn
was asked, uh, what makes a great jazz musician?
She said, it's the audience now not looking to be great or anything, but
you must accommodate the listener.
It, you know, you must accommodate who you are serving to some extent.
So here's the email.
Um, this was sent, uh, roughly four or five days ago.
Uh, so it starts like this.
Uh, what have Leviticus nine 1926 Greek, and that's an old caps.
Uh, does it make steakhouses and local weather news off limits?
What's the actual translation there.
Also, can you speak about the ethnicities in relation to sons of the Elohim,
daughters of Adam and the Nephilim?
Is there a relationship?
Why is there so much black hair on the planet?
Who was Quasi Quattro really?
Why are Mormons obsessed with ancestry?
You said the leaders were changed at a certain time.
What will they change into from your description?
One of the kill shots sounds like a pyramid, which fits
scripture as a mountain.
But what about the millstone?
If I comprehend you correctly, when ingesting the body is actually
being told to create whatever is in the food, drug, et cetera.
And in all caps, that is paradigm shifting, exclamation, exclamation,
exclamation.
Could the body be tricked into making things?
Sorry about the 20 questions, but asking you shall receive my reply
simply to that was received some, but most people just need a little
direction, essentially.
So that's basically the a good representative sample of what has
been, let's say, invoked or jostled in the minds of people.
And you notice there's a there's an underlying thing theme there.
It's sort of, quote, unquote, religious, and of a certain rate.
It's sort of social in a way, and it's also has to do with the physical body.
These things are all very real, by the way.
And the reason why I read it, because it was written in a certain with
certain sense of enthusiasm and excitement.
And some do get that when they hear things that they haven't heard before,
but not just like that, because look, you can hear bullshit you've never
heard before all the time.
This is a different way.
Now, one of the comments here within, you know, is that is paradigm
shifting?
Well, is it really?
Or does it actually completely negate the paradigm that has been put in
everyone's mind?
And it's not just for the series of negating or just being contra or against
because that's actually satanic.
The term satanic means to be adversarial.
Key here is not to be adversarial.
The key here is just to get some keys because it seems like there are doors
everywhere that people are sleeping at, if you get what I mean.
So the the paradigm here again, just to bring this up again, the paradigm
shifting is not going to shift.
The paradigm is winding down and going away, but no one's going to notice.
Now, what I mean by that is let's just look at secular history for a moment.
20th century, perhaps anyone remember that?
You know, it's around the time everything that you think about was created.
You know, typically, if you look at some of the events all the way up to 9-11,
for example, and the absurdities before that, you know, you had a president, a
major event, American president was assassinated.
9-11 would be the two main things you had, what's dubbed as World War Two, which
is not what you think it is.
For example, this aspect of being in industrial society, then leading to
information based and all that.
Uh-huh.
So there's a mindset that's been put behind there that hasn't really
been followed through, has it?
You know, what paradigms have been set other than some of these
shocking, let's say, historical milestones, which, by the way, regarding
the assassination of a president and what supposedly happened on 7-11, as
someone once said, which is because septem means seven, and I just want to
give a shout out to, I think it's Master Lewis out there for that.
It's very rare.
Yes.
It's very rare that you engage human, surface-dwelling earth inhabitants in
conversation and find one, just one, that is aware of something, just one thing.
It's very rare.
They all tend to go with the flow, but I was in a conversation once and he says,
well, 9-11 is really 7-11.
I said, really?
Why do you say that?
Because September is the seventh month.
It means that.
I said, wow, that is really cool.
So, but even if you go from an event like that, the major assassinations
and the explanations or descriptions that were given are completely absurd.
If you look at the fashion trends and what you might call industrial trends,
technological trends, absurdities, again, you know, what they're doing
is repackaging, rehashing.
By the way, when it comes to anything geopolitical, you have to lie to the
people, I'm sorry, you know, meaning from their perspective, the mainstream
quote-unquote establishment, regardless if it's a religious, scientific,
medical, political, governmental, whatever, you cannot tell people the truth.
Why?
Think about it.
Well, of course you got to keep the masses asleep.
Well, you don't have to keep them asleep because they'll do that fine on their own.
First hour discussed that your job is pretty much done just by showing up.
When you show up, you've done 90%.
The last thing you want to do is disturb the people.
But the thing that is disturbing about how some of these major events are
explained, which is minimal, they like it showing a lot of descriptions,
but no explanations.
What's really disturbing is they seem to counteract all the other aspects of
their sciences and medicine when they explain them, which is proof positive
that this is a society of morons.
But when you spell moron, you got to put, you got to capitalize the R somehow,
figure it out.
It could, anyway, you get the point.
Now, how else can anyone explain simply what you're doing here?
I'm talking about simply, can you prove otherwise?
No, very difficult to.
Now, the paradigms that you see that were established now, you're pretty much, you
consider roughly the computer monitor shows here roughly 17 years past the year
2000 or so.
I'd say you're about 20% civil, 17% into the next century.
And you're still just dragging along and rehashing all the same old crap over and
over and over.
Yeah, of course.
You got a bunch of people making noise.
Oh yeah.
Mainstream's bad.
They got fake news or the doctors don't know what they're doing when they say,
yeah, really, really?
That's just a little bit of a complaint, but not much is changing and it won't.
Here's an example.
I was in a conversation recently with someone who works in industry and they think
they're cutting edge.
And I said, what you have now is what you're going to get.
You're not going to get any jet packs or a hotel on the moon or any miraculous stuff.
This is what you need to do.
Yes, you need to do is figure out what is available and make it hyper efficient, not
just efficient or super efficient, but hyper efficient and function.
So you have less waste.
And by the way, have you ever heard of, for example, when a new product or
technologies put out, they call it a miracle of science.
They call it, Oh, this is miraculous.
This is a fantastic, um, whatever.
Right?
Well, you know what?
There's a lot of truth in that.
Why do you say that?
Well, have you ever met anyone that works or more than one person that works or
manages what's called a government research lab or a corporate research lab?
Now, do you want to tie that back with it?
If you've got more than an eighth grade education, you've got irreparable damage.
Uh-huh.
And he actually, someone with a PhD will agree to that.
And they've got double because these are all of these labs and developmental,
whether it's medical, even the social engineering aspect of it, scientific,
technical, or whatever, even religious, because they were hatching new ways to,
to reform your, the religions that everyone buys into.
These people are morons.
And speaking from firsthand experience, meeting people that work within these
institutions and the cutting edge, just like, for example, if you've ever heard
anyone ask about CERN, I remember being aware of CERN before they started building
that, I said, there's no way these idiots are going to build this.
This is just like, you know, the, you know, the elevator is space or whatever
that they're not going to build because it just doesn't work.
Now what's interesting is when I saw when they built it, I was like, Oh,
that's, that's completely out of control.
Because that's just like pimp my ride.
That's like taking a $200 car.
That's ready for the junkyard and putting in a hundred grand to make it whatever
that is just, and also is to show you that we have access to the credit
system and you don't mother efforts, right?
Basically they're like CERN is like about as ghetto ghetto can get on a planetary
level when I mean ghetto, I mean, in the colloquial term, just like, you know,
another colloquial term that is like redneck, you know, they got all these
pejorative terms of something that just is out of place or overdone.
CERN is just pimp my ride, ghetto in your face, sucka.
We could do whatever we want.
Yeah.
It's junk.
Now here's the interesting part.
I've always been telling people that's total rubbish.
And, and of course that's a really good filter, uh, to look at the who is
and how CERN is being commented on.
And, and by the way, I could back up every aspect of what I'm saying, but I'm not
going to do it cause it's not even worth it.
Um, but there actually have been people that have been have firsthand experience
since her and I don't that have come out and said, this is all fraud.
And obviously, you know, I've just told, I just pretty much gave you a very, very
deep rooted, truthful explanation of what's going on there, right?
This is what you're going to be subjected to until you're not.
So there's a very interesting way to filter out what is going on in people's
minds by looking at how they comment and what they're commenting on and how they're
calm and how significant it is to them.
So for example, if you are in a discussion when they bring up CERN and
they, so the, the, the more, it's amazing how creative these people get.
I mean, these people meeting on this planet.
Oh, they say they're trying to open a portal.
Oh, they're trying to do this.
None of it's just a piece of junk.
It's not going to do anything other than, you know, whatever you want it to do.
I guess.
And you could look at how seriously people take this.
I mean, there's people that do, you know, host a guest and I mean, the
absurdity is just beyond whatever.
Right.
So this is what you have access to, by the way.
You know, when you, when you go on the internet and, or in print or whatever,
start discerning what, not who and how it's being spoken of, but what
really is being spoken of the, do you folks remember all the asteroids and
the, and the government crackdowns and social chaos that was supposed to
ensue from 2012 on or before, you know, what happened to that?
Yeah.
You guessed it right.
Because it's very, very simple folks.
It's very, very simple.
Um, when you look at anything, it tends, that's circular or cyclical.
It tends to end up terminating where it began.
Yeah.
And if you've heard any Greek speak before, you know what I'm going to say,
but I'm not going to say it this time.
So it's very, very simple.
It's about being efficient.
And, and again, I read the email to bring up the mindset.
Um, these people are listening.
Uh, there are, um, there, there are pursuits that people are beginning to
discover that, excuse me, that are worth taking that are uncommon.
Well, hence, hence forth.
That's what it's called uncommon radio.
In a sense, um, uncommon, but edifying and satisfying, um, who doesn't want
to know how the body really works.
And, and just to go back to the email, this, cause this was an interesting
perspective, you know, uh, that means that the body can, can be made to create things.
Yes.
That that's exactly correct.
And that's exactly what's going on.
And you don't realize it because you have, um, covered that ability to perceive that
or, or, and actually, well, how are you going to perceive it if you've never been
told, but nonetheless, you, you, you're not aware of it cause you, you, you just
blanket it over with the stuff that you are a filter bag and you absorb things
and whatever.
So how are you going to, well, what does that mean?
You have to take time and actually observe what's happening now in science.
Um, they're supposed to do that.
They're supposed to have a theory and a hypothesis and experiment and conclusion,
but they only talk about theory because it's a prank.
Remember the eighth grade?
Well, anyway, you get the point, you know, uh, if you, so, so the point, the point
is, how do you start perceiving what is happening around you objectively?
How can you really see what's going on?
I mean, back to the body.
I started off with this tonight.
Uh, when you, the skin being a soft membrane, when it's soaked in water, we
tend to notice that it shrivels up.
Well, that means that there is a slight vacuum on the backside of it or on the
inside.
How come, um, everyone, I say everyone, well, actually I don't know anyone called
everyone, never met anyone called everyone.
So let's not use that.
Statistically, most people will ignore that.
Why is that?
Why is, why is it that everyone, again, why is it that the majority of the people
on the planet are ignoring, uh, what they can perceive objectively?
Think about it.
So if, if the society at large and the majority of the people are ignoring, uh,
their own perceptions, you know, and this is not just being deceived by your
perception, like a lady being sawed in half on, on stage and put back together.
And you swear that you saw that.
No, it's not talking about that.
Start with the body itself, right?
What's the purpose of sleep?
What's the purpose of all these other things?
What do you notice is going on?
How come there is no rational discussion or objective
discussion about that at all?
Right.
You've given up your ability to rationalize that and utilize any.
Power through knowledge of that.
You've given it all up to the entitled classes.
Now, if that is not laziness, I don't know what can be considered laziness.
The same with law, the same with your spirituality, meaning your mentality.
Um, by the way, I was looking at something, um, and what category, a category,
let's say, and it was religion and spirituality.
That was actually the proper way to say that it was religion and mentality
because spirituality is mentality.
You know, spirit psyche means the mind get it.
That's why psychiatrists have to do with the mind.
Psychologists do with the mind.
PSY prefix, right.
That has to, well, anyway, you get the point.
Um, so what is going on here?
Uh, what is going on on the surface of the planet?
Well, the same thing that's been going on for a very long time, very long time.
And that is going to change.
It is only going to change because objectivity and acknowledgement of certain
things is going to be required in the future.
Now, when I say the future, it is not a future that will be continuing as, as you
folks are right now, because if, if it was uninterrupted, there would be no,
nothing left in less than 50 years.
That's a fact.
Now, how, how was it a fact?
Well, let's just say, let's discuss it after that point.
Now, why?
Because it has a lot to do with what's called religion.
What is religion?
Something you do regularly.
So if one says, you know, this is about religion, it means something you do
regularly, you get it.
So this, this thing that people have just marked on a government form or whatever,
oh, I'm this, I'm Christian or Muslim or Jewish, or I'm Mormon, or I'm this,
I'm a Buddhist or whatever, that's just a little, they've trivialized that to a
category, just check the box, you know, get to the religion, check this one,
check this one, check and go back to just existing, right?
They don't know what they're doing or what they're saying.
So there's the importance of quote unquote, religion is that it gives you
the laws of which you live by.
It's a system.
It really literally is a systematic process, you know, where you don't have to
make things up.
And also you have the support of others that have a similar religion.
And by the way, what I'm discussing is an objectification of what it means and not
what's in the world right now.
Because what's in the world right now, it's seemingly a society at large has
acknowledged unspokenly that the purpose of being here is just being here.
And it should be obvious if you're looking into depth or looking into mastery of
things.
So back to the religion aspect, there's a, when you do things regularly, like in
certain shokun in Japan, their objective is to do the same thing every day and
become a master at it by doing the same thing every day and seeking high quality.
There is a level of repetition, there's a level of adherence to things that work,
things that have been, if they're important, they've been memorialized
because the lifespan is too short, you know, many generations will come through.
And that is the nature of what's called religion.
Now, earlier, I mentioned why people kill each other over that for a certain
degree, it is not the degree at which it is being used.
The quote unquote religion, when people fight over religion, it is just again,
the Gustave Le Bon aspect, where it's like a crowd has formed and they're
impassioned, they have a lot of energy, and you custom tailor the crowd and the
mindset to do certain things.
And people like killing, they like maiming, they like destruction.
You don't believe that you ever watch what's called Hollywood, right?
You ever watch what's called the news?
You know, you look at what people are concerned about.
Now, there's a lot of that look at their holidays, look at Okay, so what's going
on is typically you have a group of people, it could be a very small group or
a very large group, and you sequester the concept of their mind that has to
deal with a deity or a god now they don't know, that's all you have to do is
separate a part of their mind and have it adhere passionately to a concept of a
deity.
Now, when this is done, you cannot inform them or supply information more about the
gods plural or, or even that particular God, because well, then that leads to a
path of gaining knowledge.
And there's no way you can get them to do what I'm going to describe here.
So what you do then is that you once you see that they're impassioned about this,
you know, the information is it has to be very minimal.
And it doesn't have you don't have to be true, which it's not you can't show me
any religion in the world that has any truth to it, other than the truth that it
is actually a spiritual guidance of sorts, but it's not what they think it is.
Right.
So once once you get these individuals impassioned, you break up the that
impassionment into subgroups, you have the various classes, you know, you might
have one with more training in a certain field than another, and you start
subdividing them, and you give them an even stronger reason in private why this
religion needs to be aggressively promoted.
You see, and again, you have to keep the information to an absolute minimum, you
have to keep it, quote unquote, dummy loaded, no specifics, because once you
start giving specifics, then the individual becomes edified.
And it starts in the individual, then we'll see that there is nothing to do with
what they believe, or told to believe.
So you have to keep it very limited and out of context.
Now, once you have them impassioned about a deity of some sort, whether it exists
or not, is not the point.
Because remember, the information is so minimal, and it's about impassioning the
individual various types, you know, common oath, people that are completely
illiterate, and then like, then you have the ones that are functionally
illiterate, like most people on the planet today just means you know how to
read, but you don't know what anything means.
Then you have the other ones with specific training, like doctors, lawyers,
engineers and scientists, and you keep them all impassioned with minimal
information.
And then you tell them that it's a matter of life and death, and they're going to
get a reward that is that in another place for doing this.
And you need to keep this passion and fervor going with very, very little
information at all.
This is how you do it.
It's like a rabid dog.
And that, on the other hand, this is something that anyone can research, it
might be difficult, but you when you start looking, you'll see that it's true.
That if you can't just do it through the mind with, you know, probate, provoking
them through little bits of information, how what they're doing is so noble, you
do it chemically.
Like, for example, you hear about a lot of these, quote, unquote, especially what
you know, this, this show has been time marked.
It's what they call 2017, April.
So if you look at what's going on in the Middle East, these quote, unquote, people
that are running around shooting up other people of their own kind, let's say, kind
meaning relative, are pretty much all doped up on amphetamines and all kinds of
other stuff and alcohol, whatever.
And yeah, it's pretty ridiculous, because the whole thing is ridiculous.
You know that, for example, if anyone does some history, again, you'll find that
there's something called a uniform that you recognize someone's profession by
visually, it's a community form of communication, that when a woman was
covered, as it as they are considered to be in certain religions, or religion
today, that was the symbol of a particular profession.
Yeah, and you might want to guess what it is, if you mentioned this before.
So the insanity of that, and by the way, covering of any kind like that is not
even suggested in, in the book that they allegedly subscribe to.
And what that profession is, you might find to be shocking.
It's called the oldest profession.
This was the uniform.
And now there is actually a mass demand that it is symbol of righteousness.
So, so, yeah, insanity.
Now, this can be said about any and every religion on the planet at this point.
Meaning, I gave you a definition of religion from the extreme sense of
getting people to promote it through violence, because that is, it sounds extreme.
Now, there's different levels of promotion of various religions.
Now, you have to remember, historically, and academic historians, which are atheists,
by the way, have dubbed this the Christian era.
The, I don't, there's no reason to knock Christianity or criticize Christianity or
not, because, I mean, look, I'm just gonna say a few things and you could figure it
out yourself.
Look, Santa Claus, Easter Bunny, chocolate eggs, Christmas tree.
I mean, you don't have to say anything else.
I mean, that's, it doesn't get worse than that.
But, but on the, from, from the spiritual perspective, but you also have to look at
the character of the individual that defends that.
When you look at people that defend that aspect of, of the, one of the world's
religions, which is known as the Christian era, you will find nothing but a poor
character there.
Now, what I mean by that is they typically will defend that idiocy by saying, it
doesn't matter, and you will get, after about 150, it doesn't matter, then what
the hell does matter, right?
So, and, and also when you hear about these religions, by the way, they discuss
they, what they're doing as being good because that is part of their tradition,
you see?
So, is it bad?
No, but is it good?
Definitely not.
You can't say it's bad because then, you know, how, well, if you did, then you'd
have to get off this planet, you see?
And this goes across the board with everything and anything in, in terms of
what man considers religion.
But one thing that you will find that is interesting about religion, when you say
that term, it's not like when you say legal or medical or film or entertainment
or whatever, because most, when you say religion, typically the mindset goes
right to a god or a demon or a deity of some sort, meaning it's not worldly.
And that's correct about that.
But what's not correct is the way that they comprehend and use the term, and
it's not correct at all.
Because nothing good can come out of it in the strictest and even in the loose
sense, because as I mentioned earlier, Gustav Le Bon's The Crowd, when you
assemble such a group of people together, the information that brings them together
has to be so simplified that it no longer represents its original form.
It's completely corrupt by that, by operation, right?
So the, the way that, quote unquote, religion on the planet through man's
tradition, because, you know, it has to be tradition, right?
That's what they say.
The only way that it could, it could thrive as it has or has not, because some
have not, is strictly by keeping the adherents ignorant of a full scope,
showing them an extremely narrow view, very, very narrow view with very little
information about what's known as the gods, right?
And what you need to do if you're going to influence people in such a negative
way is keep them ignorant of their own stuff.
Because when I, when I say their own stuff, there is no one religion, but they
typically are all under the goddess religion, which I've discussed loosely,
and I will discuss in greater detail in the future.
They're not aware of that at all.
But what I mean about keep them ignorant is that the same level of ignorance you
will find in the, in the, what's called the major world religions today.
The, the practitioner and the adherent must remain ignorant.
That is a, that is a definite requirement.
And when I say this, this includes academia and the quote unquote priesthood.
Now, why is the ignorance very important?
Because when you get knowledge, now you can make better choices, you see?
And also when you get knowledge of all these ancient holy writs, what you will
see is there's a hierarchy in quality, right?
And also what you will see within that hierarchy of qualities,
they're all saying the same thing.
Even the mythology says the same thing.
The psyche, for example, in, in, in, in Greek mythology,
has no consciousness whatsoever in Hades, meaning the spirit after you die.
There's no consciousness at all.
Now, this is not a cartoon type thing where you've probably learned about
Greek mythology from a cartoon or a coloring book or something, some kind of
hearsay, but if you actually look what's been memorialized about it,
mostly by Homer and others, you will see that there is no consciousness after death.
And this is what you will find in any of the ancient writs.
So I'm just giving that as a thin slice, because that shows how they're all similar.
So, so why am I bringing this up now?
Well, it's springtime and springtime is a time to plant things.
So be aware that there's going to be let's say a nonspecific view of in
the forefront of the topic of religion as being a significant,
more significant than it has in the past.
Not necessarily, you know, there's, there's a lot of comment about it.
It's all false.
Obviously, you can see it, you know, if we get a little bit of information.
There's talk about this, talk about that.
You know, the war of the religions or a coming world order religion and all that.
Earlier, like I said, both creationists and evolutionists are wrong.
That's simple to, to prove.
And we'll, we'll give proofs on that in the future presentations.
The same thing holds true for what's being discussed on the future of these
mainstream religions and the aggressions of some and not the others.
But you have to realize that at this point in history, especially at this point of
history, like I mentioned earlier, you ever notice that if you speak to people or
go to internet radio or mainstream or even university, you notice that people
are starting to be seemingly getting dumber or saying things that are stupid.
It's just, it's just getting worse, but incrementally.
What I wanted to throw in earlier, how it gets worse.
You see, today, it's like the frog in the pot.
Today is a little bit worse than yesterday, but
not as bad as it's going to be tomorrow.
Because if it was as bad as it's going to be tomorrow, today, everyone would stop and
say, okay, enough is enough.
This is shocking.
Stop.
Right? But it's, it's just so incremental.
And when you're made aware of the incremental change and
the gradualness of it, then it's, you know, just start raving, you know, clear.
But if you're not aware of it and you're in it, obviously you're in it and
you're of it, you're going to be partaking and exhibiting that quality.
So, I mean, that's why, for example, there's no reason.
The Greek is not a public type person, but
the reason I come around here every week or so now for this,
which is probably going to be limited, this is the eighth solo,
might be just 12 again, or something, is because there is nothing out there.
Sorry, folks, anywhere that has anything that you want to sink your teeth in.
Now, you want to say that as a subjective, personal comment, well,
the Greek doesn't like this, yeah, you can take it that way, but
learn to objectify and you'll see what I just said is true.
There's just nothing there.
I'm talking about, now forget about internet radio, alternative media,
that too, but I mean, even academia.
Your religious institutions, your academic institutions, your scientific,
even I just mentioned the high level labs that you have.
Have you met anyone that works in a research lab of any variety,
whether it's private or government or anything?
No, you probably haven't, right?
Maybe someone has.
They're morons, yo.
Anyway, so there's a reason to come around here and
do this for two hours every week, because you just never know.
And the thing is, there's no movement, there's no following.
Hopefully you have bowel movements and other movements, but
not with anything that's being done here.
Because the suggestion that I would give to anyone is if you've showed up,
you've showed up, you're done.
You've pretty much done your thing cosmically.
Now the rest of it, of course you're going to be directed,
because it's all external input.
You're going to be directed, of course, to partake in the cosmic plan, and
you don't know what it is or what makes it even more elusive, right?
And the other thing is to do nothing, meaning do nothing,
don't start chasing these, I don't know, chasing the wind.
You ever heard of activism, right?
Or this or that, or you've got to change this.
Or someone said today, well, if you have knowledge,
now you have to do something.
I said, it says who?
It says why?
You're joking, right?
The thing is to set yourself apart and sustain food, clothing, and
shelter of whatever quality you want.
Now someone, of course, has said that's oversimplified.
But what kind of quality food would you like?
It takes a lot of work to do that.
By the way, in societies where they were not industrialized or
commercialized, you spent most of the day doing that.
But now you do something else and you exchange it for food.
And then clothing, what level of clothing would you like?
Of course, and then shelter, what level of shelter?
And even in today's credit system,
do you know what it takes to maintain a four-bathroom house on a hill?
So it's part of shelter.
It's a lot of maintenance there and cost.
So when I say food, clothing, and shelter, you'll start noticing that you have
a basic, not a derivative, but a basic foundation on how to function here.
Now, I've also said before, there's a lot of the Greeks that I've said,
you should do this, I shouldn't do any of this, shouldn't listen to any of this.
But the thing is, it needs to be said, right?
Now, what needs to, another thing that could be said,
it just seems like I have a Skype call, or Seth probably.
I'm gonna see if I could bring him in.
But to set yourself apart, and I gave someone an example of this.
What do you mean, set yourself apart?
How can you set yourself apart?
I said, okay, if everyone around you, even on the whole planet,
decided to turn the Earth into a paradise tomorrow,
I'm still gonna be a part, good, apart from it, set apart from it.
Go ahead, do what you gotta do, leave me alone.
Now, if everyone tomorrow wanted to just go and kill each other,
that's fine with me, just go and leave me alone.
I don't want anything to do with it.
So whether everyone wants to hold hands and
sing Kumbaya and make a perfect society, I'm gonna be set apart from it.
You guys go ahead, knock yourselves out, have fun, leave me alone.
And the other aspect of it is if they wanna just go and
wreak destruction on each other for no reason, leave me alone and set yourself apart.
Now, it's gonna take a lot of work to do it either way, see?
So it's not like just leave me alone, go sit in a corner like a lump on a log.
If people are fixing on killing each other,
it's gonna take a lot of your energy to set yourself apart from that.
And if people are fixing on creating paradise on Earth, wink, wink,
it's gonna take a lot to set yourself apart from that also.
So let's see if I can drag in Seth, otherwise there's a,
Skype tends to be sort of temperamental, let's see.
Yep, okay, let's see if he comes on and maybe he'll have his microphone on as well.
Greetings, Seth, are you there?
Greetings, I am.
Oh, good, you sound good, how are you?
I'm well, how about yourself?
Oh, here on Uncommon Radio, and you were calling,
perhaps you knew it knowing that we're on the air,
so speak your mind if you've got one left.
Yeah, well, I'd like to hope that I have one left,
at least what I've been given, if nothing else.
I guess there's a lot that could be said, you know, I like to ask questions.
And you've said, you know, what I was listening to earlier
while I was still doing the yob was, you know, that showing up is 90% of it,
which is very accurate in most yobs, I suppose, is just showing up.
But other than food, clothing, and shelter, which are important, obviously,
I mean, those are the main ways that we interact with our environment.
But beyond that, what is there?
A very broad question, obviously.
Well, the other thing is step two, or is that, you know,
another chunk of what to pursue is to learn about what the soul,
the spirit, and the body is, and as you learn and know about it,
to act accordingly.
Which brings us directly back to food, water, and shelter.
Well, yeah, it does.
And also, you know, if you've got food, clothing, and shelter taken care of,
you've got a lot of free time on your hands.
But again, do you know what it takes to maintain a four-bedroom,
four-bathroom house on the side of a hill in a golden ghetto?
Let's say golden ghettos where rich people live.
Or it depends on what kind of clothing you like to wear because, you know,
if you fit good Spanish or good Italian shoes, it's a form of a blessing.
You want the best shoes you can afford.
And for food, do you want to eat junk food, right,
or do you want to eat the stuff they're telling you is food?
So those pursuits right there, you're going to have to structure a way
to acquire all those things, which might take up most of your time anyway.
Oh, yeah.
And, you know, I take pleasure in making music with myself
and with others and for others.
So that's an aspect of the mind and the body then.
Yeah.
It's a way to communicate thought without the necessary hindrance of language.
Although, you know, you've listened to some of my music,
so, I mean, obviously there are words used as well.
But, you know, it's like painting.
You don't always have to paint exactly what is to get a thought across.
Well, also, you know, what's interesting about music,
it's one of the suggested mediums over most other art mediums by the gods also,
if you think about it.
I've never read in any holy writ that says you should make a painting for me.
But it does state in many writs about making music
and singing and playing instruments.
Yeah.
Yeah, as a matter of fact, the statuary and the paintings and the stuff,
that's quite ironic and sarcastic to bring that up, right?
But it's the truth.
No, very much so.
Actually, I would say that there are at least a handful of texts
that recommend against those forms of physical art even.
For very specific purposes that we seem to,
we being the world at large, not you and I,
but seem to put to the express purpose why they are,
why it's recommended against seems to be considered
some of the highest form of those arts,
which is not surprising, I suppose.
But it is ironic.
The interesting thing that I've also been discussing
is the character of the man or the woman,
because that is very important.
For example, this might be personal and general.
Many people that have come across, let's say,
and have this desire to learn of what they came across
being the higher forms of ancient writ,
which would be the biblical text, for example,
based on their character or personal weakness,
they get hang-ups about certain things along the way,
and they latch on to the lower aspects of that particular writ, let's say.
And things like we brought up,
like I would say iconography and statuary
become overblown out of proportion on their functioning.
Some people that, for example, I'll just say it more plainly,
some people that start to study what's known as Scripture
get very upset at iconography
and almost as if it's something contagious
that they need to run away from or scorn it.
Or destroy.
Or destroy, where they haven't relaxed into the concept
of what that really means.
They'll grab a concept.
And what's interesting is each concept, law, or point
that's made in Scripture has many facets to it.
And the facets accommodate various levels of quality of character
of who approaches it.
You see, so I'll give a quick example.
There's one of these Vedic places that don't serve any animal at all.
And I used to enjoy going there because it was an all-you-can-eat buffet
of some very high-quality vegetarian food.
And it's attached to a temple, not part of a temple.
And part of their thing is the monks go around there
and explain these little wooden statues, you know, what the gods do.
And being around someone who was studying Scripture,
kind of flipped out when they saw this.
They said, I can't come in here. There are idols in here.
I've got to go.
And I'm like, well, okay, well, all right.
Because their character could not.
They got the same information that I did, right?
But their character could not work through the relevancy
of what the entire message in Scripture is about it.
In this case, just to finish off a little bit more,
specifically I went there for the food because it was an excellent value.
It was very well-prepared, very high-quality, at a very good price.
So I sat down there, and the little monk, the idiot with the shaved head,
comes around and says, well, basically this god does this
and is good for that and has done this.
And I wait for him to finish, and I basically said, well,
my god made the wood that you made your god out of.
So big deal.
Right.
Do you see how there's humor, there's sarcasm, there's edification,
we have to keep things relevant.
I mean, do we have to? No.
In other words, how are people taking the information
and seeing its value according to the way they pursue things in life,
but not purely, Harris, you do and interpret it what you want,
but you need to see the whole thing to make a decision if it's for you first.
That's why, for example, I sarcastically say very often,
you listen to Greek-speak and start going down some of these paths,
you're not going to have any friends.
Well, why?
You could still win friends and influence people.
Dale Carnegie wrote a book about that.
Why?
Well, you just can't talk to them about this kind of stuff,
because in order to have friends and influence people,
you're going to have to accommodate them with whatever crap they're interested in,
and most of the people are interested in crap, yes.
So can you discern it?
Do you want to put that kind of energy into it?
It's like the purpose of coming here and doing the radio
is not to rehash the crap like everyone else does.
You know, you ever turn on internet radio
and all you hear is what the mainstream media,
they just have their own spin on it.
They just repeat what they read.
It's just bizarre.
So the thing is here, a couple more.
I think we might do 12 on this one, but this is the eighth one.
I've been speaking more about the character of the individuals on this planet.
In other words, get most of the stuff out of the way
and start trying to figure out or give a little bit of information
so people can figure out how to improve their character.
Character, by the way, comes from charisma,
or character is a base word in Greek which means grace.
Like if you read in scripture the word grace, it's actually charis.
So it's almost as if one's personality or one's character is operating under privilege.
In other words, you are the way you are and it was given to you to be that way,
but it doesn't mean you can't improve it.
Now, by the way, an improvement for some would be death or destruction for another.
So you have to comprehend that as well.
Same root as charisma?
Yes. That's where you get charisma from.
Charaktidas. Charaktidas is character.
You see, the prefix is the same, the ha prefix, which is a letter that's not in English.
They typically do it with ch or c.
But it's an interesting thing how the word itself actually shows the purpose
of what we're attaching the word to.
So the thing is, one thing that hasn't been discussed is not, I assure you,
you don't hear about, forget about internet radio or anywhere,
is the character of the individual.
Now, that sounds subjective, but is there a way to objectify good character?
And the answer to that would be yes, there is.
And there's certain things that could be laid down because the character being animated
or the mind or the spirit is dependent on the physical body, is it not?
Because if you remove the physical body, then there's no character.
So, you know, how can the physical body be improved?
Well, how can it be improved if you think you're a filter bag absorbing things?
You see, so these things all tie in together.
I've gotten certain messages like, Greek, you're saying all this stuff, it's great,
but there's something you're holding back, man, there's something in there.
Yes, if you folks want to know, yes, the Greek is holding back a lot, mostly.
I'm never going to share more than 10%, never, publicly.
That's not going to happen.
Maybe 11% sometimes.
But everything is being given.
What is being given?
Not that I have everything, but if you're dealing with people that have nothing,
if you have a tiny inkling, that's a hell of a lot more.
So the point is this, is that all of the hints,
all of the things that are being ever discussed in public need to be strung together
and looked at holistically.
Wow, okay, that's too much.
Well, sorry.
All of it ties together because basically, why are people worrying?
Because if you're here, you're done.
According to the gods, if you are born and even if you're thrown into,
if you're born and with the afterbirth, the mom throws you in a trash bag,
if you took your first breath, your purpose is over.
You took a place number.
You're here to take a number.
A certain amount of spirits have to come from here over a certain amount of time, period.
Now, in order for that epoch or all those events to take place,
they're going to be done by nature and by man.
Things are going to be taking place,
and you will be guided and given resistance where you shouldn't go
and a vacuum that will suck you towards a direction where you should go from the other side.
And that is the predestination aspect.
But you do still have tremendous free will on the way
because if you didn't have free will, resistance wouldn't need to be put on one end
and a vacuum or less resistance in another, you see.
A car's got free will.
You want a bet?
Just get it in gear, put a stick between what's called the accelerator pedal,
and jump out and watch it.
Interesting take on self-determinism.
Watch it go.
You know, on the perspective of seeing, I don't know,
what could be described as the way that everything relates to everything
or the connectivity of everything,
that seems to be something that is almost, I don't know,
not an innate ability but an innate wanting or desire
that seems to be discouraged in most of, I don't know, polite society,
if you want to give it a polite term,
or completely and totally miscomprehended in the circles
that do speak about such connectivity.
And taking that perspective is difficult because of those two things.
This is speculation, I suppose.
Well, that would be the resistance aspect of it.
Right.
But at the same time that it is difficult to possibly think
in that large of a scale,
at the same time it feels that that is exactly what the mind wants to do.
Humans have a tendency to want to see the connections,
and where they do not see the connections,
try to make the connections themselves.
I've heard genius described as that.
I can't remember where or whether or not it's accurate,
but that genius is the ability to see the connections that are there
and little more.
See the obvious.
Yeah.
Now, that can be trained.
That's a skill, by the way, and it's also a counter-spatial issue.
Have you ever had a discussion with someone
and they got what you're saying before you even finished explaining it?
You just brought the subject matter up
and they saw what direction you were going and they got it.
You didn't even have to finish the thought.
It's like handing someone a set of eyeglasses with a better prescription in them.
Yeah.
Okay, and you see the expression, right?
It's unexplainable.
Sometimes in private I discuss these are counter-spatial issues,
meaning they don't work in the way.
Well, it's basically called you exist in space and through time.
Counter-space is space times time.
The ability to observe such a thing would put you at a much higher vantage point.
Right, and the only way you can get the direction is from a higher vantage point,
but the irony of it is that everyone is getting direction from a higher vantage point,
like it or not, because it's external input.
But there's so little information about that realm where these things come from,
thought, inspiration, the spiritual side.
There's so little information even today that people are engaged in.
The information is there.
It's just no one wants to touch it.
When I say no one, I mean hardly anyone.
And those obviously that do are aware of the spiritual realm
or that other less tangible, counter-spatial, non-physical.
They don't need the physical to animate.
Well, they're not speaking at all.
That's fascinating, or at least in a way that you can go
and find it on what's called the Internet yet.
It doesn't seem that at least if any of the history that has been shared can be trusted at all.
No.
It would seem that that aspect of society, like the way that we view, as an example,
like the separation of the church and the state, that that is a...
It's an oxymoron.
Yes, exactly.
You can't have a state without...
But the church being the circus, meaning the God aspect,
no, you can't have a state without a God behind it.
Right.
And that way it's much more recognized throughout, at least like I said,
whether or not history can be believed, what has been shared through the epochs.
It seems that in the past they had a much better understanding at least
or more information was available to them on such matters.
But the thing is if it was so good, why is everyone in the shape that they're in today?
Oh, I'm not suggesting that it was good or that what was done with that information was good,
but it just seems to be that...
How often do you hear of some, quote-unquote, old religion being brought forth again
like through the various pieces of...
Oh, yeah.
It does.
Thank you for calling in, Seth.
This is Solo 8, and we'll see you at Solo 9.
Thank you, everyone.