Greetings and welcome everyone. If you recognize the voice, you know who this is.
And if you don't, it's the Greek. And be prepared for some more Greek-speak
on Uncommon Radio. It's also gone by Uncommon Sense
and it's uncommonradio.com. www.uncommonradio.com
That is a courtesy website where you can easily communicate
at your convenience. And by the way, this is a sonic experience
not just for the Greek, but for all. So if you care to participate
using, let's say, a Skype convention, feel free to go
to the www.uncommonradio.com website
and you will see an email there in red. And that email is also the Skype contact.
Yes, the entire email. That would be uncommonsenseradio1
at gmail.com and that's a numeric one. And that is the Skype contact
if you'd like to join through that convention. Also,
there is a, I guess a main switchboard
call-in line that you can get at American Freedom Radio.
And that one, as I pull it up, I know it's 218-339-8525.
So it's
218-339-8525.
And you probably won't be dialing, will you? You probably have a silly phone
or some kind of capacitive charging touchscreen.
So I always talk about perhaps, anyway,
it's a lascivious joke, maybe we'll leave it for later, about how funny
it would be for someone who's never used a dialing phone to try to
use one now. Maybe we'll bring it up later on.
By the way, Muppet Time or Pagan Time or
Pope's Work Schedule Time, I would say it's what they call March
23rd, 2017. And I like to always use
the exercise. If anyone wants to just pull up what they call the calendar, the work
schedule, if you look at today being what they call a
Thursday or Thursday for March 23rd, 2017, last year
I guess it was a Monday or a Tuesday. The next year it'll be a Friday or a
Saturday. So what is it? It's neither. It's a work
schedule. Now, I'm not knocking it, okay? Let's be ghetto
and knock it. I ain't down with that. No, it's not about that.
It's are we paying attention? Speaking of paying attention,
when things are worth paying attention to, I guess you pay attention to them, but
if you don't know about them, how are you going to pay attention to it? Lawfully.
Let's just say, you know that word lawful? Yeah, you've probably heard it, but you may not know much about
it. Yeah. Well, you know, think about keeping
time. Keeping time is simply just the recordation of events. And how do you do it so
it's lawful? Well, who's law, right? Well, maybe we'll get into that
later where law comes from and all that. I would suggest
this is the first month and the fifteenth day of the first month.
Anyone, isn't any ancient holy writs of any sort?
Even though you don't have any translations access to you, you most definitely
just have some kind of version. Or even if you're a keyboard warrior, go ahead and
plug in, let's say under a certain writ or something
what the thirteenth and the fourteenth of the first
month is supposed to be. Think about it. Well, either
way, welcome everyone and just a little bit of a
cold start there on the normal way the Greek starts off
just by maybe talking about what isn't spoken of.
Now, something interesting came up I just wanted to share.
I also want to maybe read a couple of emails as well. I always preface
that we don't get to them probably until the end of the two hours or so.
But nonetheless, I would suggest that
the concept of no one is paying any attention still
holds, folks. Or let's just say
discussion. What is discussion?
What is going on?
This is what came up, by the way. Fine print.
You've all heard of it somewhere. You've seen it.
It's on what they call contracts, the back of invoices, statements, things like
that. If that's important or if that's some kind of
condition or disclosure regarding an agreement or covenant
or something, why is it in fine print? Anyone think they can answer that? Maybe
in chat? I want to throw in why things are in fine print.
Remember, this is just, most of the time
the Greek brings up things that just aren't brought up by anyone and they're just in front of you.
It may not be the be all end all, but
we're questioning for the answer here. We're not just asking the
question and just whatever. And it's not a matter of whether
you like it or not. So think about it for a moment. Never really brought up the
fine print issue. Why is it in fine print? All right, let's just spill the beans
and say it. Could it be because they're in shame or they're embarrassed
to make it legible and readable and bring it forward into
the, let's say, the writ, right?
Writ, meaning things that are written or into the agreement or as
conditions. Why is it when you approach
administrative types, right? You know what
that is in this modern world. And they ask you to sign or agree to this.
Just sign here. And it's really long and lots of really fine print.
You want to sit there and read the fine print. Of course, there's 50 or 100 or 5,000
people standing behind you and they're all going to go through the same
dictate. Just sign here. But you want to read the fine print
and everyone gets angry. Just sign it. Everybody signs it.
So why is something so shameful, so
embarrassing that you're supposed to agree to that when you ask to read
it? Now, it's not shameful and embarrassing because you're asking to read it, but because
it's written in fine print. They're not proud of it. Think about
it. So the fine print, is something going to be hidden in it?
Well, you can still read it. It's fine print. But why is it just
whispered? You see? Welcome to the legal society, folks.
So think about it. Think about it. I mean, not
too much because there's really nothing much you can do for. Why? Because they're accommodating.
Well, first of all, they have to accommodate themselves.
How much have you heard of help yourself first? And they're just
helping themselves because certain societies, whether
the legal society, the medical society, the religious society,
the political society, on and on and on, just about
all of them, follow the old credo of help yourself
first. But here's the thing. The way that they help themselves
is only to help themselves. Why? Because what they are
engaged in, which is pranking, by the way, and this is
not a commentary or rant. This is just maybe tagging along
on what fine print is and why there is no discussion about it.
Their way of doing things is
a way that's been developed because you are you, meaning most of the
world, except for a few nations, which are toggling back and
forth under what's called a credit-based economy. And no, we're not going to talk about money
because this cosmic censorship is too heavy. No one will understand anything
than the, right? So let's get to the
point of it, is that in a credit-based society, the
people, quote-unquote, what is being used as money, have all the money.
And all the societies that are, or the, let's say
the apparatus that's built around it, doesn't matter whether it's through agency, through
administrative, through its government or corporate, they have nothing. They are part of the
receivership. Yes, receivership is a concept in bankruptcy.
Go look at it, maybe. Well, actually, don't look at it.
But you could. It's kind of maybe reverse psychology there
or reverse spiritualism, maybe. Same thing.
So what's going on is that if you can sign, you've
got it all. And if you're a company or an organization trying
to flip some kind of administrative stuff, you've got nothing. But the thing is, you've
got to get it from the people without letting them know that they have everything.
So fine print, legal society, credit society,
or credit-based society. You see how one
thing can't be brought up without showing how everything ties together.
Yeah. Let's just go back and tie again. Let's just weave back and forth.
You know, on a loom, you kind of start on the left, you go to the right, and you go back to the
left, okay, back to the right, okay. Well, think about it, folks.
If it appears to lawfully be around the first month, in the middle of the first month,
the moon should be fairly dark out there right now. And it's quite an important
day or days of observation
for those that are in the know.
Notice I didn't say uninitiated because there's nothing to be initiated into.
There's no group or crowd, by the way. But it's the first month, folks.
Now, physically in the natural world, you would say
perhaps down under and across those latitudes, it might be the seventh
month. Yes. Think about it. It's not that simple.
Could it be that many things involve tactics
and strategy and knowledge and learning and technique
and maybe it's starting to sound a little like chess and not
just simple checkers? So maybe
it's not like a television sitcom or a television
episode where everything gets explained and fixed in the last two
minutes? It doesn't work like that. But anyway,
everything is sort of tied together. I had a conversation this week
regarding boundary layers. It just kind of came up trying to explain
certain things. One thing contacts another, whether it's a liquid, gas
or solid. So you could be a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant and still be
in full contact with the fish in the deepest part of the ocean through
boundary layers of gas, solid and liquid. And this is
not some esoteric
whatever sublime thing. Just think about it.
Gases are a medium of contact. You can have a lightning
go through it. It conducts electricity. If
you're passing through air, let's say, which is a gas, fast enough
– I almost had a little joke there – but fast enough, it appears to be a
solid. That's why things get friction and burn up when they're
entering the atmosphere and things. So again, a surface-dwelling earth
inhabitant, you're in a meat bag with a frame, skeletal frame,
and you have this flexible membrane known as the skin, which is in contact with
the air. Or you're a lazy boy or the couch or the desk chair or wherever you
might be as well. Or
maybe your panties, which are probably in a twist by now if this is the first time you've
ever turned into Uncommon Radio. So your skin
is in contact with the air, and that air is in contact
with the surface of the water. It doesn't matter how far away it is, which
is in contact with the water, which is in contact with the fish, and it's all connected.
And this is the type of thinking
that goes into the longitudinal side, which is opposite
the transverse. What did he just say? What does that mean? Well, transverse is where time
and motion and waves propagate further
away the longer it takes. Longitudinal, there is no time. It's
instant. This is what Tesla was dealing with, by the way.
When you go and study the world
or society of the gods, yes, those unseen friends that crazy people
have, they operate in a longitudinal fashion.
So one way to start on that point of thinking
of instantaneous is how everything is already connected.
So again, the soft membrane, dry or juicy
or whatever outside of your body is connected to
the deepest parts of the ocean and the fish there through boundary layers
of various materials. And of course, it's easy to take the air for granted
unless you're moving at 25,000 miles per hour at about 50,000 feet
and then it acts as if it's made of concrete.
So it's a perspective thing.
So let's maybe engage a chat if anyone feels like they would
like to call, they may.
By the way, at any time, if I'm not giving the call in number, you can go to the
American Freedom Radio homepage and you will see it on the top
left in a red box. And if you don't see it there, it's on your other left
which is still the left.
Again, nothing to be ashamed of. So call in if you like.
I would suggest also when you're
let's say passing through this world, using that word passing again,
and you're looking at things around you, you ever notice how
it's always something out there, right?
Could it be that when all of your attention
is taken to somewhere out there, you really can't see what's going on right
here? Back in the 50s, they had the space men,
the space monster. And then you could always
see it's always out there, something to draw your attention.
Because maybe it starts at what they call home.
How about home being the body and how about reaching your arms out into the room?
What have you got, about a five or six foot radius? Why don't you master what is
around you there? When you're out in nature, you notice how the temperature
works differently than it does inside.
Heat doesn't go up in nature and heat
doesn't go up in living things. Think about it.
So mastering these things through perception,
you don't have to do anything, just perceive them.
How about at one point
turning off dummy loading? There's things called
influence. And by the way, speaking of influence,
I want to thank everyone who has influenced through input
to AFR regarding uncommon radio
because this is the fourth time the Greek has come around solo and perhaps
discussing as if this is the open members area, how
things might actually be or the liturgy of the back
room for those exclusive people that want to pay to hear
things, which you see everywhere, members areas and things like that.
By the way, I keep saying it, I find it distasteful to do that, but
I just wanted to thank everyone who has contributed and
shown voting by sending some
form of credits over to AFR. I've discussed how that actually works.
You really didn't send anything, but it's part of being on this planet. No, you can't change it,
but even though you haven't sent anything and it does show up as if you did send
some more, that would be great. It's very much appreciated from having
discussions with the management at AFR. This was probably the first time
any kind of an effort was made like this by the public in recent memory.
I really want to just thank everyone and
show that it is very, very appreciated. If you can
keep contributing, at least this is the fourth time
the Greek has come around solo. We had a goal. I haven't mentioned
what that number is, but we're very close to it. Very, very close. I mean like
really close. So if we can get just a few more people just to send something
Oh, it sounds like a beg-a-thon. No, no, no.
All right. Send something.
You're voting for the Greek, right? Okay.
I just want to throw this out there. There's some project in the works.
Usually you've heard the Greek. The history of it is calling in years ago
various places including here and doing what they call
round tables and things like that. It's not because I just want to do that.
The reason was basically because listening to what was being put out
and saying
this doesn't sound correct. It sounds like what people
are used to hearing and maybe the highest and best use of
a medium that is not so directly controlled is to perhaps
be talking about the truth. The truth of the matter.
Because you've got to realize, people, everyone's got their own truth now, right?
So I would call in and
try to make some comments and of course didn't do much.
And then it kind of evolved into the idea of speaking out because
it just should be spoken. Because really it's kind of
embarrassing for the human race. Actually, let's just say it this way.
The Greek is embarrassed to be called human.
Not all you fruity breakfast types, you know, fruits, nuts and flakes are going to say
oh, he just said he's not human. No, I'm embarrassed for you and myself
included at this point because these things are not being said.
What are these things? Very, very simple things. And by the way,
if you've ever turned into Uncommon Sense on Common Radio or Greek speak and you don't understand it,
that's great, you're normal. But okay, all those things aside.
But the project that's going to be perhaps coming
is going to be interesting. It'll probably be
an AFR. I should say most likely. I don't think any kind of an effort is going to be
made outside of that at this point. And it will emanate from there. And it will be
something very new, very different. And it will be Greek speak.
But we'll fill you folks in on it more. It'll be
more, a little deeper into
things and perhaps a little more stuff.
We'll just see how it develops as it develops. Right now there's just
basically not even a framework being put together. But hopefully
it will be around after maybe, let's say, the seventh
sonic event or so. This is around the fourth sonic event. So that gives you a little
bit of time to think about it and if there's anything else.
So I would suggest, again,
if you folks like what you're hearing, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
Well, send something to AFR. Just do that electronic boogie-woogie thing
and let AFR know through some credits
of some sort that you appreciate the Greek coming on. Because
I do appreciate you folks as well. Let me just say it at this point.
I've gotten quite a few emails. And they've all been
very positive. And not just, oh, I like you. What do you say? Well, I don't
know. I just like you. Nothing like that. It's all been very rational and
very much based on what's being imparted and not the Greek
sort of what the Greek is saying. And again, if these
things were being said, you wouldn't know of the Greek.
So the
feedback has been very good. And that's why I appreciate you
folks out there who have been giving the proper feedback.
Proper meaning, it's like table tennis. You know, you
put out some info and it comes back slightly different, but it's still the same
ball. So it's been working out very, very well
to understand or comprehend that there's at least about 150 to
200 surface-dwelling earth inhabitants out there that
are thinking somewhat. Yes. So
I'm going to log into the email and just maybe
start off this first hour by reading some of them. I'll also
check the chat. Because based on the
following project that's going to be coming, things are going to get a little deeper,
a little more concise and more defined.
And let me just give you folks a hint. It may not be open to the public.
Think about it. None of it. So just bear that in mind.
But at the moment, we're going to do
our best with, let's say, time allotted and venue allotted and what can be
said. So let's see if anyone feels like calling
in, please do so. And let's just see here
in the chat, there's not much. Just regarding some kind
of covenant from some really old book maybe.
Yeah, let's see. Okay, just some basic chit-chat. I wonder why
they just call it chat and they don't call it chit-chat. So just
bear with me, folks. I'm going to log into the emails here for a moment. I came unprepared.
Let's see if I can find them in the slurry. The way things have been
sorted out here is sort of unintuitive.
Here's one that was gotten today.
It might sound a little perky or something, but this is the
idea and this is part of the discussion that happens when I'm not on air.
Thank you, Greek, for covering the questions last week.
I hope you continue to discuss many topics despite how it may appear that
there are many of us out here that are very tired of the
economy low and have listened to O&G and Uncommon Sense
and it is impossible to look at any other media. There's really no going back.
So we look forward to whatever you do in the future. Best wishes. Thank you very much.
You see, that would be like the loosest commentary
that I've ever gotten, but it's still specific enough
regarding why. So when people tell you
things, maybe ask why and you get to a certain point.
How can a subject be brought up?
Look, you cannot discuss anything without
it connecting to the credit system. Think about it.
You cannot discuss almost any subject or anything unless it's
connected to the human body. Think about it. Or any subject that's
connected to the mind. Not connected to the mind. Everything is.
Or just quality. I brought up
earlier the idea of temperature.
Paying attention to what's going on around you. Just in the room around you.
However you want to consider. An indoor space versus
a natural space. Or a living body versus a dead body.
You'll notice that there is a rarefied rise in cold and a descending heat.
You want warm feet and a cool head. And when it's hot in the valley, it's cold in the mountain.
As you go higher, it gets cooler. Don't listen to these academic types that try to
well, you go ahead and listen, but have a laugh.
How is this temperature being measured with the expansion
of mercury, whether it's Fahrenheit or Celsius, and there were even some other conventions
at some point. How does that render
quality? Can you consider mercury
to be something of, what is its qualitative nature? Can you consider it to be
of quality that you would pursue? Well, maybe in a
thermometer. But why are we relying on things, I say we
meaning as it would be discussed how things are done on Earth
on something that is the expansion of the toxic substance. And again, just to bring up
temperature. Let's say it's 70 degrees Fahrenheit. You might be
very comfortable at sea level in let's say a t-shirt or a button down
shirt. And if you go below sea level,
mercury still being at 70 degrees Fahrenheit, you might
feel a tad warm. And still, if you go to the
top of a mountain or very high altitude, or not so high but higher
altitude than sea level, even if the
mercury is still at 70 degrees, you might start to feel a little chill. You notice
that the mercury has been reading the same temperature in all three locations, but
you feel there is a difference. And how come devices
haven't been measured to measure quality? Now, we talk about
food also. It's the same thing. You can take a petite Rothschild
1972 wine and a 3,000
whatever in credits, euros, dollars, whatever bottle of wine and take it to a lab
and they'll give you a chemical constituents and then you can go
ahead and based on the assay or the diagnosis of that wine
put all those things together. The tannins, the sugars, the water, the minerals.
Is it going to taste like that? No, it's not.
So you have a very limited description
and very little explanation being given to you throughout
anywhere or anything. Here's the thing.
If you want to look at statistically or hit or miss or just the efficacy
or how well or how effective an institution can be, if
university and college was so good, how come there's so many bad professors
or bad attorneys or bad doctors or bad
and I say bad, good boy, bad boy, good boy
bad boy, the good guys, the bad guys
poor in quality. And by the way
I've heard this before also. There's no such thing as a good attorney. There's a competent
attorney.
Going from just marking
because someone has passed some social rank
some form of glorification
let's say. Doesn't that render laziness?
Think about it. So a lot of the things that you hear
here at Greek Speak, Uncommon Radio
these are not things that are some far off thing. There are no
aliens that can get you or black goo or flat earth
or any of the ridiculous stuff or political talk. By the way folks
why is it, I think last week
I brought up the invisible ring in people's noses and how you're being accommodated
if you turn on what they call alternative media or mainstream media, they're the same
they're running parallel tracks
now it's a political thing and if you are going to any of these media things
you're being dummy loaded. So one way to
maybe control what you eat through the mind because
maybe thought can be food in a way. You start hearing
political talk, that's
poor character. Why? Because when you're
doing political talk, now the receiver may not be
poor character but definitely the deliverer is, that's for sure. And poor character
can be developed many ways. Censorship being probably
the most important and then good food or good intake and all that
or lack of it let's say promotes all these things
but I would suggest that the reason why it's poor
and I brought this up in several private conversations and it was kind of laid into
and I quickly put a stop to it. It's very simple to rationalize why
the poor taste and the poverty of character
of those that are engrossed in the political scene is very
simple. If you start discussing anything political it starts going into
that fray where you're going to be bringing up the way
governing agencies and bodies function. You're going to be bringing up
economics. You're going to be bringing up social control.
All of these things, the way they're being discussed is
100% false. Well let's say 99.99999%
false. So would you say that it's all lies? Yeah, it's all lies but
they've all been accepted as being lies. I mean not lies
but whatever, talk. Now let's just take those down real quick.
When they're talking about controlling agencies or the
sovereign agencies or the sovereign government, they've all been bankrupted. They're in receivership.
You could look that up, what that means.
They're under what's called policy not law. This is not a comment against or for them. I'm just stating
why political discussion is false. Do they have power? Yes, they do.
They do have power because there's plenty of people willing to
put on a uniform and do other things. Patriotism, have you heard
about that? Not that those things are bad. It's just that that's why the
perception of it is so strong. But what's been memorialized
about them, they don't exist as they think they do.
The other thing when economics comes up in this political commentary
which always does, it's a credit based economy.
Just do what forensic auditing or forensic accounting would render
to show where all this money comes from or what a debt is
in a credit based economy. So all of these discussions
and the social engineering part, all these things that are being
put on the people are because they're accommodating the mindset.
So this political talk that you hear
that's going on right now is a very, very poor quality and you're going to be
eating this when you hear it. Now I'm not going to say when you hear
political talk, just shut it off. That would be the best thing to do, but I'm not going to
suggest that. You're big boys and girls at this point.
But the thing is, again like the email stated, where are you going to go and get anything?
Silence maybe. Here's the thing.
If what they call the inane net or internet or the
World Wide Web was being used for its highest and best use at this point, you
wouldn't have much political talk. You would have edification talk perhaps.
Again, this is part of the
censorship, but this is just for those out there listening. You can just look
at pretty much everything that's being discussed in the mainstream and alternative by the way.
There's these cosmic invisible rings
in people's noses, seven billion let's say or those that have access to it
and they're all being led around and they don't know it or they do know it
but they're not doing anything about it and they shouldn't because they can't do anything about it.
But there are those out there that can see and those out there that can hear
and maybe a little bit of Greek speak will rationalize it for you.
Not telling you how to think about it or what to think about it, but just
think about it. You can say, well, is it wrong
for me to do this or wrong for me to listen to politics? I've heard this. Is it wrong?
I'll say, well, it's not wrong, but it's definitely not right.
Just by looking at the quality of the discussion and without being
ad hominem and looking at the actual individuals, you probably won't meet the people that you see
on TV or hear on radio or whatever, but I'm suggesting that there's poor character
all throughout all of it.
You see, I brought up the concept of politics, but I would also
suggest if there was a missing airplane, it would have been that.
If it was this or this or that or that, it would have been that.
How much of it would have been discussed accurately, precisely
with also bringing up things that are memorialized about that
topic? Probably none of it.
This is how humanity has been eking along for a very, very, very
long time. I've stated the obvious for the past half hour
or so. Big deal. Big effing deal. Why?
Because the obvious is where it lies, and the obvious is the last thing for people to discover.
Here's the thing. There's a lot of zealous
– not jealous, but zealousy, meaning, oh, we've got to do something about it.
There's nothing you're going to do about it. You could actually dummy load yourself
if you have that energy. Put it out there.
Wilhelm Reich talked a lot about the life force being bottled up in the body and how it can create
other manifestations that are not necessarily good for you.
Let's just put it that way. You need to get that out
if it manifests that way.
I don't even
need to go down that. This is a year, by the way,
folks, which is going to be very much like the past seven years that have passed.
Very much so, but it's going to be ending, and you're going to have a transition into
another period starting next year in the spring or the fall if you're down under.
By the way, I don't know if I've thrown this in before.
We've done a lawful measurement of time,
and you folks that are down under are not a day ahead.
According to the sun, the moon, the stars, and the planet.
According to the work schedule or the wind-up toy or some other fallacious way,
you've been told they've set you somewhere further ahead.
But the measurement taken by the moon repeatedly now
shows that it actually reaches a point where it can be
measured, and it always shows that the
more eastern part precedes it.
Let's just say this, just to
sum it up. Those folks down under that are scheduled
to be a day ahead, you've heard that sometimes.
We're calling from the future or we're in tomorrow already or whatever.
You're not lawfully according to the schedule you are, but remember,
it's about the schedule because if you don't show up to work and do these things,
you might get fired. But you may not get fired if you've never been hired though.
So anyway. So again,
lawfully the folks down there are, just brought that up because
when it's spring for up here, it's fall for down there.
You folks, just something to think about, not to add more confusion,
you are trailing behind. So where does it start
would be the next logical question. Let's just put this out. I would suggest that it starts around
the center mass of the earth with the
lawful marking of time. Not because you think it is or he
thinks or who gee what it doesn't. It's because it's a reference point.
It starts around the Levant, which would be
the east coast of the Mediterranean and somewhere around northern Iraq
is where the datum line for the planet kind of changes.
That Mesopotamia region. Yeah. You hear about it
all the time and you have what I brought up, esoteric emotion about it. You don't know
what to do about those people. Yeah. Those people in that part
of the world. Yeah. And if anyone is familiar with Greek speak, you've heard
quite a bit. But even when I do discuss the coming world order,
which is not the current world order,
it's still never in depth and that will be done in the future. I mean
very detailed. But the details right now, even
the slightest amount of generality is way, way, way beyond
anything else out there. So why even bother? Why even bother getting
into details? And a quick specific example is
in terms of the world stage, what you're witnessing is the precursor to the formation
not the formation, but actually the precursor to the formation of
a Middle East Union type thing that will be headquarters for
every aspect of man's society. Yes, it's kind of hard to see,
but that's why you have to know.
Anyway, and I've always given various explanations
and basically let's just throw this in there. I don't go much deeper
than just saying one of the signs that you will see that this is forming is a
new country being formed in northern Iraq. It has not been a nation
for a very long time. And that new country will be called the new
Assyria or Assyria. Have you ever heard of the Assyrians?
Assyrians, not Syria, but Assyrians, A-S-S-Y-R-I-A-N-S.
There are many other things, but that's just enough for now.
And I hope that puts at least some things
in perspective of what's going on. So I have not been ignoring the chat. I see there's quite a bit
of activity or somewhat of activity. I'm just going to go there and see what's being discussed.
I saw Greek in all caps.
Okay, will you elaborate on what day it is? Well, it's all perceived
in significance of the following seven days.
I've brought this up before.
The majority of the personal messages, let's say private messages and even calls on air
have been regarding what's called the Bible or Biblical stuff or the Scriptures.
I don't like calling it the Bible or whatever. Let's just leave
a personal critique out of it.
I always preface several things before I discuss that. First of all, it's very difficult
to have a discussion regarding that because when people do have
discussions, they tend to be false because they're based on churchianity or
whatever or other comments
and things like that that are not based on...
Okay, let's just say it this way. All of the information that you're getting is coming out of a version.
The actual Scripture, what has been memorialized...
Now, it doesn't matter. This has nothing to do with your religion or belief. It could be anything.
It could be an engineering document from the days of Archimedes.
Anything. If it has not been translated, it has not been translated.
A version is not a translation. You can't get a dinner napkin and a crayon
and write a hundred note on it and go and spend it, even though the one
that's printed by the banks is just as fake. It's the perception.
We have a perception that something is real when it is not here.
Sorry, folks. Just like anything, you have to go back to what it is.
In other words, if we're discussing wheat, why is it that people just want to talk
about puffed wheat? And when whole wheat comes up, it's no good.
So, I just wanted to bring up
most of the discussion I have.
A great majority of it is questioning that, which I've also stated in the past that you will see
more discussion about it in the future, but none of it will still be accurate.
The other thing I want to bring up, whenever you bring up any holy writ of the world,
most people tend to comment, and I say this often, I'll say it again,
most people tend to comment, oh, the Bible, oh, the Koran, oh, the Rig Veda, oh, no.
You know what? I'm not religious. I don't want to know anything about it.
They're excused at that point, but let me just translate that for you,
what that could mean. It means that, yeah, I've been on this planet
long enough to see what these religions do and say,
and I'm kind of disgusted by it, and that seemingly is attached to that,
and I don't want anything to do with it.
So if you want to know why people don't want to hear a Biblical discussion or anything
regarding any language, or any other holy writ,
thank the religion that hijacked it.
Just think about that for a moment, because there's not one religion on the planet that does anything
that's in the text that they allegedly subscribe to. Yes, Islam as well.
And I had a discussion, why don't you talk about the Koran and Islam?
I said, well, because most of the audience, I'm presuming, is of the Western convention,
and the entire world, by the way, is what's called the Christian era,
so that they are also. Have you ever heard of Friday worship, by the way?
There is no Friday in the Koran, folks. I had someone trying to tell me there is.
I had someone once try to tell me that King James is the true
word of G.O.D. I mean, this is
really a commentary on humanity, not on that particular subject matter.
So you notice I've skirted the issue in chat. Tell us about what's important.
A few folks are hearing this down the stream. If you have some internet
access, and of course it might make you not feel well, because I just explained why,
what the time being,
let's say the middle of the first month, 13th, 14th, 15th, it's really
the 15th till noon, apparently, through measurement, observation,
it's an important time of, let's say an appointed
time. If you look up in any kind of a
biblical search, what is the 13th day of the first month?
And that already happened.
There might be something, perhaps more
discussion. I don't mind doing it. I've done many, many hours regarding
certain things that people could look up regarding many subjects, but
the biblical one as well, that everything that you've been told about it is false.
And also I want to throw out, I would
say that there is also a slew, and it plays a large
factor in the way people pursue things, and a slew of writings through the
years and ages regarding that, that are false as well.
I don't like to bring a pinpoint up exactly, but something called the Urantia
book was always brought up, and people that were older and well-studied, and shame on you
older folks, by the way. I always tell the young people, you're on your own,
look at these old fools. But anyway, that's
a very lazy assumption that someone's
going to make a commentary. How do you know, by the way, if you look
at something like the Urantia, how do you know it's false? By the way,
if you look at something like what's put in front of you in mainstream
religion that has captured the biblical text, whether it's New or Old Testament,
because there's a couple of religions that have done that, and a couple
too. By the way, when you're shown
through efficiency, when you see something called the Shroud of Turin,
how do you know that's false? Not that it's fake or real, it's just that it's
absurd. When you just look at it, if you know
what's called the Scripture, you will just look at it and in less than half a second
know that it's not the real thing.
When you look at what's memorialized as certain sites
and days regarding certain religions,
regarding things biblical, can you determine that they're a fraud and a fake
in just a second or two? You see? It's very
simple. Once you know something, you can see it right away.
I've explained how all of those things are
that way, by the way.
Anyone can look it up. But the thing is, once you start looking for
precision and accuracy in anything, it doesn't matter, even your own field,
the field that you might be working in, regardless of what it is,
you're not going to be that likable. Through history, I've noticed
that people that excel and gain mastership in any
field have a really hard time. But at some point,
they are rewarded. At some point, something is rewarding,
I should say. Let's just see.
We might have a caller
perhaps on the line.
Let's see. Caller, I wonder if you can hear me. If you can, say
hello. State your name and maybe your purpose.
Hello. My name is Valerie. Hi, Valerie.
Welcome to Uncommon Radio. What's on your mind?
Well, I had a report and a question
on your program
with Seth on Uncommon Sense.
Toward the end of it, you all spoke about dreams.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
My report is, as a young child, I was tormented
by dreams and nightmares.
Let me just help you think about that for a minute.
You were tormented, period,
and then through dreams and nightmares. The dreams
and the nightmares are what put the terror in you. And the thing is,
who was giving you the dreams and the nightmares? They're not your own. We've discussed that.
Thank you for bringing that up because all these subjects you see are connected, right?
I would suggest that
the tormented part is accurate, if you felt
that, right? There was an intent
to torment you, and the way that it was done is by dreams and nightmares.
Right, right. I understand that.
It's not you. It's not happening in your mind. It's put into you.
It was basically the crux that I've discussed in the past in great length.
Yes, yes. I understand that.
I've been working on that for the past year.
Oh, okay.
Yes. Very, very hard at it.
I can report I have had very few dreams.
And when I do dream, I do not repeat
them to anyone. I don't tell anyone.
And I think that has been to help me.
Also, another thing to suggest openly, I think I have, you can just rebuke them
during the day because they can't read your mind. They don't know what you're thinking.
But one thing that could be done is
if where you sleep has a door, just yell at them, tell them to get out and close the
door, and then you can just softly open it. They take offense to that,
some of them. I didn't want to speak over you, but that's really
exciting to me when I hear that what's being said, it has
effect in a positive way. Thank you.
Sorry, I'm a little nervous calling in for the
first time. I've really never spoken
on a talk show before, but I think this is important.
Thank you.
Also, I wanted to ask you a couple of questions.
You had on the 5th of
what they call January of this year, you had spoken about
Iran coming to the aid
of, well, maybe not coming to the aid yet of Israel,
but they would be friendly.
Now, would you say that
I'm assuming you're drawing that from a scripture, an old scripture.
Would you say that may be Daniel?
Possibly. And Revelation.
No, neither. I'll suggest,
and since you brought up Daniel in either one, I'm not drawing it from there. I'm drawing it from
Nehemiah, Ezra, Psalms,
Reason Why, and I'll just state this this way, and you realize discussing
and you don't, and I don't, and others don't, but this is a public
forum, and I've just finished saying that people don't like to hear this kind of
discussion because of what the religion has done. You're correct.
Yeah, and you'll see that throughout public life and in private as well.
But I would just suggest that, let's just give you a hint. I said this is like an open
members area, right? So let's just give some things that work, like dreams.
Everything repeats three times, if you notice, in scripture, and I say
everything mostly. Like you notice in the beginning, the beginning, the older part
of scripture is about what happens to a man or his family, and then it's what happens to
an entire nation, and then as you get into the later writings, it's all about
the same things happening to the entire world in similar fashion.
Okay. Right? So you'll have like a patriarch go through something, and then
the country goes through it, and then the whole world will be going through it.
Now, what you look at are certain repeats. If you look at
what they call the temple, you know,
the exile into Babylon,
71 years they went back, and they were starting to rebuild the temple, which was
mostly destroyed or broken down.
Now they came out of Babylonian exile. Who aided the
Judeans and the Israelites? Remember, you watch, I didn't say Jewish, right?
The Judean and the Israelites, financially and with
other support. It was Darius and Cyrus.
These were the Persian kings. So they assisted, and they actually
helped them when they were being hindered as well.
So that means that when this particular
edifice is suggested to be reconstructed, the majority
of the financial support, and let's say public
moral support and ethical support to do this, will be from the modern
Medes and Persians. Another thing I've suggested is that most people
don't know about what they call Iran or Persia,
is they have two governments. They have the political and the religious.
And one thing with Seth on a roundtable years ago, I said,
do you remember Ahmadinejad, the president before the current one?
He wore a Brooks Brothers suit, very western, right?
And I suggested that the next political leader is also going to be religious because you will
see a unification. And after a few months there, then that happened.
If you look at the current secular leader, he is also looking
more fitted in religious garb. And then you have the supreme
leader, Ayatollah, coming out and making political comments. So they're finding
middle ground as they're developing into this position.
Now by the way, the things that I discuss regarding the Middle East coming,
you have to comprehend and understand and take it to heart to some point
that none of this will change, no matter what people try. This is being done
by the gods, okay? No one can stop this.
That's why, you know, like I may not say
if you go to a strawberry, if you go to an ice cream parlor,
you should get strawberry or chocolate. No, no. If I have information that that particular
ice cream store is going to close in a year because they lose their lease, that's what I tell people.
What flavor you get in the meantime doesn't matter.
And that's what I like to discuss. So now your question
where I got that from, let's just go back and address those two things.
Look at scripture. When did the period
when Persia and the Medes and the Persians
helped the Judeans and the Israelites was only during the
Nehemiah-Ezra return period. So read that carefully. That will repeat.
Not exactly, but it's very similar. Now you mentioned Book of Daniel
and you mentioned Revelation. Let's do those two. Revelation is really a hands-off
book for most people at this point. Now it doesn't mean you shouldn't read it because
it's the only book that has a blessing for anyone who reads it out loud.
But it's quite the opposite if you comprehend it and read it to those
that are not qualified. Because the first verse states who
it's for. It's for the servants, not the believers, not the faithful, not the Christians,
not the Mets fans, not the Dodge fans, not the Republicans, just the
servants. And what is a servant, right? If you're a servant
and you tell the master all your rules are done away with,
you're not much of a servant. You'll get a boot you know where.
So I'll just say this again publicly.
I said this is an open members area. Let's make it juicy. If you comprehend the Book of Revelation
and you start explaining it to those that are not in that category, people will
start dying. And it's good science to say that.
Meaning good science is when you do something and something happens, if you repeat it,
the same thing happens. And you know that if you do this, this happens. That's what science is based on.
So I can tell you scientifically, if you comprehend the Book of Revelation
and you read it and explain it to those that are not in that servant class, people
will start to perish repeatedly. So don't do it.
I mean, unless you're in that position and also things will not be.
It's a very, very powerful. So in that
respect, the other one, the Book of Daniel, that is extremely misunderstood
because it has some unique qualities. And one of the unique qualities is that everything
in that is referencing to the gods. And it's one of the few books,
there's a couple of others that don't reference the name of the Most High.
Now, what's interesting also about the Book of Daniel, it is misunderstood
because it's taken out of context. And the context is, for example,
or what's taken out of context is, for example, there's a verse in there that says,
and many will travel to and fro and knowledge will increase. That's a very popular verse
in that book. And people say, oh, look, we have airplanes and we're traveling
and knowledge is increasing because of the Internet. That's not what it means.
And I'm suggesting when I say that's not what it means, I won't say it's solved dogmatically,
but let me just put it this way. Traveling to and fro means you're going to
be going places that you normally don't go and knowledge
will increase would be knowledge of the gods will increase, not
what's on the Internet. Now, if anyone has any sense that says
that means because of the Internet, knowledge is increasing. I mean, if you've gone to
any homepage of any browser, I mean, does that look like knowledge to you or does it look
like penile extension, hair loss and dolls? You know, it's really dumb.
It's all dummy loading. So when you read what's called
the Book of Daniel, that's regarding the gods and keep it in that
context and you'll be fine. And also another hint I'd like to give you since
you bring this up and I'll share that we're having a private conversation that's being broadcast publicly, let's say,
is that when you have a name, well,
if you want to hold on, I'll explain it and we'll catch you on the
second part. I would love to. Thank you. Okay. Thank you, Val.
See you on the second half, folks. Okay. Thank you.
Greetings and second hour
for Uncommon Radio on the 15th day of the first month.
Yeah, and I think we still have our caller. Valerie,
if she's present, I was trying to explain about how to. Yeah, great. Here you are. Okay.
Before the break, I was going on a short
monologue there on another hint on
what to comprehend or how to comprehend is when you're reading any of
the scripture, the people's names mean something,
whether it's Daniel or Jeremiah or whatever.
When the book is titled by someone's name, when you see the name being
repeated with redundancy in the text, do an etymological
search for what names mean and replace that phrase.
It's usually a phrase in the verse when the name is being
used. And now you will see more clarity in the verse itself.
So when you're reading, Daniel went to the lions,
let's say, or was sent to the lions. Well, find out what
Daniel means and replace the name with that short little
meaning of the name and then read it and you'll see things come more
to life. It'll be more vivid.
So those are some long-winded answers, which are typical Greek
fashion, but anything else on your mind? No, that's about
it, really. I mean, I have a lot of questions. I think a lot of people
have questions about the gods. I think you referenced
they have questions about that, about the universe.
Empty space. Well, the gods are just another society,
just intangible. Just like years ago, if you left
hot coals in a room, people woke up dead because of the carbon monoxide.
They called it ether. They didn't know what it was until they were able to measure it with carbon
monoxide detectors. We just have memorialized
information from the past regarding them, which people like
to ignore. And they're here. They're right here.
Oh, yeah. They operate on a longitudinal
Yes, and they operate on a different level. There's no
time and space or distance that means nothing.
They operate longitudinally. And just to prove that, Tesla was operating
in that form of power transmission. It was instant,
pretty much. So it's longitudinal.
Thoughts are longitudinal versus they're transverse, which is like
speed of light or speed of sound. Further something away as longer it takes, no matter how fast
you're going. They operate in more of an instantaneous way.
Another way to think about it is what's called counter space. And they have a society,
just like man has a society and a plurality. There's trillions of them.
Not billions, but trillions upon trillions. And they have a
very long lifespan. And they just happen to be intangible at the moment.
But you do see their effects if you know how to recognize them.
And you mentioned the gods and the other thing was the universe.
The universe is a term that's been used back and forth. And when we say that, let's just say
out there. Everything out there. Not in the fishbowl, but what's in the living room
and the apartment and out there in the city kind of thing.
It's very simple. You hear a lot of new ager types say, well, what the universe
sees it fit or whatever. It's just empty space, let's just say.
But again, as I started speaking tonight, you'll notice
that everything's connected through boundary layers. Whether it's gas, liquid, or
solid, you're still connected to everything. And space is not a true vacuum. There's still
gases out there. And they're more rarefied and imponderable.
You can't bring them to earth. So that's another level of discussion.
But one thing, let's just throw another little thing in there for people to think about regarding
outer space is that it's not as big as you've been told
and it's not as big as it's been perceived. And that will be more obvious
and actually be displayed in the future. I'd say starting in about
15 or 16 years from now. It'll be
very similar right now when you see all the pretty pictures of what's going
on out there that they show you. And by the way, we hardly get any more pictures. Everything seems
to be computer animated, computer graphic artwork. I would prefer
a blurry black and white over what vivid color fake stuff
they're showing. But regardless of all that stuff that
takes interest and what we're told is out there, it will be
the metaphor of what will start happening in 15 or 16 years would be as if you're
sitting in the movie theater right now enjoying the movie. The lights come on
and you see a white screen. But then the screen is pulled up and then
you see this brick wall behind the screen. I mean that's a real big
shock from the film you were just watching a few minutes ago or a second ago
that got you totally engrossed. And this is the level
of let's say esoteric emotion that people will be
experiencing. And after that point
there's many things we probably will discuss.
There's a lot of things to chew on. But I really appreciate you calling in
and I mean you don't have to go. You can stay but I just want to...
I would like to ask one small more question. Yes, please.
In regards to the dreams with little children
now I have a little child in my life and
sometimes when they're sleeping you can see them struggling
or whimpering, crying. Yes, wake them up.
And I do.
Is there anything I can do about that?
The same. The same you would do
just tell it to get out.
This is where I live and get away. And the other thing is the children
you know when a child comes to you and says there's a six foot tall dust bunny with
claws in the closet. There is.
As best as it can be presented to a human
let's say. It's usually denied and you know how
things are. You know how the society deals with that.
But it's not, it isn't like
as if it really was but it is that it's being put there.
And you don't want to really
here's a way to think about it
don't necessarily address the dream or the object or whatever
it's who's putting it there if you address because if they go away
then all of that rest of that stuff goes away.
And I think with a lot of the modern what you call
Christianity, demon possession
has kind of perverted what you can really do and what you're supposed to do
in that situation. Is that what you're saying? Yes.
What they do, they really do much at all
they bring it up. They've made a mockery of it.
They've made a mockery of it. Well they've made a mockery starting from the beginning
that there's only three people, three entities
in the universe. There's God, Jesus and the devil.
That's all they basically talk about. It's like worse than checkers.
There's
trillions of plurality of them
and if anything is discussed in the mainstream it's because
when I say anything discussed in the mainstream
has such importance let's say for thousands of years, it's for two reasons.
One is because they're trying to propagandize you to think a certain way so you don't find out the truth.
The other one is because the subject is just over boiling and they have to say something.
Either way it's just going to be pittance.
Think about it this way, they're just accommodating the mindset
and also they're accommodating their position to help themselves.
It's not that simple again. It's like chess. When you make a move
can you anticipate the next four moves?
This is what's been going on. Also when you throw in that humanity has been
censored because you have to remember at one point when all of this was
overt and also combine that with people having a lifespan
approaching a thousand, people were like, let's just get off this rock.
Then how would this whole thing proceed?
You've been as a society
shut down and there's no blame here. This is just an explanation
of what's going on in contrast with the description
because the description would be the exorcism let's say or these other things
but what's being put out in public is very, very
minor and almost asinine and has very little worth at all.
That's why the whole thing is can you be objective
and objectifying it and also
if you even do a cursory study on ancient writs, dreams are given
to you. They're put into you. If you look
in history when the dreams were explained throughout history, I was given
a dream. I had seen a dream. No one ever said these are my dreams
or I dreamt this. Now I dreamt this means I received it.
If you look at what's been memorialized for thousands of years regarding
dreams, it was always something that was inputted into you.
Now it seems to be people take ownership and origin of it
also which is a big mistake.
It's part of the dummy loading. All the things that I've discussed
let's connect back to it again.
I'm glad you've had some success.
You mentioned the censorship.
That would have been around the
5th century. Is that correct?
B.C. 2500 years ago.
That would have been the time of
approximately Jeremiah's time?
Yes. Quasi-quattro in Mexico.
The burning of the Library of Alexandria. The formation of almost all of the
religions in the world today. The formation of the way
things are taught at university. The Greek system shortly after
that. Many many things
put in place. When people refer, let's say I brought up the Greek aspect
to it. Oh the Greek philosophers are so great. Oh the university system, the medical
system is from the Greeks. Really? Really? Really? It's so good?
If it was so good and so great, how well has it served you as a society?
Not well. You're still in the you know what.
Because of it indirectly. It's just a tool.
When I say all the religions, Christianity was also
started around that time. The concept of this esoteric
thinking of how to control the masses. You have to realize
at one point when you were wealthy
even with the castles and things, they built moats.
You had to build high walls to protect yourself while you were sleeping.
You were always looking to devise a mechanism, a social mechanism
that would tell people that your wealth
is somewhere else. Not on this earth. Not in this lifetime.
To quell them. So now you could sleep easy, right?
So this type of philosophy or teaching
or devise of telling people that all of your wealth and
fortune will come in the next life was a way
they would support that. Because now they could
impose that on the masses to some degree and then have them quell down.
Right. All about control. All right well Greek, thank you for
taking my call. Oh thank you for calling. You're quite welcome.
Thank you Valerie. See you again. Ciao.
Okay and we are back to Uncommon Radio.
Thank you for calling in and I hope that input or the questioning
and the answers were effective to others as well
and of course this will be archived and if you like it, good. And if you don't like
it, even better because now you've got something to hate on. So either way
it will capture your energy or use some energy either way. So let's
perhaps go back. This is external input of course.
We're talking about how dreams are external and of course most
of this has been forgotten because it's been memorialized or it's not
popular or fashionable to think that you can take responsibility for your
thoughts. Hmm, what did I just say? Yes, taking responsibility
folks. So if I look at the chat, there's still some
question regarding, it seems there's a lot of question
regarding this part of the month on the first month and what it's
about. Hmm, but either way
I would just suggest that if you look at anything
you know, look
if you have a question. Let's just phrase this. I'm thinking about how to phrase this.
If someone has a question or yourself, you have a
question let's say regarding a subject. Do some
hmm, would you say research
so you could structure the question a little bit better and also when you do the research
what do you really see? You know, when you come across a piece
of information that you might want to question
perceivably to someone who might be able to give
you an answer. Do a little bit of cursory research to structure it a little
bit more, a little tighter because
what I'd like to do regarding a certain religion
and a certain perception, a world view of a particular Biblical
character, actually the most important character who comes up twice a year
allegedly celebrating. I would suggest that everything that you're
being told regarding mainstream religion and alternative religion and alternative
is completely false. Your first
sign by the way if anything Biblical discussion comes up that you
probably are not going to be getting accurate information is somewhere
in the discussion there should be a preface that what the public
considers to be the Biblical text is not the Biblical text essentially. It's not
the scripture, it's a version. And the second thing that should come up
is time. Because there is no January through December, Monday
through Friday. Not only there but anywhere since 1500
or something. So you know I think I brought this up
there are many things that people may not be interested in but it's interesting when you bring up lawful time
and someone says, I'm really not interested in keeping lawful time.
That's really a wonderful specimen
when you look at the, well a wonderful
specimen to exhibit what has been described
as humanity at this point. Yes I'm not going to say the M word again
because it starts with a capital R.
This is your average earth inhabitant these days. So if you're listening here
you're probably not average. So anyway, again back to the
chat. It's still really very intensive
on this. So maybe I'll bring something up. Here we have someone
regarding the Passover. Could the report on today
being the end of Passover start of Unleavened Bread Feast be addressed?
Well what else is there to address?
This stuff is very simple. It's really an appointed time.
So either way we'll leave that alone
and back to Uncommon Radio. And again the second hour as I do on the
first hour I want to thank everyone who has contributed to AFR to show your
vote of support for the Greek on
Uncommon Radio on AFR. And the reason why is
because there was something much to do about
what to do. And there's
much that needs to be discussed and which can be discussed. And here's
the thing folks. Most of the stuff that should be discussed and could be discussed
at this point is really not for public consumption. It's typically
let's just say well then who is it for? Was it for the private? Well no let's just say okay
who is it for? It's for a non-carnal mind.
Now what does that mean?
Not the basic aspect.
Most people are living in denial. I'll give you an example.
The non-carnal mind. The non-body lustful type of
head. Which it's fine to be lustful I guess
because your body will draw you there lawfully. But I would say
well I should say I guess. But when it's just
based on you even being deceived whoever you are
about how the body even works and how the mind and the breath or the soul
is connected to it. Yes because you're made up of three things. The mind
your breath and your body.
This kind of discussion
only fits well or actually more information that could be said and should be said
to those that have got a firm grip on let's say that basic reality.
What I call HQ or headquarters. If you don't know who you are
how are you going to know about things that are not you?
Or outside of you? Remember the help yourself first idea?
Yeah but help yourself first and maybe
how do you do that? Where do you get the example for that?
You see that's kind of difficult. One also suggests that your operating system
is quite important. How you run. How you compute or rationalize things.
And that comes from your God. And there are a lot of default Gods which don't
address themselves as such or identify themselves as such. In other words
the state is in that position. Patriarchs
are in that position. And I just want to throw something else out
there. If you read some ancient writs there's a concept of a father
by the way. And one of the things there is you have the
physical father obviously.
Which is the physical aspect.
And then you have the spiritual father which is where you get your
law and education from. Sometimes they're the same. Rarely they are though.
That's why for example in some religions the
patriarch of the community is called father.
And that's why there is a verse somewhere that says that Satan is your father.
And the people that it was addressed to. There was this whole
spin off on this mainstream Christian community say oh well
you see Satan had sex with this woman and they're descendants from that. No it has nothing to do
with that. What you do and how you operate. Where you've gotten that information
is your spiritual father. Not your physical.
So where you get your law from or meaning from a human agent
as well are deemed as such.
So you have a spiritual aspect to it. For example if you had a really good mentor
that was a man. He could be called your
father in respect to that.
There's much stuff to be done. Much stuff to be done
regarding communication.
How can ideas which by the way I've also said
and anyone can determine this with maybe 15 years of research
that everything is information based. When you look through a telescope or a microscope
or yourself. It's not the chemicals or molecules or
energy that's holding it together. It's information that's holding it together.
And that is another thing that will be discovered. And it's bantied about. And by the way
when you hear stuff about quantum and all this other stuff that might deal with that
and consciousness. That's all breakfast cereal types.
Breakfast cereal is made up of fruits, nuts and flakes.
I'm just tired of those things. Anyway the quantum stuff.
So being able to communicate clearly
and saying what you mean and meaning what you say and having a comprehension
of where things came from maybe.
And maybe one way is modern society feels like they have to
rediscover or discover where things came from and maybe just ignore
anything that's been memorialized prior. Isn't that kind of foolish?
Why would you want to reinvent the wheel?
You know there was a writer or a film also. I think it was
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy where they went to a planet and in the film
and I believe in the book as well. I have not read that book but
regarding the society a commentary was that they invented the aerosol can
before the wheel. In this case society has
invented evolution, all of these social
maladies called mainstream religion,
mainstream university and all these other little cliques in societies.
Well I wouldn't say society has invented them. There's leaders over that also.
And it's kind of like the aerosol can coming before the wheel because in the
modern sense what you're doing and when I say they've invented them
I mean reinvented them in the past hundred years is ignoring anything that has
come before that. Now whether you're looking at anything scientific regarding
natural philosophy, the physical world, the gods,
nature, medicine, society,
history, you've got to go back more than a century
ago. Let's just say
you've perhaps heard that society has been in the credits part of
this epoch, this 6,000 year epoch let's say
since 1998, the fall roughly around that time until now.
When you think about it it's almost 20 years already, quite almost.
Well the century that came before that
let's just break them up, typically they're broken up in 50 year
segments, was kind of the wrap up century
at the end of that also. So look at what's being wrapped up when things are
wrapped up they're closed down. Look at your history or the history from the
late 19th century till the present which it seemed to have stabilized around the
1950s or 60s or 70s. Look at how that was more of a
shutting down than an opening up of a mindset to
get people prepared.
This kind of talk by the way might be a little too
big, meaning that it's discussing the infrastructure.
The reason why is I bring
up the concept that people ask what is the meaning of life, what is the meaning of this, what is the
meaning of that, and it seems to be self-centered within
the microcosm or duration that they live in.
Humans or people tend to live 70, 80, 90, even 100 plus
years. That is too short to comprehend the infrastructure that has been
placed. It's like having a discussion where people are
commuting let's say 20 minutes a day on a public rail to go to work
or whatever using the bus or at a given amount of time. It's very rare
that you hear them discussing the infrastructure, the millions of man hours
and all of the material and effort and design that has gone into design
let's say that big commuter rail line or ferry or whatever.
People don't discuss those things when they're riding the infrastructure.
They typically just discuss little chit-chat
or they might be continuing on discussing something that they started
before they entered that monorail, no pun intended.
Very little discussion in public about what's going on
in public as they see it. Of course, there's the invisible ring
in the nose that you will find in mainstream media and of course
alternative media and wherever else you go that everyone seems to be following
the same story. It's a story, folks.
It's kind of like a show. I think we defined what shows are
or show etymologically perhaps could mean to deceive.
Again,
if anyone does feel, I always want to state
that this is the fourth time the Greek is coming around solo
and the what to do next and the support that could be garnered
and all this other stuff will be determined by you folks.
As AFR tends to get more support,
we might actually consider, who's we, just from the Greek's perspective
what to do next because as I just spent the past few minutes discussing,
there's much that could and should be said but perhaps not for public
open in public. So how that can be
packaged and given out is again to be
determined and it is going to be by you folks as well.
So I see there's still more discussion about time
and lawful timekeeping in the chat.
With that said, I'm going to see, there were a couple of other
interesting emails perhaps that could be addressed
because they tend to be sort of quote unquote universal.
They apply to many of the thoughts that other people have
and I see that by grading, not by higher or lower or whatever
but by separating or correlating the subject matter
and many people are asking
they don't know each other I think or perceivably are asking very much of
the same questions.
Let's just see here. We have someone calling in
on Skype. Let's see if we can bring them in.
We're going to have to do it
another way because if I answer this it will put the call
on hold. So I see
perhaps it is Seth Michael calling. Seth if you hear me
you have to go to Skype
and do a contact request
and the contact request in the search box you would put
in UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com
and then, oh I see you have it. You have
done that perhaps. My fault. Just hold on folks. I'm trying
to walk and chew gum if possible.
Let's see if it can be done here. If I could probably
do that
and bring Seth in. No, it's not letting me do it
at this moment. Let's see how that will happen in the future.
Bear with me. We have a little bit of dead time.
Okay. So the future endeavors of what can be discussed
and what shouldn't be discussed perhaps
and what shouldn't be discussed is what isn't being discussed
let's say. But what is being discussed maybe isn't worth
listening to mostly out there. That's why henceforth
UncommonRadio. So let's see. I've sent the contact there and it's not
letting me open it for some reason. It would be interesting to have Seth
come on if you folks can just bear with this little bit of
downtime. Let's see. There's about a half hour left. So we will try
it this way. Let's go. We'll do it like this. And I've
got it. And let's bring him around
and bring him in. Let's do it like that.
There we go. Let's see if it works. Okay.
That doesn't seem to be working. Sorry about that, Seth. It's trying
to bring you. Oh, it's his group call. Okay.
Sorry, folks, for the little bit of dead air. No, it's not letting me bring
him in. If AFR can drag him in,
that would work as well. Okay.
Got it. Okay. So anyone who has contributed
by the way and has shown the effort has been really
grand, folks. I have not expected that much support from the public
listening at large. But it's still a little shy of our goal.
And if we do reach that goal, I will make it
public that we have. And these things are determinations to be made
because you want to kind of measure what kind of interest people have and what's
being said. But in terms of bringing up subject matter
and fashioning some kind of package of information to
discuss on these calls, it has not been done. It's just pretty much show up
and just discuss what could be discussed.
In the future, perhaps, it will be much more structure
and create a
sense of more structure and
more information to be imparted without being pedantic. Seth, do we have you
on Skype? I believe so. There you are. Greetings.
Greetings. Salutations. Well, thank you. You're really low.
You might want to up your volume a little bit. Is that better?
Yes, that is. Yep, you're here now. Great. So what's
on your mind? It's been a while. And you're on radio
as well. So go ahead. Share some thoughts and
whatever you like. It has been a while. I'm grateful
as you read that brief email earlier
for pretty much the same reason. You're speaking about things that
are not being spoken about with any semblance of accuracy anywhere
else. And when I realized that you had this going on,
which was yesterday, I went and
downloaded the archives of this
latest Sonic Endeavor and
listened to it. And you're doing really well.
So there's that. And still bringing information that's not
available in one place.
You have a tendency to go kind of scattershot
with the topics, like a shotgun blast of
information from many distant and
dissimilar sources and kind of bringing it all together in a way that's
rare. So yeah, I'm glad to hear that you're doing
it again. I have kind of a subpar
connection. So if I drop, I apologize. That'll be rectified here in a few
days. But I put a question in chat earlier.
I was finishing up my shift at the Job
and I put the question in
not dissimilar to what I asked actually
last night about
today being the, and today not the date,
but today being Peshach or Passover.
Because as you're well aware, it's something that I'm very interested in.
And I was admittedly a little bit
confused about what today is.
And the site that I normally reference,
barring personal observation,
listed the last full moon as being
the 12th of what they call March.
And so I was just curious as to how
can one be relatively certain with their own observation?
Oh, you know, here's the thing.
Thank you for doing that because
here's the public
display of error. You're correct. It is the
end of the first week, isn't it?
That's what I was thinking.
Peshach is next week.
That's kind of what I was after.
Last month, actually, I observed it,
the wife and I, because I was unaware of the 13th month
until I spoke to a mutual friend of ours just the other day,
like two days back.
That worked out well because of the measurement.
But the Peshach is, today would be the 8th day
and the 15th would be next week. So there you go.
Greek gave out erroneous information.
Well, if it was the 12th, today would be the 10th or the 11th day.
Unintentionally. Well, thank you. Thank you for the correction. That's right.
So it is the end of the first week and the Peshach would be the 13th
and the 14th, which is the dark moon next week.
Okay. Now, I'll ask another question just because,
as you've said a number of times
on this program specifically, this is kind of like a pseudo-members only
area and you might discuss things publicly that
you haven't in the past, at least in a public fashion.
That was the other part of the question that I asked earlier was
the significance of, not today, but a few days from now,
Peshach, how that is observed and
how it was observed in that event
that was so poorly captured in that very famous painting known as the Last
Supper, which is absurd. I mean, they're all sitting
around a table for one. Well, that is absurd, yeah. But also
I have to preface again, we don't have a translation and the other thing
is when we bring up biblical discussion, most people in public find it very
distasteful because of what the religion and the culture has done.
Understandably. But if this were the member section,
then what care would the public? Oh, the open members. Okay. Well, it's very
simple. The Last Supper is, the only commentary that could be done on that
would be a commentary that you would possibly do on
art, just art commentary. It has nothing, it has probably a lot
to do with Peshach and nothing to do with biblical. I'm sorry. Yeah, I didn't mean
to, I'm not even asking about the painting. I was just kind of making a joke
about the painting. I'm not concerned with the painting at all.
The Last Supper was an observance of Peshach.
Yes, yes, right, exactly. But it's not given as such because
if you look at the confines and how the
King James and the society was structured to put forth that version, they didn't
want them to go down that pattern of law and religion.
So they had to make something else.
Yeah, because if you bring that up, oh, that sounds Jewish, doesn't it?
That's a lot of the commentary that you get still. Oh boy, how did I miss out a whole week?
I missed a whole week out publicly. There you go, folks. I'm fallible.
No, I'm quite fallible. There you are. Thank you for calling and stressing the importance
because I actually observed that yesterday and we're going to do it again.
Thank you, folks. Maybe I was taking up on the
mothership for a little too long, but it shows you what kind of
a week I've had here behind the scenes. So let's just say
the Last Supper wouldn't be a Last Supper directly. It would be, yes, that observation
of that day called the Passover or the Peshach, which was
if you look at the ordinance
being stated in the text, it has prophetic importance.
It's not just an occurrence or do this because I say so. It has a very
significant prophetic symbolism as well
of things to come as they are or as they were and as they will be.
How about say it that way? The interesting thing there is
to show if you comprehend how capital punishment was
put forward in those days. It was death by stoning
and the position that the
victim was in delineated or denoted the
severity of the crime and the highest crime would be nailed to a tree.
After all these things had been done, all the contents,
the body, the corpse and the possessions of the person were burned.
So that's why when you look at certain aspects of how it was
done in the Last Supper, there was a slight anomaly there where he
was trying to indirectly state that this bread is my body, not that
lamb because the lamb is thrown into the fire.
Anything that's left after
the consumption of the feast by those partaking is
thrown into the fire. It's not given as scraps to the animals or anything like that.
The whole thing is thrown into the fire.
That's why, for example, when this individual was buried, the tomb had to
be guarded because the Judean authorities wanted to go and claim the body and finish that
particular ordinance.
It was quite important to understand
these things from a codified point of view, the technical
aspect of how these things are done and then apply them to what is going on
regarding that scene. That's why earlier I mentioned it would be very easy
once you do look at any body of work or something that is
let's say memorialized
to look at it very closely and get as much out of it as you can. Don't read into it.
That's why earlier I mentioned again, if you look at a lot of these ancient
religious relics, how can you denote them immediately as being untrue
or fraudulent or not pertaining to this thing? Just by looking at it
quickly. One of the simplest things that you would see in
modern, let's say, parlance when you see something, a guy nailed to a
cross and all that stuff, you know that has nothing to do with the biblical text
obviously. When you see relics, leftover pieces
of that, how you see that often still bantied about in
society, certain religious circles, that can't be either because all of that
was burned. It's very easy
to seek out the truth and find it.
Yeah, I would say that it is easy
in one respect because the source material
and the current time that we find ourselves
is easily accessible to anyone who has access to
Internet.
I didn't mean it that way. Sorry, I stepped on you for a minute. What I meant is once
you have a good handle on the reference materials, it's easy
to spot the fakes and the frauds and no arguments afterwards.
No, no, but actually getting the reference point is very, yeah, to discern
it, yes. But no, the hardest part is, actually you might spend your whole life
trying to get it and not, is to get the ground
reference material, like learning how to read a tape measure, right, to go on a
construction site. There are people, laborers on construction sites for 30 years who still don't know
how to accurately read a tape measure. So, yeah, no, no, I didn't
mean, I meant the easy part was discerning what's put out there, yes, thank you.
Because, no, actually, it sounds
very simple. If you get a hold on the reference material, that's simple
and that is not easy at all. No, that is very difficult
because you cannot approach anything anymore
on your own loosely without reading into it.
That's the start of any, to clear your mind and read
out of it, look at it objectively. Many people look at anything, whether it's
historical or biblical or whatever. When the subject comes up, let's say about this, they say
oh, I saw this in the movies. This is what my parents told me. This is what I saw
and they read over it. Instead of seeing what is
actually being said, they say I'll just skip over this because I saw it in the movies.
It's all false. They deny what's right in front of them in writing
memorialized.
Yeah, I've heard it said that it's a lot easier to
trick someone than it is to convince someone that they have been tricked.
Yes, and also it's easier to fool 7 billion
people than one because if you fool one, the
other 6,999,000,000 and so will correct them but if you fool the 7 billion,
the one that sees it, he's under great opposition.
Wow, I'm still reeling from the shock from having
the time off. I want to almost play a song about that.
Thank you for
chiming in on that. It was important to get it out on air
because if I'm on next week, guess what? I'm going to start
as if it comes around, it will be the 15th also. Think about it.
So that will be an interesting correction
to have and thanks for making that point.
Yeah, indeed. There was speculation on that very
point in chat so I figured that I would.
Yes, but that's good. I started seeing all that and I was wondering, you know, I'm being a little too sure
about this and all that speculation, all that jumping around and all
that is kind of good
because if I would have said, yeah, I was just testing everyone, it's really not the
15th, I'm just trying to see who is really paying attention, that would have worked also
but actually, I didn't know. I fled the scene
consciously and that's why I was wondering why it was stuck on there
but the chat seems to be like a little clubhouse sometimes, I guess, for each
what they call host of a show, which I don't like using the word show, it means to deceive
but this was not meant to deceive. This was one of these, I was actually
blinded to the fact of taking it for granted
that 14 days had gone by since the last time I came on and it was
only 7. So talk about lost time.
But I hope things have been well with you and I appreciate
let's say the appreciation and the approval
of Uncommon Radio and you coming on.
I've always gotten very positive criticism about, I really liked
it when you came on and did stuff with Seth, so that was always
a very good positive thing to do but this time, I decided to go
around solo just to keep it going because I think it's
you might remember when we used to do round tables somewhere else, I used to say,
I'm not here to talk to people, I'm here to throw rocks.
I'm not going to be
toilet papering anyone's house, just rocks, just stones.
There is a time that's going to be coming,
it's not now, it's roughly a year from now where this period
if the chronology seems to be correct, you will see changes and at that point
it's going to be very popular to start catching up
on thousands of years of things that people have essentially been blinded to
and based on the cosmic censorship, that will start to change
because remember when the gods do something
you have to be in full knowledge of it or enough knowledge that you know
it's the gods that are doing it and that's going to be
an interesting time. I always used to say in private, I'll say it now that
anyone, any of these biblical patriarchs that you read about would give their left testicle
to live today where we are in this time period. It's a joke.
Joking with them because
there's a lot of humor in there as well. The seriousness
of the time period that we're living in
has to be perceived with the cosmic
irony that's been throughout society.
Other times when people were far away from things becoming
overt, they were very conscious of them being overt and now
the time is actually coming where many things will become
overt, no longer hidden. People are not conscious of it.
They tend to discuss it to some level but they have no specifics
and with no specifics, now you're like a boat without a rudder.
You're just going with the flow. I think
much of the information that could be thrown out is probably best
given with specificity and to guide
the thought. Not how to think or what to think but
if the thought exists or the subject matter exists, a slight criticism and a little bit of
info might be a correction factor.
Redundancy does that, like oversampling does it.
A lot of the things that is going to be said perhaps here
and by others is going to be redundant, just repeating. I've gotten a comment recently
I've listened to all the archives and all this and you're just repeating the same thing.
Out of all that stuff that's been repeated,
which one don't you get yet?
Just as a case in point in validating
that repetition is necessary, we've
spoken at great length
about the observation of the day.
What day is it? I still struggle
with it. Like I said, I totally missed
the fact that there was a 13th month in the
previous year. For the past
however many days, I've been a month
ahead, inaccurately obviously.
I got a call. I spoke to
a friend just a couple days ago that I hadn't spoken to in a while.
He mentioned that observation.
I wanted to get in touch and get a little bit of clarity on that.
When I saw the response that the question had garnered in chat,
I figured that I would call in.
Thank you. That's good because it got me going as well because I had not been out looking.
I've just been counting and miscounting to some degree
by a week off. Somehow I had lost a week, which is
okay. Worse things have happened.
I just want to go back to the 13th month. That's like a squaring off
time. I went through that live
as I was ending the previous Sonic episode
with Chuck O'Chelly. I just ended that one
I think at 12 episodes or something and then jumped immediately next week and started this.
In real time, we were discussing the 13th moon, why
it's the 13th moon and how the first one came around again. The easiest observation for
that was if you're familiar with any landmarks or buildings or windows that are
lined up with Cardinal east and west, you will notice the sun coming
in dead square, northern or
southern hemisphere. The sun would be completely squared off
to the east. If you have a wall or something
that casts a shadow. You said Cardinal
so not magnetic, but astronomic north.
Astronomic north, yes. Not magnetic at all.
Magnetic could be off quite a bit.
Magnetic, I tend not to refer to that
much. The Cardinal is garnered from the ecliptic. It would be the centerline
from where the sun passes in the summer to where the sun
passes over the earth in the winter. The moon and the sun, you can do that at any
time of year. Juxtapose that and a centerline through those movements
or the gates. It came through the center gate.
What's interesting is once you do this, find a landmark.
I have a landmark, for example, when the first and seventh month come around.
They're slightly different on height. There is almost like a hole in a
door with what they call the viewing hole or a peephole type thing.
It's so square that it puts a brilliant white dot on the wall
only for a few days during that time of year, very much like a
sundial would. Not a typical sundial,
but the ones in India, let's say. If anyone wants to see
some interesting solar monuments, go ahead and do a search
on a browser. Sundials in India.
You'll see some of them are several stories tall and they're very abstract
looking.
We have another
week until the middle of the month.
It's interesting how the chatter in the chat
was directed that way and I somehow
couldn't see it until you called in. Thank you very much.
My pleasure. It's good to hear that you're
doing this. I hope that you're able to get into more of
what I say with hesitance is
being Scripture. Yes. Well, that time will come.
That time will come roughly beginning in a year from now. But if you recall
years ago when you and I first started
speaking, I said that there will be much more discussion regarding
seemingly Scriptural or Biblical topics, but none of it will be
accurate. But the direction people's attention will be going
that way until a time in the future when
some of the censorship is lifted and it's deemed to be accurate.
So you might notice that for years now
and that time to be accurate is yet a time in the future.
Other than perhaps what anyone who can give accurate information
is, and it's not exclusive to the Greek, it's exclusive to anyone who can
read out of it instead of reading into it.
There's a lot of information there.
Well, the interesting thing about any of these older
writs is there's a lot of redundancy.
Much like a jigsaw puzzle, it's very redundant because
you're always looking at each piece along the edges to see what
piece it will fit next to. It's the same methodology with each
piece of a jigsaw puzzle. You're memorizing and learning
what it should fit into by looking at the
geometry, let's say, on the edge of a puzzle piece. And then you always have to compare it to the
main picture to field it. What part of the
geographically, let's say, on the table where the piece goes. But the redundancy
in putting a jigsaw puzzle together is immense because you're always
studying the edge of the piece that is supposed to interlock into another.
And that's basically how these works work, I should say.
Yeah, you mentioned
earlier that things are often
repeated three times in the text.
And one of the reasons, I guess
this is sort of anecdotal or anecdotal, I've never been clear on the
pronunciation of that word, but one of the
things that has made me concern myself
with the observation of what they call Passover
is that it's mentioned in the text
at least there is
a call to observe it
at least seven times in different
texts comprising what's referred to as Scripture
at least seven times that I can
think of directly. So it seems
perhaps that it's something of import to those who view
such things as being worthwhile.
Well, check this out. Okay, seven times
yes, it gives it some import. Now when you want to find the import of the import
you look at the fourth time that it's being mentioned. Where is
it mentioned for the fourth time? Because when you're counting seven
the fourth position is really the first position
and the one and the seven are first and last. You'll notice they'll be equal.
So what I'm suggesting there, again, whoever's listening
if you want to start, quote unquote, decoding, I'm using that term lightly
the number seven or when something is mentioned
seven times, try to seek out the fourth time and you will find
it is the most important. And with that, thank you very much. This is the
fourth time around and on the eighth day of the
first month. Thank you Seth and thank you AFR and don't forget to
send some credits to AFR if you folks can. Greek signing off.
Ciao.