Greetings everyone, it's the Greek, it's Uncommon Radio time again, and it could be
uncommon sense or Greek speak, however you would like to call it.
And this is American Freedom Radio, and this is also a place where you are welcome to call in
and participate somehow.
If, just right out of the gate, I'd like to say the number for calling in
to Uncommon Radio would be 218-339-8525.
That's 218-339-8525.
And for the Skype, if you prefer better clarity, you can go to uncommonradio.com,
www.uncommonradio.com, and there you will see an e-mail which is uncommonsenseradio1
at gmail.com, and that's a numeric one.
And that is also the Skype contact.
And what I will do in the meantime is bring up the phone lines and perhaps get that started.
And again, it's the Greek.
This is the sixth time around.
We've been archiving these as solo, solo one all the way through five.
Now, this perhaps would be number six.
I would suggest that it'll be a carryover or follow-through of what was discussed last week,
which was number five.
And the reason I'm bringing up the numbers is because, indeed, numbers do matter in this case.
There is a convention that sort of lies behind it.
It's a form of numerology perhaps, maybe, maybe not.
It's a form of Dematria, maybe, maybe not.
But let's just say that numbers are important.
It's rational communication.
So I'm going to try to bring up the phone lines and see if I could walk and chew gum today.
And speaking of today, by the way, for a time marker, on the Pope's work schedule, it's what they call April 6, 2017.
But I would say lawfully it's the last week of the first month, and I would suggest it's about the 28th day of the first month.
So also I wanted to bring that up real quick because there's been a lot of chatter on chat regarding timekeeping.
And, yeah, I did get thrown it back.
I was not doing the observation about two weeks ago.
I think I'm back on track.
I haven't done due diligence to the point where I can really have a good verification or validation of it.
But I would suggest that forming records like that for oneself is just for oneself.
To do them formally, there is a social rank that is almost required to do it.
It's to make it official.
So is there a right and wrong?
Yes.
I wouldn't say anyone is particularly wrong, but I wouldn't say anyone is particularly right spot on because there's an element of authority.
But you have to understand this is a different type of society.
Just because you're born into it doesn't mean that it's correct or right.
So we'll get into that.
I think I have the phone board up now as well.
So with that said, we'll probably continue.
Number six, I had gotten an e-mail also regarding something that pertains to that.
I don't think the person who just e-mailed is aware of it.
But I see these things in a certain order, and I like to communicate them.
What you will find by listening to Greek speak or on common radio is there's not a lot of who-gee-was-its and we don't know and a lot of descriptions.
This is what you're going to get in the world today.
And when I say in the world, I mean university, all of your people that are imparting in academia.
Now, by the way, academia means theoretical and practical, not leading to a conclusion.
Alternative media, mainstream media, what you will do is approach all of these mediums of informational exchange or impartment.
Now, by the way, they're typically entertainment, but let's just say people don't consider it as such.
Why?
Well, because at a very young age, I remember watching – this is when just black and white televisions were on.
A woman, a very old woman, a Greek grandma type came over from Europe, and she was actually crying watching cowboys and Indians get shot.
And it had to be explained to her that these are actors because where she had come from when people were shot so realistically, it appeared to be real.
So what I would like to suggest is a lot of the information that people are getting I think is real, even if it is contrary to the convention, which is allegedly what the alternative media is.
So I just wanted to bring up a few points like that.
You won't get too much of the stuff you hear everywhere else, so be prepared.
And if you're here and you don't understand anything that's being said and you can't follow along, that's great.
You are completely normal, and you'll be fine.
You just do what you're told, and you'll be fine.
Actually, oh, wow, here's an old colleague or young colleague.
Okay, here. Hello, Chuck.
Okay, let's just say the Greeks speak about the war that is now in progress in Syria or has been.
Okay, that's interesting. That's good.
I did think about that a little bit.
I mean the war is not good, but there's many levels to that.
Very often when things can be explained, it's not in the television sitcom way.
I have not, by the way, been up to snuff on what's going on in terms of the progress with Syria,
because I discussed what that area would be a point of contention along with Turkey as well as Iraq over a decade ago with specifics why.
The one thing about knowing what's coming is you don't necessarily know how it's going to come, but you know it's going to arrive.
So I'm not really aware of the progress part, but Syria is an interesting aspect.
If you understand the history of Syria, and it's not what you've been told, by the way, well, of course.
There's a lot of people pontificating things.
How many times have you heard, like, oh, the pyramids were built 35,000 years ago or whatever.
It's not a matter of arguing that if it's 35,000 or 5,000 or 3,000 or whatever.
It's just that these pieces of information are given out without any form of backup, or they seem to be noncontinuous.
They just kind of jump out of whatever.
But discussing Syria, if anyone wants to plug in anything specific about the war in Syria, because it's not really a war.
Here's the many levels that you can't really come out and answer something immediately.
When you listen to Greek speaker things along this, anyone else explaining or trying to give an explanation, not just a description.
There's no pat answer to do it.
There's many levels, and typically three.
It's like almost three doors that you have to go through.
One is the door of perception.
The other one is the gathering of the information, and the last one is basically hashing it all together.
And remember, information is not just what it's about because it's tied into the perception.
Like, for example, I give the example of forensic crews that look very closely where others have said they looked and they have not.
That's why the word, for example, research means you've already searched it out.
Most quote-unquote researchers are just searchers.
It's all searching.
So when you have everything, then you go back and look at it again.
So in this case, looking at what's called Syria, again, there's a certain mindset that needs to be sort of considered.
Or let's say I invite people to consider a certain mindset.
How about that?
And the mindset would be that if it's impending that there is going to be a loose confederacy of nations in the Middle East,
the formation which is going to be starting around next year and pretty much be beginning as a union,
as a loose confederacy of nations around what's called 2025, 2026, around there, perhaps even 2024,
one must consider what it takes to have a loose confederacy or union of nations.
Typically, I don't like to use the EU, European Union, as an example,
because that is just an achievement of the old National Socialist Party.
You folks know them as the Nazis, and that's the National Socialist Party.
One of their main goals was to unite Europe under Germany.
They had succeeded with that.
As a matter of fact, most of the EU mumblings and rumblings were in the late 90s,
but I think around the mid-2000s or so last decade, they had their 50th anniversary.
So how can that be?
So if anyone wants to look into that history, that is not what I'm discussing.
What is interesting about this Middle East confederacy that is coming around,
it is not going to have a centralized aspect to it.
Now, one can see, let's just jump around a little bit.
At this point, this is the precursor to the formation.
This is not the formation.
This is the precursor.
Now, let's just consider something on a very rudimentary level.
If you're going to have a group of nations, in this case it's ten,
which only nine are on the map.
But in this case, or any case, if you're going to have a loose confederacy of nations
or a group of nations forming together to work together,
and in the type of alliance that one can say is a form of a union
or a centralization of world power,
you cannot have nationalistic or unstable governments
or those that would run the central power base of each country
or are known to run as being over-nationalistic.
In other words, another way to say it is if you have a group of nations
that are having border squirmishes, political squirmishes that are bordering each other
or even just skipping a few borders,
there is no way you're going to form a relaxed enough atmosphere for them to work together,
for it to be the actual world center for almost every aspect of humanity.
Think about that for a minute.
Again, I don't like using the European Union because that would be misleading
to say it's going to be like that.
But if you comprehend on several levels, the level of nationalism that had,
let's say pretty much the norm of the day in Europe prior to what's known as World War II,
that would have been very difficult to establish what has been established now with the EU.
And when you look at it consecutively,
it's past the cessation of hostilities that led to the reforming,
not immediately, or the forming, I should say, of the EU.
What you're witnessing in what's called the Middle East right now
is actually various aspects of what I'm discussing,
as well as a global aspect that it is the starting line of a particular event,
meaning the civilization of mankind.
And because all things are sort of spiral or circular,
you might actually be witnessing the finish line.
So this is a discussion that can be elaborated on over and over and over.
One thing one can actually observe at this time,
other than all the things going on, not only in Syria,
because there's also other countries that are, let's say Yemen,
and Lebanon has been in shambles since the civil war.
Iraq has been sort of like a really big mess.
And so on and so on around even the, if you go northeast,
the former Soviet Union countries that are now sovereign again, supposedly.
You could pierce around the veil and see how things get a little unstable
as you use what's called the Middle East as the epicenter.
But the most unstable would be the Middle East.
And I'm using the term Middle East because that's a simple way to communicate it.
So you can see the instability.
But where you will find stability is the two current, let's just say,
not even in name only, but simple descriptive, let's say analogously,
you can say that Israel and Iran are the superpowers of the Middle East right now.
Yes, there's a lot of attention to Saudi Arabia and Dubai and other UAE
and other places like that.
But I don't really want to get into too much of their history
because that would be UAE and Saudi Arabia and all that
because you cannot be very objective about those places or those nations.
The reason is because no matter how objective you are,
it sounds like you are not saying good things about them.
So I would rather just leave them alone and remain neutral on the approach,
not only neutral on that.
But I would consider that what, let's just put it this way,
what the Greek had put out and parted over a decade ago
is that the main aspect of this, let's just say loose confederacy of nations,
is going to be the number of nations that come on the scene,
and that number is 10.
And there's a list of them in scripture.
But if you look at that list, and it's not listed like a laundry list, by the way,
it's actually part of a verse regarding Assyria.
And what's interesting about that is Assyria does not exist.
And now I said Assyria, A-S-S-Y-R-I-A-N.
The Assyrian people or the Akkadian have not had a nation in over 2,300 years.
And they predominantly, several million in population, live in Europe,
what's known as the U.S. and Australia.
They're scattered all over the world.
They have not had a nation in over 2,300 years formally.
They typically were at what's called the Nineveh Plains or northern part of Iraq.
Now what was written regarding this situation was that when Assyria forms,
it will be most likely a product of a loose civil war,
more of a political civil war in Iraq that will allow that territory to be formed
or reformed, which it has not in thousands of years.
Now you could look at the Assyrians, by the way,
and there was a genocide regarding them and an acknowledgment of such.
There's some notoriety regarding their history, but not much.
But what had been written regarding the situation over a decade ago is that
when a loose sort of political and economic civil war allows Assyria to form,
it won't just form in northern Iraq.
If you comprehend the borders, let's say spiritual borders,
because let me just jump around a little bit here.
Every nation has a principality behind it.
Yes, it's kind of a patron deity.
They might be slightly different.
The patron deities might be the ones that the people prop up,
but there is a principality or spirit behind it.
So when you look at maps, it's not just men squirting ink on paper.
There's a little bit more about that.
Now when Assyria comes around and it's acknowledged as a political body,
according to its older borders, you will probably discover that parts of it,
of the formal border of Assyria, goes into what's called modern Turkey,
more of like the southeastern part, and it also goes into Syria.
Not much, but enough.
So part of the communication that was drafted over a decade ago
was to watch Turkey and to watch Syria,
because they're going to be giving up a small amount of land.
Now what's interesting about that, many people here,
when land is given to another, let's say, sovereignty or political state,
it can be purchased, like it is, let's say, the Americans bought Alaska
and other things, you know, other pieces of property, let's say,
that they consider part of their rule.
But you would say that in this case, there's some very, very deep ethnic differences,
and I wouldn't see it as being financial solely,
and I would see that there's a destabilization that's going to be coming in Turkey
and Syria, and this was written, let's say, around 2005, 2006.
So not a lot of specifics about what's going on specifically,
but when you see what's going on, it makes complete sense if you know what's coming.
The other thing about what's going on in Syria is that it is going to break up
in different jurisdictions, so is Jordan and other things, and I can go on and on.
Now I believe I would say that there is a tremendous amount of specific information
with references where they can be sourced, and a little bit more history on the matter,
which will be coming in the future.
Now I just want to, this is just to maybe digress just for a moment.
I want to thank everyone who has contributed to supporting the show
and acknowledging that it is worth contributing to Uncommon Radio.
I suggested that the first four weeks of doing this, the first four solo events,
and sonic events were going to be sort of an open member's area where anyone was willing to call in
or bring up a subject, it would be discussed pretty much as it could be
within a two-hour open platform like this.
Now I would suggest that in the future there is going to be a project that perhaps will be with AFR,
perhaps not, we'll see, but it will be coming in the future where it will be not a member's area only,
perhaps there's got to be something better, but a non-public venue where information regarding
what the Greek discusses in greater length and greater specifics.
There is quite a bit of commentary that I've gotten where you bring up all these subjects,
but you don't give enough specifics.
And then the same people will comment, well, I have to go back and listen to it again,
because every time I do there's so much in there.
So there's a dichotomy there.
So I'm not sure how this is going to be exactly structured, but it will not be open to the public at large.
This is not being done strictly as something to monetize anything,
and if anything is monetized to an extent it will be put back into it to keep the project going.
I recently found out certain university libraries are charging some pretty high fees for scanning old documents,
and it's quite interesting to be working for free sometimes, but anyway, what they call gratis.
So whatever kind of exchange can be garnered, and I'm sure it will be very well worth it for anyone who participates,
and this is a project that will come together in the future,
and it will be based on some very, very specific aspects of things that have been discussed and your questions.
So again, I didn't see anything else come up in the chat,
but all I have to say about any war in progress, especially in the Middle East, is that its sole purpose, as was discussed,
and the interesting thing is perhaps maybe it's discussing something that's too far into the future,
because it seems like things change on a weekly basis or a daily basis too often.
The attention span is like that of a cat with humanity at large.
So I tend to see that knowing the terminus point, or the termination of something,
helps you understand what process it goes through before it reaches that end, instead of watching it just as it goes.
So what's interesting also, one thing I just want to maybe, that's all I can say about the war in Syria at the moment,
but the other interesting thing is that there's a couple of other countries that are next in line for a major destabilization,
and if you read between the lines, or reading out of what I'm saying, and it's not Israel and it's not Iran.
So you take your pick, that leaves you about another, let's say six or so.
But I have given these countries out in the past, and we can get into more specifics.
Now there will be destabilization in Iraq and Israel, but not now, and it will be much later, and it will be for different reasons.
But I would suggest that if anyone wants a new idea, read a really old book.
That's the beginning of looking at things with fresh eyes, as they say.
So with that said, I see someone is probably bringing back on track, what is the role of man on Earth?
And I would just suggest that that's a very simple way to look at it.
It depends on where you get your information from, and how you classify information as being valid or not.
There are several ways to look at that.
So let's just see.
We're getting a couple of other messages here.
I'll see if anything is pertinent, and then we'll just go on,
because I would suggest that when you're discussing mankind, what is the role of man as a steward?
But ultimately, man is actually a product.
I've discussed this many times before.
When you start getting into these matters, it has nothing to do with belief, by the way.
Whenever you hear anyone say the word belief, it means you have knowledge of something that will be coming or happening.
And if it's a good belief, that means that the knowledge is firm, and the possibility of something happening is eminent.
If the belief is not good, it means the knowledge is not very good, and it may not happen.
So when people say, what do you believe in, it has to be action-based.
I'm not saying it to be dogmatic, or this is what the Greek says it is or whatever,
but looking at what beliefs are are totally different the way people use them.
Okay, I'm getting some questions here.
These have been answered before, and how do the gods perceive man in their bigger picture?
I've explained much of that before, but I would just suggest that from a spiritual perspective with mankind,
it's a form of spirit that manifests on this earth that is pretty much animated through the physical body.
In other words, it's a high form of spirit that is limited to be animated through the physical body.
So when the physical body is removed, there is no more animation.
That is the other interesting aspect of mankind.
You will look at various cultures, and they talk about the first man or early man.
Now, this again is different from belief.
If you contrast what's being said here to academia regarding evolution and all this other stuff,
that is a whole other field, because all you can do with evolution is explain it,
and it's not in a very good way, because it's just a prank.
That's what academics do, and that's what the entitled classes like to do.
They like to play pranks.
So the description of mankind is quite simple.
You're a spirit that's animated through the body, and everything around you was made or remade to house you,
just like you would build a house for someone to live in.
There is basically a 7,000-year curing period.
It's quite simple.
Now, it sounds like, oh, well, that's not enough information.
Well, it's actually the mindset required to look at the rest of the information.
When I say required, I mean there's many things you could look at in this world if you feel like being pranked.
It's not like, well, the Greek believes this.
There are things that I believe, meaning like what I just discussed,
based on knowledge of things that are going to happen, and the knowledge is pretty good.
When someone says, for example, just for a minute, this is a mindset, folks.
Oh, do you believe in God?
Don't even answer that.
That's a ridiculous question.
It's completely ridiculous.
Believe in God.
What does that mean?
I don't know what that means.
Believe that a god is going to do something?
What are you speaking of?
So the level of the reductionist, the level of information and the dumbing up
and the reductionist communications that are being partaken in by the society at large right now
is almost something to be avoided, almost in wholesale.
It's almost, I would say, almost impossible to have a rational conversation at this point.
I've had people from different walks of life come and say, yes, I do see that,
and it's kind of an interesting thing to discuss on its own.
But mankind being here, and this being the number six, by the way,
when we give a little bit of timekeeping, if we're going to do a little bit of timekeeping,
you're roughly, I would say, about 19 years into the credits, which the time roughly ended.
When I say roughly, there's a little bit more fine-tuning,
but it doesn't matter at this point because it's gotten too far into the future from this point.
Around the fall of 1998, and let's just give a few tidbits here,
because what's interesting is redundancy is important because it seems like when I say things,
there's many questions regarding the same thing that has been said many times.
So there's a time and place, and it's not time yet.
When it's not time yet, you can pretty much give out a secret, and it won't be comprehended.
But I would just suggest that the year 1998 was around the year 6,000,
so you add roughly 19 to that in the fall.
That's how many years since Adam, because Adam is the reference point.
Now what's interesting, and here's the little secret.
The most critical and most significant figure in the Scripture is the Christ.
Now I'm not talking about Jesus or anything Christian.
That does not, in Scripture, there's nothing in Christianity that is scriptural.
Zero. And that sounds irrational, but if you've done your homework, you will see.
And the Bible is not the Scripture by far.
You know, King James, that is an interesting thing that I will be giving the history on in the future,
most likely in private.
But I would just suggest this, folks, that the Christ, the most important figure, was born the year 4,000,
because there is a number sequence here that I have described, I think, with the Ocelli and the Greek
several times, probably at the end of the second hour, about discerning the number 7.
So you need to think about that for a moment, and I will bring that up with even more information in the future.
So this is regarding an email I recently just got a few minutes ago.
If the Christ was born on the number 4, and that is his number, when would another character be born?
What millennial would he be born?
If you guessed the 6th millennium, the year 6,000 around 1998, you would be pretty accurate,
about as accurate as one would want to be.
So that, let's say, is a directly, indirectly answering the question regarding someone emailing earlier.
So I would just say that the position of man and its 6 is also very interesting.
When you look at many people, this is just a social commentary,
when they think the number 666 elicits some form of Satan or something demonic or whatever,
where 666, by the way, that comes out of what is called the Book of Revelation,
and if you don't fit the description as one of the people in the first verse,
you could read that book every day, five times a day, and I assure you, you will not understand a thing in it.
I mean, after the, or up or down, or hot or cold, you will not comprehend anything.
And the other promise on this, or assurance, I should say,
is if you consider yourself Christian, Muslim, Jewish, Buddhist, or any of the mainstream religions,
you will not understand anything in the Book of Revelation.
That's an assurance. That's pretty simple.
So there is a lot of problem still with communication and just bad information.
So there is regarding something regarding the law on the seventh day and all that.
Yeah, okay, that, you know, it's interesting.
There's been a lot of questions in chat and other places regarding specific verses,
almost from a legalistic point of view.
And I've had some pretty good Skype conversations regarding scripture,
some of them hours and hours long.
And just to be apologetic or defend the point that looking at just one verse is not the way to do it.
Yes, you need to know what you need to know, and you will find it in singular verses or groups of verses.
But what's interesting is when you see a subject come up,
for example, like a specific question is being asked in the chat right now.
I'm not going to read it on air.
But what I will say is that whenever there is a question regarding something in what's called scripture,
even if you're reading it out of the Pittsburgh King James or whatever other language,
you're not going to language of preservation.
If there is a question about it, it's because that is usually interjectory thought or interjectory verse,
where it's interjected within a body of information or a storyline.
And more information regarding that is found in other places, okay?
And you also have to remember when you're reading something like the scripture,
that is about the gods.
It's not about you.
There's plenty to read.
If you want to read stuff about mankind, there's plenty of people that are willing to write it.
But whenever you read the scripture, it is about them.
So even when they are discussing in scripture information about men, it is regarding the gods, you see.
So you have to consider certain things.
Who are they?
Like I've given metaphors before.
We don't know what a bear is, but we know enough about its characteristics that we can discuss.
We know what bears are, but we really don't.
We don't really know who the gods are, but we know enough about their characteristics that's been memorialized.
Because on the other hand, you may not know if one is riding the bus with you.
At this point, they are covert in appearance.
They are not overt in appearance.
And I'm not discussing any of the stuff that you have in your mainstream you,
meaning people at large, surface-dwelling earth inhabitants, not you, the listener, for example,
have in your mainstream religions.
That is completely different.
There is something very unusually distasteful about that.
But anyway, so one thing about getting specific answers about specific verses and specific concepts,
yeah, that could be answered.
There's a question there, sure.
But it's not what you think because it's not strictly related to that one item.
Let me just give another little thing.
Well, we'll save that for another time.
This is regarding how to comprehend and read scripture.
Because you have to realize the gods have IQs of over 2 million, not to insult them.
And when you read any of the holy writs, they're really speaking baby talk.
And if anyone says that it cannot be understood, that's like indirectly just wanting to kick the gods in the nuts
or saying that the gods act in futility.
That was your little lascivious comment for the day.
Okay, so the gods do not act in futility.
There's many things in place here that mankind is not aware of.
That I have tried to explain, not just describe.
One of them is cosmic censorship.
The other thing is you're in the credits part of society.
Yep.
But discussing mankind and any question that might come that way,
if I harken back to the previous number five solo episode, I would suggest, or sonic experience,
I would suggest that what was brought up, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
And if you've heard Greek speak before, by the way, what does Greek speak and heavy artillery have in common?
Well, once you hear it, it's too late.
But either way, if you were to objectify the present civilization, surface-dwelling earth inhabitants,
and just pretty much anyone you will meet in a general sense, statistically,
can be described as what would be in the next few-minute installment of the explanation of what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common.
Now, if you want to, there are things that kind of perplex people, fancy words and tongue twisters maybe,
but just go ahead and ask someone, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
Now, by the way, just a little bit of history on this.
I've been saying this for quite a while.
And people that do enjoy it always want the Greek to say it.
And I say, well, why don't you say it?
And it doesn't seem like people are able to string it together for some reason.
Some say you're more eloquent Greek or whatever.
No, I am not as described.
I just find it very unusual.
So anyone is free to use this, by the way, if you want to perplex or confound the average surface-dwelling earth inhabitant,
and also exhibit their vileness.
And one thing, again, I just want to recap here.
When you do tune into Uncommon Radio or get into Greek speak, you'll notice it is chock full of explanation.
You won't get too many I don't know whys or it's like this or like that.
What you're going to get is the gateway into objectivity.
You will not get objectivity.
You will get the gateway into a certain mindset that will make you extraordinarily perceptive of the obvious.
That's right.
You will become extraordinarily perceptive of the obvious.
And no, it is not good for making friends.
No, it's not.
I mean, yeah, well, neither is like you've got a stain on the shirt there.
You know, are you eating spaghetti?
Anyway, you will not make friends.
So let's please, please, folks.
If anyone comprehends the question and the answer and the explanation, feel free to use it.
Feel free to spread it around.
I'm not looking to create any form of social currency or anything.
As a matter of fact, I don't pursue anything that much of the aspirations of others that are in this electronic media.
I do not do YouTubes and all that other silly stuff.
So I'm not saying that if you do YouTubes, you're silly.
But most people do it just to whatever you get the picture.
There's no reason for it.
Well, the reason for speaking is solely that.
Now, it has to be done one way or another.
And just to recap again, there are many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many things that need to be discussed.
Yes, you heard, need to be discussed, but they will not be done in public at this time.
So please be aware there are projects or projects coming in the near future where that can be done.
It will be well worth anyone's time if you are not looking to make any friends, of course.
But anyway, cannibals, birthdays, and dolls, feel free to use it.
As a matter of fact, if you're going to objectify pretty much everyone on this planet and leave this planet
and communicate what everyone on this planet is about just in a few minutes, this is the way to do it, folks.
Now, I haven't met everyone.
I don't need to because I'm not really speaking about everyone on the planet.
I'm speaking about the great majority, statistically the great majority.
If you put 7.5 billion people, which is the World Bank statistic, by the way,
and it's interesting how that metric is maintained and garnered by the World Bank, folks.
If you were to eliminate, let's say, 50 million or 30 million, you wouldn't see much of a difference.
It's actually the number of people that are objective, perceptive, and sort of aware are much less than that.
It's actually a small percentage of the 50 million.
So speaking a certain way regarding the majority of the people on this planet,
let's just say give it a rational communication of 7.5 billion, it sounds like you're speaking poorly of them.
Yes, it's not difficult, yeah, to do that.
Anyway, what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
So this was asked last week.
Again, let's just go back to Chapter 4.
We start then and said, okay, someone is – okay, we can get to these discussions regarding the Earth and other things as well, and they will be.
But what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
We have 20 minutes left in the first hour, and I'm going to go slowly with it because I don't think there's much that can be –
much can be added to it, but much will not at this time.
Now, the interesting thing about – again, just to say it again, the reason why this is asked is because it is a simple representation
or simple representative explanation of what is going on on this Earth.
It doesn't matter what country you're in or when you have lived.
So what do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
What's interesting – here we go – is that even if you look into the crap education system, whether it's private or public,
they will all admit that life somehow, man's civilization, started in and around the Mesopotamian region of the world.
Okay, Mesopotamia, Tigris, Euphrates, and all that other stuff.
And what's interesting about that is you will also find that most of the writs of the world have that as well.
And there's points that can be argued, but typically that is the accepted and truthful aspect of it.
Now, regarding a region, let's say something like Europe, you know, like most of the countries,
let's say Portuguese, Spanish, French, Italian, those are known as Latin languages.
They're different unto themselves, but they are known as the Latin language.
The language of these early civilizations in Mesopotamia was the Chaldean Hebrew, Akkadian, that style.
You might call it Hebrew-Arabic, but whatever, but there's a distinction between the Chaldean Hebrew-Arabic now.
But they were generally grouped together as a Chaldean type of language.
So what's interesting is that in their religious practice, by this time, they had admittedly and functionally had various priesthoods,
and the priesthoods were known as the Qahans.
And typically they would set up institutions, very much like the circuses or churches you see today,
and other temples and houses of worship that are called such.
And the people were attracted to go there because if you did certain things and made certain offerings,
you were garnered prosperity and other things.
So basically what had happened was the overt aspect of human sacrifice had been in place,
and the human sacrifice was for the Baals.
Baal is an elemental, I would say, a little bit more than an elemental.
They're personified in anthropomorphic forms, and I would suggest that the priests of the Baals were called the Qahan Baals,
and the way they suggested the people would gain prosperity is by bringing a child and having it slaughtered on an altar publicly.
And when this was done, some of the flesh and some of the blood was passed around,
and that's why the consummation of or consuming of human flesh is called Qahan Baalism.
This is not a play on words like telling lies on your vision or anything like that, or history is history.
Qahan Baal or cannibal is where you get the association of eating flesh.
So this is the story that we are going on.
What do cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common?
Now typically if you comprehend human nature and society and the familial structure,
with a missing child, if there were other children, they would ask,
where is our missing brother? Where is our missing sister?
Typically it would have been a male, but let's just say.
So the altar boys of these priests of the Lord, because by the way, Baal means Lord, right?
If translated today, a Lord of some sort, and these were priests, so today you have priests of the Lord as well.
But nonetheless, they had altar boys that produced an item, maybe an effigy of such, or something called a doll.
An appearance of a child, and they were told to give this to the children that were asking about the missing child,
to keep them occupied until they forgot about it.
So now you know the history of dolls.
Now the interesting thing about that is, go ahead and ask anyone about dolls they don't know,
and they don't want to know, and if they hear about these points, they just don't care.
Because see, they're having a good time playing with dolls, and it's part of the culture.
As a matter of fact, there's an industry behind it.
Yes, that's right. There are doll factories.
Never heard of such a thing, huh?
Okay, yeah.
Now you know what cannibals and dolls are tied in together somehow.
Now what's interesting about this, many of this did not bring prosperity, for obvious reasons,
and a lot of them were run out of that area, and they went and settled northern parts of Europe.
Have you ever heard of the Druids, by the way?
Yeah, mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, so yeah, this is humanity, folks.
So they get run out because it doesn't bring a lot of prosperity, obviously,
but there was remnants of this, and this is all they knew how to do.
So they said, well, let's instead of sacrificing a child,
why don't we just take the next child in line, or that would be offered,
and have a celebration where we bake a loaf of sweet bread, and that represents the body,
put some lights in it, have the child blow out, which represents blowing out the life,
and everyone participating would eat a piece of the body,
and when you're participating, the child is told to make a wish of prosperity
and to show that it works, anyone that comes brings a present.
And I studied this, and I was like, I wonder, this is an odd kind of celebration or ceremony.
It took about six months to figure out that's the origin of the birthday cake by description.
So, yeah.
You know, what's interesting is there's something called a goat which will eat anything.
You know, a goat-type personality will find things pleasant that are pleasant
and, you know, find things that are not pleasant as being, you know, should be avoided.
If you're speaking to someone and they find this story to be a gasp
and they invite you to a birthday party later, they're a goat because they just eat anything.
So anyway, here, folks, I didn't want to throw the goat part in because that's very common,
but now you know what cannibals, birthdays, and dolls have in common.
Or the story, as it goes, is cannibals, dolls, and birthdays,
but it seems like cannibals, birthdays, and dolls almost has a little rhyme to it.
Limerick, maybe. Doubt it.
So this is the representation of the attitude, the intent, and the functionality of humanity.
Now, I just want to throw something in here.
This is the way you explain who is on this planet.
It doesn't mean that you're a part of it.
It's just the general consensus, and it doesn't matter what culture you're in.
This goes on everywhere.
Now, I just want to throw something in.
I don't really like discussing that television show or radio program they call the news,
but there's been something about a certain gate regarding a certain Italian food.
You know, I put it all together.
It's a flat thing, baked pizza, whatever, about humans and children and all that.
Yes, this has been going on everywhere, and as a matter of fact,
as a matter of fact, if you want to know how bad this is from an intentional point of view,
from the spiritual side, go into a local market and ask them if they sell birthday cakes.
Yes, that's all.
And if they say yes, you are up Schitt's Creek without a paddle in that society.
Okay, so whether it takes just a few years or a few generations, you're not going to fare well.
So for one aspect, yes.
Are there children being taken underground that involves every aspect of all of the entitled classes?
And I don't need to name who they are, who the entitled classes are, your professionals, I should say.
They're all involved in it.
And the ones that are not involved in it are somewhat used as buffers or whatever.
But you're involved in it at large with all of your other ceremonial stuff.
There is not one religious holiday I see in Christianity that is not based on human sacrifice, by the way.
And this is the Christian era.
This is not just speaking out against a specific religion.
When you say the Christian era or Christians, you're talking about everyone on the planet.
Yes, why?
You ever heard of something called the Pope's work schedule or the calendar, the Gregorian calendar?
That is a timekeeping nomenclature, and it's not even timekeeping in your face.
You can't keep time with it.
It's a work schedule.
If you ask anyone, by the way, what day is it, and they say anything between January and December and Monday through Friday,
they're admitting with their own mouth that they are the Pope's subject.
And the worst is these idiots that go out and start bad-mouthing the Vatican.
Just pull them over and say, what day is it?
And he'll tell you something between January, December, Monday through Friday unconditionally.
It's okay to use that conditionally.
What's called January?
What's called March?
What's called Tuesday?
Yeah, I'll meet you what's called next Friday.
Or I'll meet you what's called next Friday or next Wednesday.
Not Wednesday or Friday.
How can it be?
So anyway, is anyone paying attention?
No.
It's about mindset, folks.
So let's just say, what do cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common?
Here's your mindset.
Keep that in mind and use that as a reference point.
It's all about reference points.
If you know, let's say, the tape measure in inches or feet and someone says,
well, you know, that board's a foot long.
And you're like, well, you know, I know what a foot looks like in 12 inches.
That looks kind of short, man.
Really?
Okay.
And you're like, this is fine to me.
Well, you know, there's no argument about this because I've got a tape measure right here.
Oh, yeah, it's 11 inches.
Oh, yeah, I see.
Okay.
No arguing.
Once you have reference points, there's no arguing.
It's part of academia, by the way, to argue.
Now it's creeped into regular communication.
And you hear it.
I just want to run away.
I mean, I don't listen to Internet and all this other stuff and even anything in print anymore
because it's just the quality is too low.
Right?
I mean, most of the stuff that you see in what's called the news and other places like that are current events.
And who is not interested in current events?
Everyone is to some degree.
But the problem is the quality is so low.
Okay, folks get the point.
If you're listening to Uncommon Radio, you know exactly what I'm saying.
So at this point, looking at what humans can be explained or derived as objectively.
Now some people might say that they have.
No one ever has.
That's not how people are or denies it.
Just like, for example, I've been saying this for quite a long time,
and anyone I've ever told that anyone you've ever met, anyone you know,
and anyone who you're going to meet is a complete moron.
No one has rebutted that ever.
Think about that for a minute.
And I'm not saying that to be degrading or I'm saying that to be put down or this or that
or whatever prankster kind of psychological reasoning or whatever attitude reasoning you imagine.
It's just that I find that it's very interesting that it has not been rebutted.
It's very interesting how certain claims, yes, claims can be made regarding the typical condition of humanity,
whether how short or how long, as long as they're objective, they will be conveyed and they will stand.
So that's the interesting aspect of it.
So I think we've achieved part of the aspect of saying what mankind is about at this point in terms of status or the state.
But there's much more to mankind.
And here I'll just say something before we continue.
I would just suggest that mankind is so unique at this point and always has been.
And when I say mankind, it is, yes, I'm talking about the anthropomorphic form where a spirit is animated through the body,
that mankind, let's just use the term we, are being made to join the highest-ranking aspect of the highest-ranking beings in the universe.
And just because you don't see a lot of them or any of them doesn't mean they don't exist.
If you, for example, study or know anyone who studied the explicit varieties in deep-sea biology,
and I mean explicit, all the ones that are known, you will see that it will bury you.
There's so much going on down there, even though it looks barren at first glance.
Anyone studies the nature of the gods and their category, categorically of the gods,
you will see there's a tremendous amount of information regarding that.
And there is a hierarchy there as well.
So when we study mankind, it seems to fall apart,
because the level of division and the level of quote-unquote arguing and the level of ignorance is beyond reproach.
So let's just say, this being the sixth solo event, and almost tidying up the first hour,
I did want to get the what do cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common out there,
because it is very important to comprehend.
Use that as your ruler.
Like earlier, there was a question regarding the progress of the war in Syria.
You can get drawn up into these little vortices, right?
And by the way, if you look at what I call the news matrix or whatever,
I'm not using the word matrix as what it really means, but as people use it,
you will see that it changes every week.
And what people are vehemently passionate about this week, they don't care at all in a week or two later.
So try not to get sucked up into that vortex.
But if you do understand regarding the question about the progressing war in Syria,
if you do understand from a reference point that there is an upcoming loose confederacy of ten nations
forming in the Middle East, and how can that come together,
and the conflicts through just practical history of man's civilization,
you will see that this is starting to make sense.
So I would suggest that if new ideas are required to look at things,
you're going to have to go back and see what was written about similar things from times of old.
Well, let's just give a little bit of attention here.
We'll just have a few more minutes and see what can be garnered out of e-mails and chat,
just to keep this going.
Okay, all right.
People don't seem to comprehend you have to hold back because of other forces, man and otherwise.
Okay, that was a suggestion. Thank you.
And in chat, yeah, close to the second month, middle of the 28th day of the first month, Sabbath.
Seventh starts midday. Yeah, pretty close.
Someone says it's wrong.
The 11th is the new moon.
Well, on paper, here's one thing.
I want to bring this up, folks.
There are some pretty good references on what's called the World Wide Web regarding moon phases,
and I would suggest that you go and research how they determine a phase.
It's pretty technical, and they do say they do it astronomically,
which is through observation point.
Now, one thing that they don't give is when the datum line or when the phase actually changes,
because if these things go in a cyclical pattern, when does the moon become full and when is it not?
Never really quite discussed that.
Typically, let me just give a little bit of a hint for anyone who's doing both observational
and let's say formulative study of the moon,
which is where you go online and it tells you the moon phase is down to like decimal points.
Typically, I found them through the past 12 or something years of looking at that,
is that they're typically succeeding the point.
So, in other words, the full moon in the western world proceeds when they say it will be full.
But when they're like 98%, 99%, it could be full still.
Now, traditionally, the moon was rendered full when you saw it rise in the east,
but it was nearly the end of the 12th hour.
So, okay, I'm getting a little bit of a mess here.
29th day is – yeah, it's the 28th.
Yes, that's correct.
So I would suggest that the actual observable measurable full moon,
it precedes what you see on the Internet in terms of days,
because they're also garnering days on the Zulu time.
Okay.
One thing I haven't discussed specifically, and I will in the future,
this is not a teaser or holding a carrot out to get people to come over to someplace else,
but I'm just saying that whether it's being self-conscious or not,
I don't like to discuss a lot of these things in public,
even though there is a specific show called Uncommon Radio,
and the Greek can pretty much, according to the AFR policy, say whatever he wants to say.
I find that still many of the things are viewed distastefully by humanity at large
because of just what's been going on for so long.
So going on for so long, that's hour one, and we will see you folks at the top of the second hour.
Greetings, everyone, and welcome to Uncommon Radio.
Yes, and I've been looking at chat, folks, and you guys are hot about trying to figure out time.
That's good.
Is it wrong?
No, but it's not right.
And here's the interesting part about anything, folks.
It is fun to be authoritative.
It is also necessary to be authoritative and quote-unquote official sometimes.
But for these things, you are outnumbered, folks.
You are surrounded if you are interested in anything lawful.
By the way, lawful, yes, that term has nothing to do with attorneys or courts
or the laws that you're familiar with.
Lawful has to do with fit and proper.
Yes, I haven't used that much.
I've used set-apart much, but if you're interested in anything lawful,
you will not make friends, and this is the wrong planet to be on at the moment.
And yes, one day you'll have a conversation with the earth, and she will tell you the same.
So what's interesting, anything lawful is quite interesting to analyze and to know
because it makes good reference and it makes good posture for comprehending events around you.
Like there's many things we can get into, many things that we will get into,
we meaning whoever is listening to Greek speak and the Greek, of course,
but I just want to, because this is archived, just inform anyone who is listening to this,
there is a chat on AFR, and they are discussing, they meaning whoever is participating in the chat,
the right and wrong about lawful timekeeping.
Now let's just give a, because mankind is sort of the subject loosely on this sixth solo episode,
and I believe that what I wanted to define this episode with is the description of mankind,
which is what do cannibals' birthdays and dolls have in common, which was pretty much completed in the last hour.
So right now I just want to bring up in terms of timekeeping, folks, this is just really simple in terms of lawful.
See, lawfully the day starts at noon.
Well, it's not what I believe.
Well, actually I do believe that because I measure it every day.
It's a good belief to have, and it's not because I'm an oddball and everyone else is this and that.
And by the way, I just want to throw something in, and we'll get back to it.
I've discussed certain concepts, economic, judicial, quote-unquote religious, scientific, with people in media,
both I'd say more alternative media, and no matter how progressive they are, very often I do get,
well, Greg, I don't want to discuss that because nobody knows about that.
Think about that for a minute, folks.
Okay, let's go back to lawful timekeeping, the day starting at noon.
Now, there's many conventions that will show you that.
For example, the timekeeping authorities that are listed perhaps in what's known as the Americas
would be the Naval Observatory in Colorado Springs and Greenwich is the other one in England, I believe.
They have websites, and if you study what's called Julian calendar date,
which is the format for the current calendar, which was now called the Gregorian calendar for different reasons.
If anyone would like to research the papal bull of Pope Gregory around 1580-something,
you will see the purposes behind this work schedule being installed.
But I would suggest that its format or its code is based on the Julian.
You will see on these timekeeping authorities, if you research what they proclaim about the Julian calendar date,
they will tell you for astronomical and scientific purposes the day starts at solar noon.
And other times I've read it where it said, you know, for astronomical and scientific purposes,
the day starts at solar noon, but for the people, it's civil midnight.
That's kind of how dictionaries, when they first started arising in popularity,
they didn't know exactly how to define words, so they said, well, oats.
It's what they feed horses in England, but it's the staple of the people in Scotland.
Kind of a put down there, but anyway, let's just say if anyone is old enough to remember
non-electronic banking conventions, if you made a deposit in what's called the bank,
because they're not banks, folks, they considered it afternoon after not necessarily solar noon,
but the wind-up toy known as the clock, which is another discussion.
They considered, by the way, the deposit to be accredited for the next day.
Some people like now to say, well, it's 2 o'clock or whatever,
but now things have changed again because of electronic convention.
There's a level of absence of anything as a reference point on that.
So when you consider noon on these old western movie courts and western frontier courts,
they would have sentencing and execution on the next day,
and there are many popular films where they'd be hanging at high noon.
So also, noon is a really good time to measure.
You see, as the day is winding down, the shadows are going towards the west,
and when the new day begins, the shadow goes towards the east.
So there's many aspects of that which will be discussed in the future.
Now, one thing I haven't gone into, this is timekeeping, lawful timekeeping,
is in terms of the day, there are 12 hours in the day of daylight.
Now, how you do that, and I'm just going to say this once.
If you want to replay this, it's in archives, and listen to it again,
and I will get into this more in the future, maybe not publicly, maybe so.
There are 12 hours of daylight, but the sky is divided into 10 portions to do that.
So let's say 180 degrees, you have 18 degrees each,
and remember, 6 is the number of men, 18 is 6 plus 6 plus 6 in each hour.
Each hour has three divisions.
So yeah, you heard that right.
So let's just say this.
If the sky is divided into 10 divisions, how do you get 12 hours?
Should I hang that rhetorically, or should I just keep going?
Let's just keep going.
When you are noticing that the sky is black, it's nighttime,
and at dawn you'll notice that the sky starts to illuminate,
but you do not see the sun disk above the horizon.
When that condition prevails, until the sun disk is visible,
that is considered the first hour.
When the sun disk is visible above the horizon, into that first tenth in the east,
in those three portions of that tenth, you will see that is the first hour.
Now let's succeed through the day.
When the sun is at the western horizon, that is the 11th hour, and you guessed it.
When the sun goes below the horizon at sunset, twilight I guess, you still have sunlight.
It's albeit dim, and you will see that is the 12th hour.
So you see the disk of the sun 10 times during the day,
and the first and the last hour are the same where it's below the horizon.
Oh, interesting, the first is the last, and the last is like the first.
So that is for you men and women, mankind, time lawful, timekeeping.
So think about that, or actually don't think about that, but just have access to the information.
By the way, when people are on a path of developing a mindset that is objective and lawful,
it will not make you happy, it will not bring you pleasure,
but have you ever heard that it's better to have love and loss than to have ever loved at all?
Isn't it better to have known what's fit and proper than to have never known at all?
Think about it.
Actually, that you should think about.
Now, let's go to the formidable topic, perhaps, maybe momentarily, is the moon,
because as I have, I don't like to necessarily go over it,
because when you do public speaking, if you make a mistake, just keep going.
No one will notice, but I just want to bring up a few weeks ago, I was not doing any observation.
It was a very important time, but I had prepared personally, let's just say,
on the Greek's personal life prior to that anyway,
but I would suggest that the moon is a very interesting way to look at it.
Now, the moon reckons the month.
That's why, for example, if you research how people in commerce,
they would always settle all their debts before the full moon came around.
That's why today they kind of keep it in a way you get a monthly bill.
You get it, it's a monthly, well, anyway, and that's why I've discussed how the credit system works.
Anyway, you can't just discuss one thing without leading to another.
Now, what's interesting about the moon is that it follows the path through the sky in the winter,
that the sun follows in the summer, and vice versa, they switch places.
So, the moon and the sun together mark the year.
By the way, if you ever hear of a lunar calendar, walk away.
There's nothing there.
That's just a carryover.
That is like fossilized thinking and just to accommodate a mindset that knows something is wrong,
but can't quite put their finger on it.
There's no such thing as a lunar calendar, and there's no such thing as a solar calendar, folks.
The moon rules the month and the sun rules the day,
and their paths through the sky give other determinations as the year, singular,
and the years in epochs are ruled by the stars.
Now, I haven't gotten into determining the year.
I have given various descriptions, but I haven't given specifics,
just like I will not give more specifics on the moon.
But what I would suggest is that when the moon is sighted in the east,
it typically comes up fairly yellow, and then as it rises above what would be called the second position,
about 20 degrees or so, you would see that 20 to 30 degrees, it starts to turn bright white.
Now, what makes a full moon a full moon is not how big it is,
but it's how round it is and how bright it is for its roundness, for its area.
Because the moon will always seem larger after a full moon, but it's not quite round,
and it also comes up later.
It usually comes up after the 12th hour, after there is no light in the west.
Typically, the sighting of the new moon, which is the full moon,
you will see it's past the second half of the 12th hour,
when the sun is already below the horizon and there's just a little bit of light left.
So this is an interesting thing to denote.
Now, there are secrets about this.
I have given them in the past, and I knew they were heard because I had gotten feedback about it.
But one way to determine something is by two witnesses and double verification or validation.
Now, I'm going to say this.
This might sound absurd, but anyone who has heard this before and has used it has confirmed it.
So it sounds absurd because, unfortunately, it's true.
What you will find out is that there are two full moons, folks.
Yep, same moon, but it's full twice.
First time, it's very, very short, and it's not in the east.
So I'm just going to leave that hanging for now.
But what's interesting is that the full moon, the first day of the month, is the first day of the month.
It is set apart to itself.
So the second day of the month is the first day of the first week.
So you've heard in various traditions, cultures, quote-unquote religion, and hold your wits,
the seventh day is to be set apart.
It's known in certain languages as the seventh day of rest in their corresponding culture.
Now, what you will find is that that corresponds with the moon phases.
So that would be you have the first day of the month, and then the second day of the month is the first day of the first week.
So you count from the second day of the month, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, right?
So that's the eighth day of the month, because remember, you started counting on the second day of the month.
So the seventh day of rest is always on the 8th, 15th, 22nd, 29th of the month.
Now, that's why, for example, in the biblical text or scripture, there is the story of Jericho,
where they marched around and they blew the trumpets and the walls came down.
They marched around for seven days and all that.
And if you discuss any academic, anyone that has gone to school of divinity, anyone that has studied the biblical text,
and you bring up the point that what were they doing, waging war or battle on the Sabbath,
their answer is, well, God could make them do whatever they want to do.
This is your academic.
And the reason I'm using that voice is because that's what they sound like when I hear these professionals speaking supposedly.
But that's not the case, because the irony here is they started on the first day of the month,
and the seventh day was really the sixth day of the week.
And the story of Jericho is a primer for children to understand how to keep time,
because the double entendre here is that Jericho means the moon.
The city of Jericho literally means the moon.
And they also worship the moon god.
So what's interesting about that is that you will find these primers
and very small descriptions of how to learn things through story.
So I just wanted to throw that in there just to satisfy maybe if there is any interest in many of those things.
We will discuss in the future also the origin and the purpose of these books
from a perspective that is probably not public, not known,
and I think it will be very edifying to anyone who wants to hear them.
But again, these specific things will not be done in public,
because even though people say it, Greeks say it,
I believe that still using a public forum to discuss very specific things like this is viewed in bad taste for some reason at this point.
In the future, they will be known, and they will be discussed.
But why not give some people that are really interested a head start?
Now, the interesting thing here, going back to the timekeeping,
is that if you do any kind of a reference on what's called the moon,
you'll go to like a, whatever, they'll tell you the moon phase is 28.96…
…days long.
That's not how it goes, because they're even calling the new moon the dark moon,
which started during a time period around when the cosmic censorship started.
You can't, and the other thing here, there's a certain religion or religions
that count the day ending at sundown and the new moon being the dark moon.
And that is absurd and ridiculous.
Not because I say so, because it is objectified as being absurd and ridiculous.
You cannot take a measurement at sundown or with the dark moon.
So, you folks that do that kind of stuff, wake up!
Anyway, I don't think really even strong coffee or anything else is going to wake you up at this point,
because you are subject to cosmic censorship.
Now, this is not because it's being dogmatic or whatever,
but when you say something is lawful, it needs to garner a form of measurement.
Because if you can't measure it, you can't manage it.
How can you measure sundown or a dark moon?
Hmm? I'm listening.
Okay, I thought so.
Anything lawful has to be measurable.
That's why, for example, when you look at the money system,
they tell you the Federal Reserve notes, everything you guys are using in the credit,
the way you're using it, is unlawful.
Just because everyone does it, doesn't mean that it's lawful.
Okay?
There's nothing there to measure.
I've discussed how the credit system works.
There's nothing there.
People say, well, I have to wait for money to be wired.
There's nothing going to be wired.
They can't wire anything.
It's created.
They're just messing with you.
So, when you start looking at the lunar cycle being 28.6457... days,
you're being messed with.
When the day ends at sundown, you're being messed with.
When the dark moon is the new moon, you're being messed with.
Yeah, it's fun to mess with people.
That's why apparently, I mean, it's been done for so long.
Now, personally, I don't think it's fun to mess with people at all.
When I say mess with people, take that word however you want.
So, in essence, there's something called mixing where, you know,
there are certain things that you might say are absolute.
I'm not speaking in absolute terms, but I am suggesting that when something is
considered to be lawful, it also instills and incorporates a form of measurement
that allows one to objectify its lawfulness.
In geometry, that's, for example, known as the construction of geometric figures.
In order for a figure to be lawful, it has to have certain attributes in terms of
angles and sides and things like that.
So, when I say lawful, it should hearken the concept of measurement and management.
Okay?
Now, let's just go for just a quick recap.
High noon is very easy to measure, and also the full moon is very easy to measure.
And when the two shadows correspond of the moon and the sun, that is your equinox,
because equi means to measure or equinox meaning night.
So, yeah, if you're confused, that's quite well,
because welcome to planet Earth.
So, I just wanted to get into those points, because these are for man, by the way.
If you leave the subjectivity of the Earth, your objectivity of the sun and the moon
change radically.
By the way, I'm going to just throw this in there.
If you were to leave the Earth, you would be able to still perceive the moon,
but you will not perceive the sun.
Let's just throw that in there for future discussion.
So, in terms of mankind, his purpose and all that,
let's just go back before we continue, if we do,
and see what has been thrown around in the chat,
because there's one way to continue something known as Uncommon Radio
by seeing what people would like to hear.
Oh, it says, okay, U.S. just had an airstrike in Syria.
Well, yeah, well, was it John Matthew Bright's U.S. just had an airstrike in Syria.
Damn, they really want to get the pipeline going.
That's not about a pipeline, but it seems like it.
Yeah, well, the U.S.
Well, everything that's in there is from the U.S., France, and England.
It goes through various things.
Have you ever heard of, you know,
anything that shouldn't be done is done by those who tell you you shouldn't do it?
Have you ever heard the term, by the way, do as I say, not as I do?
Yeah, that's what's going on.
But, you know, they're going to have their airstrikes.
There's going to be – let me just say, just discussing mankind.
I've said this before with previous sonic experiences and episodes.
This thing you guys call war with dropping bombs and bullets and other things like that,
the state of capability of mankind to wage war is typically done that way.
But what people fear with that type of embattlement is that it will wipe out a whole people.
It usually doesn't.
It's a form of terrorism, typically.
Nuclear devices, tactical nukes, as you see, have been used through history.
Actually, you probably haven't.
You're probably just aware of Hiroshima and Nagasaki and all that other stuff that's been put in front of you.
But, for example, nuclear ordnance is an act of terror.
It has no strategic purpose, even though they call them strategic.
And I still see – there's some news sites I do go to occasionally,
and they do say, oh, nuclear attack, nuclear – so what?
Basically, a nuclear device is like hitting a hornet's nest with a baseball bat.
It will be rapid and destructive, but guess what?
It's left over.
Lots of angry hornets.
So the use of high-speed chemistry and shorting out dielectrics, which is known as atomic energy –
I shouldn't have said that, but I did anyway – is essentially a form of terrorism.
The way people are wiped out or genocided is through biologicals.
Sorry, folks.
And through something called radionics.
You don't need guns and tanks and bombs to do – if you wanted to eliminate a group of people.
It's not done that way.
What you are witnessing is an industry.
It's basically the legal society and the banking society that are doing this.
This meaning not the conflict and waging misery on a society,
but the way it's done, as you see, with tanks and guns and planes and bullets.
I had a conversation recently.
There was a major mainstream media outlet about 10 or 12 years ago.
There was, I think, a squirmish between Lebanon and Israel.
And it was a JAG officer who came on and said,
Basically, war works like this.
The attorneys call the other country and ask for money.
If they don't, we bomb them.
That's what's going on.
But you can't discuss this because people don't.
Anyway, we will.
Whoever is willing to listen,
we're willing to bring forward any information regarding these matters
so you can go back and measure what's happening.
But the horrors that are going to be put into what's known as nations in the Middle East are only just beginning.
But there's going to be a respite.
I think I've mentioned there's going to be a tremendous amount of brutality and bloodshed,
very rapid, that's going to be occurring in the future.
Not this year, not next year, but in the near future around that few years from now in other places.
Yes, it is very unfortunate.
But this is a society mankind has learned and has adapted legitimizing savagery.
Yes.
So it is unfortunate.
But nonetheless, let's see what else is in chat before we continue.
But I hope we're throwing certain topics around here.
There's a lot to be discussed.
And if anyone is more interested, the archive is a good way to go back and listen to it again, perhaps, if needed.
And there's also communication that could be had at www.uncommonradio.com.
You could email the Greek and perhaps I'll entertain or consider anything that's being written.
So, okay, I see there's still time discussion on the chat, which is important.
It's a hell of a lot more tangible and rational than a lot of other things I've seen being discussed about the earth and society at this point.
How can these things be measured if you have nothing to measure with?
There's a lot of guessing going on.
And hopefully that anything that could be said to get away from the guesswork is really where it's at, at least for a rational perspective.
So in terms of mankind, what else can be discussed about mankind?
Well, here's the thing.
You're going to be, as a society, I've mentioned if you've heard Greek speak before, you're in the credits part of civilization.
And what that means technically is that civilization is still going, but it ended, just like a film ends when the credits are rolling.
But technically the film is rolling.
But if you came in when the credits are rolling, the film is really over.
The major storyline is over.
And the credits have very specific characteristics, which lend themselves to be known as the credits,
which show things that you had not seen during the film and they're less interesting.
So when you consider this, bear in mind that this type of talk that you hear regarding the Middle East Union
and there's roughly around 15 or so years left for most people on this planet,
when these times start to manifest, the mindset is going to be completely the opposite.
Roughly by the mid-2020s, most people on this planet, I should say all people on this planet,
except for a very, very, very, very small group, will be aware and will be completely enthralled and enticed
and intent on not only believing, but living in a perfect society, which will be pledged and manifested.
Yes, there will be no war.
You will not have any of the conditions that you consider to be maladies around that time period.
You will have a new world order that is in place that is not the old world order, new world order that you hear bantered about.
That new world order that's been talked about for the past century or so is going to support this one.
This is going to be completely different.
It is still going to be based on a lot of the goddess religion things that you're familiar with now.
Have you ever heard of the legal society, the medical society, education society, entertainment industry?
That's all goddess religion stuff, right?
She's a malevolent goddess.
But like anything malevolent, they always present themselves as being benevolent.
But again, back by the middle 2020s, you will have a bona fide, almost perfect society on the planet.
Why?
It will not be propagandized, by the way.
You will see that it will be sort of, I should say, well, materialistically, it will be tangibly considered a perfect society.
Now, the reason why you're getting this is because when the gods do – see, when man does war with man, he softens the opponent and then does the kill shot.
When the gods do war, they raise their opponent to their highest position and best and most optimum position and then go with the kill shot.
This is what people will not understand.
So again, this type of conversation and information that you do hear imparted through Greek speak will almost not be possible around that time period because no one wants to hear it because what are you talking about?
Look at this.
This is a perfect society.
And the more perfect it seems to become, the closer you are to the kill shots.
Now, this is – try to keep this light.
There's a tremendous amount of specifics.
There's a tremendous amount of more information that can be given and discussed.
And I think that in about a year, that time will be where more of it can or will be discussed.
And then after a few years after that, it will probably start to go away and shut down because the manifestation of this new reality is going to begin,
especially around the 2021-2022, what you call 2021-2022-2023 time period which is prior to the formation of this Middle East Union.
None of this kind of talk will be acceptable because you will be made promises that pretty much the conditions are going to last a thousand years and you're all going to believe it.
Yes.
So when I say you all, you know who you are pretty much all of you.
So the interesting part here is when you want to discuss mankind, is it perhaps a way to discuss mankind in generality from the beginning to the end?
What of a better place to start than the beginning?
But when you look at the finish line, it's very much like the starting line.
As a matter of fact, it's the same.
So discussing mankind is important, especially if it's the six solo event because the number corresponds to man.
And I also want to just bring up again, if anyone brings up, evokes the number six or 666, that has nothing to do with the main adversary that's ruling the planet, by the way.
The only thing it has to do with that main adversary is that the one that is identified with that 666 is going to be probably the only and the first human to be possessed by the adversary.
Yes.
So anyway, there's some pretty interesting stuff to get into that as well, which will not be possible, by the way, when these things are manifesting, if you get my drift.
So one thing to say is that it's a very interesting time.
I think I've said even on air that any of the patriarchs and the old holy writs would have given their left testicle to be alive today.
And most people don't even realize what's going on.
Because, look, there is a certain setup.
You're being set up.
And in order to be set up, if you know that you're being set up, it's not a setup because you'll resist it.
Another way to think about it is that avoidance of a trap is knowledge of its existence.
But certain things are just so appealing that the possibility of it being an entrapment is just maybe secondary because it just looks so good.
And this is something to consider about human nature.
But the purpose of man, one thing I just want to throw out there again is that I had a conversation with a caller a few weeks ago.
And the suggestion was to discover who you are, where you are, and when you are, and then food, clothing, and shelter.
Now, that sounds really base, and was the comment on that proposal.
But when you go on a path to improve and discover who you are, when you are, and where you are, and food, clothing, and shelter of highest quality,
there is nothing that cannot be known by mankind that you will not run into on the way of improving and discovering those things.
So bear that in mind.
Why?
Have you heard all things in moderation?
Yes.
But you know what, folks?
Nothing exceeds excess.
So I just wanted to say that if you discover that you, humanity, mankind, in this technical, functional form, and spiritual, which is also technical, are made up of three things.
You're made up of a mind, a breath, meaning a living metabolism, and a body, which body will exist and constantly change depending if it's alive or dead.
So again, the mind, which in English typically is the PSY prefix, or in Greek would be the convention that is used.
Whenever you see the psyche or the PSY, as in psychology, psychotic, psychopath, psychiatrist, PSY prefix denotes the mind, which is the spirit, which is what makes you you, your mind, or the mind.
Whenever you see the PNU, pneumatic, or pneuma in Greek, or pneumonia, PNU, that is the soul.
That is the breath.
That is something that is in the nostrils, and it's part of the metabolism.
And then when you see the carne or the body, the carnal, that is the body.
That is the flesh.
That is the almost identical elemental composition as the soil.
Okay, so that's the three things that you're made up of.
And by the way, I've said this many times, I'll say it again.
All these quote-unquote gurus and people think they're so spiritual, ask them to define soul and spirit, watch what happens.
Can't do it.
Can't do it, because you're not supposed to project this type of knowledge the way that it's being done.
And their reward is ignorance.
You ever run into someone called a guru, or a spiritualist, or an astrologer, or a psychic, or a wizard, or a witch?
Right?
You ever run into these types?
They're all over the place.
Intuitive, right?
The way they're projecting it unlawfully, their reward is bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh.
Right?
So you might hear them using a particular language, but when you put the Babelfish translator on, all you're going to hear is bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh, bleh.
So, you know, do you want some candy?
And one way to prove that to these idiots, by the way, is ask them to define soul, ask them to define spirit.
And they will give you a million reasons why it's not those two things, but they can't give you a reason for why anyone can know.
No one can know is one of the things I recently heard.
Anyway, I just want to throw a little dig in there, because look, if you're going to sit around and put a dig on seven and a half billion people,
that's going to take a really long time.
So you just take these large swaths at a time, just slap them in the tuchus, like they say in Yiddish or whatever, and kick them out the door.
And that's perhaps – because no one is doing that.
I don't know if anyone can do it at this time.
And the other thing I wanted to just bring up – this is not a rant, but you old folks out there, you guys like over 50 or 60,
you've got to start talking to young people.
But the problem is, listen, I feel you.
You really don't know Jack.
So what are you going to say?
Nothing.
But here's the thing.
I know Jack.
Anyway, who's Jack?
So one of the things, if you watch, folks, that's why the old people have been rewarded with being thrown into nursing homes,
completely drugged up, and they slap a pair of diapers on them.
Yep, that's what the old folks have been.
All have been reduced to a band of fools.
And I say all.
I mean pretty much all.
I haven't met any that are not foolish or heard of any that are not.
And by the way, it's not what you believe.
If you like what someone is saying and you really like them, that's not what I'm talking about.
Are you listening to what's being said and measuring it up?
Do you have any reference points?
Next time you have a family gathering, hang around the old people and ask them some questions.
Don't even bring up Greek-speak stuff.
We're not using like what's lawful as a measure.
Just really listen.
What's happened?
You young folks are in deep, deep doo-doo.
Yeah, because, see, the old folks used to be bastions of wisdom and experience,
but now they've been reduced to a band of fools.
Not only that you're not only at home, let's say, or personal, go into public places,
listen to the older people, even on the Internet, alternative media.
Listen to these old folks, not too many of them, but you got to wonder.
Yeah, you're in big trouble, you young folks.
Can't turn to them.
Now, you can go to anyone you like, and you might think they've got wisdom and knowledge or whatever,
but I'm telling you they don't.
Sorry.
You know, why?
Measure it.
Anyway, I just thought I'd throw that in there because there's a whole bunch of stuff going on
that you folks are still not aware of, and it's in your face, and it's obvious.
Because, remember, if you're going to go out and make any discoveries, it's nothing far away.
It's the obvious.
Yes, yes, and when you discover the obvious, it's not going to make you happy.
Because, well, it should make you happy because it didn't take a lot of traveling to find it, did it?
It was right there in front of you.
So, anyway, regarding mankind, again, just to go back, there's not much time to discuss these things,
a few years at least, but at least it is being discussed, right?
And the other thing about mankind is once you discover who you are, the spirit is the mind,
the soul is the breath and the metabolism, the life force that pulses through you,
and also nitrogen is the primary constituent in mass or in volume of air.
You ever notice you're breathing nitrogen mostly?
Think about it.
What do you know about nitrogen?
Oh, it's the oxygen that you need.
Yeah, yeah, you need oxygen.
You need all of them.
Yeah, but you're breathing your nitrogen breathers.
So, that's by observation, right?
And you've got to know about the body.
You're not a filter bag, are you?
No, you've got things absorbing, huh?
If you've got anything absorbed into the body, you'll be dead in a couple of days.
It's called sepsis, folks.
You're completely sealed up in a vacuum.
Yeah, go figure that out.
Don't ask any old people about it.
They won't tell you or a wizard or an intuitive or whatever.
Yeah, they'll tell you a million reasons why you're absorbing,
but they can't explain it, of course, because you're not.
So, you're going to have to, yeah, grab a boot.
Anyway, pull your pants up, tighten your belt, and start walking around like a man
or like a woman if you're a woman or whatever.
You know, put your chin up and realize that, yeah, you've been lied to.
Why do you think they tell lies to children all the time?
To prepare you for the world.
Now, what's going to happen is you're going to need to figure out what's going on in front of you first.
And that's really the thing about mankind is, you know,
if you want to think how big the Earth is, you know, it's really, really large, right?
Well, yeah, it could be.
You know, it's relative, I guess.
You know, it depends on how big you are.
And there's a lot of things to see, a lot of places to go.
But what I've noticed is that when people typically, through the lifetime, went on vacation,
they're all wondering about if they locked the door or not or when they're going to get back.
So why even bother going on a vacation if you're stressing that?
You get a big-ass flat-screen TV and throw in videos of Madagascar if you're interested.
Don't waste your time.
Be effective.
Be efficient, right?
I'm not saying that all vacations are a waste of time, but just think about it.
So mankind is don't be enthralled, you know.
Mankind has been led down all these things.
You're being told through society and your whole life what is good, what is bad, what you should do, what you shouldn't do.
Really?
Yeah, all of that holds true to a certain degree.
But, you know, what do you know about yourself?
And if you answered you think you want to know more, that's correct.
And you don't need some esoteric feeling to lead you in that direction.
What is necessary is to perhaps pull the veil slightly away from the cosmic censorship.
If you're heavily censored, by the way, you will not understand any of this or comprehend or see its importance.
Not that it's important because I'm saying it.
But if you don't think that knowing who you are, where you are, and when you are,
and food, clothing, and shelter of the utmost quality that you want to afford or can afford is important,
you're really not of good character.
And it's not meaning that I'm demeaning those who are not interested or not of good character.
But let's just go back and measure.
You ever hear about people talking about politics or the economy like there's really money?
Or the body like you take these drops and you'll feel better?
Yeah, you know what I'm saying?
Go get to know these people personally and you'll see that their diet sucks.
They don't know what food is and good food is or anything.
And they put crappy fluids into their body.
I think one time the Greeks said that people who put crappy food and crappy drink into their body
are promoting poor character.
So next time you hear people talking about these categories,
get to know them a little bit more and you'll find out they eat junk.
And you eat junk, you think junk.
Can't help it.
Anyway, this is something to think about, not a criticism.
If you could criticize what's going on in the community at the same time,
make it positive for who's listening, why not?
What you're going to find out is as you improve your intake, what passes through the body,
you're going to notice that your attitude, your energy level,
and your cognitive ability will be better as well, especially if you eat seasonally.
And if you know how to dress, by the way, you're going to feel a lot better.
By the way, never buy shoes you can't run in.
Think about it.
And shelter.
Make sure your shelter is clean.
It doesn't mean spraying chemicals around.
And if you've got those nasty cleaning chemicals in what's called a living space,
develop a chemical box or a chemical closet outside of where you live and sleep.
And if you're in one of these apartments or something
and you can't keep those strong chemicals in the apartment, let's say,
just ask if you could put them somewhere else, like down the hall or in the basement somewhere.
Or if you really can't keep them outside of the living space, don't use them.
A really good cleaner, by the way, is like hydrogen peroxide and water in a spray bottle
or a little bit of alcohol in a spray bottle.
Yeah, alcohol's not going to kill you.
By the way, you folks in AA and all that, you're mentally sick and you're unrehabilitatable.
Alcoholics Anonymous, I just want to say this.
I ran into a couple of people once who mentioned alcohol, like,
I'm going to touch alcohol.
I said, you've been in AA, and they're like, yeah.
One of the most demoralizing, demonic, downright satanic organizations man has ever put forward
is Alcoholics Anonymous.
Why?
Because most people think they're being helped.
No, yeah, that's true.
Because the worse it is, the more people want it.
But because it is demoralizing the human spirit.
It is getting the individual or the idiot or the moron to go in there and admit that they are a behavior.
Think about it.
I have never seen a more demoralizing.
Now, I'm not talking about someone locked in a basement in a cage that's being urinated and defecated on every day,
saying they would admit certain things.
I'm talking about overt public, because there are worse things in Alcoholics Anonymous.
Like being locked in a cage and never seeing daylight and being defecated and urinating on
and admitting that you like it.
I'm talking about public stuff that anyone can access.
It's far worse.
And what spurred this on, by the way, is just a commentary.
Think about it.
So anyway, back to the alcohol.
A little bit of isopropyl, or if you get Everclear, which is moonshine,
a little bit of that in some water in a spray bottle.
Excellent cleaning.
Hydrogen peroxide, which is acidic and oxidizing.
Excellent cleaning property.
So now you keep the living space, your shelter, clean.
The shelter you're using, clean.
Now, unfortunately, many of the modern materials outgas all this crap.
Always leave a window slightly open.
Promote good circulation.
So pretty much covered everything.
Where you are.
Well, we covered who you are.
Well, maybe.
When you are.
Maybe you've covered that.
And food, clothing, and shelter.
Food's been covered in archives.
I'd like to discuss it, but at least how to think about it.
Yeah, can you take someone who's got a lousy character
and make them good character with good food and good water?
No, not really, but it does help, and it is a major factor.
It is a variable.
When the variable is changed, the equation changes.
Or it's a variable in the equation, I should say.
Get the right one, and everything adds up.
And then shelter.
Don't poison yourself and the shelter you're using
with cleaning chemicals and things.
Just use basic water and basic soap.
By the way, have you ever heard about soaps cause cancer?
You know, these artificial soaps and dish soaps?
You know what?
It's the fragrances that do that.
Yeah.
So unless it's one of these like adjuvetic or organically made fragrant soaps,
if it's got one of those toxic floral smells,
that's the stuff that makes you sick, not the surfactant or the soap.
So think about that.
Yeah.
So that's pretty much the general coverage for mankind.
The rest of it is just a matter of being present.
I always tell people, you know, doing a particular project or something,
I need a lot of bodies, is it a show?
I don't know anything about that.
See, if you show up, that's 90% of the work.
Well, if you showed up on this planet and you're at Manifest,
you're about 90% done.
The other 10% is up to you if you're going to set yourself apart or be part of it.
So we actually have someone coming in on Skype.
We just have about a quarter of an hour left.
Let's see if it's possible to add them to the group.
Let's give it a shot.
And we'll see if it comes up.
Seth Michael, let's see if he does come in.
We'll try him again.
Maybe the board can bring him in.
For some reason, he is not coming in.
I know Seth's got lots to say, or it appears that he does.
Maybe AFR can bring him in, can drag him in, because he was trying to call in.
We have less than a quarter of an hour left here.
So this being the giving some notoriety to being the sixth time around,
I just like to bring up things in accordance to how they are.
And also, folks, don't forget, it's springtime up here.
You've heard the Greeks say that in the spring it's really quiet.
It's when things are planted to grow.
Even throughout history, since when is where the noise is being made,
where it's really happening, where it's really at?
Think about it.
Very rarely.
Giving you folks an example, you've heard of something called the Great Depression
and all that other stuff, a lot of noise being made.
You know what they pulled under people is that they're under a credit-based economy
and everything is paid for, but you can't tell people that because human nature is so shitty.
Yes, I use that biblical term.
Dung.
So think about it.
Right now, there's a lot of stuff that people are making noise about,
and you've got to look at where it's quiet.
And how are you going to find it if it's quiet?
It's not going to take your attention.
You kind of have to keep it in the back of the mind.
Like, for example, if you're running a retail store
and a bunch of guys have a fight in aisle six,
you should direct someone to go and check out what's going on
and at the same time, you should go and run and go look and see if the front door,
entrance and egress door, and the cash register is okay
because typically when something like that happens,
it's a distraction for the money or to pull the register and run with it.
This is maybe an old-school thing to say, but you get the picture.
So controversy or controversy is always profitable,
and there's no way to make a profit, by the way.
It's a credit-based economy when you think about it.
So Seth, if you're listening, I see you're trying to come on for some reason.
I cannot bring Seth Michael in.
I'm sure he can say a thing or two.
And if we had AFR present, maybe they could bring him in.
I don't know if AFR is listening.
Oh, okay, that's fine.
He's probably having a connection.
Okay, so a connection issue.
So there you go, folks.
How much can you stress something that's considered an idea?
See, if it's just an idea, is it worth stressing it?
Well, no, not really.
Is it worth just saying it?
Absolutely.
And I think taking what's being said however you want to take it could be important
or just trivial if you can even understand it, by the way.
So learn to discern and be objective.
Another thing about mankind, which I would just maybe want to suggest,
and just to, I don't know, there's much to say,
but the other thing to consider about mankind
and how basic the existence here on this planet really is,
is you are the only, well, I should say,
there is a cognitive ability regarding the society of the gods that mankind has.
In other words, the supernatural beings, the other side, that is very unique.
And at that point, what that does for you is that you're never really alone.
And the other thing what that does for mankind is that you're going to be
interacted with whether you like it or not.
Have you ever heard of things called dreams?
Those are not your own.
You're being plugged.
Yeah, regardless if you want to believe that or know that,
you will find that out later, might as well just say it now.
Okay?
And the other thing about that is there's various forms of assistance,
both good and bad, from the other side.
And there's also various forms of acknowledgments from what mankind can do
regarding the other side.
And because of his limited lifespan and because of the world of the unseen,
man is solely reliant on the memorialized information to really have proper
knowledge.
Just, like, for example, going back to the concept of dreams,
if you don't have proper knowledge of the spiritual realm,
you will not be able to manage the dream state or shut it off if it's
negative or encourage it if it's positive.
Or I would suggest that anyone that does have proper knowledge would not be
encouraging any plugging in to the mind or the spirit while you're asleep
because that is a time of recuperating the body.
Now, most of the intuitives, pagans, atheists, or whatever,
they like the dreams because they don't have proper knowledge
and they don't know what's going on, and sometimes best to not know.
Because the last thing you want is an entire population that is aware of
what's going on, and that might just affect the plan.
But one thing that I would suggest is that mankind is almost a perfect vehicle
to interact between the physical world and the nonphysical world just by the
elements of creation that were put in place for him to exist.
You're not an animal.
That's the thing I would suggest.
I mean, there's so much to say, but mankind might share some of the
mechanisms and organs and things like that, but mankind is not an animal
spiritually.
And he is the medium or the in-between, the go-between,
the gods and the material world.
But unfortunately, the cosmic censorship, which had to be put in place
2,500 years ago, otherwise, I don't know.
Folks, if they were in full knowledge of what's going on, you probably would
have wanted to leap off this planet a few thousand years ago,
or a couple thousand years ago and not be around.
And then they'd have to gather you all about like the frog and put him back
in the water, back in the pot.
So there's a curing period that has to be comprehended.
Things have been discussed through Greek-speak, and fortunately,
that period is almost over.
And unfortunately, it's almost over because it's going to be very,
very dynamic.
But the inclination that I would give anyone, well, the inclination that can
be gotten from Greek-speak is that you're going to have to start referring
and start looking at things that have come before you because the ancients
were not ridiculous.
They were not ignorant.
You are always being given the vision that they were backwards and ignorant
because of sandals and horses and various things like that.
That was not the case.
There were qualitative decisions and limitations that were put on the
ancients in contrast to make you seem like you're modern because you have
airplanes and cellophones and things like that.
That is not the case.
There were interactions and other things that were done that were far beyond
what is being done in the modern world.
So there is no reason to discount that.
And believe it or not, just like anything, it's like a muscle.
Once you start comprehending everything that's been memorialized prior to this
society by other societies and civilizations,
what you're going to discover is how many holes have been deliberately left
there, how much is being censored from you,
and how similar everything kind of is.
So one thing, again, if you're looking for new ideas,
go back to some old information.
And being man or woman, when I say men or man, it also includes woman,
you are extremely unique and extremely powerful to come, though,
not at the moment.
And I want to just bring something up to that.
You're being talked about and talked at that you are wonderful individuals.
And you have all this power and you can do anything you want or whatever.
You hear this all the time in all forms and shapes and forms of poetry,
media, and instruction in general.
But when you start dealing when specific people individually deal with other
individual people, that message tends to fall apart.
And what you get is you have to be like everybody else.
So there is a level to consider what society will be and what mankind will be.
It will not have the vile, when I say vile,
and repugnant hypocrisy that is in place right now.
And what I'm discussing here is not like this might be considered an alternative
media platform.
When you turn into these alternative media types,
they're always bashing, quote, unquote, the conventional government,
corporations, and whatever, whatever.
This is not it.
The vileness and the hypocrisy, it begins at home.
It starts with the parents and the children.
It starts within the group think.
Gustave Le Bon talks about the crowd.
If you start listening to all these people everywhere,
you will start finding out there are crowds forming.
And you'll notice that the faster and the larger the group,
the less cognitive or dumber they are.
So this is a fact, folks, on this planet.
These are facts about mankind.
It might sound dogmatic because you don't like it.
But I will suggest that pursue things that are pleasant.
But unfortunately, if you're going to have measurable and lawful things that are of
quality, you will not find them in crowds,
and you will not find them in groups.
Typically the best things in life are sequestered and are held more separate.
So pursue the best things in life.
This is solo number six.
Thank you for coming, everyone.
We'll see you again soon.