Greetings everyone and welcome to another sonic experience with the Greek, also known as Uncommon
Radio, perhaps also known as Uncommon Sense Radio or Greek Speak, or if you kind of hear it, it's
too late. So, by the way, it's what they call April, according to the Pope's work schedule,
roughly the 13th in the year 2017, according to their Lord. And let's just say, lawfully,
I'm reckoning, it's the middle of, just past the middle of the first week of the second month,
or roughly the fifth day of the second month till noon. So, let's see if there's any
clashing of the brain cells on that. And I do see a little bit there, yeah, regarding in the chat,
by the way, this is a very interactive experience, sonic experience. So, when this is,
the liturgy of this event is conducted, let's say that callers are welcome, the chat is engaged,
emails are engaged, because it's really, you guys are the guests. In other words,
if you are listening to this, even though if it's further down the road, you are still a guest to
it. And like a little joke, like what does Greek speak and heavy artillery have in common? Once you
hear it, it's too late. Notice I didn't say if you, but let's just say again, to go back for
date time, because it's not just a matter of nomenclature, just dating the quote unquote show,
as they call them. It's a matter of also, I wouldn't say poking fun, but yeah, don't you
want to kick them in the shins a little bit sometimes, or who's they? But what's lawful
is what can be measured. Now, most people think it's what they call April 13th. And by the way,
most people will glaze over when you bring up this topic, and they'll just have a real shallow,
dumb look on their face saying, I don't know what you're saying, man. But for those of you that do,
on the Pope's work schedule, it's April 13th, 2017. I know I'm being redundant,
but it appears to be just past the middle of the week of the first week, let's say,
of the second month. So it's roughly the reckoning, roughly the fifth day of the second month.
That's interesting. By the way, I want to thank, I do get some messages, Skype and email and such,
and someone had been doing some pretty good reckoning. And let's just say, from a radical,
truthful perspective, I heard the Greeks say that when you measure time regarding lawful time,
things that are measurable using the sun, the moon and the stars and other positions as such,
you will find that events repeat themselves accurately. And I had some confirmation on that.
Now, it was slightly anomalous because there was a 13th month, but nonetheless, the lineup was so
precise. So I want to thank people that report back on what is lawful. Of course,
just to reiterate real quick, I would just say that lawful just means it's measurable. And if
you can't measure it, you can't manage it. You ever wonder why there's so many managerial problems?
Well, anyway, speaking of managerial problems, if you'd like to join the, I wouldn't say
conversation, but if you'd like to join the sonic experience and partake and contribute
using what's considered the normal telephone lines, it would be 218-339-8525. And that would
be again, 218-339-8525. And if you prefer using the Skype convention, you can go to the uncommon
radio.com www.uncommonradio.com. And the email for the Greek and on that site is also the Skype
contact. So you would actually type in uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com. And that's a numeric
one. And that in the Skype search box, if you'd like to join in Skype now also looking at the
chat, which happens to be on American freedom radio. And by the way, if you are hearing this
now and didn't get all that other information, you can go to the American freedom radio homepage
and you will see on the left, there is a call in number in red with a box around it is on the left.
If you don't see it on the left, it's on your other left. And that would be 218-339-8525. So
with that said, it seems like right out of the gate, you know, it seems the topic can be regarding
time and what's lawful. It's a good way to segue into other things. And speaking of segueing into
other things, it appears to be around the seventh solo episode of the Greek. And we've been numbering
these on the archives solo one, two, three, all the way down. Now, what's interesting about that
is that earlier I stopped from saying join the conversation because this is not a conversation.
When the Greek speaks, he doesn't have conversations. He talks at people. Now,
does that sound rude? Yes, it sounds rude, but is it rude? It's not. If you've been on this planet
long enough, and you can classify the surface dwelling earth inhabitants as I won't say it
because I've said it enough. Some people think they find it offensive, even though they do like
to listen to what's being said. It is a reality that is just not, let's just say, discussed in
normal dialogue. So if you like to want to be talked at, or you want to talk at the Greek and
the audience, please call in and partake. But nonetheless, being solo, I just want to again,
bring up there, there's a project that's pending. And it's going to be somewhat different. And why
is it going to be different? Well, the interesting thing is because it's not only going to be
informative, because information is not only the key that people think it is. The information is
what you get inside after you get the keys and unlock the door. And you need a mindset for that.
You ever take out some keys in the dark, and you can't find which one fits in the right. Okay,
you get the picture. It's going to be regarding a mindset. The whole thing is how to develop an
objective mindset. And no, these are not memory techniques or objective techniques.
It's just a very simple, organic way of discussing how things are, and why they are perhaps. So maybe
you can irritate people by explaining things instead of just describing them. So this is the
seventh time around in the last time, kind of mentioned six being a number of men and got into
a little bit of what the structure in terms of explanation of why things are going on the way
they are, is and that is basically what do cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common,
and that would be archived. And that is a typical Greek cliche type stuff. But if you've ever heard,
I just want to tag along on last week's thought there, you ever heard having your cake and eat it
to that's pretty much stems off of that. What do cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common?
When you hear people having their cake and eat it to literally it means I can have my child and
eat it also. Because you're really hell bent on that stuff as humans. But here's the thing.
One thing that I had done on another recording, somewhere on the internet, I had described why
there is a obsession with human sacrifice. And I wouldn't say in a lascivious manner, but tends to
be once you know what it is, the gynic and phallic symbolism throughout society, whether it's an
just symbolism throughout. And then of course, how the concept of sexuality has been bandied about
in many ways, you know, expressed, whether it's natural or unnatural, meaning unnatural,
meaning part of the goddess religion. Because if you want to understand, there are spiritual
beings influencing the earth. And just like here, I see someone in the chat. Yes, seven is about the
will get into that as well. Thank you, young Matthew. I would just suggest that just a few
more things. When people when you hear things being discussed, or even in print, or even university or
anything like that, you'll notice that the information sounds like it's being packaged
like it has a lot of value, but it really doesn't. That's one of the reasons why Greek speak is being
done. So, you know, when the gods come up, it usually goes to we don't know it's what you
believe or their ets. And it seems like everything has been flushed away and no one wants to look at
it. And seriously, mankind has a serious case of the fox and the grapes. That's a Aesop's fables.
If you're not familiar with Aesop fables, maybe you might have heard of the hare and the tortoise.
And well, he did one called the fox and the grapes. And that is a really good description
on the attitude and the mindset. So I just wanted to add one more thing to the pretty much like an
addendum to what was discussed about what do cannibals birthdays and dolls have in common.
And just to tag along how this obsessive nature of development of gynic and phallic symbols and
human sacrifice has been, you know, through society all throughout society so much that you get used
to it just like riding a bike. You don't think about it. You don't think about walking. You don't
think about riding a bike or tying shoelaces when you reach a certain point of alleged maturity.
Now, what's interesting about that is you can search many forms of holy writ or other writ,
and you see that mankind being an agricultural based creature, even though right now you think
you're modern and information based, you're not. You could lock a computer geek in a room
without anything agricultural. He won't even have pants on, by the way, or she, and you'll
probably starve within a few weeks. Yes, a few weeks, because you can stay alive, whatever.
So you're all agriculturally based. Now, the thing about the production of life on earth,
let's say the production of life on earth, maybe we'll re-coach that a little bit. The continuation
of life on earth through procreation with most things tends to be with a seed and a fertilization
of that seed and so on and so forth. You might call it the polar opposite of male and female,
and they both have a seed, for example, that comes together and you form that procreation.
That's why, for example, when mankind was considered through holy writs and others
to be the most important creature on the planet, meaning the steward of everything here natural,
he is important. But what is the most important part about man? Well, obviously,
you could say the heart. You could say, well, the lungs, the internal organs,
the brain. That could be contested. And also, why are we discussing or why was importance discussed
in significance? Ultimately, it was just the agricultural perspective of how does man continue
and what that continuation or procreation is based on is obviously the most important organ.
And that would be the gynec and phallic aspects that you see in architecture and
quote-unquote pagan culture, which you will see throughout Christendom and other religions as
well, because they are as such as well, very much so. By the way, if you're running anyone
that insists that they are pagan, I mean, that's a really good candidate for the next pope.
But anyway, I would just say that when you consider these things in a metaphor, you would
say the most important thing for the farmer other than the production and yield and bringing to
market is that he has seeds for his next year crop. Otherwise, he's temporarily or only an annual
farmer. So in order for him to continue, he needs to have some seed. So what the consideration was
with mankind, where does the seed come from? It is the sexual organs of genitalia. And that's why,
again, you see it throughout architecture and symbolism. But nonetheless, when offerings were
made, it was the best of what you produced. Okay? Now, what is the best of what mankind can produce
in this realm? Yes, a child. That is the product of the seed and the procreation mechanisms and
organs. Henceforth, the human sacrifice. This is the type of inspiration that humanity has had
for thousands of years. Essentially, it was decided, inspired, and put into effect.
But the most important organs were the genitalia, because they considered the ability to procreate
and keep man going. And the offspring was the product of that, which led to the sacrifice to
these demons and things like that. So when I say demon, meaning spiritual beings that were
influencing mankind of low tier type, which is a typical thing that most people, when they consider
gods or angels or religions across the board, they are actually just considering these lower
entities. They know nothing about the higher entities. They might in passing and in literature
and allude to it, but it seems to be still very much taboo to discuss these with accuracy.
So I wanted to throw in the aspect of why you see this obsession with human sacrifice,
especially of children, and of the Gainix symbols and all that throughout. And by the way,
this is a first. I've looked high and low, but I didn't look low enough. Anyway, I looked high and
low on what they call the World Wide Web, and I have not found anything similar to this. So it
adds value to what's being said. It actually makes the Greek feel like he could stop what he's doing
and do this two-hour thing once a week here. But again, pending, there is a project that will have
much more information. It won't be this strange stuff that I hear, well, we're giving you the
truth, but in my opinion, okay, well, we've got a serious problem here, a little bit of
schizophrenia. But anyway, there's a level here of sanity that you folks will find in the future
in certain projects that you will find unnerving because you're not used to it. And it will not be
pedantic. It will be expressive and explanatory and hopefully edifying. And why not? Because
ultimately, tonight, we're going to be speaking about the gods to some extent, based on other
input, of course, no pun intended, because one of the first sonic productions I've done here with
Ocelli was all external input. And it is managed by the gods. And again, I just want to reiterate
the piss poor, the just very piss poor quality of information and what they might call the
information matrix, and also the desire of people to learn more about this situation known as
man's relation to the gods. Because when you discuss the gods, it's a temporal aspect of
the lifetime that mankind experiences is too short to take these things seriously.
People don't want to think beyond their lifespan. And now you've heard perhaps there are certain
groups that do and fine for them, but I'm discussing people in general. And once you
kind of get an idea of what is going on with the infrastructure, and I've typically given the
metaphor, people ride, let's say an infrastructure of a subway system, and they just partake for 20
minutes or an hour a day. They don't really think about what went into it and what it's really about
and the effort and the cost and all this. This is almost the same way analogously how people
experience their lives on earth. And it's very simple, folks. Let me just throw something else
in. The influence of the gods is on everything. Now, whether you acknowledge it or not or know
it or not is not relevant. What is relevant is that a statement like that is true. That is the
interesting part about it. Now, the hypocrisy that you find within the entitled classes of any
field, whether it's legal, medical, judicial, economic, or even the religious fields, those
that have come out of certain ministerial schools, divinity schools, Bible colleges,
it's all the same. These people are in those positions that are trained as professionals in
simply to accommodate the mindset of humanity. They have very little information or even the
proper mindset. Just without getting into bantering about the entitled classes, who you
call professionals, because that's simple. Anyone who is even half aware sees that they're all
idiots. Now, all of them are not necessarily idiots, by the way, because there are a few who
do find out that it's all a scam and they try to make an exit strategy to get out of it.
But the ones that stay definitely are. Now, here's the thing.
If there was true education offered on mankind society, no one would go. No one would partake
because real education would be so far and different and in contrast from the mindset
that's been instilled for so long that they wouldn't recognize it as such. It would just be
gobbledygook to them. So, there's many ways to look at this and we'll discuss more of that in
the future using certain exercises of perception. The thing is, do you see what you see or do you
see what you want to see or do you see what you think you see? Do you know how to see? You have
eyes, but can you see? You have ears, but can you hear? That's why maybe we'll dedicate most of this
time on maybe expressing some of the aspects of the number seven as well as the relation to the
I haven't looked at the chat. Hopefully, we're going to start steering this sonic event
perhaps into it. So, let's see. We have someone here. Jan is messaging.
Greek, you mentioned in a past broadcast one-third of the gods will be forced down to earth in the
future. Will they inhabit human bodies or will they just influence from the unseen realm both?
And even when they're inhabiting a human body, you can have someone x-rayed and you won't see it.
There's sort of a counter-spatial. This is a counter-spatial issue which we'll discuss in
the future on another project. Now, folks, you have to remember that, yes, there is an audience
for each quote-unquote episode that you hear or go to, but essentially, this is still public
speaking even though if it's private thinking or private conversations, let's say, that just
happen to be on a minor internet platform, it doesn't matter. It still is public and you have
to realize, folks, that the truth, yes, I don't like using that word because everyone's sort of
using it and it's turned into something not very good, but things that are actually accurate and
lawful are, when you start discussing them, they're viewed in bad taste. It doesn't mean
that I'm intimidated by it because I think I've suggested that this planet isn't inherently
inhabited by surface-dwelling earth inhabitants that are specifically, you guessed it, yes.
So the issue is not a matter of discussing it because everyone thinks or not discussing it's
in bad taste. The issue is the way to do it is a certain way and there is something about live
radio that you're getting right now and even most people get it down the stream. It's in a can,
but the future stuff will not be live. It'll sort of be pre-recorded and what's interesting is
it'll still be in a neat package and many packages and it'll be useful to most. Well,
it should be useful to anyone who subscribes to that form of thinking.
Now, many people say, well, just because I don't think like you, does that mean that what I'm
thinking about is wrong? And I'm like, wait a second, you're presuming that you know what
thinking is, you see, because if you've ever heard someone says, well, I don't think like you,
so that can't, you see, so right away that means that they don't even understand that thinking is
objective, you see, so it's kind of like what the legal society, what has done to mankind
and or any aspect of society. This is the thing before we get more into the gods and also see
what questions are posed. One has to comprehend that the more malevolent the force typically
that's designed to be long-term malevolency, the more benevolent it appears,
right? And a good counterfeiter will always make it look like the real thing,
the perception of what the real thing or the genuine article should be like, right?
This is where humanity has been. So you're pretty much in a really piss poor shape,
but on the other hand, if you've ever heard Greek speak before, the advice is to do absolutely
nothing because the most important thing for you, yes, you, if you're listening,
if you have a general lifespan that those that are descendants of Adam do, which you know what
the general lifespan is, you should absolutely consider the most important things in the life
that you're living to be food, clothing and shelter and also to consider discovering what
you are made of. You are made of three things and we'll get into that as well.
A spirit, a soul and a body and yes, if you'd start discussing these things with accuracy,
not because the Greeks said so, because you can discover them accurately on your own.
Just like if you're on the telephone and someone says, well, you know, I'm selling windows. I'm
bringing one right over. How big is the window in the room? Well, just a second. I've got a tape
measure. Anyone could look at this stuff, but you don't because you're under the influence. Anyway,
you will see that things are not quite as you've thought them to be, but let's see,
where were we? To discuss things that people inherently shun. Finding out that you're made
up of a soul, a spirit and a body, by the way, when you discover any kind of ancient holy writ,
that is brought up very often. I actually had the misfortune today. I've said I don't do this,
but I actually did it for two minutes today. I went around the web and I landed on some
internet radio somewhere and fortunately, I was wearing plastic on the shoes because I didn't
step in shit directly where I had to wash it off the shoes. I just peeled the plastic off and all
the shit fell off real quick. But anyway, that's just a hint. If you're walking through the dog
park, put those plastic booties on. So I turned it on and these people are professing reincarnation
in Buddhism and all that. I'm like, what a bunch of idiots. Not that these people are specifically
idiots, but just general, you know, idiocy that you see from humankind. And they're discussing
aspects of reincarnation in Buddhism and you will not find that in any Buddhist doctrine,
by the way. As a matter of fact, these people are so stupid that they're actually, I dropped
some things and I actually saw some links that the Buddhists say, well, how can you reincarnate
if you don't have a soul? So they don't even know what the soul and the spirit and the body is.
So when you run into an idiot, a good mark of an idiot is that they believe, quote unquote,
reincarnation over and over and over and all these other religions. When I say other religions,
I mean the conventional religions. And by the way, before we get into the gods,
in prior sonic events, I used to like kind of dispel a biblical cliche. Not because,
oh, the Greek says it's this, because anyone can see it. It's like, wake up, you know, don't be
whatever, asleep. You know, it's kind of dangerous falling asleep behind the wheel eventually.
One of the myths I used, well, I dispelled most of the common ones, which are directly
mistranslation. But here's one that is kind of based on rationale. And I just want to suggest
this, you know, this is what they call, I'm not going to say it, it's a pagan holiday or whatever
in the springtime, you could guess what these morons are doing, which has nothing to do with
anything other than what they've been led to believe. But you know, there's something called
the New Testament. And if you run into someone that's in this convention, by the way,
I'll just say it, this is the Christian era, secularly. It doesn't matter what your religion,
you are the historians, who are typically atheists, considered to be the Christian era. But
nonetheless, chocolate eggs and Easter bunnies and stuff, I said it, oops, ridiculous. But
here's the thing, a lot of people that I do come in contact with have fallen for this syndrome.
And they always bring up what's called the New Testament. Now, you've heard me say, yes,
it's one contiguous document. And actually, in reality, it's not even a public document,
but it was made public. But it's fine, because no one will understand anything in there anyway.
But the interesting thing is, a certain event happened, let's just say at the resurrection
of the Christ. And almost immediately within a few days or weeks or so, people were,
let's say, tasked, called out and tasked to do something was to spread the Gospels,
what they say in the religious thing. And I'm like, well, hey, wait a second.
How are they going to spread the Gospel when it wasn't even written yet?
I'm going to take a pause here and have a sip of coffee. I want you folks to think about that.
Because what you're reading about, when you do read the New Testament, are written accounts that
were memorialized for recordation, which I will get into in the future more accurately of what
they really are, much later than when those events happened. So when they were told to go spread,
just like when you see people today, well, you got to do this and that, and they're talking,
well, not even New Testament, so it's Churchianity, not even Christianity, but Churchianity,
because Christianity doesn't really exist. It's broken up. There's many, many thousands of
factions that they all go to battle with the same crucifix, you see. But anyway,
the thing about it is this. How were those men initially tasked? And when they cursory look,
reading into the Bible, what they saw on TV, or church, or Sunday school, or the movies,
that they were preaching or teaching the Gospel when it wasn't even written yet. That sounds kind
of interesting, but if you're listening on common radio, it should be turning your head inside out
like a sock by now. But this is one of the rational dispelling of cliches that are out there,
and we will get into the future of what more accurate descriptions of what was going on.
But just for the sake of it, this is a seasonal thing or whatever. When you look at the movement
that came out of the first century out of the Middle East, what's called the area of Judea,
and you as people believe that Christianity and Judaism came out of this first century event,
you are completely wrong. You are just as deceived as saying that 19 Arabs with box cutters
hijacked the plane and flew it into a 200,000 ton steel tower that disintegrated into dust in
eight seconds. And if you believe that, you'll believe pretty much anything. Now the reason why
you have the ridiculous official stories that Oswald shot Kennedy, and the 9-11 story, and all
these other things is because you have fallen for, yes, you guessed it. Now I'm not anti this,
because if you didn't fall for that, you would fall for some other stupid shit. But anyway,
this is just the nature of humanity. So just to discuss the gods, and maybe perhaps not discuss
the gods, but maybe beat around the bush, so to speak, because discussing them is very, very
arduous. I mean, which one are you discussing? The only thing you can discuss about the gods
publicly is just make people aware of the general outline, which is still so piss poor.
Now there are, you do have the ability, anyone does, by the way, to look at a hair under a
microscope. You might even look at several hairs, or a tuft under a microscope. But you will,
unless you know where it originated from, or you're able to see, let's say, the animal that
it came off of, you don't know what kind of animal that hair comes off of. They all look very similar.
Some are extremely identifiable, most are not. So I would say that at this point, just discussing
the overall creature, let's just say, is an interesting aspect to it, which is still severely
lacking in any circle, whether it's the entitled classes. Now by the way, you might have heard some
Greeks speak before, if you have more than an eighth grade formal education, you have irreparable
damage to your spirit. What does that mean? Salvage what you can. And I took a pause there,
because I'm serious about that. So the irony of humanity at this point is they're actually proud
to associate themselves with credentials higher than that. It is just absurd. So most likely,
by the way, there is something called cosmic censorship, and I never really got into
the aspect of cosmic censorship too deeply. Most people haven't asked. Maybe I'll touch
on that a little bit more. If you've ever heard any Greek speak, that cosmic censorship is brought
up. And I'm going to perhaps tie that in why I say do nothing at this time period.
But maybe just to do a quick recap on the gods, because being redundant is sometimes the way to
go. When you see someone in the second grade and they can't pass the second grade, most likely
they're going to do it again. But by the way, since I brought up education before, this is just
a commentary on humanity again. What is the most degrading thing you can do to anyone, especially
a child? Could it be grading them? Think about it. So when people talk about they had a good
education, or they went to a good school, or they need better education, I would just stop and say,
hold on a second. Do they have grading in that system? They're like, yeah. I'm like, uh-huh.
Okay. So how is it going to get better? Just because a fast food restaurant serves
something that you think is better, guess what? It's still fast food junk food.
So you're not going to get that. You're not going to get real education. And like I mentioned earlier,
because you wouldn't recognize it, it would be just as alien as anything else that is alien to
you. You would just run away from it. I assure you that. Now, you will have education in the next
society, but not this one for sure. Now, again, I want to get into just a simple profile of the
gods. But one thing I want to throw in here, just as a little bit of a dig on humanity,
not on your leaders, by the way, and also tie it in with why I say you shouldn't do anything other
than good quality food, clothing, and shelter, and learning about what you're made of, soul,
spirit, and body. And someone once mentioned that sounds kind of base and superficial,
but if you pursue high quality food, which includes drink as well, food, clothing, and shelter,
and you pursue knowledge of what the spirit, the soul, and the body is, you're going to pretty
much encounter knowledge of everything else in between as well. It's kind of like one of these
alluring things that seem really simple on the surface, but end up being all-encompassing in
detail once you engross yourself in them. But just for a dig on mankind, one reason to show that you
are, well, censored, first of all, the majority of people are censored, but not you, the listener,
specifically, that you are in the credits part of humanity, and the censorship is very strong,
and no one is noticing that any discussion, any public discussion, whether it's political,
judicial, economic, religious, entertainment especially, you can go on and on, is not done
and is incapable of being done. And also, by the way, alternative media, don't leave those guys in
because they're all geniuses, of course. And alternative media, it is not possible at this
time in this society to have a conversation, especially now that is above a third-grade
reading level or eight-year-old mindset. It is not possible, viably. And that means if you're
structuring some quote-unquote programming or something directly into society to accommodate
the masses thinking you're going to grow and be successful, you better keep it really, really in
that range, just at the beginning of your, the end of your formative years. Now, if you have
family members or anyone like that, there might be some videos, YouTube, about teaching school
children up until the second or third grade, watch third-grade stuff online and then just carry it
over. Now, just do a transcript of it and the mindset, carry it over to when you watch political
television or politicians or kings or monarchs speaking or listening to the quote-unquote news
or university. Now, what's interesting, the university professors, they tend to be able to
mask over that really ridiculously immature mindset because they have a set of ways, they get
a training on how to say certain things and structure and they might use some words that
might be a little bit beyond third grade, but their mindset, I assure you, is still there.
So, and the other thing that you will comprehend when you see that you're in the credits portion
and the censorship level right now, and by the way, the censorship is because it's autopilot.
In other words, the past 18 years or so, you're on a track, there's nothing that can change,
but perceptively, you might think so, but that doesn't matter because we just mentioned you
only perceive, well, anyway, okay, you get the point. So, what you will also see is that
the events that are taking place are all reactionary. No one knows what's coming
around the corner and speaking about it, by the way. Everything is just reactionary,
which will change next decade, by the way. You will have big promises being made,
thousand-year type stuff, so you'll all fall for that rosy picture, of course.
But you will see also that the censorship is so thick and the autopilot is pretty much instilled
that there is no movement outside of that other than what you find to be in your own personal
space or personal desires, which leads you back to food, clothing, and shelter,
and discovering the soul, the body, and the soul, the spirit, and the body,
which I will go over again because there's a reason for it. If you don't know who you are,
then, well, if you are headquarters, if you're made up of those three things,
and you're deceived about it, well, the only thing that you'll resonate with is deception.
You ever hear these New Age morons talking about, oh, that resonates with me, or I like it,
or that doesn't resonate with me, I don't like it. Well, they don't know anything about themselves,
and that's why they're into the New Age stuff. Some of this stuff just sounds dogmatic to a
typical moron, but that's fine because if you just take an average common oaf off the street,
plebeian or idiot, and put them on a construction site and insist that they use a tape measure and
everything, unless they have any training or vocation, they will not see the importance in
that, and they will be promptly removed because they will be disturbing production. If you don't
think there's any disturbance in the production of the way things are going for mankind, you're not
paying attention. But nonetheless, let's just continue a little bit more. I think the promise
of going into the idea that there is a society known as the gods is a very, very old concept,
more than alluded, but explained not in great detail by the Greek through the years. Why?
Because in contrast to what you're being told in any society, and by the way, one of the worst
things is when you see this transition, man right now is deliberately cut off from the society of
the gods. You're pretty much left with red fire trucks, teddy bears, and whatever is left over
from whatever human sacrifices are being done. But what you will see is that essentially there's
no knowledge of any of this stuff, and one of the worst things is when you have these
societies that have, well, it's not the worst, but typically societies have cultures and traditions
that they carry on from generation to generation, like the eastern religions, the western religions,
and whatever, north and south also. But one of the worst combinations is when you have these
typical westerners, it also happens to easterners, they tend to transition out of their cultural
religion that is instilled geographically and traditionally on them, and they switch over to
something else. And I'm like, you know, this also happens with Asians. I've seen very often you have
a large quote-unquote Christian contingency that has been discovered by the Chinese and Koreans
and such and such, and I ran into a Korean individual once and I said, well, you know, they're
like adamant Christian, and I'm like, what happened? The demons that you worshipped in
Korea, you gave those up for the demons that are worshipped in the west? What's the difference?
And the same thing for the westerners, you know, when they go over to eastern
cultures and eastern religions, I'm like, you gave up the western demons for demons in the east? I mean,
why? You're just sideways. They're all on the same level. It's all a lie. But it's not a lie
because it's a facade. Well, it is a lie, obviously, but it's a lie that you are supposed to follow to
be like everyone else, because you don't want everybody to find out what's going on on this
planet. You're supposed to live 50, 60, 80, 100 years, die, and then carry on because you're just
a number. You're just coming here because a certain number of people have to manifest over a certain
period of time. Yeah, that sounds kind of crazy, doesn't it? Yeah, well, you'll find out later. It's
true. How do I know? Just the same way you're going to know if you don't know. You just study
it, because perhaps even in the future, if you're not interested, you may not even find out.
So here's the aspect of the society of the gods that no one understands or comprehends,
that there are many, by the way, and they have a hierarchy, yes, just like the military. And by
the way, the military has a hierarchy as well, and that hierarchy you will find from the enlisted
men all the way up to the officers to be very similar across time and across culture, because
that was not invented. That was given to mankind. And sorry, folks, if you think you invented
anything, there is no such thing, because all thoughts are external. So thinking you invented
something is like having a portable radio on the beach, and you are inspired to open it to get the
little tiny jazz band or the little tiny rock and roll band that's inside the radio playing music
for you. And it sounds ridiculous, doesn't it? But it's the same thing, folks. So anyway, I would say
that there is a society there. Now, what's interesting, again, if you're able to put things
together and rationalize, it's been said somewhere that man is of very high importance. And of course,
most people don't know what that even the word important means, but let's just say of significance
and of great value. And mankind was made to be incorporated into the direct family of the most
high of the gods. All right, and we will get into discussions of that in more specifics, because
there are three bloodlines on the earth right now, which no one is really discussing. They have been
discussed, and they actually quite a bit, but no details. And yeah, so the other aspect of that is
once someone asked me once, do the gods have a God? And they said, yes, they do. And that will
be discussed in future as well with great detail. And that is the nature of being able to not be
pedantic, but be able to offer this information, those that are interested. And you will find out
in future projects that what your interest is when you come up to it, and you'll say, well, do I
really want to do this? And you will discover that if you do discover within yourself to want to get
this information, and you move forward on it, it will be pretty, pretty rewarding. But personally,
you won't make any friends, and your friends and family will hate you even more than they do now,
by the way. Because if you're listening to this within 40 minutes or so, you probably figured out
enough to know that what's going on on this planet, and it's time for something a little bit
better. I wouldn't say a lot better, but just a little bit better really is a lot better.
But back to the society of the gods, and they don't exist like humankind does. But even though
they made humankind, I would say that at this point, there's an irony, because humankind is at
the point very soon, well, two decades or less on the outside, where more overt knowledge and
presence will be of the gods on earth, and within your perception, let's just say. But the irony of
it is that you're going to be coming into an aspect of society that will be very convincing
that your society, meaning what man believes is his society, let's say the way it's structured,
will continue unabated for the next thousand years. But within that, there will be knowledge
incorporated of the gods, and the simple reason why is because if the mankind did not have some
accurate knowledge regarding the gods, after this thing was wrapped up, meaning man's epic,
you will see that there'll be plenty of sniveling humans. We didn't know. We didn't have a chance
to straighten up. We didn't know what was going on. Why did you stop us? And the gods don't act
in futility. So you will know enough about it, but you will be obviously misguided, just like
you've been about everything else. And if you don't think you've been misguided, you got any parents?
You want to sit down and ask them some serious questions? Got any grandparents you want to sit down?
Or any older individuals? Yeah. You want to ask them basically something outside of what's on the
cereal box, or what's on TV, or why they do what they do? Yeah. Do you want to see a real dumb look
on people's face? Yeah. This is where you're at, humanity. This is at large now throughout
the entire planet. This has nothing to do with just the American culture, which tends to be some
of the most interesting when it comes to that. So you will find out more as time goes on.
So regarding the gods again, you know, one will say, well, how much do you want to get into? How
much can we get into? Much. But I would say that when you start researching anything that is put
forward as being spiritual, you'll always run into the concept of the gods, unless you start
getting into these pseudo-spiritual things. I mean, well, actually not because spirit is the mind,
they're not pseudo, but they sort of are, where they are more of the self-help or something
based on integrity. And then you have to understand how to measure it for being lawful, or measurable,
or real, or practical. So again, the gods are going to come up somehow. You also have to
comprehend that in terms of the earth, there is a central aspect to the earth. Just like the body
has the navel, there is a certain part of the earth that is very central, and things emanate
from there, from a spiritual perspective, and they're shut down. Sometimes they become a sewer
hole for a while, and sometimes they become the most, let's say, set apart sacred places on earth.
That's another thing people don't understand, location regarding the gods. The earth is the
earth. What makes a place special is not inherent to the earth, even though the earth has ley lines.
So these things do change. But you will, if you study any spiritual material, you will find
in your studies, talk about the gods. And if you have any formal or informal, or just laymen
participation in any of the world's religions, you will not be able to comprehend what the
mindset that you've been given that's in the world, anything that's what's called, let's say,
a holy writ. It doesn't matter what religion it is. And you might want to think about that for
a minute, because again, discussing the gods sounds very new to most. It may not to most
tune into this type of talk or Greek speak, but it has absolutely nothing to do with any of the
mainstream religions, which are there for pure social control. Now, one of the big fatal mistakes
most people make, especially in contemporary times, is that if you bring up, let's say,
the biblical text, they say, Oh, well, that's Christian, and I'm not into it or a Christian.
Or if you bring up Christianity in a positive light. Oh, yeah, that's all in the Bible. No,
it's not none of it. Zero, not even 1%. The same with Judaism, practicing Judaism,
which is out of Babylon. And the same with the Quran, if you bring up there's, there's a news
site that I sometimes go to, and someone's writing a supposedly a review on the Quran,
and none of it's out of the Quran. It's just with Muslim tradition. By the way, Islam is not based
on the Quran. Sorry. Now you can take it out of context and lawyer it. What do you mean by lawyer
it like what attorneys you ever read a court case, ever read a court transcript? Yeah, you see what
they do in that. But anyway, none of it is scriptural, or out of the Quran or Buddhism.
There is no Buddhist that understands what Buddhism is. They're talking about breakfast
cereal. Do you know what breakfast cereal is made of? Fruits, nuts and flakes. And you go on and on
and on across the entire planet. Humankind is in very sad shape. So why discuss the essence of the
gods on many levels, or just on any level to start would be a start. Because it's an essential
aspect. Why? Because they're primary, they come before everything else. Why? Because they're higher
in power. Why are they higher in power? Because they're primary, they came first. So there's a
very interesting aspect to how society works regarding these things. And let's see if I'm
getting a message here. I don't think I am. Am I getting a message? No. Okay. So let's just see
go back into the comments here. Let's see if there's anything. I've tried asking those older,
allegedly wiser about things of the past, i.e. money, government, slavery, civil rights. And they
look at me like I'm growing a pink unicorn. Yeah, they are. Here's the thing, folks. There's nothing
sadder than to see the older, wiser people that are supposed to be guiding society as being a
pack of fools. And even the ones in alternative media, the ones in university, your own family
down the street. And you wonder why there's very little sympathy when they throw them in nursing
homes with drugs and slap diapers on them. Think about that. Now, if you folks are not old right
now, I'm talking about like 50 plus. When you're not old, you're probably not. You just add 15
years to whatever age you are in right now. And you might kind of get an idea of where you're at,
but going to be in terms of lifespan. Think about the little ones. Stop considering them to be
disposable. You may not with your own mouth say that the children are disposable and who cares.
You say that you love them and you care about them, but your actions show otherwise. And by the way,
sending them off to institutionalized aspects of society does not mean you love them. It just
means, again, it's like you're wheeling out the garbage to the curb. It's funny how I see the
people do that. But I would suggest that you've got much that has been lost because the older
generation has been reduced to a pack of fools. Not all of them, but pretty much most of them.
And let me just, from the Greek's perspective, I haven't met any wise or older people yet
in the past couple of decades. None of them. It's been diminishing. Maybe 30 or 40 years ago,
I do remember some that were much older that did give me some of the best, wisest comments that
I've heard, but they've since died. So you're in really sad shape as a society from that.
This is measurable, by the way. It's nothing to do with opinion. I've heard many comments of
people going around and listening to, let's say, what can be discussed. And they bring it up to
their elders and they're like, no, you have to do what everybody else is doing. I don't want to hear
that. So it's not hard to prove it. And I don't want to pretty much stick on the point that the
older people are pretty much goners at this point, because when you read in ancient writs to respect
them to a certain degree, that was very specific. By the way, when you read ancient writs, let's
say it's the biblical text. I shouldn't say the Bible because that means you're going to go to
King James. Anyway, if you do discover that there's something preserved in scriptures in
Hebrew and Greek that one day will be translated or go into a good interlinear. And in future
endeavors, we're going to show where all the mistakes in the King, the 30 to 50 mistakes
that are recur repeatedly, most likely tend to start off with. So you could actually make use
of that document instead of having it as a doorstop or something these the goddess religion
people make you swear on. Heaven forbid you ever fall into their clutches. But
there's, yeah, there's things, things to consider, folks, that the wisdom is not going to be found
with the old anymore. It's another sign of the times. And these are specific things. Let's just
see here. I agree. Has the crowd been translated? Or is it a version like the King James? Yes,
it is a version like the King James. One simple way to see how moronic all of the members of every
religion on the planet are. You're ready. This is an interesting thing to try. And this is remember
it tonight, we're going to bounce around, but it's all about the gods. Again, we'll do more talk
about the body and food and some technical aspects of things, but it's always going to bounce around
the gods. If you want to see how moronic a religious person is, and I want to say religious
mean, religion means something you do regularly. So it's nothing to do with what you do regularly.
It's this institutional thing, every one of them, you know, there's like, I don't know,
1000 aspects of Islam. Some people say 2000. I once read a statistic, there are 30,000 or
20,000 aspects of Christianity, 5000 aspects of Buddhism, Hinduism, all of that, right?
It's just, it's not very good for mankind. Why? Well, you'll find out. But one way to see if
these people in any of them have a handle on any of the writs, in terms of it being translated,
or them being familiar, are you ready? It's really simple. Just ask them to do define,
ask a Christian, a Muslim, a Jew, a Hindu or Buddhist to define what the soul is and to define
what the spirit is. They can't. Okay, why? Well, because in order to be able to do that,
you have to stop what you're doing for about five minutes. That's all. And look things up and see
how it's being used. Right? Well, actually, it helps when you get a hint in the right direction.
But it seems like when you have people do it, it has more punch. When you tell them it helps.
But here's the other thing about regarding the soul and the spirit. When you go to look it up,
they've actually twisted it in the reference manuals. It's like they got a bunch of attorneys
to do it. For good reason, of course. Because, you know, when I say legal society and attorneys,
I don't mean that as a dig on a human institution. They represent the adversary, boots on the
ground. Okay? So more than just someone with a t-shirt, they are actually functional satanic
humans. Now satanic meaning adversarial. There's no escape from that, by the way.
That just happens to be one of the realities of being on earth. What you think about them
is irrelevant. I'm discussing here what they are. There's a big difference. They're adversarial,
and that's otherwise they wouldn't exist. But here's the other thing.
This is a long-winded answer regarding if the Quran has been translated. The answer is no.
Actually, in some countries, it's illegal to even do it out of what's called Arabic.
But none of these people in any of the formal religions know, and they cannot define the soul
and the spirit. So they cannot go back and render any useful information from the writ that they
subscribe to. Now, why do I say all of them don't? It's very simple math, folks.
Because once you go down that path and discover that there is accuracy to be garnered when you
read these quote-unquote holy writs, you will find that everything and anything that is done
in the religion is in the abominations category of the text that you're studying now.
So now you have a decision to make. For example, if you study the Quran,
you'll never call yourself Muslim. And this is a fact, by the way, because I've had many
discussions with quote-unquote Muslims about the Quran. They don't know anything out of the Quran.
They know a few verses here and there, and they're quite proud of that.
And the ones that have discovered it abandon the quote-unquote religion and do understand the text.
The same thing with Christianity. It is not possible to call yourself Christian unless
you have ulterior means or alternate desires for something. Let's say, and I'll get into what that
is, and know what's known as the scripture or even the Bible. There's no way. It's not possible.
With every religion, there is no religion on the planet that does anything that's in the writ that
they allegedly subscribe to at all. And if they do anything that seems to be out of there, it's in
the don't do category. Now, another thing that you can say that is very factual regarding mankind,
and we just have a few minutes, is that the people that are in mainstream religion are either evil
or ignorant. Ignorant because they don't know, or evil because they do know, but they like to do it
because they want to take advantage of the ignorant. And that's one of the realities of being
unwelcome to planet Earth. So we've pretty much gone through about an hour. We're going to be
coming up on the break, and we will get more into the gods or otherwise. But this is episode seven.
We'll see you soon. Greetings on the first week of the second month on the Pope's work schedule
known as April 13th, 2017, in the year of their Lord. As I say, I would recommend anyone consider
that when you do hear that you have been had, especially when you're coming to a venue like
what's called alternative media, and yes, I just happen to be here as well at the moment, you hear
about very often mankind has been deceived, but yet they cannot discern what is just right in
front of them and what they're using, and the quality of what they're using. That's why one of the
things that you can't just lay off of is the Pope's work schedule, folks. Sorry. And that is, by the
way, is a really quick litmus test to see who's super glazed, you know, like a raised and glazed
donut kind of thing. No, not that, but just like glazed over. Bring up lawful, anything lawful.
Timekeeping is the easiest way to do it, just to see. Now, I mentioned earlier that the members of
mainstream religions for thousands of years are either ignorant or evil. Now, I say thousands,
meaning at least a good 1,500 for sure, because prior to that, you had a little more knowledge
and interaction with the gods. They tried to, even though it's been basically cut off on many levels.
I would suggest that if you were to come to a planet like this one and leave with a report,
and the category of religion would be brought up, you would say the participants across the board
on the planet are either evil or ignorant. Why? Think about it for a moment. Should I take a
pause? I just mentioned it earlier. And the pause is there. It's a rhetorical pause, maybe to relax
the brain, because you've probably never heard this before. And it's very, very simple. It's
not something you have to memorize. Or even like one, what did he say? It's just a realization
moment, right? And it's very easy. Why are they ignorant or evil? Well, very simple.
The ignorant kind of speaks for itself, because none of them know anything about what they're
supposed to be doing or what anything is based on. But the evil ones are quite interesting,
because they do know. But see, they're what's called opportunists, or even to the point of
being predacious or predatory. Think about it. And then there's a whole other level to it. When
you hear about the molestations, right, of children from these mainstream religions,
and not so mainstream ones. It's not because it's a horny rabbi or a priest or something like that,
or an imam. It's because it's part of their religion, meaning that the religion that you
know about, but because the entities that are behind such a structure. Now, one thing that I'd
like to bring up is that the earth has been under the influence of malevolent entities for since the
beginning of known history. There are several ways to discern that. Let's just discern the more
typical modern one. Actually, they're both typically modern, but changing. The typical
modern one is, if you have a discussion, and when I say religion, I mean also anyone in the legal
society, medical society, what's called the homosexual community, the judicial society,
economic society. These are all based on religions. These people do these things regularly.
They're all unlawful, by the way, at this point. When you start bringing up the history of what
they are involved in, or anything with precision or accuracy, typically they will bring up the
notion that they're not interested. But if you pursue it, you start to see a look in their eye
and the expression, body language, and other things that they actually want to bring violence
to you. Whether it's verbal or physical, it can go in either way. That is because they are so
heavily under the influence of malevolency cloaked as benevolency, as a necessary thing.
How many times have you criticized, let's say in the Western culture or even Eastern culture,
why people do the same thing they do? Especially an older person will say,
well, that's the way we do it. That's the system we have, and they're so proud of it.
Now, right there is an indirect proof right now, but it'll be more direct proof later as one's
experience and knowledge increases on how humankind, the majority of the people,
can be dubbed as unrehabilitatable. Another way to see that humankind has been under malevolent
influence, and they don't notice it. It could be the same group and others.
Is mankind, it can be established whether you're into the creation aspect or the evolution aspect,
which, by the way, what is put out academically and colloquially and conventionally about
evolution and creation is wrong. Yes, they're both incorrect. That will be discussed in the future
with specifics how, but anyone who's listened to Greek speak to this point can figure that out
to some extent, but it'll be illustrated and demonstrated.
But even if you look at evolution or creation, you will see that there is a very deep and
heavy integration of mankind in the natural environment. Whenever you see man and his
industry and his culture or whatever start to disintegrate from the natural reality,
okay, what does that mean? Well, not disintegrate like the disintegrating rate,
but the opposite of integrate. For example, putting fluids in flat bottom containers just
for the sake of commerce and not really realizing that it degrades the liquid,
okay, not wondering about the subtle energies of food, okay, or, you know, whatever, you know,
these things that are seem to be not natural. Now, why do I say both of these things change?
Because you'll see through as the censorship is lifted to a certain extent, people that were
didn't want to hear about anything with precision and accuracy regarding the past or even spiritual
matters of the mind, let's say, will start to open up to it. Okay, and also on the physical
aspect, you will see that there is something called a biomimicry movement that has been coming
around. Biomimicry is where you don't have to reinvent the wheel because nature has done it
already for you. In other words, if you have a certain task in industry or otherwise that you
would like to accomplish efficiently, see where it's being done in nature and try to copy the
structure, the movement, and the approach. You'll be more successful. This has to do with, let's say,
aerodynamics, fluid dynamics, energies, kinesthetics, you know, the movement of bodies,
all these things copy nature. So there is a little bit of a movement on that, but still,
society at large is, you know, if you ever look at the architecture, even in art and industry,
you will see it is not natural, meaning not because people don't have the freedom to express
something different. It's just that if you're going to employ something within this environment,
it should be in accordance or in some harmony instead of being disharmonious. So those are
just two simple ways to see how the malevolent forces have influenced mankind. They're not
necessarily coming at you directly. They're coming at you sideways. That's the thing that
people don't understand either, is that when you get an influence, it tends to be lateral, right?
When I say lateral, I mean it doesn't come head-on. That's part of the deception. It's like
a sideways push instead of head-on that you can directly resist. I wanted to bring those things
up because they're little tidbits, like a potpourri of various thoughts when we discuss the gods.
Another thing I wanted to bring up, which I did bring up originally, is the number seven.
Let's just bounce around here. In case there are any other questions, I'll just be bouncing around
trying to stick within the topic of the gods because on previous Sonic episodes that you
might find on archives, that's been discussed quite a bit. Now, it's interesting how discussing
and bringing it up is one thing. There's always going to be a very small group of people that
are going to have an aha moment to see how simple this is. It's not a matter of the Greeks said this
or the Greeks, if I don't think like that. No, it has nothing to do with that. It has to do with
precision and accuracy. It also has to do with if you're listening to the Greek, it's because
there's still no one discussing anything like this at all. If they were, very simply, I wouldn't
be doing this now. However you want to take that, there's probably better things to do than trying
to figure out how to impart, let's say, 10 or 15 years' worth of almost full-time study to a society
that is just completely ignorant of anything basic and real. There's better things to do like
go live in the forest or something. Nonetheless, at this point, we're here. If you're seeing the
Greek speak, it's because still there's probably a job that needs to be done. Unfortunately,
the Greek maybe is the one that's doing it. The thing is, it has to be simple. It has to be able
to have a formative aspect to it. One thing about it is the number seven. When you bring up the
number seven, people say lucky seven. Well, think about it. Luck is a lady. Again, it ties into that
goddess religion. Are all goddess religions bad? No, I wouldn't say so. Being influenced by a
goddess is not necessarily malevolent unless she's bent on being malevolent. It tends to be the case
on earth at this time. By the way, wisdom is personified by a goddess also. She is not
malevolent, but you are under the influence of a malevolent one right now.
One of the ways, by the way, I'll just throw this in there, you've heard in the past,
what do you know about justice? A woman with scales has nothing to do with law, by the way,
but it does because your law comes from your god. Anyway, what do you know about that ancient
goddess religion? Very cruel, isn't it? The number seven, when you look at primary aspects,
it needs to be reckoned again. I've done this in prior times. Let's just do it again for the
sake of redundancy. Of course, I do get comments of private, well, you've just been repeating
yourself. I'm saying, yeah, that's pretty much what you folks are going to get from now on until
maybe another project that has a little more detail. It may not be so public, but it'll be
quite enthralling. There might be some new stuff. Occasionally, coming around here, there might be
some new stuff as well because even tonight, a couple extra things were thrown in. You got to
go slow with this stuff because remember, we still have about another year before some of
the censorship is lifted. The censorship will be lifted because it's one of the prerequisites of
having some comprehension of why things are happening the way they are. You're not so shocked
when roughly seven or eight years from now, a Middle East union that has centralized all
of mankind's power has taken form. You won't be in so much of a shock.
But anyway, going back to the number seven, what's interesting about the number seven
and considered lucky, I wouldn't use that term. Let's just say fortunate. I wouldn't use that
term either because one of the greatest misfortunes you can have right now is being in the explicit
presence of a god. You will not last too long. Anyway, this has been discussed also before.
Also, understanding that what is known as dreaming is a deception that is put upon you by the lower
gods. When the higher gods send a dream to you, they identify themselves. If you're not getting
that kind of stuff, you're being messed with. There's another reality that can be discussed
with the number seven regarding the gods. What makes it so interesting is that it's been
sort of associated with the gods and also good fortune. You could take it as you wish. I gave
you some reasons why it might be otherwise. But what you can examine about the number seven
is let's say you look at something that has seven elements. You just spread out seven items in front
of you. You'll notice that the fourth item is in the center of the seven items. You'll have three
on the left, three on the right, or however you want to look at it. That central element of number
four is really the first position when you're reckoning what those seven things are. Think
about it. What's interesting about the first position, which we could number one, and the
seventh position is that they equal each other. When you're looking at number one, it's also
number seven. When you're looking at number seven, it's actually number one. But the fourth position
is where you start your count. Isn't that interesting? Have you guys heard this before?
If the answer is no, that's okay. That's right, because you probably haven't. Now why bringing
this up matters anything? Whenever you see that multiplicity of the number seven,
yeah, you scratch your head and say, well, I guess that's good. It's the number of the gods or
whatever. Yeah, but now you've got some discernment. Let me just go through that again. If you have
seven items, whether they're literary items, hint, hint, literary points, something that comes in
sevens, hint, ancient writs, it's the fourth one that is the first one, and the first and the last
are equal. But you can count one, two, three, and then you go five, six, seven. The fourth one is
still the first one. So you can go four, five, six, seven, or you can go four, one, two, three,
or you get the picture. It's really interesting. In a particular culture, in their tradition,
they have something with seven lamps on it, even though it's unlawful what they're doing.
It's not in the writ that they're supposed to be subscribed to the way they do it. But what's
interesting in their culture and tradition, they light the fourth position first. Interesting.
So this is a secret. Now, what a better place than a minor internet radio platform with this
arrogant son-of-a-bitch known as the Greek coming out and giving out a secret that is really a
secret. What a better place to do it than this, than here, now. Why not? So why did I say the
word hidden? I'll just go over it again. Think about it. The numerics of seven. Just remember
the fourth one is the first one, and the first and the last are the same. And what does that do for
you? Well, you won't see the number seven the same way. And you see when you see seven, instead of
just walking away or hitting what they say the gas pedal, by the way, and going faster, it's
really a speed bump. You're supposed to consider what's going on there by the arrangement of the
number seven. So why not give that out? Now, what's interesting about the other numbers is
you will find a similar center always in odd numbers. Even numbers don't have a central
position like that. They have a space or a gap or no number or no position in the middle with
the even numbers. So not to discuss getting into what's called numerology or gematria,
but there is a rational lawful aspect to it that can be, you know, it's a form of measuring
something or considering when a number is an aspect of something, you can consider a little
bit more, you see, and it's functional. How does that help? Well, it'll help for those that have
interest. And for those that don't, well, you don't. So that's how one can pursue the functional
aspects of what's called knowledge. For example, you know, you've heard knowledge is power. That's
you know what? It's not. Because you can ask anyone, is knowledge power in the knower or is
knowledge power in the doer? And even if the knower is a delegator telling someone to do something,
he's still a doer by proxy. So knowledge alone is not power. Now, there is a level of knowledge
when you're not animated or strictly animated by physical form. If you are in a godlike state,
then it is power as well, because then you are an emanator, you're capable of more than that.
But we're discussing it now, in terms of sentient beings are eliminated by being in an animated
state. What a better time to segue into the spirit, the soul and the body. And we'll just do it again.
And of course, people are, whoever's listening, or the one or two people that aren't listening
live right now, probably turning around in their chair saying, Oh, no, he's going to do the spirit
and soul again. Yes. It's very simple, folks. Whenever you see the PSY prefix, that is the
mind or the spirit. Whenever you see the PNU prefix, that is the soul or the breath. The PNU
is where you get pneumatic or pneumonia, that is the breath. So when you see the interchangeability
of the mind and the breath, you know that that's been lawyered or twisted to some degree,
where you're not really, there's no intent there to be clear. Yep. And the body is the
which is very similar to the earth material. Now, this is like an interesting sort of Damocles,
not really such, but it's more like the thread that you pull from a cheap sweater.
Whenever you go into a conversation with those that claim to have wisdom or spirituality, or
whatever, whatever, whatever, even knowledge, ask them to define soul and spirit and watch what
happens. Yeah, you've guessed it, they fall apart. It's a good thread to pull on. Because
if you have a cheap sweater, you just keep pulling on that thread and what happens, it
unravels very, very quickly. Now, this is not meant to be adversarial or confrontational with
the morons on this planet. But you are going to be subject to idiocy pretty much wherever you go.
So be prepared. I would also suggest that when you do bring up discussions regarding the gods or the
spiritual realm, you always have to assess who you're discussing it with, always have to assess
the audience, you always have to assess the listener. Why? Because if you're not accommodating
them, they don't want to listen, they don't want to be present. Okay, so what does that lead to?
You're going to find yourself alone. Yes, you will. There's no group to join regarding this.
Why? Because the entire society has been under siege for a very, very long time. And just to
bring it up from one aspect, if you don't think that it's been under siege, you haven't been
paying attention. Have you looked at all of your leaders? Have you looked at all of those that are
supposed to be your teachers? Are they saying anything with any merit? And by the way, I have
someone calling. Let's see if I can bring him in. And maybe we can have them come on. This device is
misbehaving at the moment. So let's just see. I believe it's Seth. Let's see. I'm going to try
calling him again. If he has hardware in order, perhaps it will be successful. Greetings, Seth.
I think you've made it, but no sound. You're coming in very low, but that's all right. Actually,
that's not all right. I can be fixed. Oh, there you go. Okay. Greetings. How are you?
I'm well. I've been listening to the conversation. I thought that I might be able to
ask a few questions directly based upon the gods and the subject matter at hand.
Oh, yeah, please. First, I would say for my own benefit and for the benefit of anyone else that's
listening, just for being that we lack definitionaries in the society we find ourselves,
just to define what a god is. What is a god? Well, loosely, just like we don't know what a bear is,
but we know enough about bears to say that we know what bears are, but no one's really sat down
with a bear and had an eight-hour conversation that I know of. Maybe someone has, but I never
heard of it. But when we communicate the term bear, we know its qualities and characteristics
enough to discern it. The qualities of the gods is that they do not need a physical body to be
animated spiritually or to be animated or conscious. That would be the first thing that I would suggest
is the definition of a god. Okay. Then, looking at it as well from a perspective that is admittedly
difficult for myself because I grew up in the Western tradition of things, but looking at it
from the tradition of the Near East or works such as the epic poems of the Mahabharata and things
like that, they speak of gods and purport to be stories of gods and things of that nature that are
significantly different than the monotheistic bent that has been forced upon those interested in such
things in the Western society. I found, I should say, in my own studies that reading such things
helps to add another aspect to one's perspective on it because the Western society and things like
that is certainly not the only culture that has traditions that involve these entities that we
refer to as gods. I guess the question is what are they? It's a passing thing no matter how
accurate you want to be. The same thing is going on not regarding what are the gods, but almost
what is anything. What is money? What is law? It needs to be communicated simply just like if you
look at a large building made up of all these thousands of bricks, how did it get there one
brick at a time? They're all very simple and they come in pallets. If you drop them on your foot,
they hurt. One little simple concept, one little bit at a time to carry over. The simplest thing
to regard what the gods are, they do not need a physical reality as we do to be conscious,
to be awake. That is a place to start. Right there, it does not discuss the hierarchy. It
does not discuss what level of power they're endowed with. It doesn't, does it? The question
was what are the gods? Very simple. The problem with the Western side is let's go back to the
historical aspect that's been pretty clear in a certain writ that 2,000 years ago there was a
calling that there will be no more calling. In other words, everything is shut down from a
certain part of the god's realm. You have 2,000 years of being, let's say, in the metaphor that
was used, the grave. When you're in the grave, not much happens, not even tic-tac-toe or solitaire,
you know, you're dead, right? The aspect of the spiritual world regarding mankind has been very
dead for the past 2,000 years. I would say when I mean dead, I don't mean the literal sense,
but an analogous sense in regarding to what has come out of it. When you open up something that
has been dead for a long time, it typically stinks. If you look at what mankind has been
discussing regarding the gods for the past 2,000 years, it also stinks. It's a very good analogy
to say that it's from the grave. Just a little hint, when you discuss the thing about the gods,
most people will reference, let's say, biblical and other things. One of the things that you'll
notice is there's a hierarchy in information. What makes a hierarchy in information is things
to come. The less prophecy a document has about the future of mankind with accuracy,
the less bona fide it is or less ranking. The other thing that you will find is that people
always wanted to be about what they like. That's why when you read something known as the Bible or
the Scripture, you see there's very little health remedy in there. There's very little history that
you might be interested in. There's very little, let's say, technical information that you might
be interested in. When you read the biblical text, it's not about you. It's about them and
how they view you and what you need to know about them. When you consider that they have an IQ of,
let's say, 2 million, I don't like that term IQ, but it's just a reference here.
When you read the writ, let's say something like the Scripture, it's their baby talk.
Okay, so it's not all-encompassing. Just like when you first started having a conversation,
let's say, with a three- or four-year-old, you don't get that all-encompassing regarding aspects
of being on this planet, do you? You just pretty much want to discuss things that
you think are important for them to know about in that conversation. It tends to be minimal.
But the proof of Scripture is in there simply by showing you things to come with great accuracy,
and that's the proof of it. I would say that the three- and four-year-olds actually have
a slight advantage because, at least my own experience in speaking with my own progeny,
is that when they ask questions and you attempt to answer them with earnestness and to the best
of your ability, oftentimes you will say things that they've not heard before, specific words and
things like that. And at that age, it's very common and encouraged, or at least should be
encouraged, that when one hears a word that they are unfamiliar with or does not have a grasp of,
they immediately ask, well, what is that? Right, more objective.
Yeah, that aspect of learning is very lacking. It's frowned upon, it seems like,
in conversation to do that, to ask, well, what does that mean? What does this word mean?
And in doing that, you can unravel a lot of what's being said.
But what's interesting about the writ, the memorialization of this, is it's not a true
conversation directly, literally, but it actually gives you instruction on how to impart a two-way
communication as well, the irony of it, right? It's called prayer, right? And it's not what
people think. But the other aspect is that they're not speaking with you, they're speaking at you,
even though there are certain instances in there where there is seemingly a conversation going on.
Again, it's all memorialized, so it's not in real time. But the interesting thing about
understanding this is just like understanding, like, when you ask what are the gods, or we
go back to the writs that have been memorialized, is that there has to be somewhere in society,
an exhaustion of that information. And not only is it exhausted, meaning looked over,
picked over completely, a place where it can be imparted holistically. And without,
what do you call it, when you skew something, without being colored or skewed. And that does
not exist at this point on the planet. You ever think about that? It does not exist.
But here's the other thing, it doesn't even exist in any of the fields. If you go study economics,
you will leave there not knowing any more than you could have learned on your own in a third or
quarter of the time. You can learn how they put their jargon to use, I suppose. That's right.
Technical aspects on how to present yourself, just like the dictionary, is how the subject
should pronounce the word and not necessarily what it really means when it was in its inception.
So there's a technical, yeah, so the aspect of this is, not only is it, but most people call
it religious talk, and it's not. It's primary talk. If we can infer, even if we don't have
knowledge about that the gods are more powerful and they're primary and they came before us,
well, it's a primary aspect of the subject matter of existence. Just like in medicine,
if you don't deal with the primary causes, you're only dealing with the symptom.
So one can say it's not difficult to go into obsession about learning more about the gods
as much as you can, simply for the reason that there is no place you can go and get
that information anywhere on the planet right now. And there was at one point,
and that's part of the censorship. But again, it holds true for almost any subject.
But the thing is, any subject has a primary aspect to it. When you bring up money, very simple,
what is money? Portable land, very simple. It's a representation of what you have from your
environment when you move from your environment. Very simple. What is law? Law is the way that
you function within the environment without severe or malconsequence. Very simple. Very,
very simple. What's the soul? What's the spirit? Very simple. Let's just come down to basics and
explain these things. And then if there's interest and it seems to accommodate the mindset,
because you have to accommodate the mindset, then you can expand on it.
But right now, the expansion just seems to be very well directed by malevolent forces,
which always present themselves as benevolent, which again, leaps forward into the gods.
So this is the condition. We've just pretty much covered 6,000 years of human history. Well,
let's say 2,500 years of human history in less than three minutes.
Which leads to another question, which is very, very basic, I suppose. But between
maleficent and beneficent, and good and bad, or good and evil, or righteous and wicked,
that's kind of a hint in and of itself, I suppose. But what is good? What is bad?
Oh, that's interesting. I've kind of been meditating on that
all week. And here's the thing about bringing it all to recall at the moment.
But typically, from a sociological perspective, or man's perception based on his traditions and
his cultures, pretty much most of the things that man considers to be good is downright evil.
And if they were made aware of what is really good, they would call that evil.
So you notice, I didn't say what they think is evil is really good. And what they think
is good is really evil, as you'll find in the writ, let's say, right? I said that the majority
of what they consider to be good is just downright evil. But if they were presented with
what is good, they would reckon it as being evil. So that shows immobility. That is from the human
perspective. And I think that's the best way to communicate it, because it's always going to be
taken as a human perspective, because you're speaking to people, not bears. Right?
Correct. Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. So would good? And I guess another question would be, could one define good and evil,
separate from one another? And was what is evil? Simply, just very,
very basically and simply be defined as what does harm?
Sure, it can. But here's the interesting part. And this kind of messes around with a lot of the
conventional religion. But if one, again, goes into more, not so exhaustive, but looks very
closely at what's been memorialized about the gods, you will find out that both good and evil,
ultimately, in a primary sense, come from the same source.
Oh, certainly, certainly, everything comes from the same source.
It's not fair to say certainly, because most people think, for example, especially if you turn
on the television, the History Channel, you've seen God versus Satan or God versus the devil,
so you know what I mean. If you remember earlier, I said that the best specimen,
representative specimen, if you went on this planet right now, and you said,
who are your best people, you took a specimen of what they thought was the best, I can prove to you
they have not developed beyond eight years old, or they're in a third grade mentality.
So this is what's being accommodated still. And if you can tell, I've been very, very patient
through the years, if you and I have been speaking, about a time when these things will,
going, let's say, to a nine-year-old or 10-year-old mentality or 12-year-old mentality is
what I'm really waiting for. But again, just to go back to the good and evil, what's interesting
is that ultimately, let's just go back, you can only discuss these things from a human perspective,
because we are solely animated through this material realm. I said earlier that mankind is
very strictly integrated into his environment, air breathing, whatever. You don't do well
underwater, you don't do well in outer space without aid or assistance. Our position is
very well known in the environment. And the precursor to mankind was adjusting the environment
so mankind can inhabit. So the majority of the laws that you see, especially in the Holy Writs,
are how man should behave in order to keep or maintain harmony with the spiritual or mind
of the environment. It has a spirit in itself, albeit different from mankind. So in this case,
specifically, it would be the earth. So if you understand most of what is considered good,
it is proper fit and proper behavior to sustain life on earth, basically. And if you don't do
that, then you're sustaining the opposite. And sometimes that's accelerated, known as evil,
just to stop you, you see. So some remnant or something will remain. What it means very simply
is it seems like even in man's system, when someone does bad versus good or evil versus good,
they mete out punishment to that, don't they? Even in man's law. And the term of punishment is
supposed to be edifying, but at the same time it's also supposed to settle some kind of deficiency.
Right. Yeah. So there's an interesting aspect to that as well. But I assure anyone that's
listening or anyone that has been on this planet long enough that is even can rub two brain cells
together, does any research, will find out what they think has been projected as being good or
within the convention and tradition, the culture of society. With a little bit of research,
they could find out that it's actually not very good. And you can give examples in just about
everything. Yeah, absolutely. I suppose what led me to that question was a conversation I had
with my wife earlier in the week was we were discussing the moon and, you know,
the full moon versus the new moon. And there's a passage in what is it, Enoch, that speaks of
the path of the moon. I'm quoting this from memory, so it's probably not a direct quote.
For the righteous. Yeah. The path of the moon is light to the righteous and darkness to,
I believe the word or the term used is wicked. And I was, you know, prefacing the statement
itself with the, you know, looking at it as righteous is a much easier word to discern
its actual meaning than wicked, because righteous is just correct. It's just right.
It's been given a as you as you would say, you know, a religious taint to it. But that is right
is just that's simply what it is. The righteous is something that is correct and right where it is.
The getting through the the religious jargon and its obfuscation can be challenging,
but I've found it to be rewarding in my own comprehension of anything from driving around
and, you know, maintaining one's health with all of the people driving these incredibly quick
and heavy machinery, you know, every day to studying, you know, ancient ancient writings.
So, yeah, but the other thing, you know, let's just throw this in just a couple of things.
The when you say the Book of Enoch, that's typically been in the mindset of most people
attributed as authorship as well. Let me just give a little history on that. Yeah, it's a it's a
group of it's a writings that perhaps started around, let's say, 1000 BC that were finally
compiled a chronicle writings of those that were functioning within the temple. Let's say, let's
say from Solomon Temple all the way down. And it was kind of like led out into the world around the
first century BC. Right. So it was attributed, you know, to be called the Book of Enoch. But
essentially, it was chronicles of those that worked. It's almost as if you, you know, people
that work in the fire department, you know, had all these stories for 1000 years or 900 years or
800 years and compiled them and put them out. And these are basically oral, oral information that
correlates quite nicely, let's just say, in the British sense are quite well, not nice, but,
but harmonious harmoniously with a lot of other aspects of what's known as scripture.
It actually shows that there's a level of meditation, you know, thought being put into
these matters as they were put together, because it's almost when you look at, let's say, the central
part of the book, it's very didactic and technical regarding a lawful timekeeping. Right, right. And
it's also further into the what they called what second and third Enoch, they shouldn't be looked
at as chapters of the same book, because just in just in reading the poor translations that we have
available to us in English, it's the authorship of each one of those books is very, very obviously
different. And as they're referred to as pseudographic, just means falsely attributed to an author.
So as, as you said, as they're known as the books of Enoch, the, the idea of them actually being
penned by the hand of the, the, you know, the historical figure that goes by that,
that nomenclature, that's not the case. But I haven't, like I said, I just I'm the only reason
I brought it up is because of that, that, that passage in particular. And there are there are
others, I mean, there's certainly information in it. But yeah, the moon, the moon, just for everyone
listening, again, is your the fixture that that reckons or governs the month, what's known as the
function of time known as the month. And the month is basically a function of the year. And the weeks
function within the month and then the days function both through the year or the or the weeks or the
month. So it's just the moon governs the month, and the sun governs the day. And together, with
certain movements, you can determine year the year. And then if you want to go beyond the year
in large swaths of years, you're looking at constellations for that. And even though there
are subtle movements in between, but that's why, for example, you still hear very often,
is that a lunar calendar, you know, or we follow a solar calendar, you can't, it's not, it would be
when someone brings up solar calendar or lunar calendar, it's like, you know, the wind up toy
taking one of the hands off, you know, taking the long, let's say, you know, the sun is the long one
and the moon is the short take one of the hands off the mechanical clock. And can you reckon much
with that? No, it's going to be arbitrary, you're gonna have to start making stuff up and getting
people to agree with it, and you can't measure anything with it. Right. So that's pretty much
the function. But this is the state of mankind. One of the things I brought up Seth earlier was
that if one can get over their relatively short lifespan, in contrast, or comparison to the
infrastructure that's in place known as the natural world or the way the gods function and take a
more than a step back, at least in the mind and look at what's been memorialized over the years
and see how it actually works out quite well. You won't have so many people walking around
on the planet wondering why we're here asking the questions that they're asking, or, you know,
what am I, you see, you know, in other words, the level of inefficiency that mankind has experienced
because of this lack of knowledge of the basic infrastructure, that is way beyond his lifespan
has caused the majority of the grief that one is witness, you know, one can witness in modern
society, let's just say, especially now. Because what I say, especially now is because of the almost
instant access to the information and still, it's not being garnered, you know, I mean, you know,
books, I would say they're very expensive. Yeah, good books are expensive. They that is something
that I've noticed actually, in the last several years, is having access to the internet, and
information and whatnot is that at first, let's say the first 2025 years, you know, we have this
great tool to use. But actually finding books was not incredibly easy, at least in the digital
formats, came very easy. But recently, recently being within the last decade, let's say,
there has been much more of a push to the digitization of scripts of just books.
Well, the point I was going to make was that books were very, very expensive, let's say an eon ago.
And then when they became cheap, there was one of the major complaints, you know, with the printing
press was now that everything we're everyone's talking about all this crap is going to be
published. So we're going to be inundated with junk, right? Okay, so then, you know, so then,
you know, computers were very expensive, and electronic access to media was very expensive
when it was, you know, it's Advent. And then as it became more popular, anyone who was paying
attention could readily said the same thing that Oh, now that it's going to be inexpensive and
accessible to everyone, it's going to be lots of junk, which is true. But it doesn't mean you
know, you can't discern the, the easy, you know, the good stuff and enjoy the easy access to it
where it wasn't there before.
Certainly there you have to, or one not you in particular, but anyone has to deal with,
I think it's been termed the fire hose of falsehood. And that refers specifically to
bad information being intentionally disseminated, and then, you know, repeated, and how easy it is
to do that now. And it's one of the reasons that I continually just avoid most forms of what people
call that that show they call the news. And I, there's been specifically within the last,
I don't know, two to five years, the inundation of the information that just makes no pretense
at all towards accuracy, things that are just being said to be said, the idea of the headline
is the entire story has become much more prevalent. And we're currently seeing that in, in effect,
and in, in everyday conversation, the opinions that people espouse, and the it's, it's, it makes
your stomach turn. Well, it's a sign, it's still the sign of the time we have about another year
before it starts to change. What you will see coming after the next springtime is more of
an understanding that, yeah, the Middle East is very, very important. And offering, you know,
mental and material support to what is going on there is going to be more important than it is now
than just a fight over there, you know, and when and also while that attention is changing in that
direction, there's going to be a little more access of the information of the stuff that you
call, you know, it's called Greek speak coming around. I think you and I have had discussions
in the past, that it's not just the news, the news is part of this frustration, this tension,
time. And I think I've briefly mentioned what's going on in this time period, which is one third
of the host, you know, the spiritual realm is being those that are to be quarantined and corral to the
earth are being brought, being brought here at this time, and no one's really noticing.
Because you can't, they're very discreet, right? Unless you're able to discern that
through information. But But the other thing that I wanted to say about this time period and the
time period that's coming, is that it's not just about the Middle East, that's just things to
look at, because the gods function very simply, you know, where where it started is where it's
going to end. You see, when when you watch a play, the curtains open, and the play resumes,
you know, or continue or begins, commences. And when the play is over, the curtains close. So
there's a lot of, you know, opening and closing in circular fashion here of what you can you can see
with mankind. And it's ultimately, those who know are not going to be better off than those who don't
know, ultimately, in this condition, right? But then it brings up the question, would you rather
know, would you rather not know? And you know what, I've heard directly from people's mouths,
they would rather not know many things. So likewise, so yeah, so that mindset, okay,
that stubbornness, that rebelliousness, and that just, you know, spitting in the face of what is
real. When you said about good and evil, evil will be brought upon them. In other words,
what you will see is they will be rewarded for that attitude. You see, and quite handsomely,
actually. But the the aspect of the information in the news and what people are concerned about
and all that, no, that's still not really important, unless you know what's coming,
and you have to sift through it. But the general state of those even putting out information is
very, very piss poor. You see, so in other words, the people that the general people at large,
the layman, looking up to the entitled classes, even those in alternative media,
and they're not getting anything with any anything to bite into. There's occasionally
something good and edible, but it's like sifting through someone's poop to get undigested corn.
So you don't want to do that as pleasant. Yeah, about as pleasant. Yeah, typically, you will,
you will find there are things out there, there are little tidbits, but it's very,
very distasteful to do so. So obstinance is what I've been recommending. And it's kind of ironic,
because, you know, you want to promote, you know, this kind of platform, and I can't, it's just that
I happen to be here and, you know, speaking, because no one else is, and it's simply that.
But I think the time period that's coming, and to do more diligence for others, if you can do it,
that's why it's probably going to be pending a project where it will be more specific and elaborate.
And it won't be live, there'll be something people can access, quote, unquote, files,
and it'll be much more detailed, and give references and things which might sound,
you know, two hours, we have the liberty here to do that, you know, do like four or five
continue, you know, weeks on one subject, but I believe that just coming and being redundant
is important. You know, to some extent, just repeating the basics is really where it's at,
at this point. I have one more question. Before time escapes us directly to the theme of the
program, or not the program, but, you know, the sonic endeavor, and that is, are we one and all,
whether wittingly or unwittingly, servants of the gods?
No, you're not. Well, yes, you are. In other words, your law, yes and no. When I say no,
I meant more specifically the, a certain part of the hierarchy, but everyone is serving some
form of god, because your law comes from there, right? Even a staunch atheist says, you know,
it's very easy, it's like, well, I don't believe in any gods, Greek, I got you there. Well, no,
will you follow the laws of the state, or do you acknowledge the laws of the state?
And they'll typically say yes. Well, then, you know, the state is your god, and April 1st is
your holiday, and the state even provides you a god in statuary and iconography, don't they?
And in name, they provide you a god. Okay, let me rephrase the question then.
Is all of creation a servant of the Most High, whether they are aware or unaware?
No, oh yeah, yes they are, but they're not aware of it, right? In other words, even the most
malevolent entities are still taking marching orders from the Most High, because that is their
god. That is exactly what I was looking for. Yeah, and that is, I'll just give a little tidbit,
which I'll discuss more. The gods do have a god, and it happens to be the Most High,
because he is not subject to death. That's what makes the Most High the god of the gods,
where the other gods are still subject to death. Right. So, they're almost mortal,
well, they are mortal in their own realm, which is the immaterial realm.
Uh-huh, and more information and examples, and it's sort of, and it could be pedantic,
you know, if someone wants more detail, it could be given, and descriptions can be given,
and the whole thing is it always has to tie into something that's tangible, because you're still
dealing with, you know, you're dealing with an aspect of existence that we are in right now,
that it has to be somehow materialized, it has to be tangible. Even if you can imagine it,
a material metaphor has to be given, you know, this is just the thing to consider,
to accommodate the human mindset right now. Otherwise, you end up going off, and you try to,
you know, people make things up, and it's easier to give a material analogy. You know, that's why
you hear things like quantum physics, and it's ridiculous, and initially the concept sounds good,
you know, yeah, of course, you know, strange things can happen, and it's wonderful that the
mainstream acknowledges it, but when you look at the premise of it, it's absurd. So there's the
essence of counter space, how that exists, because like, let's say, electricity can only be
reckoned with in counter space, let's say, it's a notion that someone brought up in the early
20th century, his name escapes me right now, the German fellow, the naturalist,
but most of the stuff is very flaky. But nonetheless, that'll be brought up.
And here's the thing, folks, if you really want to comprehend one essence of the gods,
try to wrap your mind around electricity. That is directly an essence of the gods, basically,
when you're dealing with electricity, it's the closest, most direct, intangible, or intangible,
if you go to science, godlike type energy you can deal with at this point, that most people
are interacting with or considering. So we'll get into that as well. And essentially, maybe,
how about this, Seth, because we're running out of time, is that what separates the man from the
gods is very simple. Well, man needs material to be animated, right? And the gods don't. And also,
the gods have technology that man doesn't. What separates the animating spirit
from the gods? What separates the animation of man, aside from the corporal?
You have to rephrase that, I'm not getting the question.
You say that what separates man is the need for material for the animation.
To be conscious.
What comes when the spirit is removed?
Oh, unconsciousness.
Okay, so the spirit without the body is unconscious.
That's right. And typically, it works the other way around. In other words, the body is subject,
and the soul, and the body becomes subject to death, which then it goes into chemical,
the soul dies, it ceases to exist, which the soul can also be attributed to the metabolism, right?
Because when you're breathing, it's obviously more than just breathing, you know, diaphragm,
fluids, all these other things, right? So the soul is terminated, and the body then goes into
chemical decomposition. And fortunately, when those things happen, you go into a light out
condition, typically, which is just like being asleep, without dreaming. And that's basically
what death is. Is there any concept of time? Do you think? No, I suppose I'm asking for
no concept of time. No, just like when you're sleeping, there's no concept of time. Yeah.
So to one who may be reincarnated in the future, it could appear to be nothing more than
the blink of an eye. Correct. And when most people will find that out.
Okay, well, thank you. Thanks for calling in Seth. This is Uncommon Radio.
And we will see you folks for solo eight, hopefully. Thank you very much.