So we're on good just another beta test see how the solar flares are affecting things right Uh-huh, okay good So this will probably be archived or edited or somehow Adjusted if necessary this is still a beta test right in the future.
It'll be This is not the uncommon.
This is the what is it?
What's the other one question everything yes?
hmm I'll put a link in the chat.
Maybe if anyone wants to come in participate.
I'm only gonna be on for a short while
We'll do that about an hour or so
Okay
so just I was just thinking just throw another beta test and
See you how it works out
you know if you ever hear Greek speak, it's the same stuff over again because
Someone look I won't be the one to do it, and I don't know if anyone else will if I don't
Not because I'm best suited for it, but I maybe I am and that is to unofficially declare all of
Humanity or most if not all possible
Ones that you would meet surface-dwelling earth inhabitants as morons
No one has really done that yet
And I think that's not that needs to get out of the way
So I would say yes if you are visiting this planet or found yourself aware in any way you are completely
Surrounded with morons meaning everyone you've ever met everyone that you know and everyone you're going to meet is a moron and
Once you establish that it kind of puts together the
Protocol right like for example you've heard of people in the armed forces or in the what they call law enforcement
Which is an oxymoron as civilian and non-civilian you know this is how we talk to civilians versus people in the force
You know they discern between the civilians well once you start to get discernment
You will find that there's really no one you can discuss this with or speak on it now.
There are several levels about it There is the initial level of its rejected laughter on or violently opposed And there's the other level which I've noticed which I haven't discussed much Is when you run into a typical surface-dwelling earth inhabitant you bring up?
Let's say an anomaly of the Pope's work schedule you ever notice like Celebrating a birthday or Anniversary every year it's a different day of the week.
Oh you dropped or something dropped Are we still recording?
Let's see if I wonder if we're still recording Okay, so I'm gonna have to hang up on Okay, okay.
I think we got her sorry about that all right, so let me know when we're ready.
We're good Okay, let me know when you got the mic going yep, everything's set.
I'll just edit that out oh That's fine because you could push the little button that connects right or the mic that is Locked where you have lock on the tab right?
We're ready to go you mean It's selected and it should be yeah, we're on Okay, that's fine.
That's why it's a beta test.
Yeah, it is That's fine, okay good, so they see this is why I felt like doing this because before Starting a schedule of any kind or whether I should be doing it solo Or you know we'll do it together you over there me over here, and see how well we could come together But that's fine.
I think the majority of them will be solo, and they'll be uploaded to a pod bean Mm-hmm server which is very fast Just to keep it smooth and going and then when we do one We might want to just do it on this particular link so people know it's you and I how's that for no concept works fine Yeah, okay, so most likely the uncommon radio.
I'll probably
Do a scheduled there's something about doing it live where you can access questions in real time
But the interesting thing is I've noticed as time goes on no matter what quote unquote current events are going on
The same things apply right you're on the planet with a planet full of idiots or morons
Oh, you know however you want to look at it, and you're you're your concerns
You know are shouldn't change much in other words
What I'm trying to say is when you go to the stupid rectangle whether it's the television or the internet people are curious
They're curious creatures right
I'll be at their clueless.
They are curious
They do want to know what's going on quote unquote current events or the news right right and what happens is that there's a big
slurry of
scripted mainstream, and then you have the non scripted parrots of the
alternative media
They you know they're not as scripted
But they do actually you know Polly want a cracker type stuff right and it just goes on and on and on and it's been
Going on that way for a very long time
And not so much with the alternative
Because years ago if you grew up in the 60s or 70s or even 50s you remember it was done more on pulp and
and mean on paper
Alternative stuff and also what's called pirate radio
More just cafe speak right, but it was still parroting the the typical idiotic human perspective
You know here is the interesting part
You know how do people get licensed or feel they have the right to go and call themselves
Researchers on topics when they don't even know what day it is
Or they can't even discern the difference directions of natural temperature versus artificial temperature
Or what or they don't even know where law comes from or they think that when they eat something the body absorbs it you see
so how
Can a society of beings the surface-dwelling earth and heavens be so lacking in discernment
In earnest by simply examining them not because I say so because anyone can see it if once you're aware of it
And how can some of these people that are in complete state of more on see or more on see or what's it verb for moron?
the claim that they are researchers or scientists or doctors which means teacher by the way and
procure knowledge to our society when they themselves are morons I
Guess that's an oxymoron
So you see what the reason why I'm saying this because
There I think hammering the entire
Concept of food clothing and shelter, and what's basic to oneself is still
severely lacking
Just like I've said before you know good drink and good food promotes good character
You know poor food and poor drink promotes poor character
It's important to be able to record things for memory and for memorialization
Starting with proper.
You know things that are lawful like time and how the body works How are you were working in this natural environment all of that is still severely lacking?
You know there's no place to get it.
You know give you an example You know after the last sonic event on American Freedom Radar.
I decided to continue, and I was like why?
I've said enough that I've given out a thousand times more than I've ever gotten directly There's got to be at least two or three or five or ten people I could carry this work Or at least the seed and make it grow and of course not much, and I'm not being facetious, but in a sense It's like well It's not it's your time's not over yet, so you have to keep speaking on the matters, right right?
And the thing is there's no reason to expand as I predicted it was possible
But I think it's best to rehash and recomb and go over all of these concepts once again
And maybe fill in a little bit more with a little more density
Right food clothing shelter, and then you know who you are
And move on from there and this way those who do want to access something that they can access meaning
Accessing the the Greek speak stuff is not to be at the all-end all of it.
It's just a hint on how to access What you can access?
Right, it's like it's like break glass in case of fire kind of thing.
It's not the Really not saying anything that anyone can really work with what it is It's a mindset in a direction that then one can take and say hey now that I realize that this is so simple And it would behoove anyone to take notice of things that are just Easily accessible and easily realized and then do something with it Right and fortunately some of the personal feedback.
I've gotten back most people are What is it proactive?
You know with with trying out?
You know?
Just more than just a thought experiment.
You know trying to corporate incorporated in their lives or however whether it's the the food suggestions or You know perceptions or anything else and along that matter so what's interesting is that there's still a too much of a Lack of value on what people others are putting out there and On one part.
It's very sad.
It's very saddening and but the other part from From an opportunistic part.
It's like well if no one else is saying this and this stuff works, and it's real
You know you've got a monopoly on it right you know which is kind of ridiculous in that sense
No no what I mean about having a monopoly on it is
Not necessarily like I will be the only one or only one speaking in this way and giving this type of information
it's just that it happens to appear to be so at the moment and
It's kind of funny and surreal
For example when I think of speaking on something like this like a sonic event
I'm you know sometimes contemplating like you know what should I say?
What should it be about right?
And I'm like oh come on.
You know this is like a freaking acid trip
I don't believe I'm going to be saying the same stuff over again the most basic parts of existence that seemingly everyone misses and
It's just like an acid trip right I mean how many give so many examples again with time with the human body
I mean you know everyone hears about you know, but you absorb vitamins
You know keep your whatever body right so it could absorb and calories and blood pressure
You know how many people are subject to that information and how many people work in that field and how many people actually look and examine
Those terms to see if they even have a bearing on reality
right
Very few how many people you know are out there in the field saying wait a second
I can't determine blood pressure in the body unless they strap on the sphogiometer and start looking at this particular reflex within the beats
There's no blood pressure
You know or how come the anatomy students look at diagrams of the intestines
And you see three hydrophobic impervious layers, and they're still talking about how to anything go through that
How can you absorb anything through those layers?
Mm-hmm right and how come no one's like raising their hand not in class, but outside the building at least It's like this is like a cosmic You know I keep saying cosmic censorship now.
It's a cosmic joke Right right, and then then it then it goes from a cosmic joke to be becoming An acid trip kind of reality.
You know right.
It's quite interesting And then there's the you know the levels of censorship You know you can discuss this, but let's say the man on the street and one out of a hundred might want to listen But the moment you walk away Someone asked them what were you just discussing something very interesting like what well?
I don't really remember something about something like absorbing.
I don't know Real interesting right I've experienced that many times not myself or with other people.
Yeah, well actually myself yeah like for example taking captive the attention of those out in the marketplace and Start speaking on a certain subject and someone I remember an old couple once said you should write a book And I'm like why?
You know because if I write a book.
I'm presuming that people know how to read and she goes Well, I know how to read and I'll buy it Okay, well, I like that that's simple aspect of it.
That's the correct answer But you know she was also presuming that she was for sale Right so you see one presumption leads to another so but the point here going and it's stop being so presumptive And look at what's in front of you What are the things like to bring up also?
This is around the sixth day of the eighth month.
It's what they call pagan time October 9th Late afternoon American Southwest American continent about quarter to six on the wind-up toy and What's interesting is?
Again if anyone's been following
Anything lawful you'll see that it tends to be worth memorializing and
And the physical reality is an agreement with it right
So meaning you know if you learn to keep time and measure events
Using lawful time they in things that are on a cycle
You'll see they'll come around on that day and not on the Pope's work schedule
Calendar day right right now an interesting thing with that is also how the body works
Once you understand that it is basically electrical in nature
But not as electrical as you plug things into the wall
But things pass through the body and the body uses gets what it can out of it as it passes through whether it's air
Liquid or solid food right then you will have a
more subtle
Perception of what the body is actually doing right so when you you know most
Common, you know white American whatever when they have heartburn they say oh, that's got to be acid
Let me go get an acid reflux tablet right or something right not necessarily true
You see so it's it's a something you are feeling based on something passing through the body is very different
And once you tune into these subtleties again, it will be
Within that point and the reason I said common
You know let's say white American because in other parts of the world when they have a certain feeling what you might call heartburn
They don't attribute it to that right right you see
It would be something another matter, but so if you have let's say a particular feeling or characteristic feeling meaning your senses, right?
If five people have a different point of view on each one which one is correct
You all can't be right if you're all different right so basically
The essence of speaking is that there is a lot of grunt work that it's that's been done through the millennium
Meaning grunt work done by academia scientists and all these other people that have amassed
Bodies of works telling us what day it is how our body works
Let's say how nature works what physics as well
If you see it all these grunts have amassed a tremendous laborious body of work that you can access
But I am what I'm telling you is that it's all suspect and the majority of it is not true at all
so
the thing is
Should you relax into let's say it's a farce a farce is another word for a prank, right?
Or should you relax into the sense if you have the sensibility and the sensitivity
To see what is really going on based in contrast with the grunt work that they've presented you
Just like for example the grunt work would be all of the anatomy that's done for the human body
You just look at that and you tell me how something goes through those three different layers in the intestines really five
How does something get absorbed through that and you can clearly see
Actually hold that up next to a profile of a steel belted radial and just turn the tire inside out where the treads on the inside
All right.
Can you show me how anything gets through that tire?
No, unless you puncture it, right?
Right.
So so in a sense is what they've done is the grunt work of showing you what a pretty accurate Representation of the intestine for example, but what they're telling you it does is clearly contrary to what you see.
So now You take the grunt work.
In other words use the grunt work that they've done Right, and now that you can see anyone can see a four-year-old can see there's no absorption taking place there So what is going on?
We don't fully understand, but we know it's not absorbing anything, right?
so maybe through the process of elimination we start to get a a base or a body of knowledge that is functional Right, right.
So that is the whole purpose of discussing these things
and and these things meaning things that are just blatantly obvious and
For example, if you go to a shoe store you discuss shoe types shoe size shoe materials
Right in that venue and if you go to an ice cream shop, you discuss flavors and things like that
So there are venues of the mind, you know regarding oneself, which is you know, their mind their metabolism
They're you know
the soul and the body and then there's another venue of how those
The compilation of a human body reacts with another human body which are social things
right, right, and then there's another level of
Thing information that is social that anyone can access but is also personal
You see and not to be philosophical here, but when you pick up let's say reference material
Let's say it's even electronic or a lot a book on the library.
All right, it's typically attributed to an author or several authors But thousands of people if not millions of people can access that you see So it's still coming out from one body one person You know influences anyone on a social level or the information can be kept within one's personal Like this is personal information.
You've heard that also very few people in society are aware of it, right?
So there that is another venue of information
But ultimately whether the information is to reference things that are social in a vast
Way, you know, let's say you were look up
Melville's I think Melville wrote Moby Dick
And you know, he wrote that let's say or had some help and that was a very personal thing
But then it got spread out and became a classic because millions of people became aware of it
The information albeit being personal you will find that because it applies to the person next to you and they don't know that it does
that's where the interesting point of
Not being a moron comes in
right
Because because at this point many people also wanted to be able to share and and and refer to others
About how things really are and yes, there is a real reality and a real truth to the matter
but they find that there's let's say friction or repulsion to it or whatever and
That is the night even a TV or being naive
about the condition of humanity
But once again, it's like we started earlier if you declare
Unofficially that every all the surface dwelling earth inhabitants are morons or idiots
Now you have to say yourself.
Well, do I want to share this information with a moron or an idiot?
Well, most likely because you are probably compassionate and sympathetic you do
But you also have to examine that state of mind of moron see or idiocy
It has a variety to it some are very willing and able to listen and
Actually even observe and you know partake in even more work into the field or a subject that you bring up
You know and others are very, you know
apathetic or some are
repulsed or or rejected even violently, so
but one thing you have to keep in the back of the mind is that you're dealing with morons and
They come in different flavors and they react different ways
Right.
So that is the interesting point Yeah, so because people become very relaxed and they say well, here's another soul right another Standing woman or man and they might benefit from this.
Well, yeah, you have to also tag on there or moron Right, and you have to be careful and they're gonna react different ways to these things and what's interesting About making such a commentary in which you might sound harsh is that there's something like I mentioned earlier called sensibility and sensitivity and Sensibility would be you know being sensible right?
Well, you know, is it does it make sense, right?
So you would see
Let's say someone you want to communicate to they've been on this planet
What 10 years 30 years 50 years 100 years and they haven't seen this stuff because it's obvious
So it's sensible to approach them
Very in a very tactful way because in one side
It's new information, but it's new information that's in front of them that they should have seen on their own
Anyway, so they might be they may feel a little slighted because it's so obvious, right?
You're not saying that you found this at the bottom of the ocean you're saying that this is actually happening five feet from of them and in Unintuitively or intuitively they're thinking sometimes this guy's telling me something that anybody could see but even though I don't see it What does he think?
I'm an idiot Yes, I do think you're an idiot.
That's right because it's very easy to unofficially establish That humanity is in that condition all of them not some of them all of them.
That is the rule So you see and then there's the sensitivity sensibility and the sensitivity of it You then have to be sensitive when you're communicating with another on how sensitive they are regarding that right, right?
So very often it while you're speaking you have to be listening to what they're saying Even though they're not speaking you know, they have an inner dialogue if you can read that It's very interesting.
Otherwise, you're really wasting time and the reason why I'm saying you're wasting time It doesn't mean to try not try because you're just turning soil and not planting anything, right?
Is that a waste of time not really?
Because if you're turning soil some earthworms will come up and the birds will have something to eat, right?
Correct, but you're not going to plant and grow anything that way
Also be aware that majority of the people that you do discuss in no matter how agreeable they are the moment you walk away or
the conversation ceases it has a half-life of about a minute and
in two minutes it
3-quarters after you you know disclose whatever
Dialogue you had regarding with these subjects that are spoken on Greek speak
It has a half-life of about a minute and after about two minutes about three quarters
The information is lost within three minutes seven eights within five minutes
You know 27 29 29th is lost right now within five minutes.
They've forgotten Pretty much everything you've said so you have to remember that as well So this is just an interesting perspective.
I've never really given
I've hinted in the past that
It's not only
It's not only a criticism on
Humanity it is actually an assessment
Right because to be critical is so no one is really going around and assessing this stuff going back to what we were saying earlier
There's so many events people are curious, and they want to find out what's going on in the world
But they are in such a poor state
Cognitively of what is really going on anyway
That's loading this crap.
They call the news or current events on top of them It just makes the layers even thicker and thicker and thicker and the point here is that when you reserve?
Revert back to what is really important.
You'll see the current events as being like just almost unimportant
Unless it actually affects your way of food clothing and shelter
You see so it's a very very interesting perspective in other words it ties back into being having a
Life without worry or as much worry and concern and
being more efficient
right and again just the funniest thing is to remember that this is a
These comments are broad-spectrum
There what I speak on are the rules not the exceptions because hopefully you're the exception whoever's listening
Right correct
So with that said we're going to keep it a real short recording and see how that works out sure
Okay, all right well
Thanks everyone, and let's just make this a real short one
And we'll see how things will proceed there will be some changes to the uncommon radio site in the future to reflect scheduling other things
Thanks, everyone.
Okay.
You have a good night Okay, bye