Good evening there, folks.
We're live with the Greek.
And how are you doing tonight, sir?
Greetings.
Another stream.
Doing okay.
Doing.
Still on this planet.
Let's see if we get any stream monkeys to call in this time.
I kind of dubbed that.
You know, might as well have fun with it.
Yeah.
So I just put on the chat again.
And do we have a link on the chat for the stream?
I will get that up.
I'll get that up right away here.
Okay.
And see.
So let's see if someone might want to come in.
Basically, I was thinking just calling it just speak instead of just Greek speak, right?
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
This is, these sonic events are, I would say essential, but let's just say essentially about what it's like to be on planet Earth if you're a bipedal anthropomorphic looking kind of creature and what you're going to expect when you encounter them, right?
Yeah, there's a handful of things that could come up on that one.
Yep.
And you're going to hear stuff that you've never heard before, but it makes sense because it is full of sense.
That's why it's called common sense also.
And it's not because I'm saying it.
It's because it's really sad and piss poor and pathetic that no one else is.
So how else can we, you know, make a claim or say anything unless it's self-evident and back it up.
Because whenever you make a claim, they'll say back it up, you know.
So, you know, I put a video, by the way, recently with Denzel Washington saying if you don't read the newspaper or media, I guess, you're uninformed.
But if you do, you're misinformed.
So you have all this crap going on everywhere.
And we have someone calling, it looks like.
We'll see how she wants to announce herself.
She's calling, so I'm going to hang up on her and bring her in.
So, yeah, there's nothing out there, by the way.
And I've looked.
It's pretty sad.
Yeah, it's about as sad as it gets.
It's sadder today than it was yesterday, but not as sad as it will be tomorrow.
And I'll get into that, how.
You and I have got a few years on us, and we've watched news throughout our whole lifetime in some way or fashion.
There's a steady progression going downhill.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
But it's done in a proper way.
Okay, so we'll see.
Oh, here we have our first.
Who's that?
Oh, and she hung up.
Oh, no.
I lost you.
Okay.
Well, maybe we'll let you reclaim her.
Back there she goes.
Oh, and she's off.
On and off.
We could hear the tinkle.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Well, yeah.
Okay, so.
Otherwise, we do have a dial-up preference if, of course, cell phone charges could apply on your end.
We also have the other Skype connection if we need, depending on.
What is that?
Oh.
I've just put her on a mode that Skype aids me.
I'm going to put in a message for her to restart.
There you go.
Yeah.
Let's see.
I can probably get rid of that one.
I hate messing with this stuff.
Delete conversation.
Let's try that.
Yeah.
It's all deplorable, but you have to use it.
I recently had a conversation with someone.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Well, I'm watching your conversation be twixed earlier, you and her.
That's what was going on.
That's okay.
Recently someone in conversation wrote, well, where are you on the Internet?
You know, basically, you know, because of that whole thing, all the.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not going to start printing a magazine, you know.
Right, right.
It's just bad.
You know what?
I think essentially, because most people are so censored, by the way, that I know that about 100,000 people have heard Greek speak, and only about four or five really can react favorably or not even favorably, just rationally to it.
Right?
Sure.
I don't think anyone's reacted to or listened to Jack Presco's.
The people are irrational, and there's a reason why, and there's many reasons why.
Right.
And there are very sound, firm reasons why.
So, the thing is, if anyone's going to get anything out of it, it's a little bit of irritation and maybe some entertainment, so I try to bring in some humor.
And, you know, that's why I always say I want to make one more serious comment every time.
Correct.
But essentially, bring your popcorn, bring your aspirin.
And we're basically speaking about what's going on on Earth.
Most people are so caught up into their own subjective, opinionated perspective of how things should be, and they don't have the information to do it properly.
Well, I've got to share the fact that prior to my ever hearing of you...
Or this talk.
Or this kind of talk.
The programming that was given was, to me, you just never took it for...
you just took it for granted.
It was there, it was like a tree or a car or whatever.
Never questioned when I woke up.
Never had a reason.
Yeah, the humans...
well, people have been targeted by higher powers to not see any of this.
And at the same time, it's so thin of a veil.
In some cases, it could be very heavy of a veil.
For example, how the natural world really, really works.
In other words, where you can walk through walls and, you know, snap your fingers and make something appear or disappear.
Right.
You know, the difference between humans and the gods is technology.
When I say technology, I don't mean like, you know, microprocessors and things like that.
Right.
This is from far, far advanced still.
Yeah, what they're doing, the gods, in terms of technological achievement and attainment and ability, is when you're studying, let's say, martial arts, that's a technology.
When I say technology, meaning it could be technically accessed.
For example, if anyone went to God's school, God's school, you know, where...
There are many things in media where they show you, you know, training, you know, like Karate Kid or Harry Potter or whatever.
If they had a school here on Earth to train you about how they do and what they do and how they do it, actually, and why they do it, you'd be able to do it as well.
Right.
And that's where the censorship is very, very thick.
And rightly so.
You don't see that.
Yeah.
Rightly so.
All right, let's see.
It should be, yeah.
I mean, just look at people.
Yeah.
Let's see if this will work.
She should just come on in on her own.
Taking a pause here.
There we go.
Oh, and it dropped her again.
Wow.
Comes on and drops off.
I wonder if she's got some kind of Wi-Fi or something.
What I'm going to do is send you a contact request and accept it.
And then we'll see if that helps.
Because I'm running a really old version of Skype.
If you accept her contact request, maybe it'll tie the digital profanity into something that makes sense.
Sure, sure.
Let's see if I can find her here.
If you go to the Uncommon Radio, I just dropped in a contact request that she shows every so often.
Okay.
I hate this new version.
Yeah, I think part of the requirement is that, let's see.
Someone else wants to come on also.
Yeah, anybody's welcome.
Yeah, let's bring in.
I'm going to try to go to the other one.
I'm going to add her to a group call.
There we go.
That might help.
Okay.
I'm going to add Jason to a group call.
She's dropping.
Yeah, yeah, she is.
So we'll see.
And it looks like we have Jason.
There we go.
Jason, yeah.
Hey.
Good evening, Jason.
Hi, Bruce.
Yeah, Bruce.
And we have someone else that's trying to come on.
Yeah.
So, Jason's not all that bad.
He has a black cat as a moniker.
Ah, okay.
Yeah, it's just for whoever can't see.
So, greetings, Jason.
Greetings, Greg.
Oh.
By the way, are you on speaker?
Let me know if that's a problem with the echo or anything.
Nope, everything sounds clear.
It's gating properly.
Okay.
Yeah.
And Nicole is trying to come in and she can't.
I'm sending her a message and see if we can get her in this way over here.
Yeah, tell her it's probably a device.
Yeah.
Could be the device.
Sorry about that, Jason.
We're just trying to walk and chew gum here.
Okay.
Sorry.
Just send a message.
We'll see how it works out.
It's a deplorable program, but we like it anyway.
Yeah.
I think through the years, many have tried to mimic its capabilities with little or little popular success, so here we are.
Okay.
So, Jason, greetings.
By the way, for everyone, Jason also does, I shouldn't say also, but he does stuff on the Internet, right?
Am I correct?
You have a website and all that?
Yeah.
If you want to just plug all that in.
If anyone likes what you're saying enough to go and visit and support what you're doing, you should.
So tell us what you do.
You're not ashamed of it like I am.
Well, I'm not ashamed of it, but I'm not.
I mean, I feel like I'm sort of out on the frontier now talking to you, so it's not necessarily that I'm doing it.
I'm definitely not doing it to get more listeners or anything like that.
Yeah, what's it called?
How do we find it?
It's called Auticulture.
Auticulture.com All right, great.
Yeah, so for a while we were doing what they call, on the Pope's work schedule, a Tuesday night stream, and we're doing it again.
And one of the reasons, you know, today I came out and just basically said just to discuss the existence of humanity on this planet we call Earth.
So if you notice, I didn't say anything good or bad or society or culture or the times, just the state of affairs on this planet.
And I think trying to objectify it, you know, like I say, try is the best way to see things clearly.
Oh, and here, I keep hearing Nicole trying to tinkle and come in and out, so it's all over the program.
I'm sending her messages also, and we'll see if we can pull her in on this one over here.
Okay, so maybe we'll leave the tech talk in the background.
Jason, since you're here, go ahead and plug away, Jason.
Talk to us, say something.
Well, I came with some questions, so that's probably what I would start plugging.
If you put me on the stove, I'd just start asking you questions.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, sure, you know, there's also the possibility of asking questions that there is no answer.
So, those are the best kind, you know, but anyway, yes, please go ahead.
Well, I was planning to start with the tall, as far as that goes.
Right.
Yeah, the tall poppies, yeah.
So, as you know, I haven't been listening to your stuff for very long,
so some of my questions might seem obvious, I don't know, because I don't know how much you've covered,
but one of the things I've heard you say quite a few times,
and obviously you talk a lot about the gods, you talk about the most high god,
you talk about hierarchy of gods, but I've also heard you say that there's no one god,
you know, there's a multiplicity of gods versus one god, like you seem to posit a dichotomy there,
or an either-or thing.
Not verses, not verses, but go ahead.
There's no verses anywhere.
Everyone, let me just interject this, all the gods are, as far as we know, have a god also, and that's the one that's ruling everything.
That's the thing, when I used to discuss, by the way, the gods, people say, do the gods have a god?
And I said, I don't think you can handle that.
And for many years, now I just say it, well, the god that we read about in the attempted biblical versions is the god of the gods.
So let's say we were to go to the heavenly realm where the gods are, or the non-physical realm where the gods are predominantly, and we walked into a bar, you know, and there are all these gods hanging around in a bar, and we said, do you guys have a god?
And they said, yes we do, and this is who he is.
And when they identify him, it will be the one that is supposedly in the biblical text, which is not identified.
Right?
Because in the biblical text you just say, god this, lord that, and I'm like, which one?
So, anyway.
It's not identified by name.
Right, and that means it's not identified.
So what about Yahweh then?
Yeah, that's the identification, correct.
It's very simple.
So how is it not identified?
It's not in any of your versions.
Right.
Right?
You won't find it anywhere.
There are attempts, for example, I was speaking to someone who's Hebrew is their native tongue, and they use the term Yehovah.
And I'm like, ooh, that's not good, because that means actually to bring mischief, doesn't it?
And he's like, yeah, actually it does.
And no one really uses it.
These things are very simple.
So imagine, I'd say the question can be, let's lean the question against something that would be a concept of, imagine that people were not able to do math clearly.
Sometimes two and two is four, sometimes people just said there's no answer, sometimes people, you know, two and two is five, you know.
And the reason I use math as an example is because it's a very simple, rational communication.
So it is possible to rationally communicate the gods based on what information we have.
There is much license and much right given to the way that you research anything.
You know, if you can't see over a tall wall, you can build a device to go over it, or you can make a human pyramid, have someone climb and describe, make a jet pack, get in an airplane, many ways to see over things.
But once you start making things up that were not based on getting to the real information, that you're not allowed, you have no license and you have no right to do that.
Meaning, regarding this subject, many people say, well, I think it's this.
Big buzzer, the gong, you have no right to do that, and there's no license to do that, you're an idiot.
You have no right to do that regarding something that can be firmly established as factual.
You see, a lot of times you hear, well, I think this means that.
You see, no.
With no research, now, you could still produce that within a cultural element where people, let's say, are studying an ancient writ, and there hasn't been a firm answer.
Then we go into the scientific mode, where you can do the hypothesis in theory, and bring up, well, I think it might be this, I think it might be that.
And then you're correct, because you're still leaning on the reference material that anyone can see.
And too often I hear, even today, and it's been going on since ancient Greece, well, I think it means this, and I think it means that, and they have no support of what's been established about it already.
Let's go back to the question, the gods versus many gods.
I'm not clear on how your interpretation of the scripture is so radically different from my own, for one thing.
I'm not a Christian, but...
Oh yeah, thankfully.
I've become less hostile to the Christian mindset, let's say, in recent years.
And some Christians, I've spoken to, do seem to have a pretty good grasp of...
well, I shouldn't put it that way, not necessarily a good grasp, but their interpretation of the deity seems sane, let's put it that way.
Yes, in appearance, yes.
In appearance only, yeah.
Well no, I don't mean in an appearance-only way.
It gets complicated when we talk about individuals, because how they live their lives and how they act is much more important than what they say anyway.
But what I'm trying to get to is that, yes, there's legions of Christians who, when they open their mouth, they have contradicted themselves before they even finished the first sentence.
I've been well aware of that kind of Christianity my whole life and been very hostile towards it.
But in more recent years I've talked to what I call more discerning Christians, who seem to have thought about it a lot more deeply, but they still have a more or less, certainly a recognizable interpretation of Scripture in terms of the One God and the Incarnation and the Trinity and so on and so forth.
And you've often expressed, let's say, disparagement for that worldview and suggested that it has nothing to do with Scripture.
Correct.
And yet I don't see very clear distinctions between what you've described in terms of a multiplicity of gods with a supreme or a most high god that they're all beholden to or extensions of, or however you describe that.
And what I understand is the Christian view.
I mean, that does allow for less powers and principalities.
Yes.
You could say that going down...
The only thing I can do with what you've just brought up, the Christian view, is a critique on the Christian view.
I would say that on the surface, many things seem to be similar.
But the genuine value is radically different.
I think once we discuss the difference between a real Rolex watch and a fake Rolex watch, at a distance, most pedestrians would say they're the same thing.
But when you really come down to the nuts and bolts in value, one is junk and the other one's not.
Literally junk.
So that's an analogy, a very quick way, sort of damocles, to cut anything that might produce a lengthy critique.
So, I mean, I could see how that could be tested over a very long period in terms of their understanding of script, but...
Which is minimal to nothing.
Well, OK.
What they understand is their traditions, Christian traditions, and they'll tell you that.
Not scripture.
And part of the Christian tradition, hear me out, part of the Christian tradition, they're fully aware of Christian tradition, or Churchianity, I call it.
Many call it that.
Part of that tradition includes using verses and parts of the Bible and certain versions of the Bible to build doctrine on.
How many times a year is it?
The King James Version is the only true word of God.
What a hunk of rubbish.
Right?
So they do use that.
Just like, for example, anything that man is engaging in, any field, they promote it as being such, but when you look into it, it changes based on the era, the times, and who was controlling it, and the doctrines change.
And they tend to go so far away from anything that's force that it no longer resembles it.
Which, obviously, Christianity resembles nothing scriptural.
It's a social phenomenon that you'll find in Hellenism, in Zaroism, in any other type of world culture, defining the era.
That's all it is.
It's powerful, by the way.
If you were living in a Zaroistic Parthian empire, wherever you went, call it bullshit or not.
Let me just repeat that.
If you were living in a Zaroism culture and tradition, let's say in ancient Parthia, no matter what you did, thought, or whoever you spoke to, would be heavily affected by that, you see.
So this is what you're, you know, like I think I've mentioned, the academics who are self-professed atheists, not all of them, but if you said they're atheists, it's pretty accurate, because most profess that they are.
They have dubbed this historical era of the past 2,000 years as the Christian era, so they know more.
By the way, one of the things, I took a mental note, just to divert for a moment, does anyone want to bring up the Hippocratic Oath?
Because we're on the topic of the gods.
Put in Hippocratic Oath on the Wikipedia, I could start reading it in Greek, ancient Greek, but the translation right below it is pretty accurate, believe it or not.
They did a banging job on whoever translated that.
Right below it, if you start reading it, it says basically that you swear to the gods Asclepius, Hygieia, right?
It's a pledge to the gods, Asclepius, right?
And Hygieia, which we get the word hygiene, which just means balanced.
And all these other gods in the Hippocratic Oath.
Many times, when you were asking me about the gods there, Jason, I said, people get their law, their morality from their gods.
Like in this culture, they ask for justice all the time.
Justicia.
Go ahead and scroll down to where the Greek is, and scroll down below that and read the first sentence.
I swear by Apollo, the healer, by Asclepius, by Hygieia, and by all the gods and goddesses, making them my witnesses, that I will carry out, according to my ability and judgment, this oath and this indenture.
All right, let's stop for a minute.
This is the Hippocratic Oath, which is involved as being part of the convention of your medical, what?
Sciences.
This is not some minor cult that we're talking about.
This is, whether you're walking down the street in a small place that has one traffic light, that guy, including the largest cosmopolitan arrangements and laboratories, this is one of the things that they lean on as being where they get their moral judgment.
Now, I just want to add that they have taken the gods out of it.
There's the modern oath now, that has been adjusted several times, that left the gods out.
But nonetheless, they're adhering to the deification of the oath.
In other words, there's enough of the body there that you could remove the part about the gods, but it's okay.
The rest of it that doesn't show the gods was still dedicated to them anyway.
So that's why my...
Jason, my point of speaking is not to tell people, this is that, or I have an interpretation, it's to say that don't you bipedal anthropomorphic figures on this planet notice that your morality, your law, and what you consider right and wrong comes from a god?
This is part of your operating system.
You can't escape that.
And that's the point.
And as many times as that, just that point of notice goes out, whether you want to discuss Christianity versus the scriptures, or, you know, Buddhism in the ancient pre-crit, or Hinduism, or Islam or anything is irrelevant, is do you realize what's going on?
Well, and they made contact with us.
Back then, yeah.
Yeah, back then.
They made contact with us big time.
And gave us basic principles as a species.
Yep.
Done.
Weaponry, chemistry, physics, all this, many of the sciences.
Just like today, ask anyone, you know, how did you figure that out?
Well, I don't know.
It happened by accident.
Yeah, right.
I'm pretty sure it did.
I want to bring it back to this question of the one god and the many, if I can.
Sure.
Well, let's just start with a very specific.
Then, in the scripture, the I, Natta King James Version, it's a very famous thing about Yahweh being a jealous god, there are no other gods beside me.
Jealous.
Jealous, not jealous.
Right.
And, in other words, because when the scripture is given, it's given as a constitution to the people of Israel to show that the Most High God also takes a position as the son of gods, but a righteous one, right?
See, because each nation has a principality, or even a sons of gods, their job is to dictate the borders and the nationalities and the separations, and they weren't doing their job, let's say, to a point where one can justify that you can see the history of what's going to happen, because you could have history of the future.
So, he ended up taking, Yahweh ended up taking a group of people and giving them the oracles of the orders of the universe, of the orders of human society, until, you know, the next step, right?
So, he took a position with one of the group of people, just as if you're a father and you have many children, and they're playing a game, that you bought them, let's say, you know, and can't you take a position and go into the game also as one of them?
You see what I mean?
Can't you be a player also?
So, anyway.
Okay, so...
So, he's a zealous god that way, yeah.
And you're equating Yahweh with the Supreme God, the Boss God.
Yeah, he's the Boss God, but he's just so half-king.
You know, when all the workers at a factory take lunch, you know, can the boss of the company come down and have lunch with them?
Of course.
On their level?
He doesn't have to be at the top floor, you know, in the...
wherever, you know, corporate lounge.
Well, I mean, maybe this is where I'm going with this, because it seems like this is mirrored by the mystery of the Incarnation and all that, like, can God incarnate as human and still be God?
Right?
That question.
Yeah, there's a danger when they do that, though, because if you...
that's why I tout the best thing in the movie, The Matrix, is remember when they told you if they kill you in The Matrix you die in real life?
If you're a god and you incarnate, and you're killed in that condition, you die on the other side as well.
Okay, so, but if you're THE god, then, presumably, that's not a possibility.
Sure it is.
If you're the Most High God.
Sure, can you...
I mean, he did die.
He did die.
Sure.
In other words, can an inventor of an automobile be run over by the same automobile that he invented?
Of course.
Very simple.
Well, I guess this is what I'm trying to get to, because what's your concept of God?
Because my concept of God is what incorporates everything.
The infinite, eternal, complex...
Yeah, see, I don't have a concept of God.
What I'm doing is just reporting on what's been memorialized for thousands of years that no one is talking about.
In Scripture.
Yes, in Scripture, right.
What's inside people's heads is irrelevant.
Okay, so, but when you're in Scripture, it becomes inside your head.
Yes, but in other words, what's inside their head, what's inside their head that people are speaking, and it's not really inside your head, you know, it's being transduced.
There is, on the surface, some discussion through the eons about Scripture, and then they veer off into culture and tradition.
I'm saying, why don't we keep it pure, don't cross-contaminate what we've been taught through the ages, through various cultures.
Keep it pure, just look at what's been memorialized, you see, and then talk about that, and then there'll be less to bitch and moan about, you see.
And there'll be less division.
You know, how many times have you heard of armies going to war, and they each opposingly, you know, oppose each other in battle, and they're each carrying the same cross, right?
Have you heard it?
Right?
Does that make any sense?
No, it doesn't.
And yes, to many people it does, because they say, well, that's the way it is, you see, and Scripture has a lot to say about the way things are.
And no one's discussing it.
When I mean no one, I mean no one, publicly, either in written or spoken.
There's many aspects, there are many people that have attempted to do it, and when anyone attempts this type of, what would you call it, a project or a life direction, guess what?
You have to eat.
You need to do exchange, you know, what they call credits or money.
The people that I've spoken to in the past that have tried to do an objectification of the Scriptures stopped at a certain point, and when I confronted some of them, well, why are they omitting X, Y, and Z, or A, B, and C?
And they said, well, because if we put that in, no one will buy our books, or it'll separate everyone, and no one will listen to us.
And then what are we going to do?
Live on a park bench and eat out of a garbage can?
Oh, how little faith you have in the gods.
You see?
Sort of, but isn't an objectification of Scripture what all of these different denominations have been doing over millennia and been fighting about, essentially?
They might not be doing it right, but that's kind of...
Yeah, but ultimately they have to eat, and they like conquest.
You know, I've given many, like if you're around the mob, the underworld, they view who they're going to victimize by what level of a sucker, or a punk, or a bitch they are, what level, you know?
And they say, oh, this group here, or this individual is a sucker, and he's going to lose his assets and his money anyway.
We might as well be the ones that benefit from it, because if we don't go there and take it from him, the next guy is, and where does that leave us?
It's an opportunity loss, you see?
That's why they went to all these different countries, you know, converting people, because if they didn't, the Muslims might.
You know, this was, if you read some of the writings around the 16th, 14th, 15th, 16th centuries, we better go and make sure that we rule with a heavy hand in using Christianity, because if we don't, the Muslims will do it.
In other words, they're saying, these people are stupid, they're going to lose anyway, we might as well take advantage of them and gain from it anyway, because if we don't act on it, someone else will, you see?
So basically, you know, humans have been relegated as a bunch of punks or suckers that are going to lose what they have anyway, and who's going to be the first predator to come in?
Oh yeah, who's going to be the first predator when you have the carcass on the road?
Is it going to be the vulture or the coyote or the dog, you know?
There's a little bit of a battle there.
This is what's been going on with religions, whether it's Islam, Christianity, or whatever.
Well yeah, when they become movements and when they become mob mentalized.
which is three or more.
Right.
Three or more, right.
We're just on the edge of that right now.
But my point is that all of those things, or most of them, probably all of them, presumably started with one person or two people trying to work out scripture and get it right.
Don't leave the spirit, there's always a spirit behind this too.
Yeah.
Well, okay, so my question is, or my thought, my feeling is, maybe the problem is just with attempting to objectify scripture, period.
Or to find the spirit in a letter, inside a letter, or to think that the law of the gods, or the reality of the gods, can be set in stone and then adhered to or understood as something other than a living moment that is constantly changing.
No, well, yes and no.
Let me just backtrack a little bit so we have something to lean on.
I remember reading somewhere once that if you, why don't you wash the outside, or why don't you wash the inside of the cup and that will also wash the outside of the cup, you see.
Right?
Remember that?
Christ was commenting on the Parashima, the Pharisees, on their rituals, and he says, look you fool, if you wash the inside of the cup, just focus on that, the outside will get washed anyway, right?
This is without any information.
How are you going to have a rational discussion regarding anything, whether it's the human body, timekeeping, physics, natural law, anything, if the people are just focusing on being rational on only one aspect of their lives and completely irrational on the rest?
You can't.
It's the whole being that has to be.
A sick being cannot act healthy in just one aspect.
If someone is really sick, they can't just go to work and fake that they're well, and then when they're home act like they're sick.
It's going to catch, it doesn't work.
You're either healthy or you're not.
Humankind has a very unhealthy, unrational approach to anything, you see.
That's one of the problems, by the way, it's personal, but I'll bring it up in personal situations.
I've run, when I started studying scripture, I ran into people that recommended, oh, you want to study scripture?
I know someone who's been doing it for 60 years, and they were part of this group.
I said to myself, oh, that's going to be great, because I know the concept of mentorship and all this, right?
They're going to save me a lot of time.
And they're full of crap.
They had a couple of nuggets, but the moment you bring up the Pope's work schedule, or what about this, what about that, oh, no, no, you can't do that, who do you think you are?
Everybody else is on this, you see.
So they're sick, and they're going to be sick until the day they die, in that perspective.
Then I'm saying you don't have to be.
You know?
In science, it's like cross-contamination.
When you do one experiment, you have to reset all the instruments and clean up before you do the next one, because if you don't, you have residue from the previous that will infect or affect the results of the next experiment.
So there's no way you're going to comprehend scripture if you don't know how the body works, that you're limited to the Pope's work schedule, that you've been lied to, the nature of the culture that you live in.
You see?
Yeah, well, I understand that, but does it follow from that that in order to get your body working, you've got to understand scripture?
Ah, yeah, is it a catch-22?
Is it what came first, the chicken or the egg?
Obviously, all things were created in their own kind, so the chicken came first.
But there's a little scripture in there that says that no one comes to the Father unless he goes through the Son, but he doesn't go to the Son unless the Father draws him.
So, then again, it's kind of like going to a private club.
Well, they won't let you in without a pass, but how do you get a pass?
Well, you have to be invited.
Uh-huh.
So, knowledge, I mean, how important is knowledge?
Well, you go to the God by knowledge, not by anything else, because if he if you have the wrong faith, you're not going to the gods, and the wrong faith is based on knowledge again.
You know, if you believe in Santa Claus and Guy Nelson across wearing a diaper in the Easter Bunny, you're not going anywhere right now.
Right.
You're going to have to wait until the Resurrection.
Well, I could see how bad knowledge would prevent a state of faith, or whatever we want to call it, but...
Well, technically, Greek, wouldn't the people going after Santa Claus and all that kind of stuff be actually worshipping Baal at this point?
Oh, yeah, Molech, specifically.
Yeah, Molech, yeah.
Yeah, which is mentioned in Scripture as well, which is mentioned very clearly, yeah.
So, what about knowledge as a nail to drive out a nail?
Yeah, you can, but what if, you know, if you're having a problem with wood and nails, just set fire to the whole thing, and then you'll just have the nail separate and the wood separate, you see what I mean?
Well, what I mean is that, what if knowledge is only good for driving out, good knowledge is good for driving out bad knowledge, and then that's it.
So, you need all the right knowledge in order to...
Well, then, if all knowledge is...
Well, the thing is, it's knowledge of what?
Knowledge of the truth or knowledge of the lie, and most people that believe in the lie think it's good, because no one's going to say, hey, I know it's a lie, but I believe in it anyway.
Actually, I've had people say that to me before.
So, that's not a good analogy.
Yeah.
Those are the unrehabilitatable ones.
Those are, you see, what everybody has in common is that everyone takes up space, you know, you can measure that through displacement, and everyone gives off heat when they're alive.
So, that defines everyone on this planet as your starting point as a space heater.
So, now, do you have an intelligence, what kind of, what kind of space heater are you dealing with?
You see.
And then, that's the best starting point, because that's the common denominator.
By the way, most of the great literary works that have survived to this point that are considered helps, or, you know, something like Art of War, or whatever, the author first contemplated what everyone has in common as a common ground, you see, and that's where you start.
So, now, we're going to space heaters.
Is it a smart space heater?
Is it just a real dumb one that you plug in and it gives off heat?
Plug in meaning, you know, whatever culture is supplying it with its operation, you know.
And then, you have the ones that complain, my cord is kinked, you know, my switch isn't working.
Then, you got a place that repairs the space heaters, you know, the space heater repair the psychiatrist so they can adjust you to whatever fucked up culture you're in, you know.
But, the scripture is very simple.
But, it doesn't mean that it's easy and it doesn't mean that it's going to be comprehended because, again, it's written by the gods to mankind.
So, later on, no one can say we never got anything from you, but at the same time, you have to comprehend they don't act in futility.
They work on a very high level of efficiency, even when they're pranking you.
So, like ghosts, you know, someone sees a ghost of their grandfather, that's not their grandfather, that's a god or an angel or a demon pranking you.
They're operating on a high level of efficiency there and you need knowledge for that as well.
So...
Well, don't the gods give us that body to...
Well, they set up a system.
The best thing is, you know, people who set up businesses, for example, they set it up so they put a manager in there and they could walk away.
They don't have to be there all the time.
So, we have the ability...
There's a life force that comes in to the planet, a very specific life force that generates through various forms of what we call biological functions and geometry.
All that we see that is alive, including people.
You know, like the plants are one expression of the...
of this ether, let's say, this primary field.
Humans are another.
Chipmunks are another.
Birds are another.
Fish are another.
Well, humans are a very special one, you know.
Yes.
Yes, because we're very special because we have so much and we have so little and we're absent of so many things at the same time.
Yeah.
We have no download like the animals have.
Animals, when they come into the world, they get everything, all the knowledge they need.
We don't.
We have zero knowledge when we come in.
That's interesting, but I think there's an opportunity in that, which, like, I once noticed that the word book, I once was looking for acronyms in words, like, so, for example, the word book, I came up with body of organic knowledge was an acronym for book.
And, the reason...
It came from somewhere, though, but...
Yeah, it's just imaginative, whatever, you know, speculation, but I'm remembering it now as many years ago.
Yeah, yeah.
It makes sense.
Because my sense, what I'm grappling to express now, I'm trying to express it from a bodily place rather than from a mental place, is that the body already has access to all of the knowledge and information in scripture and beyond.
Yes, access to it, right.
We don't need to refer to the book, we don't need to study Greek or Hebrew, we don't need to, you know, unpack every syllable of scripture in order to access that knowledge.
Well, scripture says you do, temporarily.
But, because we're smart to a certain degree, we look at how it's been preserved, even with its failings, and we see that there's another pattern in there as well that accommodates our level of technology, right.
I found that everything that I discuss can be considered counterintuitive.
You know, how many times have you heard, go to a doctor, you'll get better.
It's the contrary.
It's like, you want to throw dice?
Because that's what they don't know anything.
And, you see, you want to go, spiritual, go to a guru or a priest or a rabbi, no, they don't know anything anymore.
Actually, they never really did.
And the ones that did were promptly disposed of or dispatched into unreality.
So, meaning the reality of what people can access.
Because, you know the concept of a lease, when you get a lease agreement?
This whole existence, even spiritual one, has been leased to the malevolent entities, and their lease is over now.
You see, so there's going to be a new re-arrangement, a new tenancy.
In legal, they call it joint tenancy with humanity and these malevolent beings, you know.
So, that's the beauty of it.
In the meantime, you're going to have a struggle.
You know,
let's say you have
a roommate
who is a serious
drug dealer
and a pimp
and involved in
the underworld
and you didn't know
that,
but after a while
you wonder why
he's most active
in the middle
of the night
and he has some
real surly characters
coming over
and why things
go missing
and,
you know,
why he went
into the bathroom
and looked under
the sink
and there's a hundred
grand in cash
that's stashed there.
You know, like, what's going on?
Nothing makes sense when you look at the rest of the neighbors.
So, this is the planet Earth.
And when I say the rest of the neighbors, there's a harmony in the universe that you can see through a telescope that we don't see here on the planet.
So, we're it.
We're part of that harmony.
Yes, in other words, it's like an apartment complex.
This particular flat just happens to be the pimp and drug dealer with this other guy.
But the rest of the complex, the apartment building is fine, you see.
So, I'm not making this up.
This is not what I believe and this is not my, this is what I've discovered.
I'm trying to give reports.
Well, it seems like you said two different things there, at least I got two different things.
Because,
I mean,
what I was getting
was that
it only seems like
the problem
with the drug dealers
and that part of the
apartment building,
because actually
the apartment building
is part of a town
which is part of a city
which is part of a street
which is part of a planet
which is part of a,
you know,
a whole universal system
in which something
is unfolding
and therefore
the drug deal
going down there
is just part of
a much larger unfolding
and everything
is just fine
because the gods
are doing what
the gods do
and whether...
They're not just fine because they tell us that there's war in heaven also.
So even though we have a bad situation in this specific flat the block is under conflict as well.
Well, even that must be fine somewhere, like even the war in heaven.
I mean, well, this is where concepts become problematic, but there's some part of it that's fine no matter what's going on, right?
There's some part of it that's fine with absolutely anything.
Yeah, because no matter how fine something is if you're subject to death it really sucks.
It's when you're no longer subject to death that it's really, really fine.
That's what you're supposed to say.
So it's part of us that isn't subject to death.
Yes, but it's because that part of it goes into complete disanimation when you do die it's irrelevant.
In other words, if I can experience it now while I'm talking to you then it's not irrelevant.
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
If you die you go into complete stasis or disanimation and if you're never reanimated it's as if you've never existed.
Well, okay, but that's your opinion from my point of view.
You can cite all your scripture and all the rest of it, but you don't want me to believe you because you said that.
So all that is the nugget of quasi-information that someday I'll find out if it's true or if it's true I won't find out and if it's not true whatever, you know.
Sure, well, let's put it this way.
It's information for the wise, right?
You never want to convince the fool that what he believes in is wrong.
It's a different kind of system.
You have two systems.
You have the foolish majority that engages in all that, then you have the quiet and the wise that retract and, you know, it's kind of like...
But what if you get two people together head-to-head and they both think they know something and they both appear equally wise?
Appearances can be deceiving.
Well, absolutely they can.
So, it's back to this objectification as well.
Yes, very important.
If you want to objectify your subjective experience of scripture and tell me that when I die I'm going to be disanimated and et cetera, et cetera, well, I mean, that's an imposition and all I can say is no, you can't impose that on me.
Yeah, that's fine.
I don't know if that's true or not.
It's okay if it is, you know, it's not like I'm fighting to say it's not true, but I'm going to stand my ground and say I don't know if it's true and I don't know if you know it either.
That's fine.
So then we're in a big liminal space of I don't know.
No, you are or anybody else is.
In other words, I'm not invested in your belief or what level of belief you have.
I have no investment in anyone else's concepts of what truth is or what scripture is or anything else.
The only reason I'm saying what I'm saying is because what's important, what I've been saying for a long time, even when I discuss people in industry and they don't want to do something, I say why don't you just file it away for later because obviously now is not the time and because it's one of these things that people like to go around circularly with, it's just a waste.
I see it as a lack of efficiency.
Just file it away for later.
In other words, let's just take, for example, let's be poignant.
What I said and what you just said in the past few minutes, let's just stop right there and file it away.
Well, this guy Jason thinks it doesn't work this way and the Greek says it works this way on his report.
Let's just file it away for later.
That's all you can do.
Otherwise, we get engaged in the I call it the time spin.
You know, for example, Hollywood is based on taking up your time.
You don't get anything out of motion pictures or entertainment.
Years ago, I remember meeting someone and he says I'm going to the movies in the summer because I don't have air conditioning and it's real cheap.
I could stay in there on the weekend from the matinee all the way to night and I'm in an air conditioned room.
I never thought of it that way.
Why would I compromise all these possible interests that I could have in my life in the world with just staying in a dark room with a projection because it's air conditioned.
That's what he does though, you see.
So, um.
Yeah.
In other words, it's comfort.
In other words, everyone has their comfort space but what is comfortable for one person is really discomfort or what do you call it a compromise to another, right?
So.
Well, I don't know if it's necessary about comfort because I mean I said last time we talked that a lot of the stuff that you disseminate I'm actually quite comfortable with it but I but That's too bad because it's very contrary to what's been said out there and if you're comfortable with it maybe you're not listening but this is not a personal critique I'm just Well, no.
It's very disturbing what I'm saying It is very disturbing but there are people who have a predilection for disturbing scenarios Okay.
That's different.
Yeah.
Of course.
That's why some people are morticians and surgeons and other people can't do it.
Yeah.
I mean I'm not interested in whether something makes me uncomfortable or comfortable in terms of what we're talking about knowledge or at least I know myself and knowledge well enough to know if it makes me uncomfortable that's not a good reason to back away from it I tend to go into stuff that does That's personal though.
Right.
So I'm just saying I don't have that tendency but what I do try and discern now is what kind of knowledge is actually useful to me Oh.
Food, clothing, shelter Yeah.
What's going to just generate obsession or unnecessary fascination let's say It doesn't have to be negative It can be positive Like I could think for hours on end about your scenarios about the gods and it would be like porn for me that's like mystical metaphysical porn that stuff Huh?
There's nothing wrong with going out and doing a history search and looking around on things either you know to gain more knowledge to get more input Yeah.
There is going to be more
by the way
if you're
like with Jason
and even what you're saying
for us to get more input
on what he's saying
it would be
a form of
you know
porn or whatever
to them
I hope you're aware
or have the sensitivity
and the sensibility
to notice that
as we go through
this time period
there will be more
and more discussion
regarding the metaphysical
the spiritual
the gods
the supernatural
paranormal
all of that
but it will increase
in a way
that it will be
as part of the norm
it won't be
a trend
where it booms
and everyone's like
oh we're tired of this already
it will be incorporated
It's funny
you mention that
you know
last couple of weeks
I've seen these cars
and trucks
with advertisements
on them
for paranormal
research
that will come
out to your house
and
God knows
they have radios
all of them
yeah
they don't know
what they're doing
but I just
I was just thinking
now
right when you said
that I said
yeah you know
it's the last couple
of weeks now
I've noticed
never seen them before
you know
and if you did
you went to these
like hole in the wall
shops
you know
read my palm
or some kind of thing
you know
well they have
the ghostbusters
things
and they are
each major city
does have a paranormal
research
PI
you know
investigator
that they'll know
if you call up
a professional
investigator
they know someone
usually
that's in that field
but they're all idiots
they actually think
they all fall
for the thing
you know
they fall for the spirit
all of them
yeah
even the best ones
I heard an interview
with this one guy
Pagano or
something a while back
and he actually thinks
these were disembodied
spirits
and all that
and he was the best
in the world
the same
you know
it's like
the doctor
let's check your blood pressure
why
there is no blood pressure
get out of here
or the guy
in the train
so you
you can see the future
he gets slapped
across
you know
anybody
oh yeah
the psychic
you didn't see
that coming
did you
you didn't see that one
yeah
but anybody
can see the future
based on whatever
skills they have
including psychic skills
you know
but
again
if you go back
to scripture
there's a caveat
there
in the end
the psychics
will be
shut down
they'll just be
babbling and
murmuring
you know
bullshit
blah blah blah blah blah
just like
look at
has anything
these public psychics
ever said come true
no
so
has there ever been
a time period
where a psychic
did say something
and it came true
yes
many instances
so
to be considered
yeah
and privately
by the way
I do consult
with people
on the concepts
of the gods
you know
in other words
prayer
the spirit
the spirit world
in terms of
you know
contrary to what
most people
consider the spirit world
you know
dead people
and so they're all
demons or ghosts
you know
being spirits
demons
angels
minor gods
you know
territorial gods
based on
what I call
elementals
you know
like if you're
in the tropics
it's going to be
a very different
set
than if you're
in the desert
usually the desert
has the worst ones
by the way
and
how to
cognitively
you know
deal with that
and what
prayer is
and
from a technical
aspect
which is just
a communication
if you see
an army battalion
out in the field
you'll
near the
commanding officer
there's always a guy
with a couple
of boxes
and some long
antennas
that's why
in the field
they always look
for the long
antennas
you know
that's where you
want to shoot at
because that means
you're usually a
commanding officer
nearby right
but that would be
the guy that's
praying
that's sending
the messages
back and forth
you know
it's a technology
so just like
anything else
I have another
question for you
it might seem
like a total
non sequitur
but I
if you want
I can tell you
why I think
it's related
it's about
circumcision
do you have
thoughts on
circumcision
and the covenant
and what that's
all about
oh I don't
want to think
about that
getting your
thing chopped
right
is that something
anybody wants
to think about
well it's the
first on my
plate
yeah
knowing the
society
we saw
the cut offs
to deep
pride
as snacks
for rabbis
oops I just
said that
what kind of
God
would ask
for that
and why
well you gotta
realize
it was
well you said
why
do I need to
repeat
why
what the
purpose of it
is
a cursory
study of
scripture
will tell you
what the
purpose of it
is
right
if you want to
get into
other aspects
of it
which I've
been saying
more
I've always been
saying but only
more recently
publicly is the
gods don't care
about your
physical condition
unless they have
a purpose for you
to have a good
physical condition
as a reward
or to accomplish
something
so they have
no problem
taking 80
million people
out for target
practice
and if you
ask them why
did you just kill
80 million people
like why we don't
need a reason
maybe we just
needed something
to do
fuck off
you know
you're still
here
yeah
they have
what do you mean
by you're still
here
you know
you tell somebody
fuck off
you're still
here
so they're
not
well they do
care about
physical condition
if they're
asking for
circumcision
as a covenant
then
so they do
care in some
way
and they care about
it's a
communication
yes
it's a
communication
yeah like
but that be handed
down to the
generations
so like if
your generations
gave a damn
you know
you would pass
that along
it's
strictly as a
communication
as well
right to show
do you remember
in Genesis
when Joseph and his
brothers went
off to the
back room
what why did they
have to do
what was the purpose
of it
it's not just
the soul
it's to communicate
that we are
right you see
you know someone
was once contemplating
the purpose of being
an artist
or art
I'm like listen
dude get over it
art is just a
communication
that's why it's
used in many
other ways
than just
a simple
expression of
art
the female
of the species
doesn't have
that ability
by the way
it doesn't peak
at 8 days
it only peaks
in the male
you mean it has
less ability
after 8 days
yes
and less ability
before it
yeah
right
so what about
the effect
of the circumcision
ritual on
that infant
psyche
well the infant
fortunately at that
point is too
small to receive
external input
it's kind of like
you're just
plugging the
motherboard in
you could start
trying to
download from
the internet
nothing's going
to happen
frankly I think
that's bullshit
yeah that's fine
you're entitled
to it
there are lots
of flowers that
need bullshit
if you've got
some real bullshit
well so what
about an infant
that is
gestated
in a
womb of an
alcoholic mother
who's drinking
the whole time
you're saying
that doesn't
affect the
development of
the infant
oh physically
it does yes
but the infant
is not cognizant
of it
no I didn't
say physically
are you talking
about physically
or the memory
of it
I'm confused now
well I said
psyche
no there is
no psyche is
the mind
no the psyche
is in the
most base
state
it's like
what we're
discussing
with the
calculus
at that point
it's
yeah
stick around
well psyche
isn't the mind
first of all
psyche is
Greek for soul
so like an
infant baby
doesn't have a
mind
it doesn't have
language
so ok
hold on
the soul
is pneuma
the breath
and psyche
is the mind
that's where
you get
psychologist
and psychotic
you can go
to any
dictionary
will define
it as such
the soul
you know
a car is not
a house
and an elephant
is not a banana
right
the shoe
is not the sock
there are three
different aspects
to it
if you want
to throw away
um
the reference
on that
and refer to
how it affects
the person's mind
that's fine
but to say that
the psyche
is the soul
I have some notes
I ran into
by the way
from a decade ago
regarding that
and
one of the
there was a
little thin book
I found
on linguistics
I don't have
its name
but the reason
why
one of the reasons
that I saw
that the
disturbing
whites
the most people
to define
the psyche
was because
of the nature
of such a definition
and having
something workable
and what I
started doing
by
defining it
and I noticed
that they put
psyche
it's the spirit
or the soul
or the breath
like the wind
what they did there
to define it
as the soul
and the breath
and the wind
was
in ancient writs
when people
were asked
or even the Christ
what is the spirit like
he says it's like
the wind
it's not the wind
in other words
meaning that
you don't see
the wind
but you see
its effect
you don't see
the spirit
but you see
its effect
right?
there's a difference
between
saying
I have an elephant
on my chest
or it feels
like I have
an elephant
on my chest
there's a lot of
commentary
that's been written
on this
but the moment
it's very scary
to people
to define
the soul
the spirit
and the body
because now
what that does
is guess what
it makes them
responsible
the legal system
is based on that
when they're not
completely
trying to destroy
someone
they
through each step
of the process
they have to make sure
do you understand
do you comprehend
and if you don't
you don't continue
so to have
a firm grip
on the mind
is one of the keys
to manipulating
people
you never define it
you can't define
the mind
or the spirit
that's
that would be
throwing
casting pearls
just flying
go ahead
soul is your breath
I mean
psyche is a
Greek word
right
so it seems as though
they
conflated
these different
concepts
of soul, mind
and spirit
no, they're accurate
there's
three distinct
things
in other words
when I
when I say
let's go to
for example
soul
it's not just
your breath
it's your metabolism
your heart rate
is tied into that
right
your metabolic
rate
which is
you know
when you're upset
your metabolic rate
is very different
than when you're happy
like you don't want
to eat
you see
so your metabolic rate
is your soul
it functions
autonomously
or involuntarily
because
how do I know
you're still breathing
when you're asleep
so it does have
an auto
auto
autosimplistic
form
where it functions
on its own
you see
once it's attached
to the body
you see
now if you have
no soul
the body dies
no heartbeat
no breathing
that's what they
look for
and the spirit
is
you know
the mind
that
when people
say they're of
the same mind
they still are
distinct
unto themselves
but on that
particular topic
they do share
the same spirit
or mind
I'm kind of
a little confused
when we started
then
because you were
saying the soul
was the mind
and now you're
saying the spirit
no
the soul
is the metabolism
or the breath
if you want to
see your soul
it's very simple
take a piece of glass
and exhale on it
and when it fogs up
that's evidence
of the soul
anyone in the
medical profession
when they
approach someone
they look for
evidence of the
soul
breath
pulse
body temperature
so what about
spirit as an
inspiration
or respiration
like the root
the word spirit
is also rooted in
those words
like
respiration
right?
right
so
it might be
esperito
uh-huh
but it has to be
because
if you have to
make anything
as tangible
as possible
for people to
work with it
if you put someone
in front of an
assembly line
and you said
you're going to
assemble this
but you can't
touch it
well how am I
it's you know
it's torture
then you'll never
get anything done
yeah
well
of course
and these
concepts are
notoriously intangible
or even by definition
they're somewhat intangible
so
let's bring it back
to the body now
but hold on
the spirit is only
intangible
completely intangible
unless you have
the right
system
uh
a record
a vinyl record
or a CD
no one
knows what's on it
unless you put it
in the right system
and if that
system's not
plugged in
you'll never get
what's on that
DVD
or record
I even
as a joke once
as a retired
material scientist
I brought him
a DVD
and I said
what is it?
and he gave me a three page report on it on its weight its chemical composition did XRF analysis on it he gave me all the dimensions I said it's the Beatles White Album did you see that?
nope
you see
because he didn't
all the science
did not have
the right equipment
to play
the information on it
that's where it's intangible
and that's the difficult part
okay
and what are you
referring to then
as the instrument
for playing
the body
the body and the soul
okay
the body
right
so
and soul
if you kill
the dead people
don't have a spirit
right
and if
a body without a soul
is
what
dead
or
a vehicle
for something else
it's dead
well
it's just
a biological machine
and
you have to also
and you do know
I'm sure
that once the body dies
you have
a rapid
inset
of decomposition
that degrades it
to the point
where it could not go back
to it's original
function
very rapidly
right
okay
and before it's born
the body is in the womb
and it's
breathing
well it's breathing
through the
umbilical
yeah
the umbilical cord
it's in a vacuum
it's in the most
optimum condition
to do that
yeah
right
so
and a newborn baby
is
has a soul
absolutely
it shares
it shares the soul
with the mother
that's why
you said earlier
if the mother's
soul
she's taking
uh
she's
what do you call it
marinated in alcohol
I call it
right
yeah
you know when you
marinate something
and it goes through
and through
yeah
pickled
yeah of course
thank you
yeah
that's of course
so um
yeah that baby's
screwed basically
if it's pickled
if the mother is pickled
yeah
right
so
which is proven
provable scientifically
by the way
right so the baby's
born
whatever happens
to that baby
physically
uh
it goes into the body
right
like you talk about
how objects
memory
well certainly the human body
has memory
just because babies can't
form memory
the way we later
form them
doesn't mean that the
body doesn't remember
isn't imprinted
with what happens
to it
you know
to the womb
you do lose a lot of
your juvenile memory
when you lose your
first set of teeth
ok
there's memory
and the memory
is uh
the illicit memory
is held in the bones
heart tissue
the
the early
uh
schlocky
and who's the other guy
maybe Bruce you can help me
the earliest
chip
memory chip
and transistor
researchers
oh boy
schlocky was one of them
right
in the 1920s
uh
one of the guys
that was part of the
bell labs
he said
these memory chips
that you're building
look at this
and he gave them a list
of all these compounds
and he says
well where'd you get that
that's exactly what we're using
he says this is a list
of all the compounds
found in teeth and bones
oh that's interesting
yeah
mhm
and you know
to touch back on
that uh
when you mentioned
about the spirit
that is the most
valuable to the god
or to the gods
right
that's right
because when you're done
being animated
they check you off
in the book
that this one came through
this
living
freaking hell
from a
cognitive
language
point of view
and we're putting him
back on the hard drive
on the shelf
until the resurrection
or it might be
one of the ones
that we destroy
but anyway it never
comes back
right
so
low level
yeah
they say
basically everyone
will come back
so uh
yippee
anyway
so
bringing it back
to
what I was trying
to explore here
and this is kind of
I guess a living
example of why
I'm so wary
of
high concept
stuff
to me all this
stuff that you're
talking about
resurrection
and reanimation
and the gods
and all of that
is
way less real
than the reality
of an infant child
being traumatized
to 8 days
in such a way
that
it's development
is probably
severely
sabotaged
let's say
yeah it is
don't get over it
by that ritual
where I wasn't
circumcised
I'm glad to say
I'm the pickled baby
with the alcoholic
mother
and I'm still trying
to get over that
but
so that's why
I try to bullshit
that because
it seems as though
you were
disregarding
what I see
as a reality
there
the circumcision
ritual had some
purpose besides
just identifying
the tribe
that it had to do
with what I call
traumagenesis
which is
interfering with
the natural process
organic process
by which the soul
becomes
embedded in the
body
well it's
all trauma
because
Eve was told
she will
bear her children
with trauma
and if anyone
has been around
any other creatures
that bear their young
a cow
most cows
will just be
chewing the cud
and oops
what's that
mmm
ok back to chewing
the cud now
I just drop the calf
no big deal
I've seen a cat
come to me
comes into the closet
comes out
I look
oh there's a kitten
she looks at me
I'm going to go
nibble on some food
comes back
drops another kitten
meow
hi
you know
it's like wow
it's all trauma
ok well
but that
I mean
at that point
you can justify
MKUltra
and you know
satanic ritual
abuse
and whatever
just
throw a
it's all trauma
get out of jail
free card
no because you
can do something
for example
on a social
cultural level
you could get
you could stop
the satanic
satanic just
pretty much
all the major
stuff right
those are just
satanic
manifestations
aren't they
yeah but
but if you say
we're going to
stop the trauma
by stopping
childbirth
at least
and all that
then everything
stops
and by the way
they're going
on that direction
the goddess religion
is that
is
anything to
stop
the plan
but it has to be
done voluntarily
in other words
the goddess religion
she will not
shoot you
she'll just convince you
to buy a gun
and then say
oh pat you on the back
you got the gun great
I'll see you next week
and next week she says
why don't you aim it at your head
and pull the trigger
no not this week
I'll come back next week
and convince you to do it then
you see
well my point was just
that it's an unnecessary
conflation
like you can say
everything's traumatic
and that'll be true
but they're not all
the same kinds of trauma
and
there are more reasons
to identify trauma
genesis
rituals
than to say
trauma's bad
and it shouldn't be done
like it's
also a way
to understand
better
the
well the way
in which
we've been
psychically configured
I suppose
but if you could
say for example
real quick
from a
a pseudo
philosophical
theological
point of view
is
circumcision
necessary
for the resurrection
and what's the answer there
no
so you can stop
all the circumcision
and it has to be done
voluntarily
either way
you see
I suppose
but I mean
I'm not talking about
social change
or social reformation
either
no I'm not either
I'm just saying
is it possible
yes
but that's
that's
that's a generational
thing
I mean it's
it's
mom and dad
making the
yeah it's making
it's mom and dad
making the decision
it's not like
the baby's getting up
and grabbing the guy
by the
by the shirt
hey
put that
many western cultures
do the chop
at the hospital
unreal
unritualistically
meaning scripturally
I mean
but it still is
ritual to them
if you
I think
I think with a boy
if you don't
unless you
you object to it
they do it automatically
don't they
in western culture
supposedly
yeah
in high school
so that's an interesting
from an objective
point of view
to see what's going on
yeah
mhm
so I mean all of this
I think
for me all this
and the reason I said
it was somewhat congruent
with my earlier questions
is that for me
it comes back to
to my own sense
which is that
if the body is healthy
and the energy
of the body
is all flowing
in the way that
it's supposed to be flowing
then we have
just natural access
to the realm of the gods
as you call it
to reality
as it is
no you don't
ok
so
why not
if you have
let's just
put it this way
it's very simple
let's say you're living
in a big city
in New York
and you walk by
the Waldorf Astoria
and there's a big party
going on
and you say
well I have natural
energy flowing
through my body
I'm going to go into
this party
at the Waldorf
mhm
they're going to
stop you right there
well how is that
a parallel
so explain to me
how the Waldorf
I don't know
how more simple
can that could be
there's somewhere
I read that
if you invite yourself
you may not
be wanted
in that position
you might be told
to go
either leave
or sit in the back
yes but this is all
so in other words
the gods
the gods are not
some kind of
pond scum
uh
purely like
ooo
goop
that oh
you just go into it
you know
they'll surround you
and all that
no no no
they have a
they're a parallel
society
in other words
if you're like
a headhunter
and you come to a society
that has electricity
cars airplanes
and all that
hey I'm at your
customs let me in
let me into your
country right now
they're going to say
hold on a second
where's your papers
where's this
where's that
were you invited
mhm
they'll stick you
in a detention cell
well let me know
this movement
that's your viewpoint
that's the very thing
I'm questioning
is that hierarchical
well I think
you're
god's viewpoint
that's fine
I do respect the questions
but let me just make a
criticism on it
most people think
because
when you hear
even the word
neter
which is the ancient
Egyptian word
meaning gods
when you hear nature
right away you think
gods oh god is nature
all this other stuff
this natural stuff
that's part of the creation
um
uh
the gods
um
the thing that
I like to report on
is that they are
a parallel society
of very high
advancement
this is just
language that I'm
using now
more than advanced
because they're primary
to us
um
and to associate them
with palm scum
or air
or a
mountain valley
or something
that you just lay down
in the grass
and you're with the gods
it's total rubbish
uh
from what can be reported
on that's been
memorialized
now I'm not
am I saying
you don't have the right
to think that
of course you do
as a matter of fact
you've reinterpreted
I mean you don't really
know what I'm thinking
I might not have expressed
it very well
but I certainly didn't
express what you've
echoed back at me
now a lot of people
think that
let me just
maybe it's not
directly to you
but the thing is
that
how difficult
is it to comprehend
that the gods
are just a parallel
society
of much higher dynamics
basically
they're still
parallel societies
yeah they're
that's all they are
how difficult is that
in other words
just like we have
a society
you know
with different
orders and levels
the street sweeper
and the king
and the guy who
drives the train
the guy who makes
the airplanes
all the various
aspects of a society
I'm not saying
just a family
because you know
when I say society
in other words
there's a very big
cross section of industry
they have a big industry
going on over there
as well
ok well I mean
it's fascinating
it's a fascinating model
it's your model
in your interpretation
well it's not
my interpretation
when I read
in scripture
all the writs
they have one god
for this
one god for this
one god for that
and it keeps going on
with a list of a thousand
different things
that can be done
with a thousand different
gods to do them
and even their gods
they actually have
helps to do this
and they call in another
god to do that
shit
that sounds like
you know
mid-century America
TV's broken
what do we do
call a TV repairman
a tooth hurts
go to the dentist
oh the roof needs to be fixed
you see all the various
things you have access to
and the various
hats and jobs
that people have
that's what I'm noticing
and reading the ancient
writs
I'm like whoa
there are very
they have a tremendous
variety of things
going on over there
well maybe you're
projecting your own
experience onto that
and
well I'm
I know
because I'm doing it
familiar in such a way
that it works for you
well I'm not
this stuff was written
before you and I
were born
in that way
you can go read it
yeah I know
but I see your
interpretation
that you're interpreting
I don't have an
interpretation on it
well you do
I'm just reporting
what's
what's there
you're reporting your
interpretation
well my version
there's only one
interpretation
there are many
versions
it would be more
accurate if you said
my version of it
right
and I can only
give my version
of the report
that's why I always
suggest people
why don't you go and
study and come back
and give us a report
on what you've
discovered
well I have
you know I have
been doing my
studies
for the last
whatever how many
years
just because I
haven't studied the
same things
or in the same way
so let me show you
where is it
my version
when he says
for example
let's use the
biblical text
I'm going to send
a destroying angel
oh I'm going to
send an angel
who's going to
show you how to
build these things
oh I'm going to
show you another
angel that's
going to give you
knowledge
oh I'm going to
give you another
angel that's going
to torment you
give you another
angel that's
going to make you
stubborn
and send another
angel that's going
to make the frogs
come out of the
water
send another angel
and make the rivers
turn red
and send another
angel that's going
to do this
where am I off
well can you
mention the Gods
that come to all
the different
countries
you can choose
how literally
you interpret
that
and even if you choose to interpret literally, you can choose whether you interpret that
in a way that matches your experience as a human, a socialized human being.
Like when the Egyptians talked about the netas, as I understand it, my limited way, the neta means principle, something like principle, and that the netas were an extension of Atum, which was the single god, and all these other gods were merely extensions of that one god.
So when you read about a destroying angel in the scripture, you can just as well interpret that as the one all-high god extending some part of his awareness into the chattel realm and causing something to happen.
And by that same token you could see that human beings were made in God's image, therefore we are also extensions of the most high.
Therefore everything that happens is an extension of the most high, from the gods all the way on down to our, you know, crack-smoking, fucked-up, traumatized, circumcised baby, you know, culture that you're reigning against.
So that's what I mean by access to the realm of the gods, because the realm of the gods is embedded in everything, it's in me, it's in the sinews of my flesh, and then every thought I have is an extension of that.
So I can go straight to the source, not with my ego, not with my concepts, but some part of me can't extricate myself from that anyway, like I'm only here because of that.
Sure, what you just gave is accurate in a corporate sense.
Like for example, when the washing machine breaks down, I'm not discounting it, just consider this, Maytag, someone's at the door, who is it?
It's Maytag.
Oh, come on in, the washing machine's broken.
What Maytag?
What do you mean it's Maytag?
It's a guy that works for Maytag in the uniform.
Of course he's an extension of Maytag.
And you know, for example, if
you read a lot of the corporate covenants of banks, most people don't know this,
but you could look this up, is that when you go into a bank, which is an association,
all banks are called associations, they have a corporate side to them also, to confuse people,
but in the association side of the bank, if you go to a bank and they admit that you're
now dealing with the association of the bank, whether you're speaking to the teller, or the
janitor, or the CEO, or the head boss, they all have the same authority.
In other words, they cannot discount one's position over the other, right?
You see what I mean?
It's because it's an association.
So now corporations are different, and there's different layouts and different groups, but from an association point of view with the gods as a realm, I would say yes, they all are extensions, of course, just like the Maytag repairman is Maytag, and no one questions that.
But what's really going on, is what I'd like to bring forward, is that when he sends a destroying angel, that is an entity unto itself.
In other words, if we went over into the world of the gods, and walked into the bar, where they all go and have their drinks, and you say, do you guys know the destroying angel?
Oh yeah, he's over there in Iraq right now.
Right?
Well, the cells are all entities unto themselves also.
Yeah, they're an expression of the ether, of the life ether, because when you actually start examining, which is extremely difficult, a live cell, all this talk about biology is rubbish, because everything that they're talking about biology is dead stuff.
Once you view it and put out the information, as they do academically, you know they're talking about dead things.
Very rarely can they deeply analyze or observe things that are alive in a cellular nature.
The moment you extract the cell from its living host, it goes into death mode.
Right?
Who's doing the live research?
Oh, there's quite a few, and they always get shut down.
Right.
Yeah, always get shut down, because it goes against the laws of physics.
You know, things appear out of nothing.
It's not one of the man hunters.
Right.
Plants are a wonderful thing to study.
If you have asphalt that hasn't been rolled that well, or even one that doesn't, you'll see sprouts push up through the asphalt.
You get where I'm going with this, right?
Yeah.
That doesn't work with physics, because, you know, a scientist engineer will pull out his, you know, tablet or whatever, and say, wait a second, you know, you need 350 pounds per square inch to do that.
And, you know, wait, how does that sprout that you can crush in your finger do that?
It's geometric expression, you see.
Once you start to contemplate that, if you really want to get into what the gods are expressing to us is the signal that's being sent to the earth, this free-form primal field, which, by the way, there is no branch of science that can define a field.
They always tell you it's a wave or something.
Once you comprehend that is what pretty much everything that we consider alive is being affected by in this expression geometrically, you know, your body is a geometric expression, you know.
That's how other, if it wasn't, then cells would not be able to be identified, because cells are identified visually through their geometry, by the way.
You know, so, right?
And chemically, of course.
But that's all.
Outside of that, they stop and say, well, what keeps procuring this rigid geometric pattern?
They can't deal with that.
Wilhelm Reich spoke about that.
It's the emotional armoring.
You know, just like a knight in shining armor, he feels real confident, but once you get under the armor, he gets really perturbed.
I try to stay away too much discussion on the ether and the life force, because guess what?
I spend every day, a little bit of every day, researching it on my own, through direct experimentation.
When I mean direct experimentation, I mean not thought experiments, you know what I mean?
It's quite a thing to heat a rock to incandescent and put in some potassium chloride distilled, you know, reagent grade, sterile, and sucrose or even sucralose that's been heated to sterilization, close it off under some UV light, and three days later see critters coming out of the rock.
You know, little moving things.
It's quite a thing to see that, and you know, part of you tells you that's not really happening, but for sure, there must be some contamination here that allowed this, you know, some spore, or not a spore, but we're not talking about spores like fungi, we're talking about things with legs and antennae moving around too, you know?
So the part of you that you're, the culture that you're in, says this should not be happening, but all of your sensory perception is telling you that it is.
Um, we're live on three right now.
Oh, um, I started looking to identify them, and there is no identification for them.
They look very similar to, like, a translucent crawfish.
What's that?
Without the claw.
Go ahead.
In other words, that species, that type of cross-section, you know, the thorax, and the tail, and the leg length, that's how things are done by proportion.
Um, you know, we've got another guy going right now.
We've got another one.
The trunk is, it's purporting, you know, to express its body and all that.
I'll see if I can get you broader in on this, too.
Yeah, there was an interesting guy named, uh, Peter Cross, I think, back in the 1700s.
He took rusted pieces of iron, and he wanted to dissolve the rust in, uh, sulfuric acid, and he put a lid on it, and about, he forgot about it, and two months later, he opens the lid, and a lot of microscopes...
Oh.
Let's see if we get you in.
Am I still there?
Yeah, go ahead.
Oh, and a creature crawled out of the sulfuric acid mixture, which shouldn't be happening.
Yeah, we got another fella calling in here also.
Okay.
See, we'll bring him in.
Okay, go ahead.
No, but do you see how these...
Greetings.
Oh, we have a telephone caller, you mean.
Another Skype line.
Oh, Skype, another Skype line.
Okay, great.
So we got, we got three of us on here now.
Okay.
Four, Peter.
Yeah, four.
It's amazing what happens when some of us can count.
Yeah, yeah, anyway.
Uh, you had a question?
Go ahead, introduce yourself, let us know what...
Uh, we were...
We could be talking about you.
Go ahead, produce that.
What would you like?
Have you, have you heard of what we're discussing?
You want to add anything?
Okay.
So, so anyway, Jason.
Yes, we got a, we got a beautiful copy.
Can you hear us real good?
Right.
Yeah.
Yes.
You're welcome.
Okay.
When you get older, you might feel like they're dropping, but anyway.
By the way, uh, I don't think, I don't think you can hear us.
Yeah.
Sure.
Well, uh, can you, you probably can't hear me, can you?
Can you, can you hear Greek?
Oh, you can, yeah.
All right, so you could speak, uh, uh, well, does he hear, if Jason speaks, does he hear Jason?
Can you hear me?
You hear me?
Yeah.
No, I would tend to think, let's see if we got it.
Apparently they call him on the, on the stream.
Yeah, the gods are doing, remember I said they're parallel, so we have a parallel conversation, Jason, uh, the Greek and Bruce, and, and then we have Bruce and the caller.
Yeah, Bruce here, I guess.
And the guests, so Bruce and, oh, down here, yeah, so that's a parallel condition.
So, Bruce, it's up to you to juggle three on one side and one on the other.
Correct.
There we go.
You got your hand.
Okay, there we go.
The gods.
We're talking, okay, yeah, yeah, the gods and the body, yeah, the extension, the gods, everything being an extension of the gods, um, and essentially I basically said, you know, like the pot is the extension of another metaphor, be the, the pot is the extension of the potter, but you can smash the pot to bits and the potter won't mind, or won't, you know, he can, you see.
Well, he might mind a little bit, if he's a good potter.
Yeah, if it's his prized pot, he's going to mind, and that's actually a better analogy for what's going on.
So, oh, gravity?
No, it's not.
Gravity, gravity is just an incoherent field, and this is the secret.
If you understand how to make it coherent, then you can, then you can go whichever way you want.
It's an incoherent field that gives the impression of pull, but it's actually push, and it's not really a pressure as much as it's, it's by voidance.
You know, when, when there's a voidance between two things that come together, you get the impression that they're being pulled together, but they're not.
It's because of the voidance.
It's like when you're stuck in, when you're stuck in the soda pop through a straw, the liquid comes up because of the voidance in the straw, not because you're really sucking, right?
Through voidance.
Yeah, it's a void that when you bring them together, they're not really attracting, and you could prove that.
I think in chat, I gave an example of how you can take two magnets that are what they call
the same pole that repulse each other, but if one magnet's really small and the other one's really
large, you can, even though they're the same poles, they repulse, but once you center them perfectly,
you'll push the small one into the large one, and it will actually stick,
because in the center of every magnet is its opposite pole.
So, this is perfectly illustrated in the yin and yang symbol, but it's not perfect because it shows, the squiggle shows a little bit of white in the black, and a little bit of black on the white on the other side.
Those need to be folded over on each other.
And didn't you say one time that if you did that and got the magnets to stick, and then went like 10, 15 feet away, and pointed another magnet at it, it would just fall apart?
It jumps off.
Yeah.
Right, which means that the field is not just what they show you with the iron columns.
It affects everything.
Yeah.
No.
I'm going to disconnect here.
I hope I don't lose you guys here for a moment.
Just give me three seconds.
Hopefully, this will work.
Okay.
What is most conducive to human health is a mixture of what we call air, with the corresponding elements, which happen to be mostly nitrogen, 78% or more nitrogen.
When the nitrogen goes into the lungs, the lungs convert through low L-E-N-C, I call it, or it's been called low energy nuclear conversion, the nitrogen into oxygen and other things, water also, on the inside of the body.
And if you look at the periodic table of elements, when nitrogen goes to oxygen, guess what it passes?
Carbon, doesn't it?
On its way.
That's why you get the illusion that you're taking in oxygen and giving off carbon dioxide.
You're not.
When the nitrogen turns into oxygen inside of the body, one of the residual effects, because it's going through the cycle from nitrogen to oxygen, passing through carbon and other elements, those are also created and bonded and given, and the scientist is fooled.
He has to give an explanation that is based on his lack of being able to see what's really going on.
They're not allowed to say what's going on, by the way.
Now, the other aspect of that is if you're doing a L-E-N-C conversion of carbon into iron, I do this all the time at a rate of 15% per cycle, meaning you can give me a 99.999 or 100% chunk of carbon, and within a few seconds, I'll turn 15% of that by volume into pure iron.
Right?
In the kitchen.
Now, in this iron, you can have it measured, it's pure iron.
No one's like, well, how did you get such pure iron?
But the thing is, it won't rust when you put it in water at all, because when carbon goes to iron, and guess what?
It passes through nickel, doesn't it?
So you get all the attributes of nickel in the iron, even though it measures as pure iron.
Now, the ancients knew of this.
Anyone can look this up, that's within earshot.
You go online and research in India, in India somewhere, there is an iron pillar.
About eight feet or six feet is sticking out of the ground, most of it's underground.
And people touch it, it gets rained on, it's been there for hundreds of years, and it never rusts.
And they've done chemical analysis on it, and it's pure iron.
It's not stainless steel, it's not an alloy, and there's no oxidation happening on it whatsoever.
And I have to chuckle, like, how does that happen?
Well, that iron that they're showing you was, they understood transmutation, they took carbon and converted it to iron at a rate of, like I just mentioned, and they used that iron, that's why it doesn't rust.
Well, iron created this way will not rust.
I had, there was a Native American tribe here that wanted to, got a big grant, they wanted to do some technology.
I said, do you guys have any garbage?
And they looked at me and laughed, they said, we got more garbage per capita than most other societies do, you know.
I said, let's go to the landfill and start burning the garbage and capturing all of the heat to turn turbines to make electricity.
And the carbon that's left over, we convert to this pure iron, you see, and also power your homes, you see.
And you have no, in other words, now you're burning garbage, but you have no heat waste, no toxic waste, and you're producing iron from the waste, from the carbon.
And you see, it's a purely closed system, you know.
We're going to run this by the university first.
Oh, yeah, sure.
An iron cap, what do you mean by, what do you mean by an iron cap?
No, no.
Yeah, you could, but what I'm discussing is just basically what's going on in the natural material world, how one thing becomes another.
In other words, it's called transmutation or low energy nuclear conversion.
This is a field that is completely open, that no one is researching.
Silver, for example, this is a, cars are something different.
Cars work, the reciprocating engine is only popular because of its pound to horsepower ratio and price ratio.
In other words, a reciprocating motor, for the cost that it takes now to make one, will give you pound for pound, cost for cost, the cheapest way to make power.
But we know pound for pound, an electric motor gives more energy pound for pound than a reciprocating car engine.
But the problem with electrics is your power source.
The battery technology will not advance.
And then, of course, I've brought forward that electricity is not what we're told.
If anyone investigates the energy machine of Joseph Newman, the free energy thing is already, that book is closed 40 years ago.
You know, free energy, it's not free.
You just have to understand how the field works.
Electricity really works.
But no, what I'm discussing here, we went off because you mentioned the body and gravity and all that.
Once we get over the fact that things are, you know, everything seems to be ephemeral, not empirical.
When they show you an element of gold, well, it just so happens to be gold.
Now it can change into something else.
I don't know why you'd want to change gold into lead, let's say.
You want to do the reverse.
By the way, lead doesn't go to gold.
Copper or silver goes to gold.
So that's another misnomer.
The only reason they say lead goes to gold is when they bombard it in nuclear, high nuclear situations.
They get a little bit of gold out of lead.
So we're just talking about the human body.
By the way, I'd like to read an email if you guys are still there.
I'm going to move again.
Hopefully, I just traveled quite a bit.
We'll be right back in the office here.
I'm going to read an email regarding the human body.
And I'm going to comment on it because even though the outcome was good, this is not exactly how I would have done it.
Meaning with the with the limb.
I had a thumb injury unloading my pickup, jammed my thumb on a piece of metal just underneath the nail.
Hurt like H-E-L-L.
So immediately wrapped it with napkin and duct tape.
Later applied more duct tape and bandage over the previously wrapped.
Never removed it for one or two days.
First night hurt like hell.
That morning pain subsided.
That evening no pain at all.
Following day, removed all tape, bandage, washed soap and water.
Looked almost as if nothing happened.
Normally would have lost the entire nail.
Not this time.
Four or five days later, can't even tell it happened.
Okay, that's a success story.
But what I would suggest is that you, within the first 15 minutes or an hour, you do want to unwrap it in case it's too tight to let circulation take place.
Obviously, this person did not have it so tight where, let's say, the finger would be in danger of losing circulation.
I'm presuming because it is a happy ending.
But usually, the tighter it is for the first 10 or 15 minutes, the more effective.
But in this case, this email that I just read, it was a one or two day healing.
You know, versus something that would take days or weeks, you see.
But I suggest that the only thing I have here is that it was not removed for one or two days.
I would suggest after the first 15 minutes or an hour to remove it or open it and make sure everything looks okay.
It hasn't discolored or gotten numb, you see.
So that was the only thing that I wanted to comment on that.
Yes, well, I wanted to call in and report back also on this whole, how do I say this, the ex-Christians.
The Christians, they're moving into the yoga field.
Like you said, all the yogis are ex-washouts, Christian washouts.
Well, that's totally true.
I've been experiencing that first-handedly.
So they try to convert the Sanskrit into the King James Version.
And they even write it out as in the Sanskrit, and then they put the colon, and then they put the number.
And I think you said that was some type form of spellcasting, and I've been seeing it everywhere.
And so when they try to preach, it could be.
But also keep in mind, there is a Romanized Sanskrit as well.
In other words, Roman letters that we can all read.
I didn't quite get the gist of it.
So what they're doing is translating the King James, or they're just basically making signage with old Sanskrit.
Print, print.
They're making signage with their own old Sanskrit, and then they're bringing the passages that they chose, they choose from the King James, and putting it into, they're like measuring it up and incorporating it into one.
And they're teaching it like this.
And I was in a class with this woman, and she had her master's degree.
And I was in a room, and I was the only male in the room.
It was all females.
And it had this Sunday school type vibe to it.
And I started asking questions, you know.
And I was asking a lot of questions.
And it wasn't the presenter who was looking at me bad.
Everybody else in the room started to look at me.
And it went from a positive vibe, and almost instantaneously, everyone looked at me with hatred, because they thought I was offending the speaker.
When I was just asking questions, and the speaker wasn't offended, but since yoga, it was practicing yoga, is very subjective.
And subjective is feelings, and objectivity, you don't really have feelings.
And so I got, my feelings were like, well, I'm feeling all these emotions.
And I just had to leave the room.
But it was very, an interesting experience with all these people.
I just wanted to share that.
Well, thank you.
Yeah, there's a spirit behind that.
And right now, and has been for a while, and will be, these lower level spirits that are involved in all the world's religions are really having a hard time.
There's even a book that says something like, woe to the inhabitants of the earth, for, you know, the adversary has come down with great wrath.
And, you know, so that means these lower minions also are having a hard time with what's coming.
And by the way, I've said this before, I'll say it again, these lower level entities or spirits are just as ignorant as humans in many cases, even though they are in the realm of the gods.
Yes, and then capturing these lower level entities, would it be just a form of getting carbon and making it into carbon?
So you capture the carbon, or no?
No, I wouldn't.
It's not chemical.
They're smarter than that.
Yeah, I'm sure there are some of them that are susceptible.
Are you familiar with what's called an old Assyrian or Sumerian demon catcher?
What you did back then in their homes, what they would do is they had a terracotta bowl and there'd be writing on the inside of the bowl.
And the writing would go around and around the bowl, starting from the upper outer edge to the center in a spiral.
And it sometimes had a symbol in it.
And what you did is you put water in the bowl.
So if a demon came through the house, it would go to the bowl and be captivated by the writing.
You know, there's a whatever story they wanted to tell the demon, they would spiral into the bowl, into the water, and it would be held there so you could sleep peacefully, right?
So, you know, some of these people are dumb and primitive, but I'm telling you, they're not.
You know, have you ever heard of it?
Anybody want to look up a Sumerian or Assyrian demon trap bowl?
I don't even know if there's something like that online.
As a matter of fact, I'll go to the office right now and look it up.
But yeah, so when you brought up carbon, I'm not, you know, putting them in carbon.
I'm not totally discounting them.
Remember, it has to be discounting that chemical side or aspect of it.
But I'm telling you that there's a voluntary nature in the world, and you could also call forms of entrapment.
You know, marketing people, advertising people, politicians, religious leaders, they all use these techniques, because they're also used in the spiritual world, you know?
I mean, I've read somewhere that King David, as a young man, was playing an instrument to pretty much take up the time of a spirit that was sent to torment King Saul, for example, you know?
What, if the spirit is sleeping on the job, he's sent to torment someone, but he won't when the music is playing?
I mean, what's wrong with the guy, you know?
That's the OCD.
They're called incantation bowls, apparently.
Are they?
Okay.
Majority were written in Jewish Aramaic.
Right, Aramaic, which would be the language of the Assyrians also.
Incantation bowl, okay.
Yeah, there they are.
I just went to images.
There's quite a few of them.
So I'm going to have to look that one up.
Did you capture a mind parasite in that way, too?
Yeah, sure.
Well, they hang on to you, you know?
What do you call those little, they show it in cartoons often, where, you know, someone has to make a decision.
They have a devil on one side of their shoulder and an angel on the other.
You see it personified in cartoons.
Yeah, it doesn't mean that they're going to go away once you've made the decision.
I mean, we've read somewhere that I think one human being was able to house 5,000 of these guys.
This also regards the people that are most susceptible from the oppressive side and the victimization side and being oppressed and possession, which is very rare, are the ones that are ignorant of everything.
See, if you know exactly what's going on, they leave you alone and go usually and go for the next one that doesn't know.
It's kind of like the tax authorities are like that.
Usually when you hear people have problems with tax authorities, it's because they don't know any of the laws and they're dealing with the authorities that don't know any of the laws anyway.
And there's only one law for taxation.
It's very simple.
It's lawful money or private credit.
If you're always endorsing private credit, you're going to pay or you're going to jail.
So anyway, it's very simple.
It's the same thing with the gods.
Who do you have your allegiances to?
If you say Santa Claus or the Tooth Fairy, you're in trouble, potentially.
I'm not saying that your life won't be difficult if you have allegiances to the Most High, but at least you've cleared up anything and everything you can do, you see, in that respect.
Because Paul the king had allegiances to the Most High.
He just didn't behave, you know, he was tormented.
Yeah, that's helped about.
I just wanted to add in to another report.
Just applying.
I don't think this is called Greek speak.
I mean, this is just a separate chat, right?
Or no, are you labeling it Greek speak?
Yeah, it could be.
But this is the sonic event.
I think we're eventually going to just call it just speak because I'd like to see just this kind of speak in the world to counter the bullshit.
But go ahead.
So applying that, I just recommend everyone listening.
Get a spray bottle of alcohol, hydrogen peroxide, water, mix it in, and just start with your little square corner wherever you are and start from there and just work your way up and just keep building.
And get an etymology dictionary.
I found three old ones real fast.
And I found two random house college dictionaries.
One was printed in the 1969 and the other one was printed in 1993.
And when I was printed in 1993, Webster bought them out in the 80s.
And you can see the parallels that are different between those two dictionaries.
Like in the 1969 dictionary, the word kid, the third informal definition is a younger child or alike.
So the first two is a baby goat or a lambskin.
And then in the Webster dictionary in 1990s, they switched it.
So the informal is first and then the kids are going back down.
I thought that was interesting to share.
There's a bunch of different similarities in these dictionaries.
And I wonder if you've mentioned something about the after the World Trade Center event about all the dictionaries being.
Yes.
Ground zero.
Yeah, before 9-11, ground zero, 99% of the time was a very technical term referring to zero time and zero box.
Zero time is when the device is detonated.
Zero box is the device and ground zero is the location of where the device is detonated.
And by the way, when the term ground zero was used on 9-11, it was done by the technical people going to inspect the site from the NNSA, which is the National Nuclear Security Agency.
And you don't send out the National Nuclear Security Agency to investigate jet fuel incidents.
You know what I mean?
Right.
But yeah, what happened after that, there was an obfuscation, a public obfuscation of dictionaries.
And eBay within a year, by 2002, 2003, any time an eBay, a dictionary was put up on eBay at any price, it was purchased immediately.
And part of the joke was, let's just put up, let's go to the Salvation Army, get a dictionary for a dollar and put it up for $75 on eBay.
It got sold in eight hours.
Someone bought it for $75 just to start pulling dictionaries off the market.
And when they started putting them back on the market, they started changing the definition of the term ground zero.
Oh, very interesting.
So is that still happening then?
Like, can I still sell dictionaries for $75 on eBay?
Try.
Yeah, I would try.
There's something called apathy.
And what is it when the general public is really interested in something and then they're not?
There's a term, a psychological term for that.
But yeah, I would try it for sure.
If you're so inclined.
I don't do private credit, electronic banking or all that stuff, so I'm out of that loop.
Well, I was curious, I mean, about testing your theory for one, but also working...
Oh, it's not a theory.
This was going on pretty actively.
The FBI, by the way, in America, does have what's called a book confiscation list.
A book seizure, yeah.
Book seizure program, yeah.
Yeah, I found that very interesting.
And then, yeah, if you just go to yard sales and if you want an etymology dictionary, I'm just finding that more helpful than reading the King James version.
I don't plan on reading it.
I don't want to read it.
But yeah, so...
Yeah, that's OK.
Well, you know, the less stupid you become, the more stupid the people around you appear to be.
You're familiar with that concept, right?
Yes, and it takes a lot of energy just to deal with people, you know?
So I'm losing a lot of energy.
Pretty soon, you're going to have to cut some ties with people pretty soon.
Oh, you could be more efficient.
You don't have to cut ties or lose a lot of energy.
That's just to get more efficient at it.
Yeah, you become more objective.
And it's still kum-tsi kum-tsa to everybody else that drank the Kool-Aid.
Oh, yeah.
Doesn't mean I got to be a jerk.
No, no, you don't have to be a jerk.
Sometimes it's just all the, you know, the people.
People will get to you.
But you try not to.
But ultimately, if you start thinking, what can I do to help this individual?
Anything, you know, not, you know, without being imposing in that.
Just keep thinking that thought.
And all of a sudden, things, they pick up on that feeling.
And they get, the event becomes more streamlined.
To be of service.
Right, right.
To serve and being served, they're both of the same cloth.
Yeah, stewardship.
Got big fish to fry.
Big fish to fry.
Well, Rama, I'm just calling in just to say, hello, I'm driving right now on mobile.
Feel like I'm out in the field.
If each bit of information is, helps me out a long way.
And I thank you guys for keeping on there.
I know Sam sounds like he's getting a little agitated and frustrated.
But for me, it's just working out.
I'll try to call in more.
And I guess on the final note, I'm going to say is, for anyone who's listening, is when your parents tell you that they sacrificed everything for you, they have it twisted.
They sacrificed you so they can have everything.
And maybe that's just a little harsh on the parents, but it's okay.
That's the kid culture.
So maybe next week I'll call in and we can talk kid culture.
Sounds good.
I appreciate you calling in.
We appreciate the interest.
Okay.
All right, boys.
Have a good night.
All right.
Bye bye.
So there we go.
I think I know who that is, by the way, from chat.
I think someone a week ago put in some screenshots or shots of an etymology dictionary.
So yes, yes, that's right.
So where were we?
Or we were nowhere as usual.
Gods and body.
Yeah, I think we have Jason here.
Yes, yes.
I'm still there.
You were on a thought.
Do you want to?
We were just talking about the gods, everything being an extension of the gods.
Yes and no.
I think more specifics, you know.
You know, for example, if you hang around with car engineers or car designers, one of the, if you just had a few minutes with them about their philosophy, they always say the car should be an extension of your body, right?
Or a good hand tool should be as an extension of your body.
So there is validity in using those terms in that regard.
When a demon, you know, for example, they have something called the history channel on cable, which I once saw an episode.
They said God versus Satan.
Never going to happen.
You know, I mean, where are they getting?
Where are they getting the audience?
You know, if you, you know, what audience are they catering that nonsense to?
So then the gods, I mean, if they regard our bodies as their instruments, it seems that they would care for them more than we do.
Let's say that again.
So if the gods see our bodies as their instruments, then it seems as though they would care for our bodies more than we do.
They do tell you they only care about certain people to keep the plan going.
You see what I mean?
In other words, they have, you know, what's interesting when you study, for example, Abraham, a lot of promises and a lot of claims about things are to be done or made.
And do you know what Abraham had to do on his end?
Nothing.
You know, we're talking about after, you know, the revelation of he didn't have to sacrifice his son, right?
Mm hmm.
All these things were good that the gods, the Elohim said he was going to do for Abraham.
Did he say, as long as Abraham, you do this?
No, it was all on their side.
And then as it goes, as it continued, when we go to Moses, he presents basically a constitution of set of laws for a group of people or a nation to act as.
And he asked him, do you agree to this?
Basically, right?
You see, it was voluntary that then they agreed as well.
If you agree and you don't do it, then this will happen to you.
So when I say they don't care and all that, it's, again, based on agreements.
You know, how many times have you heard of these pagan cultures that prospered?
Have you ever heard of the Mayans and the Aztecs?
Well, actually, the Aztecs, actually, they both prospered.
I mean, they murdered thousands of people towards the middle and end of their kingdom.
They were doing, you know, if I told you they found, they estimate over four to five million headless bodies in Mexico and northern part of South America that still haven't been uncovered, would you believe me?
This is the level of carnage that they were doing on a social level, as a normal social gratuity.
And they prospered.
So where were the gods helping the people that were being sacrificed, you know?
Well, that doesn't mean they don't care, though, does it?
Because...
No, they do care about their plan.
And they do, you know, they do, you know, like the human body can last a thousand years.
The onset of aging and disease is, you know, something that is like switched on almost at a certain time.
Yeah.
There's no reason why the body can't keep reproducing and be, have the vigor and health between 20 and 40 years old for another, you know, thousand years or so.
There's no reason for it.
You know, so it's been switched off to limit...
Yeah, there's no simple answer.
But what I'd like to state is, you know, let's start examining what's going on, what has gone on, and what's been memorialized about these things.
And can we approach them rationally?
Can we meditate on these things from a rational perspective?
You know what I mean by meditate?
Just keep thinking, you know, like over and over and over.
And I would suggest, from a personal note, what I've come down to, once you are cognizant that anything and everything you consider law and morality comes from a god, and you have to, you know, go into it consciously or, quote-unquote, unconsciously, where you don't care, just do what everyone else does, but consciously you have to pick a god.
And when they tell you, well, the law is based on justice, what do you know about justice?
Nothing.
Well, that's a problem, you see.
So, once you start figuring out which god, and you are going to get...
you're going to at least personify whether you have an allegiance to or decide cognizantly and consciously to be aware of that.
Other than that, it's food, clothing, and shelter.
And discovering how to optimize, you know, who you are.
And you can't optimize yourself without optimizing people around you.
You can't, by the way.
You know, this is a fact in even musicians.
Musicians, they have this concept called jamming, right?
They want to go play with other good musicians.
They don't want to just go, you know, make...
Oh, I need to make a living, so I'm going to do piano lessons with nine and ten-year-olds.
You know, eventually that's all you're going to be able to do.
You need to jam with people that are as good or better than you are.
So, you know, how is that going to happen if they're not in a better state, you see?
You see, it's...
This is also on a community level, you know.
All the communities are...
make a better community by, you know, the...
Oops, he dropped.
Yep, I think he dropped.
Oh, did I still drop?
Yep, there you are.
Okay.
I just walked over by...
Maybe a lot of metal over here reflected on wireless.
Even on a community level, the way you do it is by having, you know, if there's...
Whatever number of people are in the community, if each one takes responsibility for what they can, then the whole community goes through an improvement.
Yeah, that's a tricky thing to gauge, like how involved to be in a community, like we talked about this last time.
Hypothetical, hypothetical.
This community is fucked.
Yeah, with a larger culture.
So, you take a position of living apart and separating yourself from others as much as possible, but you also talk about helping others and, you know, optimizing your relationships with others.
So, it could appear to be contradictory, but they're not necessarily right.
Find that golden mean or what have you, that balance.
And, yeah, I'm faced with a problem of that kind right now, actually, in my community, which is about 5,000 people.
And there's just something going on locally around that, you know, the whole transgender madness.
And there's a particular movement that's trying to...
You probably won't know about it because it's Canadian, but you'll know about the general principles of it.
It's trying to implement ideological agendas in the schools, even the kindergartens, to educate children, you know, into the...
It's a saving the states.
Yeah, fluidity.
Except it's worse in Canada, because Canada's just a care ahead of the curve, so to speak.
Yeah, that was planned more than 50 years ago, by the way, with great munition and detail, how they were going to do it.
So, go ahead.
Yeah, I believe it.
So, and that's something I've researched and written about.
And as far as using the internet as a platform to work through those ideas and talk about people, that's fine.
You know, I don't consider activism, but I just consider exploration as a human predicament.
But now it's actually come to the town that I live in, and I'm becoming aware that people are...
Well, you know, they're struggling with this.
And anyone who questions it is being called a homophobe and a fascist and all that.
It starts getting, you know, personal.
And then I have to make a decision, it feels like I have to make a decision about how involved to get, particularly as I have a newsletter.
All right, let me stop you for a moment and tell you how I deal with that.
If I'm surrounded by those that are for it, let's just say, you know, there's the apathetic, let's say there's the for and the against, OK?
I let them know very politely, and the way that they can hear it, I have to structure, I have to analyze how I'm going to say this, but this is what I generally say, is that the people that are public about this now, they're being...
information is being gathered about them, and identities are being taken, and you're being put on a database.
OK, now, for the people that are against it and find it to be abominable, I say to them the same thing.
I say the people that are doing this, their identities are being taken, and they're being put in a database.
I say the same thing to both sides.
You know why?
Do you get my point?
Yeah.
It's like, the good news is you've got 14 years left, the bad news is you've got 14 years left.
It's the same, you know...
It's the same metaphor.
Yeah, now, sometimes people say, how do you know that, Greek?
And I'm like, how can you not not know that?
Right?
You see?
Yeah.
How can you not not know that?
What do you mean, how do you know they're being put on a list?
Oh, boy.
You know?
Come on.
Yeah.
And there's probably no way of being on that list, you know, collectively.
But being on a local list is a lot more immediately problematic, right?
Especially running a local business and whatnot.
Like, you don't necessarily want to make local enemies, right?
There's the humor that one can perceive.
I tend to stay rather happy about it and just say, you know, that's very entertaining to see.
Multi-colored, hand-in-hand, whatever, you know, tattooed or spiked or whatever.
Oh, that's interesting.
And nothing more really needs to be said, you know?
I can say it to myself.
And you see all kinds, you know?
And I'm sure it's just as bad up there.
Well, here's the thing, Jason.
It may not have helped you from what I just said.
I say the same thing to both sides.
But if you think about it for a little while, another thing might emerge.
In other words, my intention of saying the same thing to both sides, those that are for it, I tell them they're being put on a list.
And those that are against it, I tell them they're being put on a list.
It satisfies them both from however they can hear it.
Obviously, the ones that don't like them like the idea more, right?
That they're being put on a list means like, you know, the right thing will be done in the future, which I don't think is going to be done.
The right thing will be done either then.
But once you take the stance that there is something that's going on that's beyond what you see right now, then you can be more creative on how to deal with them.
In other words, it's a bigger thing.
It's not just they're promoting education of transgender or homosexuality.
There's something even bigger agenda behind that.
And that's where the creativity of how to deal with it really comes from.
Again, there's a lot of these patriot types.
Like, show me the law that the government can tax your income.
And if you go to the government, they say, we don't need a law.
Right?
Well, then what law?
Then my question was, what law is the government using that tells them that they don't need a law?
You see?
And it took me a while, a minute, and I found it.
And then I just went and used that.
And now I don't have to deal with what these patriot assholes deal with.
So in other words, there's education.
Well, we know from a human side, evidence is, if you go on YouTube, there's a video or YouTube, I think, Bruce, it's called The New Order of Barbarians.
Yes.
Dr. Dan.
Fascinating.
Yes.
Dr. Dan.
He was at a lecture.
Yeah, 1960, he was at a lecture, and he gives all the notes.
And, you know, about promote the agendas that you see.
They're actually behind schedule.
They're about 15, 20 years behind schedule.
That's why they seem to be pushing it so hard.
Yeah.
So if you start seeing that there's the human socialist side to it, and it's hidden, then the answer, perhaps, to counter it is going to be hidden as well.
You see?
Right.
That's something I have no immediate response to.
And maybe it's something that an immediate response to that, quote, unquote, agenda, because that's what it is.
It's not, you know, strictly a social agenda that's being put on the people.
That might be something that's worth just covering.
You know, it could be something as simple as what MGM, Goldenmeier, the old filmmaker in the 20s, you know, when they brought up psychotherapy, he says, oh, anyone who wants to see a psychiatrist should have their head examined, right?
Right.
Yes.
Something that's important, something that just kind of turns the brain inside out.
Hmm.
Well, what has occurred to me with this, and just in terms of a really practical approach, as a writer, journalist, whatever, is that it's reached such a stage that it's possible, not just theoretically, but I think practically possible, to just present the facts around it in an entirely neutral way, and they will be shocking.
Oh, yeah.
Let us know.
First sides.
So, let us know where the neutral point is, the point of inertia.
Well, where is that, you see?
Is it political?
Is it religious?
Is it biological?
Is it scientific?
Is it cultural?
What is it, you see?
Is it all of that, politically, being neutral?
What do you mean exactly by the point of inertia, then, here?
Inertia is where no movement takes place.
In other words, if you're neutral, and I'm talking about apathy, because the neutrality still admits something is going on.
Apathy negates it, let's say, right?
There's no necessity with apathy, where with neutrality there still is necessity.
I think, for me, the neutral point is that what I really object to is the loss of objectivity.
Well, yeah.
And that's kind of neutral, in a way, even though I feel strongly about it.
It's not specifically referring to transgender, or political correctness, or homosexuality, or any of these buzz topics that people get so upset about.
It's about the distortion of reality around those topics.
That is the neutral thing.
What's a fact, and what isn't a fact?
That's the whole point, right?
It's about facts.
They're supposedly objective, and you can only recognize them.
And you can't have feelings about facts.
I mean, you can, but it doesn't change the fact.
Well, here's something that's slightly parallel.
Back in the 80s, they had something called the ADA, Americans with Disabilities Act.
And if you had a building, a small business of X amount of employees, or whatever, you had to build a handicap access.
And a lot of businesses could not afford a $50,000 for a handicapped bathroom and a ramp, you see.
Yeah, you see.
And even though they never had anyone with a disability coming into the business, some of the businesses were not even open to the public, you see.
And the argument was, well, what if you have an employee?
You know, then it's equal.
And that kind of fizzled away.
It was a big deal.
I don't know if you remember that, Bruce, in the 80s, the late 80s.
Oh, yeah.
It was a big deal.
Now, a lot of people that were selling handicap accessible fixtures, and you were very happy about that, because they got into business.
So, I don't know, who's getting into business now with all this stuff?
So, that's why I'm suggesting it's more of a spiritual, it's the revived goddess religion.
If I were to do a quick template, and I'll just speak, you know, I haven't put much thought into it.
I always say, well, what do you know about the ancient goddess religion, and the revival of the ancient goddess religion?
Unfortunately, through history, the only way you countered a religion was not getting rid of the god, but getting rid of its adherents.
But here, in this case, you have more ticks than you have dog, you see, if it's on a social level, right?
So, yeah, it is an interesting thing.
I think studying the ancient goddess religion, I mean, unfortunately, you know, actually, this is not unfortunate.
I'll just say this.
You know, if you go to San Francisco, there is a major library by the Federal Reserve Building.
It's the major library for the, remember we were there in San Francisco?
The Freemasonic Library.
It's a huge library, and I mean, probably millions of books in there.
And it would behoove anyone to go there and just look at the books.
And you know, none of the curators and the people in there know about what's in their shelves.
I know, I'm not saying this facetiously or sarcastically.
They don't know what's there.
You can go to the San Francisco Freemason Library, and spend a couple of days there, and find books on the subject that I'm discussing right now, the revived goddess religion, and the rituals, and all that other stuff.
And if you walk in, by the way, and ask any of the people, do you have any books on the revived goddess religion, I don't know what you're talking about.
But if they're right there, I mean, you could see them.
You know what I mean?
So what do you know?
That's why I was recently speaking to someone again, and what do you know about the goddess religion?
Nothing.
Yeah, thanks.
Most people don't.
And I had, in previous sonic events, I'll say it again.
If I were to distill it down, just like I do the birthdays, dolls, and cannibals, and all that stuff, you know, you're not going to find that in one place.
But if I were to break down the goddess religion, she teaches that the goal of mankind is to create a god-like state for mankind.
And mankind will achieve that by not focusing on the differences of the sexes.
In other words, every human being will be both male and female, or neither.
Sex, sexuality, polarity, that is a problem.
And the way mankind will achieve that is by promoting male with male unions, and the males become infertile, and female with female unions, and the females can retain fertility, and the human race is now procreated without male and female union.
That's the goddess religion in a nutshell.
And I just gave you, you know, when I discussed, I brought, there was a furniture I bought once I was high in leather couches a while back, and there was a old guy with a pretty proud Freemason belt buckle and ring.
I brought this up to him, he nearly, he just wanted to kill me.
He's like, basically, he was in the order Scottish Rite, which is not Freemasonry, for 30 or 40 years before they even gave him access to the revived goddess religion.
He's like, how dare I even speak it in public?
And how do you find it?
Just look in your book.
It's just like when you deal with the people in the legal society.
It's like, well, where'd you get all that information?
Right here in your own book.
You know?
So, would you say it's more men that are practicing and implementing the goddess religion?
Well, you know what the interesting, that's a good point, because there's a lot of talk about the goddess in you and all that, and we have a patriarchal society.
No, if you look at it accurately, what's happening is you have the goddess and you have the priesthood, and the priesthood tends to be the liturgy is done by men.
So, in essence, the irony here is you have a goddess religion, and the priesthood happens to be male.
Majority.
That's where they get the patriarchal society, because, I don't know, from reading scripture, I see that the woman is the head economist.
Ficol meaning house, and nomos meaning law.
She runs a lot.
There was actually one, Israel had a female queen for a short time in reign, admitted so.
There was also a female judge, and female prophets in the bible, you see.
And they were held in high regard.
So, I don't see any oppression in scripture, and I see a lot of the stuff that they discuss about castle doctrine, you know, where the man is this and that.
I don't see that in scripture, you know.
Hmm.
I don't see it.
It's in the Christian tradition.
The Muslims are the worst.
There's nothing that dictates head clothing and scripture in the Quran.
I believe there's just a place that says, if a woman is married, she should cover her vagina.
Well, that's really radical, isn't it?
You know?
And this is one of the things that's most manifest with the trans movement, that it's men displacing women, essentially.
Well, yeah.
Well, you'll take the physically more robust of the group, to control the less physically robust.
Because, basically, it comes down to who can crack whose head, right?
Basically, you know, the caveman mentality, let's say.
So, if you were to inspire a group of people to change society in an oppressive fashion, you want to inspire the men.
Because they tend to be physically stronger, and happen to be in more control of things that are more destructive.
So, it's more obvious.
Yeah, so...
You know, to catch a thief, you must think like a thief.
So, not always, but...
And trans activists are quite notoriously violent.
And I suppose a trans woman, as in a man who's surgically altered to be a woman, or even now, because you don't have to have the surgery, you can just self-identify as a woman, they'd still be physically stronger.
They'd still have the physical strength in their arms and whatnot, I presume.
Yes, I would think so, yeah.
This is where two ideologies are colliding, it's where there's kind of this opening for creating a cognitive dissonance in those who've been ideologically railroaded, you know, into the latest, whatever, obligatory position, because...
Which we've come in upset.
Well, that is to say, they're the same people who are so mad about feminism, and are all about women's rights, which is still bubbling away with the Me Too movement.
But when you actually start to look at the transgender movement, it's women who are mostly objecting to it, because they're becoming aware that it's actually the same old oppression has taken a new guise now, in the form of transgender.
No, I kind of do agree.
Because men are defining what it is to be a woman.
Men are now defining what it is to be a woman.
They say, like, Bruce Jenner was a woman of the year, but you can't get more encapsulated than that.
Well, that would be the media's approach to it, wouldn't it?
You know, could it all boil down to extreme stupidity?
Yep, I agree.
I don't know, we'd have to say insanity.
If you're going to put a...
Yeah, unsane.
You're going to have to diagnose it, I think.
Yeah, unsane, because you think insane, they have a different DMG, whatever the set of rules.
But unsane, in other words, yeah.
But when it's engineered insanity, then you can't really boil it down, no?
Well, you know, it's even more insane.
What's more insane is you need money, let's say, what they call a means of exchange in commerce to buy the makeup.
If you, let's say you're a man, you want to be a woman, you need money.
How are you going to convert all that clothes into female clothes, woman's clothes, and buy all the makeup?
And they don't even know that there's no money.
They don't even know how the money system works.
You know, they don't even know how their own body works.
You know, they don't know anything about anything, and they're doing this.
So, I think it's a spinoff of one of the symptoms of extreme censorship and stupidity.
But its source, of course, is...
Oh, that rhymes.
Its source, of course, of course, is the goddess religion.
Well, I mean, it intensifies the state dependency, because if you're transgender, you become completely dependent on the state for the surgery, for the drugs, for the protection, all the rest of that.
Sure, and the state gets all of that, let's say, quote-unquote financial from your own exemption that was given to you when you were born.
So, again, it goes down to the...
And I assure you, the state is no longer the state.
It's run by the law merchants, which are the attorney class.
When I say attorneys, I mean, there's very, very many types.
Like when you say engineer, like what kind of engineer?
If they discover that there is no, quote-unquote, personal benefit for their class in doing this, they will withdraw.
They won't offer the surgeries and all this other stuff.
Don't think for a minute that taxes pay for anything, right?
The purpose of taxation...
I'm not protesting taxation, because they...
You know, how can you protest anything stupid people fall for?
But the purpose of taxation is to create engineer's scarcity.
You know, if someone has their full paycheck every week, that equates to a full time every week.
So, if you start whittling away their resources to do exchange, it's the same as taking their time away.
Now they have to spend more time making something that they're going to lose.
It's like having a bucket with a hole in it.
The bigger you make the hole, the more frequent trips you have to make, you see.
It's a society that's engineered to be wasteful, inefficient, and destructive for a very, very long time.
And I just see this as just another aspect of it.
And to suck you out of time.
Yeah, what we actually need is an alien species that are serial rapists to come down and grab all these trans...
Man, never mind.
Yeah.
Yeah, to come...
In other words, isn't it sound like you need some outside help?
Because if you go here or there, you see, it's the state will back them up on one side.
The people will back them up on the other.
There's no...
Yeah, in other words, basically, it's a knife fight.
And you want to go with another knife.
It's just going to make it worse.
When you have a knife fight, you need someone to show up with a machine gun.
See, that's the peacemaker.
Everyone drops their knives.
But if another person shows up, you have to have ordinance that is so beyond their avail and so beyond their ability that they stop.
And the only way that's going to be done now is with the gods.
Because you can't do it with words.
You're not going to be able to do it with force.
Why?
Because they even incorporated this into the military, right?
So...
So, yeah, it's just food, clothing, shelter.
Ignore them if you have to put up with them.
In other words, if you're a public figure like doing retail or have to work with the public for most of your waking hours for your own, you know, gainful employment or whatever, gainful work, you're going to have to devise a strategy, obviously, right?
And that's important.
It's actually quite important, actually, to devise a strategy to deal with them if you spend quite a few of your waking hours or you have to deal with the public that is, you know, public at large that is engulfed in this manner.
Mm-hmm.
Because if you're quiet, if you do it the right way, it's very passive.
But once you're known to be against it, they could make your life difficult as well, just because that's what they do.
They're very spiteful as well, you know what I mean?
Yeah, it seems to be a matter of just sending out just enough of a signal that the people who are going to be drawn to it and benefit from, you know, the relief of being able to speak their own minds...
Right, but they have no minds, yeah.
They have nothing in their mind to speak of, you know.
No, I'm talking about the conversations that we're having here, like just we've brought something to the table, right?
So, like everybody has something, however small, and some people have a little bit more, but you only find out what people have if you create a space where they can actually feel safe enough to express it, like you're talking about optimizing other people's performances, that's what I mean.
So, it's just a good message to others that they can actually express themselves, however, you know, however paltry that expression is, at least they don't have to be afraid to express it.
They're not going to be condemned, but that seems to be what would motivate me more, it's not like I plan to try and change the direction of social engineering, even if I didn't believe it was all coming crashing to an end.
I'm not an idiot in that regard anyway, but I do want to nurture the relations in the community that are worth nurturing.
Right, and I think with objectifying, for example, to do social commentary, it's always the opposite, right?
When they tell you peace, that means war is coming.
When they tell you economic prosperity, it means they're going to rob you.
When they tell you environmental, it means they're going to pollute, you see?
So, what's coming is a balancing and a new convention and a new model,
new way of doing things in the next decade,
and it's going to settle in and there's going to be fruit from it,
order, peace, prosperity to a certain degree,
and people, then it'll be promoted as lasting a thousand years
and everyone's going to buy into it,
and when that sentiment settles in and everyone's quite happy,
even though there's a lot of real nasty shit still going on,
that means you've got less than three or four years left,
you know, where it physically starts to manifest.
So, do you think that the transgender and the post-gender and transhumanism is part of that?
Yes.
No, it's a setup, just like the tattoos and other things, because one-third of mankind is wiped out by mankind, of men themselves, for social reasons.
What I mean is, do you think that the ideology that's being implemented in this period that you're predicting is going to be congruent with the one that's predominant now, with the transgender?
It's not.
No, no, the transgenders and the homos and all that stuff, and other people will be dealt with before that comes in.
Okay.
They're going to be dealt with very harshly, in other words, like, you won't be breathing harshly, kind of, you know what I mean?
So then, that would imply that the whole transgender madness is a way to foment polarization...
Yes.
...thoroughly towards these groups that are around us.
What's coming in the future, the destruction of people who have marked skin and polars, transgender and homo, the destruction of that element of society on a worldwide level is going to be one of the things that's going to be shown as, see, this is what...
we have to do this in order to get to the next level, and everyone will agree.
Meaning that...
and that we're talking about a third of the people are going to be destroyed this way.
So, do you want to do the math?
Two, three billion people?
Two and a half billion?
There's more than a billion people with tattoos, at least.
Yeah.
I can't even see anybody without a tattoo these days.
I was going to say that, too.
And so, is this the reason why tattoos are serious business, or is there a deeper...
Yes.
No, I wrote about this back 14, 15 years ago.
I said, we're going to watch an increase in tattoos, and even to the point where, you know, grandmas will have full-body tattoos.
And I sent this, you know, two years later, someone came to visit, and we walked around the corner, and we were talking about the email, and there was a 75-year-old with a full-body tattoo.
He looked at me, and he said, this is just crazy.
This is exactly what you wrote about in the email.
And I said, yeah.
And at the time, it wasn't like it was now.
Obviously, I remember in the 90s, people were still getting tattoos, but not like it is now.
Do you want me to tell you why I got my tattoos?
No.
It's a pretty interesting story.
There's a spirit behind it, but go ahead.
Yeah, there was a spirit behind it.
It was during this period in my life, I've podcasted a lot about it, and written about it, where I became convinced, partly due to too many psychedelics, but not only that.
I became convinced that Lucifer was trying to incarnate through me, that I was supposed to be an avatar of Lucifer.
And I did all these various things, shaving my head and whatnot.
And I decided to get tattoos in order to brand myself, like this body is property of Lucifer.
So it was meant to be this kind of ritual of surrender, because I saw Lucifer as a benign thing.
Anyway, I saw it as benign.
It wasn't like I was a satanist or anything.
But most of the people on the planet die by that.
Sort of momentarily.
Yeah, but possession is where you don't have any...
If someone was possessed for a month, for example, and you freed them from that possession, they would not recall anything.
Okay.
It is your oppressor.
Just the sense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But when you say satanist, this is this...
If you were to fly in a galactic starship and go by the Earth, and if you point that this is where satan's children live, point it to the Earth, that's very accurate.
Because he's the father of this world, meaning man's society.
This is his world.
I'm not talking about the bees, and the elephants, and the whales, and the ticks, and the bacteria, and the grass, and the trees, and mountains.
I'm talking about the human society, the cultures.
All of the cultures are his.
All of the religions, all of the Christian denominations are satanic, 100%.
All of the Hindu, all of the Blues, all of it.
Now, what's in their scripture is not satanic, or might mention Satan, but the culture itself is satanic, for sure.
Adversarial.
You know, and you could do, you know, look at the legal profession, the medical profession, the architects, you know, the engineers, the, you know, every aspect that's, you know...
Yeah, so we're all stamped by that, whether we've got lips or tattoos or not.
Yeah, you're satan's children, basically, on this planet.
You see, that's, for, this was a normal thing, you see.
Sorry to interrupt, but why is it you and not we, Greg?
Oh, no, because I'm speaking from a third party.
You know, the Greek, we have the...
I learned how to do the third party thing from reading scripture, by the way, and other ancient writs.
But the thing is, where you get your law, your manner of law, your morality, you call your father.
That's why, for example, in the Catholic convention, the priest is called father, because unlike today, back in the day, the church was very overbearing.
You know, they were into your life very much about everything.
So, you have your biological parents, and then you have your spiritual parents, those are the ones that rear the mind and rear your morality and your law, and that is your spiritual father.
So, when you look at all the base root of all culture of mankind, the base root, the father of that is the adversary, right?
It's very clear and simple.
But when I say that, it's not the Hollywood type.
And the thing that really, it doesn't rub me the wrong way, but it just makes me want to say, what a pack of morons is the people that cry like Satanists, you know, for the avid anti-Satanists online.
You know, they're like, oh, this Temple of Set, or this other group, or they're Satanists.
No, they're not.
They tell you what they are.
The Temple of Set is reviving the ancient god of Set.
It's not Satan.
Set is not Satan.
Sorry.
He is a dark underworld prince of that particular region.
You know, this other group will revive another one.
That is not Satan.
Those are balls, or, you know, the Christians have revived Molech.
You know, you see the red creature with the child on the lap, right?
Make a wish of prosperity.
Do you think they just burn children just to burn children?
No, the ritual was to sacrifice the children while you made a wish of prosperity.
In other words, you know, for some kind of gain.
Whether it was, whatever, the interest of the individual.
That's why they ask to tell them what you want, you see.
It's a descriptive term, though, like an accuser or an adversary.
Yeah, if you say ugly, he says pretty.
If you say disease, he says healthy.
If you say black, he says white.
If you say healthy, he says disease.
Look at the doctors.
What are they?
The number one, well, the number two killer cause of death is medical malpractice.
And if you look at the number one cause of death, I don't know what it is.
Heart disease or whatever.
That's, again, you know, a spin-off of that.
So, look at the, you know, all the religions.
You know, I was really upset that I was so true about this a few months ago, when I watched something about the Dalai Lama.
The history of him and what he said and all that.
And the guy's a total moron.
He doesn't know anything.
And how can the leader of a people say that and be so misdirected?
I'm surprised you're upset by that.
I thought it would just confirm your...
No, no, I was upset that it was confirming.
Because, you know, you always want to employ some doubt.
You say, well, maybe it's correct enough to say that this is the way it is, but maybe there'll be an exception.
And you see, and then when you see that there is no exception, maybe, you know, you start saying to yourself, maybe I should be more emphatical about it.
You know, but...
Well, you know, not in public figures who are widely influential.
I think it's probably fair to say there's no exceptions.
But...
Yeah, of course.
That doesn't mean there are no exceptions anywhere.
There are exceptions, yeah, of course.
Otherwise, there would be no balance.
You know, the largest theoretical mathematical equations, you've seen some of them fill up a blackboard.
There's just...
to solve it, it's just a very small...
The solution is usually a very compact one, isn't it?
So...
Well, I could go on asking questions.
I'm not sure if we should talk more about Satan and the adversary and all that.
What do you think?
No, well, you could, and you could...
If you want to know about Satan and the adversary, look around you.
Look at a cereal box.
Look at what they're doing in religions.
Look at TV.
Look at...
Yeah?
Yeah, in a sense, it's just more redundancy, because everything around you is influenced that way.
And I think the point that I must always stress is the Satanism within the Satanism, which is the way Satanism is being portrayed, is Satanic, because when you say that, most people think, oh, it's child sacrifice.
Oh, it's the red creature with scales and a bifurcated tongue and a pointy tail and a pitchfork and the Hollywood thing.
That's the Satanic part about Satanism, is they got even...
When you discuss Satanism, it's Satanic, again, because it spins people's minds off into something that's not true, again.
So, yeah.
Yeah, that would be the squirrel page.
The dummy load.
The pranking.
I do have a question, then.
If Justitia is the deity that the institutions of the world are most worshipping or enthralled to, then how does that square with this being Satan's dominion or what have you?
I guess I can't speak to that.
No, there is none, because when I say it's Satan's dominion, it's, again, it's the least...
He's a well-known entity, right, on the other side.
And we're being told through Scripture that there are other entities that have different purposes.
You know, some rule the nations.
You know, when you look at maps and borders changing, it's not just man squirting ink on paper and making treaties.
There is an entity behind that.
When one country loses a war to another, that war, the entity that lost, has to lose on the spiritual side first.
You know, you have some that are very...
Right, so then you have many, many aspects.
The question and the mystery that I would suggest, that's still here and is a question that I would, is how do they relate to Satan?
How does the goddess religion relate to Satan?
Does it really change anything for me, you see?
Would there be a tool?
Sure.
And how do the principalities, like in the book of Daniel, the prince of Persia is a real tough one, right?
How does he relate to Satan?
You see, how do they...
I mean, do they all go to the same bar?
You know, do they all shop at the same grocery store?
I mean, you know, this is a pun, you know.
I mean, what are they, you know, what are they doing with each other?
Do they ignore, you know, is Satan up in some tower, and, you know, they have messengers go back and forth, or do they rub elbows, or...
You see, the curious minds want to know, right?
You see?
I mean, if I had access to know that, sure, I wouldn't turn it down, right?
But are we given that kind of detail?
No.
And do I have a right and license to make that up?
I don't have a right to make up what's going on in that respect, in the dynamics of the relationship, or lack thereof.
I don't have the right to make that up.
Well, there are correlations between the Lucifer archetype and the Goddess archetype.
There's quite a few, and Venus being the oldest one.
There are ways in which the Satanic archetype can be seen or identified as feminine or female.
Sure.
And there's many ways to even say that.
There was a film that said the first lies Satan procured is that he doesn't exist.
So maybe when they procure a female, it's really a male showing that he's a woman.
Is it so far-fetched that some men want to be like women?
We were just talking about that.
And maybe vice versa.
I mean, I've heard a lot of testimony and read testimony about the New World Order types, the people underground, the occult rituals.
When they do abuses, especially when it's an adult, it's almost mandatory to do the sex change on them.
If it's a man, dress them like a woman to abuse them.
And if it's a woman, dress them like a man to abuse them.
You know, adults, right?
And that always struck me as being Satanic, meaning do the opposite, you see.
Inversion principle.
And there's mater and mater, you know, mother, mother matter.
Right.
That's pretty spot on in the Latin cognate.
So it's like the hidden matriarchy is the ascension of matter, like the immersion of the principles of spirit and matter.
Yeah.
And still it would be researched, but in scripture, we have a father and the mother is not an anthropomorphic thing.
It's a place.
So that's an interesting thing from any cognitive thing to wrap your mind around.
Because when you think mother and father, you think of something you can relate to.
But in scripture, it turns out that the only thing we can relate to is the father and the mother is not an anthropomorphic thing, which is very interesting.
So in what sense is the mother a place in scripture?
It's a place, yes.
And that's something that is outside of the realm of the operating system or the program to contemplate.
So it just doesn't make sense.
What word are you referring to?
The New Jerusalem is our mother.
Yeah, the mothership, in other words, no pun intended.
And that's something that is cognitively very difficult to contemplate.
And I leave it alone.
I was going to say humanity, the idea of humanity as the bride of Christ, that also makes humanity as a female.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
That's another thing that's hard to contemplate because humans have both male and female, let's say, right?
So how can we just lump everyone, male and female, into female again?
Again, the goddess teachings of the goddess religion and the blurring of the lines is the corruption of this, these concepts that are very cognitively difficult to handle.
Well, they're defined clearly in the writ, but it's distorted by the adversary and whatever he uses as a tool.
Right.
Now, of course, if you go, if you were to do a study on the bride of Christ being or humanity as the bride is a woman, it goes into the same various things that he's the son of God.
The reason he's the son of God is because he comes in full authority.
So again, the bride of Christ is given in human terms, right?
Like a son will always trump the authority of an appointed leader, you see?
And like a prince at 13 years old will trump the authority of a regent who's been with the king for 50 years, who's in his 70s.
The prince will trump him, you see?
Now, the bride is a covenant of fidelity, right?
A bride is a bride when she has fidelity.
When there's no fidelity, she goes into the realm of the adulteress, right?
You see?
And that metaphor is given as well.
So, these are metaphors on a human perspective, a human cultural perspective.
And here's the other interesting thing that I've discussed in the past.
Once you throw away the concept of the inheritance and the position of a son or the fidelity of a woman and all this as a wife and culture, then you, once you abandon those concepts, then you cannot understand scripture at all, you see?
Can you say more about that?
Well, if the metaphor of the son and the wife is a metaphor that is denoting metaphorically a structure that's held up or upheld in culture, a wife is defined by being a woman who has fidelity to her spouse, and a son is defined by someone who has the most authority regardless of the others.
Once the concept of the son having authority and the wife having fidelity goes away in a society, that society can no longer comprehend scripture with those terms.
Right, so it's like a negative feedback loop.
If our culture isn't lawful and observant of scripture, then we're less and less able to understand scripture.
Of course.
The mindset is, especially when you're sending something through time, you know, like I said, you can't use various calendrical systems if they change, so you need something that doesn't change, which is the sun and the moon and the stars for time.
If you have the concept of a son and a wife, you know, that doesn't change, and even though it might change on a large level, I think there are still enough people in the culture to understand what a son really means, or a father means in terms of authority and importance, and what a wife means in terms of authority and importance, again, to understand scripture.
But as a group, they will lose that ability, which is obvious.
But, you know, for a while back, people were hammering me on the book of Daniel, there's going to be a great apostasy or falling away, and it's happening.
I said, no, because the human society has not been there to fall away from it.
So that falling away is going to be in rapid succession, that when they do achieve a certain comprehension, which is all still in the future.
So when people read about the great apostasy, the falling away, they say to the church and all that, I'm saying, no, they've never really had it to fall away.
How can you fall away from something you've never had?
So there's something coming in the future which is going to coalesce or form a knowledge that is true about the gods, and then the people will fall away from that, you see.
Because right now, there's not enough knowledge of the gods in order for any of the things to take place in scripture that you're reading about.
Hmm.
I mean, there's still, take, for example, the center of the world near Jerusalem, and it's Israel, like they call it there, the land of Israel, right?
It has nothing to do with social political consciousness, the location on the earth.
Look at what's going on over there.
Very little of that resembles anything scripturally accurate, other than the establishment of Israel as a de facto nation versus Palestine.
If you read things that were prior to 1920 or 1930, that area is never referred to as Israel, it's always referred to as Palestine.
But guess what?
Now it's referred to as what?
Israel.
So, other than that, there's very little change.
And of course, there's a lot of prophetic things, undercurrents going on, like I've just discussed the repeat of the book of Judges, a judge is a prime minister, and various things like that, timekeeping.
So, that's why I keep saying this seven-year period that started in the springtime, watch it very closely.
A three-and-a-half-year mark from now, or three-year mark from now, you'll have more things in place prophetically than have ever been put in place before.
Have you paid any attention to Jordan Peterson today?
No.
Who is that?
I kind of envy you.
Yeah, innocence there.
Jordan Peterson is this very culturally influential figure now, suddenly.
It started around spring of this year.
I mean, it really peaked with his book, Twelve Rules to Live By, or whatever.
But he came to prominence over the transgender issue, because he was a University of Toronto professor who refused to use the transgender pronouns if he was going to be legally obliged to use them, and this caused this huge controversy.
And he went from being this university professor to having a huge YouTube following to, in this year with his book, becoming this massively famous public figure.
And one of the things he's been doing in the interim, that's why I bring him up, is he's been doing the psychology of the Bible lectures.
So, he's been going through the Old Testament and interpreting it, Jungian psychology and apostasy, and you would love it.
It would fulfill your prophecy there, in terms of what you've talked about, this growing interest in scripture that's going to be all wrong, I suppose.
Yeah, you'll be looking in that direction, but it'll be a thought.
It'll be like a jigsaw puzzle where you just open the box.
There's no picture.
You have some picture on the outside, but nothing on the inside yet.
I would say that's a pretty good description, Peter, from you, at least in terms of his religious endeavor, anyway, the rest of it.
Yeah, I have discussed, thank you for bringing it up, but just to remind me as an update, I have said for many years now there'll be more interest in all things biblical.
None of it will be accurate, but nonetheless the interest will be there.
There are plans for more biblical movies, and also there's a TV show about, guess the Bible verse, or I don't know, something, a Bible show, right?
And there's another Bible family Christian thing they're putting on major TV.
None of it is accurate, but people are focusing on that.
If there are more websites and YouTubes about Armageddon and the end of the world than ever, none of it, eventually people are going to get tired of it, and they're going to abandon the religious side of it, and there'll be an emergence of some truth enough for at least enough people to admit it, so then you'll go to the next level.
Just like any legal action, you have to be competent.
They ask you, do you understand the sentence?
Do you understand the charges?
You see, don't lead to that level.
Well, you know, I mentioned that I almost considered, or had considered,
converting to Christianity just in the last few months because of various factors,
but a big part of it was because of my journey into occultism,
and emergence from occultism,
and just finding out how dark and satanic our culture is,
and how complicit I'd been with it,
it was a sort of natural tendency to want to find an antidote for that.
But it also coincided with this increased ideological insanity, which is just denying basic biological and other kinds of facts.
Feeling the destabilization of that, wanting to find some sort of ground, and just recognizing like Christian doctrine and the Christian sensibility is relatively sane.
So it was almost like it was offering this refuge, like from the madness, you could take refuge in traditional religion.
So I think that's happening on a mass scale now,
that's Jordan Peterson's appeal,
because he's confronting the ideological insanity, number one,
and then he's also addressing the spiritual vacuum at the center of people's lives,
like all these people are converting to Christianity because of him,
and he's not even really a Christian,
and he certainly isn't presenting Christian doctrine in any coherent fashion,
but people are so hungry and desperate,
so it takes a little nudge and they will go in that direction.
One of the things to look for is Bernoulli's principle, or you know in physics it's called F equals P over V, you know when you give an example of that force equals pressure over volume, when you let a balloon out into the room and it starts flying around, as it gets smaller it moves faster.
You see, if you remember the days of the railroad, right before they were replaced with the other modes of transportation, the railroad cars got really opulent, right at their end.
You see, the same with cruise ships, they got really super opulent.
You think cruise ships are opulent?
Now, no, they're just really large like floating cities, and they're packing people in there efficiently.
They're not as opulent as they were back in the day, you see, before they were as a major mode, you see.
One thing to notice is the level of opulence that is strived for right before a system goes under.
So, even if there was a major push, even by the state, for mass conversion to Christianity, I would just laugh at it and say that just means they're finished.
For sure, you see.
Most people that don't know or are aware of these dynamics will say, oh, there are more people, I'm not saying you in this category at all, but I'm just stating as a counter aspect to what you mentioned, is that even though more people are converting towards it, for whatever reason, I'm telling you it's because it's coming to an end.
So, is it going to be a secular regime or whatever you would call it, prophesizing?
Well, what will happen is they're going to mull through various solutions.
In other words, you know, when things are comfortable, you know, you have a problem, but when the problem overrides the comfort, then you struggle and you consider the solutions to the problem more seriously, because now you're not in a comfort zone.
So, when the tensions in this world increase to the point that they're going to see that the systems that are in place, which, by the way, would work fine, but because no one knows what's written in their books, attorneys, judges, and all that, they're going to seek other, they're going to be inspired spiritually, divinely, to go back and look at the way ancient things were done.
And they're going to grab, for example, the scripture as an adherent, as a law form, and it's going to be applied and misapplied very drastically.
So, it will be divine on many levels, but it will be applied secularly, yeah.
But that'll still be with the heavy hand of the adversary, correct?
Correct.
And, by the way, people are, you know, those guys possessed by Satan.
Satan has never possessed anyone, not until this future, this single individual, who'll be the only person he's ever possessed.
Now, I had a discussion before with Sam about Satan possessing Judas Iscariot for doing what he did, you see, but I have to go research how direct that was, because ultimately he did not, you know, he was released from that influence, you know.
And, for example, you have oppression and possession.
Like, for example, in the book of Eob or Job, he was oppressed by Satan and other demons, right?
Basically, Satan sent various demons to him, because, you know, the various afflictions he had was done by various...
You know, a general doesn't have to go on the front line and shoot at the enemy.
He gets the infantry to do it.
But, again, where was it with the secular aspect?
It's not until much later that the more spiritual aspect is manifest.
So, and I have said this before, all of these things are going to be done in secret.
In other words, the modalities of fashion, trends, the things that people are used to seeing will seamlessly, the current society will seamlessly fold into the next one.
You know, as I've said before many times, again, Scripture is so prevalent, anyone has access to it, even the piss-poor version.
If you do it with comprehension, you'll get something out of it.
And if these things are going to be so blatantly happening, majority of the people who do comprehend it will cry foul.
So I'm suggesting, if not emphatically, more than suggesting, is that the identity of all these things that are going to be happening are going to be in secret.
So you might have a young world leader who might be of
quote-unquote Jewish or Judean descent,
and not unless you're in the inner circles
you know that he had lost the use of his arm and his eye,
or not unless you know someone on the inside
to admit to you that yes, he really is not Judean,
he's of Assyrian extraction,
because the public figure will be extremely different
from what is really going on.
An example would be, if you read in Exodus, when Moses was going to Pharaoh, I'm telling you, that was extremely private.
The people in the land did not know the interchanges that were going on.
Moses would go and speak to Pharaoh, and it would be on YouTube 20 minutes later?
No.
These were all very private exchanges with Pharaoh, for example, and his court.
People didn't know what was going on.
At all.
There's no hint of that.
You see?
You know, that's why people that believe or have information, okay, you have the information or whatever, but have you structured it in your own mind to see how it will pan out or how it will roll out in the reality that you know, the reality that you live in?
And most people say, no, I just read this, I know this is going to be like this, yeah, but how does that compare to your reality?
You can't see that happening, right?
No way.
Well then, how can it happen?
That's why I'm telling you that the majority of the stuff that you read about in Scripture is totally in secret.
If this society is going to unfold or fold into the next one quite neatly, so be aware.
I think Scripture even gives the warning.
It says even the very elect might be deceived.
That's why very often...
If it were possible.
That's why, you know, I tell people if I were to go and bet, everyone that I know will fall for it.
It will be a sure bet right now as it stands.
That's how strong the delusion will be.
That's how, you know, because let's say you know someone who wants to be lawful, right?
You know, you heard somebody say, well law hasn't been done away with.
You start, you know, wearing single fiber clothing.
You change the way you keep time and the days you adhere to and how you eat and you know more about the gods.
And all of a sudden, the state and everybody rises.
Oh, now we're going to be doing this.
You're going to be so happy that the society is now saying no more mixed fiber.
You see what I mean?
You're going to fall for it.
You know, how could it be, you know, you see what I mean?
How easy it is to...
I suppose.
I can't see myself falling for that.
Well, good.
As in, you know, I can't see myself believing anything that the state does or anything that's happening on that scale as being a delusion or a deception.
But who knows?
Never say never, right?
Right.
That's why you always have to be...
There's a metaphor about the thief in the night.
If you know he's coming, guess what?
You're not going to sleep.
As comfortably as the rest who don't know.
It's much worse to know that he's coming and you do fall asleep, right?
So there's an old Buddhist saying, once you're awake and you can't go back to sleep.
So you have to learn how to sleep all over again, you see?
In other words, that's a way of saying now you have to find comfort in other ways.
And while you're looking for those comforts in other ways, you're pretty darn uncomfortable.
But when you find them, you'll see that that's really part of the reward.
Okay, we've been on for about three hours or so.
We're burning the bites pretty good here.
Yeah, I was just thinking that was a very good night to end on.
Good.
Appreciate you coming by.
Bruce, anything else?
No, just a few things.
There were questions in the chat, but we're very engulfed in what we're talking about.
Anything you want to address quickly?
I was going to, I promised Nicole, you spoke about the seeds before in chat.
Yes.
And she was hoping that maybe you could give a little more information on that.
Simply put, I'm presuming, you know, by the way, Nicole could call in on the regular phone as well.
Yeah, I have that offer in the channel and anybody is welcome.
Right, but we're going to, at three hours, we've gone longer, but actually a few years ago, I did a 14-hour stream once.
That wasn't a stream, it was a recorded thing of 14 hours.
I got a four terabyte hard drive on this bad boy, so we can go as long as we want.
Okay, but I'm presuming she's not doing it on a commercial level.
So in that case, I would just get a metal box, like the holiday cookie tins, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, those rust, especially if they rust easily, that's, you know, they're not coated with lacquer too much, those are fine.
Go ahead and put it in a paper, put your seeds in there, in the center, because you want to keep them out of the corners.
Corners are a place that focuses unusual things when it comes to this kind of, you get mixed results.
So keep it in the center of the box by using tissue paper or whatever, and put that in a paper bag, and then put that in a metal cabinet, which is like an oven.
But you're not using, so now you've got various layers of metal and non-metal for at least three days to a week.
And then when you sprout, you'll notice, if you do a control, ones that were in the box and ones that weren't, the ones that were in the box will sprout and be faster, use less water, be more robust.
Now, if you really want to go to the next level with that, you can take the south pole of a magnet, as long as you avoid the center, which is the opposite, and just leave the seeds on the south pole a small amount, or a magnetic array, and when I say the magnetic array, the magnet should be spaced far apart, that one doesn't attract or repel the other.
And when you do that array, put the seeds for at least 20 minutes on the magnet, and that will charge the seed.
It has to be the south pole.
Now, the south pole is, if you have a compass, the magnetic, the red part of the compass that goes to the north will point to the south, you see, because the northern part of the, that's the south pole, the compass points to the south magnetic of the earth, right?
And the reason, the difference between the south pole and the north pole is one is compressive, one is expansive, you want to be on the expansive side.
There were studies done years ago, this was, there's a guy, there's a tattooed bald-headed freak on YouTube, you can tell him I said this, he doesn't mind, Ken Wheeler, you can look up his stuff on YouTube, he's probably one of the only people in the world, if not the only person in the world, to completely justify and rationalize what a magnetic field is.
I appreciate him very much because I've been asking the same questions that he's answered for years, and been able to work with magnetism because of the rational approach that I had, but Ken Wheeler does experiments with sprouts, again, on the south pole of the magnet.
He's not very good at telling you how to do it, even though he shows it to you, you're going to have to use, you're going to have to be very careful about what he says, don't misinterpret it, be a very good listener.
When he tells you to put the seeds against the south part of the magnet, it's the edge of the magnet, not the center of the south pole, just like for years I've been doing demonstrations about the, you know, the same faces that repel, they actually don't, if you could get them to stick together.
So, nonetheless, the south pole of the magnet, the magnetic south, which is what the northern compass, the red part of the compass will point to, expose the seeds to that.
Ken says 20 minutes, I say 12 hours, and you will get a pretty robust manifestation.
The other thing is, if you're going to use water to water the seeds, you treat the water the same way you would treat drinking water, and I've gone through that before, I don't need to go through it again.
Keep it in the dark and make sure that the water goes down to at least 4 degrees Celsius or 39 Fahrenheit for a few hours.
Right.
Do you eat sprouted greens yourself?
Sure, sure.
The best way to do, by the way, legumes, lentils, any kind of bean or whatever, is to soak it almost to a pre-sprouted condition where the little eye of the bean changes color, right?
Right, pre-sprouted condition is where it has its most nutrition, because now you've activated all the latent potential energy, you know.
Good to know.
Yeah, and I think I've gotten into how to cook beans and other things.
Maybe the next time, the next week, what they call Tuesday night, we'll get into a food discussion just to supplement the prior food discussions, and I'll maybe cover everything from the beginning.
What do you think?
Very well.
Yes.
And by the way, anyone keeping time, counting days, we're just about on the Feast of Weeks, what's called Pentecost, coming up here soon.
It's not, by the way, what the Christians say, 50 days after the Sabbath, that puts you in the middle of spring.
The Feast of Weeks, or the Pentecost, is not a mid-spring festival, it's a mid-summer festival.
So, you count seven Sabbaths and 49 plus one day, or 50 days, so that's roughly 100 some odd days since what's called the Week of Unleavened Bread, not the Passover, right?
Right.
And so, it puts it as a mid-summer feast.
That's why, if you read in Scripture, the offerings that were done during the Feast of Weeks are clearly mid-summer offerings.
Grapes and other things like that, you know, are growing.
I mean, I have a vineyard, what do you call it, a vineyard, another vineyard, a harbor with grapes.
I have grapes right now that are ready to eat and various other things.
So, yeah, it's another misnomer.
And also, if the Christ was on earth for 40 plus days, and the Pentecost was just a few days after that, why did, you know, when he ascended, why did he say, wait now, we'll bring to you, come to you later?
They would have just said a few days later was Pentecost.
It's not like that at all.
It was a big gap of time.
It was mid-summer when Pentecost came.
So, anyway, I don't even like calling it Pentecost because it's 50 count, literally.
It's not a 50 count.
It's a seven Sabbaths and a 50 count.
So, anyway, put that in your pipe and smoke it.
So, if anyone's counting, it's usually around the longest day of the year, what they call the Feast of Weeks.
Yeah, and it's coming around now.
I'm counting, I think it's this week.
Yeah, we're coming up on about six to five seconds longer.
So, we're coming very, very close where it's going to balance out or something, yeah.
So, if anyone has a day count on that, I, sadly enough to say, I lost count a few weeks ago, but if I go back, I know when the Sabbaths were and I know when the Passover was, and I know when the Week of Unleavened Bread ended.
I could figure that out.
I think it's right about now.
So, usually, it's interesting when I've observed it more accurately in the past, it always comes right after the Sabbath.
So, if it's not today or tomorrow, it's next week.
Well, we're at the 23rd of the farz, so.
Yes, no, but the count is seven Sabbaths and 50 days, right?
Right, correct.
Yeah, so, yeah.
Anyway, I just thought I'd throw that in.
You know, I'm not one to tell people what to do, how to do, or whatever.
I mean, you know, I don't do pork on my fork and various other things, right?
But I keep that to myself.
I don't ever tell anyone to, but don't be a dick and say the law is done away with.
You know, that's a real asshole perspective.
It's not.
It's what is it done away with for you is a different thing, you know?
And that's why I never.
You'll never hear me say, go read script, you read the Bible.
You'll never hear me.
You have to do the law because of...
Never.
Right, right.
It's up to you.
And what I'm doing is making people aware of another way.
And that's up to you.
Yep, yep.
All right.
Check that out yourself.
Don't take our word for anything.
Last thing I want to do is put someone on a path of futility.
Right, right.
Well, I don't say it much, but if you're not chosen to do this, you're not going to be able to do it.
Sorry.
I'm not now.
So as a Greek, are you chosen?
I said, well, what do you say I am?
I can't.
No one can say they're chosen, right?
Because you really don't know.
But what we do know is that if you're not chosen to do it, you're not going to be able to.
It's kind of like one of those open...
That's where the mysticism comes in, which I avoid.
Publicly, at least, you know.
All right.
So in terms of the teeth, yeah, they're just little baby plants.
And we'll get into that more next week.
Okay, Greg.
Well, thanks for the call.
Yep.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Great.
All right.
Yes.
Okay.
We'll do it again next week.
We'll be here around the same time.
Okay.
Thanks.
You have a good night.
Both of you.
Be well.
All right.
Bye.
And good night, folks.