Just moving along.
It's almost the end of the 10th month or less than a week for the 11th I kind of put in chat a little while ago Only because the way things are being cited in the position in the sky.
We might have a 13th moon
Maybe I'm not sure
And someone I have to go and I don't even know if I jotted it down for a lot
it wasn't last year, but the year before we had one and
Not the year before that but the year before then
So it was typical intercalation that could be about three every decade
With some more interesting stuff
Some more interesting stuff that I will be getting into with timekeeping
in the future
Not now because I'm still working it out and and instead of doing it in a didactic way
I think it's best to find someone else who's working it there was
give you guys a little bit of a profile on the timekeeping about
Six years ago.
There was someone else out in Arkansas who knew about this on their own.
They found out about me
I found out about them and
That's just two people in the u.s
At that point six years ago, and I think now there's maybe three or four or five looking at the chat
So that's a pretty good thing and what I mean about
You know because I've sort of been the one trailblazing the mindset in this direction
I think with a little bit of experience through time other people will get a handle on and be able to be
authoritative on those movements as well
Because if I start getting into more of the detail on time
I think it's still going to be the I hate to say it's student-teacher thing and I want it to be more of a collective
So I think we're almost there from what I can judge on discussing more things
The other thing I wanted to bring up regarding timekeeping
I've had a couple of private emails regarding that and by the way if anyone I have the email open if anyone wants to email
During this call.
It's the uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com That's the number one and the Skype contact is the same you just go to the Skype contact and put it in but before I get it more into the Timekeeping I wanted to bring up that Prophetically, I think I've discussed with you last time Bruce that the purpose of Prophecy is to show the interruption in the natural clockwork, right?
Right, right.
It's it's the anomaly
You know you you have like the example I gave in the Midwest of America
It's typical to dust off the snow shovel in the winter
But if I a prophetic statement would be well, you better leave it out in what they call July
And you're like well why this you know and well, well, you'll see because of this
So, you know no one in the Midwest takes out their snow shovel in the mid mid-july, right?
but prophetically that if that kind of information and And also, especially when it happens is prophetic you see so that's the demystifying the information so you could rationalize it So but one thing I'm just gonna drop out for a minute.
I'll be right back.
Okay, okay, so Greek I took your advice and read through Zechariah and I've got a lot of meditating to do on that one my God Wow, there's yeah, you could ask him, too Yes There's a little amount there's anomalies in there that I'd like to discuss because they're they're brought up in the New Testament What's called the New Testament and I want to explain those?
Again but you know as time goes on and what's interesting about doing these calls believe it or not
I'm just rehashing stuff that I was talking about on conference calls ten years ago
so
Yeah, even a lot of the new stuff I bring out is just stuff that I just recall from conference calls from a decade ago
And you know, I think eventually maybe in another year or two if I'm still around to get on the stuff that I'm working on
now
So
But you know, here's the other interesting thing
I've really stopped studying intensively like seeking out and I've just been meditating on stuff that I've done in the past decade believe it or not
And and there's coming a time here in the near future again where there'll be a time for study again
But let me just go back to the timekeeping just a broken thought several times just complete it
One of the interesting things is that the heavenlies are going to not
Provide accurate.
Well, they're not their clockwork will get screwed up in this coming time period and What I mean by that is it's a very simple attitude to have that You know, it's the seventh day of the week when the moon phases in its particular quarter moon phase, you know full quarter waning dark moon quarter waxing full moon Those are your Sabbaths basically, but not this year this year.
It's gotten it's pretty good But the and maybe last year it but definitely the past four years or so.
There was a year there Where the moon did not agree at all It would be about two or three days off on its phases and it would reel itself in and catch up by the full moon again You know what?
I mean?
So instead of the first Sabbath being a half moon when the Sabbath was over it was barely, you know It was it was way less.
It was you know, three-quarters plus And then and then and then within a day or two it caught up and and then it went the other way So and that's I have some stories to tell about this fellow out in Arkansas who called me once it was what they call 2011 in the summer.
I wasn't around
I was on the West Coast actually and
He was doing measurements and he said did you notice that the the earth stopped moving and I said no
And it says for about 30 seconds the earth stood still
Right, and I missed that and there was and yeah, this is around
this is
Around the what they call the fourth or fifth month of 2011
so
You know, let's just let's just say it this way
The knowledge of this stuff
Yes, it's earth's shaking in a way
But you could you imagine the earth stops moving for 30 seconds and there's not a peep
Not even none of the astronomical authorities.
No way and Yeah, yeah, so how many times have you heard me say that when these things start happening?
They're gonna seem absolutely normal Right.
So we just keep that in the back of your mind.
Yeah
And what I mean by the earth stopping is, you know, you could see if you haven't if you create an archway
Let's say with a taut cable with some good concrete stanchions or something
You can see that, you know, the law the the larger the shadow the more precise you can get on the shadow movement
there was a progression in the shadow and then it actually stopped and went backwards like in the book of Isaiah and
Then it proceeded again, you know towards the shadow proceeded towards the east, right?
This is this was at the noontime break so this these kinds of things
I'm just sharing them because they just sit in the back of the mind, you know, and they just dwell there, you know
And he's a great
He's a very good observationist and
So just want to bring up there's more to the timekeeping than one might think also
There are things I'll discuss in the future in conditions that I'm around to discuss them again
Regarding the book of Revelation probably not on even not even a
nothing to be archived
on something like this maybe on a private call or maybe
if I said I wrote I write something and put it out anonymously, it's not so anonymous now, but
Yeah
regarding the the regarding the
the star alignments that no one seems to see in the first couple of chapters or three chapters even and
I ask people and you see the star charts in the first few chapters book revelation
So
Yeah, so there's and it's just right there.
I mean, it's just like once you're shown You're like, oh man, this is like really freaking obvious So but at the same time it should be sending some putting hairs on the back of your head up just a smidge.
Oh Yeah, yeah, it does.
Well, we don't put what should really be putting hairs on People the the hairs up is the ridiculousness of humankind at this time, you know, you could say they're evil You could say they're stupid you could say they're dense that they're not paying attention But they're just it's just downright a ridiculous game that's going on and it's a cosmic one.
So
It's it's
I'm seeing more and more what you mean about this hive mentality
And even in casualness, it's it's it's just it's spooky, you know that to put it bluntly
well, because you know, there's a couple of interviews lately and just random stuff that might seem of interest and
It's amazing how you know, you might look at you think there's a variety even like with newspaper articles or something
But they're all the same.
They're all the same
You know, it's like if you go to McDonald's everything tastes the same believe it or not
I don't know if you've ever noticed that
Or white people food or whatever it all you don't know
Yeah, you don't know what it is, you know, so so just eat it and shut up
So this is what's going on and in the level of and it's everywhere and everyone and I mean that statistically, you know
ninety nine point nine nine nine
Nine nine nine nine nine.
It's just there's nothing out there that I could recommend other than reference materials
yeah it's good for you it's got electrolytes yeah and this is the state
of the world and it's it's fine you're not going to change it you're going to
navigate it maybe and that's that's about it so there's yeah there's lots of
stuff to get into let's see what Sam wants to bring up I think what every
this is what he calls the day off so he can bring up some things I think people
tend to enjoy his point of view and his persistedness and he's we stay on a
subject and kind of beat it to death with him on which is good so yes any any
he approaches it from many different directions which is good it certainly
helps with the discernment and certainly an enlightening fellow and
and you both bring very good topics to the table and in like you've always said
no one out there is talking about it period and not even close yeah no it's
really sad in that but yeah it really shows the censorship that's going on
which is the more I get to see that every day though the more I keep saying
to myself oh yeah wow yep so let's see anything else you want to mull around any
questions in the chat I'm in the kitchen making coffee I made some miso miso
roasted potatoes with miso garlic rosemary and olive oil you never had
miso soup me so it's pasted more miso in its paste form is made from fermented
soybeans and it's not the soy that they typically if you get a high quality it's
not the soybeans that they serve here and it has a cheese like flavor so it's
a cheap substitute but it's made of soybean salty and it's sharp you just
have just have small potatoes and parboil them and then I dry them put them
in a pan dry roast the potatoes in a pan right you still have the skin on purple
potatoes yellow potatoes and on the side I have a mixture of chopped rosemary you
know fresh and garlic and miso and olive oil and you just a little bit of honey
and you just boil it for a few minutes and you get this delicious you are like
eating any talents it's like it's like eating steak you just have that with
some lettuce from the garden and and some tomatoes and yeah you're good to
go so it sounds like Sam is back hello hi Sam hi all right so yeah people will
have to excuse that I'm a little quiet because my roommates are sleeping I'm in
the room okay I need a personal sound chamber make a little personal oh wait a
second I don't have to whisper you do okay good isn't that funny when someone yawns and
everyone else yawns no matter how far away you are if Sam is whispering we're
gonna start whispering too watch I'm not gonna be any less forceful just
because I'm whispering but right we can we can we can certainly normalize
the sound later all right so state your purpose of pushing this week what do you
got on your mind well we'd already touched before on the subject of the
zodiac so I felt like we should just pick up where that left off last week I
think we started by looking at the fact that or I brought up the fact that the
change of the ages is visible from the earth due to the precession of the
planet and that a change in the orientation of the rotational axis
creates these different astrological signs that rise at dawn on what they
call the spring equinox about every 2,000 years so continuing down that
line of exposition it's easy to see with the help of computer programs that
simulate ancient skies that the age of Leo was from around 11,000 BC to 8,800
BC give or take a century or two and that would enclose the younger driest
period of 10,500 BC that the Genesis recreation account is often associated
with that you have this global if not solar system wise cataclysmic event
that abruptly ended things so the academic and the alternative appraisals
of ancient monuments generally reveal enough about those structures that allow
us to ascertain that their erection was done in accordance with astrological
realities be it the movement of the Sun or the moon or the placement of the
constellations or the cardinal points we see this with Stonehenge in the UK we
see which Tiwanaku in Bolivia and the pyramids in Egypt etc and it has also
been postulated by some alternative historians that based on the observable
architecture that there was a at that time a globally recognized doctrine of
creating monuments on the ground that copied the pattern of the constellations
or were in line with certain movements of the heavenly bodies so since the
position of the constellations change over a millennia it's possible to use
those configurations of the monuments to deduce when they were made and the
dates that they're meant to represent how much how much of a parallax shift
there is I did sort of bring this up the last time connected to the idea of
the Sphinx we've had conversations in the past where we saw differently on the
date of the Sphinx and one was put up alongside the pyramids and things like
that I think that you know the Giza Plateau contains quite a number of
astrologically aligned structures that allow us to hammer certain things down
for example the Sphinx is perfectly pointing to the true east whilst the
three pyramids are aligned with true north and true south so I've also read
somewhere and I I'll quote it because it feels credible that the alignment for
the pyramids is extremely exact down to three thirtieths of a degree and if that
holds true then it's indisputable that the monuments were set using astronomy
on the grounds of that accuracy alone so taking that into account so six arc
seconds uh-huh go ahead yeah so um by the way am I coming through clearly yes
you are yes so taking that into account then we can then see that the
constellation of Leo would have risen in the east above the Sun at dawn on the
spring equinox to set off the younger driest slash recreation period of 10,500
BC so that would mean I think you can deduce that since the Sphinx points
directly true east its gaze would have been fixed directly on the rising
constellation of Leo at that time now of course you could also claim that since
the Sphinx is gazing east it would be looking at whatever constellation comes
into effect each 2,000 years whether it's Aries or Pisces or whatever but I would
say that only one of those provide a sky ground match ultimately the Sphinx is a
lion with a human head but it's more lion than it is human and at only one
time do you find a lion Sphinx interlock and that is 10,000 BC at least
over the past 25,000 years additionally sky ground correlation can be seen at
that exact time also with the three pyramids since they're positioned in
almost exact likeness with the three belt stars in the constellation of Orion
which would have been rising at the exact same time in the south so the point
that I'm trying to make is simply that ancient cultures were well aware that
the ages could be observed and acknowledged using these monolithic
structures but the exact significance is I don't know that's not known to the
public but we don't have to guess what the age of the pyramids or the age of
the Sphinx is if we accept these astronomical connections well there's
several points to look at one is why build a megalithic or a monolithic
structure in the first place the question is why the other thing to
consider is that orientation is still done now if you're building a custom
home for a client that likes to sleep in you don't orientate the bedroom
towards the east you see you right because the rank is little right so you
still have orientation concepts with solar orientation but you're bringing up
more of the constellational one the other thing is why build the monument
right well what's you know how we say to memorialize something right so the
true purpose of or it's a tool or it's a tool yeah but also you know you didn't
have to build it such a big tool the best tools are the ones you could pick
up and walk away with I mean also yeah that's like saying that's like saying
why build a cruise or what's it called these huge battleships like you we could
just build a tiny boat no it has to be a battleship but actually that's that's
government spending actually smaller ships with more potent rockets and
things are more more have more efficacy but but anyway that let's just think of
it and from this point of view also we have a dark let's say a cloud over
history on the purpose and you know here let's just say this might air
philosophical or just like I'm brushing it away but I'm not do you know that
within this generation we will find out the purpose of these things we don't
know them exactly right now sure so speculating is healthy as long as it's
done within the realm of what you know good sound presumption wishes say but but
to be to be a bit more assertive I don't think that these are just merely you
know hypotheses we these are facts on the ground the astrological alignments
with their period sure so that has to be sure well let's just look at
something different for a minute now you have skyscrapers being put up
everywhere using the common term you know very tall buildings there's 167
story buildings being put up now where you know anything over 100 stories was
remarkable 30 years ago so are these things any kind of a geometric beacon or
alignment with that in there isn't any of that you see my point no one is
really building well yeah there are some sundials in India that were built in the
past century that are massive for that are for keeping time in public parks and
they're not sundials like the ones we see in cartoons and the things that are put
in front of us they're very curvilinear I should say so the purpose of these
things is not just to have them aligned but also to go for a long time I usually
give the metaphor that you know a thousand years ago things were built to
last a thousand or let's say three thousand years ago they built things to
last three thousand years right a thousand years ago they built them to
last right so now a hundred years ago they're built things to last 100 now
they're building things to last only a couple of decades so we're gonna find out
within that lack of endurance and time we're going to find out more about it
but also who was it took Moses the fourth who dreamt the location of the
Sphinx right and dug it up and because before him doing that by the way back to
the Sphinx it was a legend even within their own culture that it existed so and
that was around the time of the exodus let's say right so there's things that
are being dug up right now still yeah but to touch on what you were saying as
far as people putting up the skyscraper thing I mean you've also said in this
conversation people don't build temples and large-scale structures and sphinxes
of that nature on a whim I mean sure you might have you might have a place like
Disneyland that's centered on fictions of Mickey Mouse but it's all just fiber
glass and aluminum and plastic facades that's a completely different thing from
a big-ass pyramid mm-hmm yeah now also the the other thing about it since you
bring up astronomers throwing some tidbits do you know how a lot of the
information that we look at regarding ancient astronomy seems vague to the
current scientists and they disregard a lot of it if you take the literature
into account the stars of the heaven they and if you look more into the
meaning of what they meant but the stars in the heavens they actually just
described the stars in our sky they never really get into the you know how
many light-years away it is you know how they do now with the astronomical
societies they try to put a distance and an image on everything because the
ancients knew that you can only see those stars from the through the Earth's
atmosphere and this is one thing I want to bring up because this is being hidden
from society today if you go into outside of this Earth's atmosphere into
the atmosphere of space you do not see the Sun even the closest star you don't
see it at all you'll see yourself lit you'll see the planets lit but you won't
see the Sun and if you stare at it the radiation will burn your light
sensitive organ out you know the eye in the innards of the eye so the ancients
knew this but they didn't elaborate on it because you didn't have to they knew
that the Sun and the stars simply appeared in only our atmosphere and how
do we know that because they didn't discuss anything about outer space you
know specifically you know so that's an interesting concept how now it's
coming back around but by the way people will under the current system you
will never hear the authorities say what I just told you they will never admit
that that you can't see the Sun in ours but right now you can do your own
research and see that you cannot see there are no visible light photographs
just straight visible light photographs of the Sun from outer space at all they
don't exist you just see all these various spectrum the same with the stars
and I think I want to bring up again when they did the Hubble telescope and
they said they had to send a crew up there to correct it it wasn't to correct
any focal length or anything it was simply just to add diffraction lenses
filters because it didn't see anything at all so that just shows you how it'll
communicate you know it's just it's just the whole thing is a mess right now but
the reason we discuss these things is to tie it into history and show how much
has not changed but let's just say coming up here in the next couple of
months if you can get well I should say cities are not that good or mountain
rangers could block it but if you can get out into a plane somewhere you know
physical open area and just around the next full moon a week before not the
next full moon two or three full moons from now you can see the constellation
alignments in the east right you'll see Pisces and Aquarius so and you'll see
about 75% of Aquarius and 75% of Pisces it's not squared you know what I mean
east hmm so yeah I've only recently started looking into these things
myself I don't I don't bring them up to launch into some kind of really long
exposition on them but just to wrap up we were talking about before and to just
hammer down that these things are also backed by scripture as far as being
referenced so it's worth keeping in mind and clearly the ancient cultures were
aware of that also and they had some kind of an emphasis that they placed on
what was happening in the stars and things on the ground to represent that
well they placed stally and stones and minor monuments you know some of the
monuments were not so minor but throughout especially the patriarchs
they had a stone that they either adorned with writing or attributed as a
commemorative place you know so you know because the other question there to ask
is if you actually look at where these places are in scripture can they be
found well you there's then you have the fork in the road one is yes it could be
found or they could be found or the other one is where they subject to
vandalism like for example there was the folklore of where Joseph was buried when
he came out of Egypt and when a certain part of the Negev was given over to I
think Egyptian or Jordanian control allegedly the first thing the people did
that either the Egyptians or Jordanians is go and destroy Joseph's tomb because
he was a biblical figure right so this was done I don't know recently not
recently but you know with a few decades ago so or more the history of that I'm
not just came across and once I'm just stuck in the back of the head you know
would the gods allow these things to really be vandalized I would say it can
go either way you know but usually when they let something go like that they
state a purpose for it so anyway we do have a lot of monuments still and I
wouldn't suggest that any of them are held in high regard would you know
they're generally left to fall apart or some of them are underwater like the
what's it called the Yonagumi monument near Japan I'm just supposed to be some
kind of a city but it's underwater yep there's one off of Florida there's
there's several of them let's say in the Caribbean Caribbean yep so wait not just
let me just throw something wait just wait and see what's gonna happen to this
society you just wait but anyway what would people be saying later about what's
left from this shithole of a civilization but anyway did I just say
that let's just never mind everything you say can and will be used against you
later yeah that's right but it is no oh yes that is obvious but I mean even
secular people know that that's why they say people are so stupid as a sort of a
general cliche so keeping in sort of the theme of I mentioned Japan in terms of
Eastern cultures when when I look at the teachings and the tenets of the Gnostic
worldview throughout you know the various subsects they have a bunch one finds
that asceticism is quite prevalent because of their view that the physical
incarnation of matter is evil and that the flesh has to be repressed blah blah
blah it doesn't seem like a coincidence that the Gnostics sense of asceticism
also overlaps with the scenes the so-called Jewish community in the rather
Dead Sea Scrolls and I can't find any source of these ascetic leanings other
than the East Asian religions as far as where they would have come from there
seems to be information pointing to that influence of Hinduism Buddhism creeping
in at some point in the Middle East at first you have the ancient Vedic
religions roughly between 1700 and 500 BC which were dominant out of which
later comes Hinduism and then Buddhism develops in opposition to Hinduism in
that area also well they all wondering if we have no they all redeveloped around
the 6th century 5th century BC let me just interject this when you when we
discussed the Gnostics and the Gnostics are like the pretty piss poor because
they're synthesized from a reactionary movement that took place in the first
century right just like if you look at 9-11 research now they talk about space
weapons and nanothermite and just stuff that's just impossible and stupid for
stupid people but without interjecting it like that let's just put it this way
the concept of asceticism is a misunderstanding and a misplacing of the
concept that the love of money is the root of all evil it's not money it's the
love of money that's root of all evil so most people still today if you ask them
do you know any biblical verses like is you know for example money is the root
of all evil most people will say yes it's not money is the root of all evil
it's the love of money it's the love of wealth it's the love of personal gain
the greed that is the root of all evil not the the actual substance itself you
see so these people had misplaced that just like they do now how many times do
you go on the stupid rectangle and say money is the root of all evil and you see
it on all blogs and the internet you know all over and and you know in print or
whatever so it's misplaced so what happens there is the simple let's kill
the messenger we don't understand the message or the message even though it's
simply simply stated is contrary to what we think it is so we'll just kill the
whole thing anything that has to do with money you see if you look at the
patriarchs they're quite wealthy the ones that are mentioned very few of them
were in squalor right even the ones that had really hard times let's say
Joseph even right he didn't end up in squalor and they didn't prefer it no one
prefers it so the concept of asceticism is the very simple concept of let's say
what Christianity is today what Judaism is today what Buddhism is today and all
these religions are all misplaced like I say none of them know their their their
texts or their writings so it's just misplaced you see so I don't spend a
lot of time on the asceticism because I know it's misplaced understanding now
doesn't mean that they can't choose to live that way because look at
Christianity look what they choose to do talk about you know going the wrong way
and everything they do so you know let me just throw this in about the Essenes the
Essenes were a cult type group that removed themselves from society and they
gave a little too much over to the other side you know they had like various
doctrines like you know if if we don't need to spread what we're doing it'll be
brought to us right and they viewed that when someone came to them that they
didn't come on their own volition that it was came you know from the most high
let's say right strictly so they what they did was they abandoned discernment
from that perspective but also they knew they had a there could have been a
hidden purpose of evil somewhere so they had a very Spartan and almost draconian
rules within their society so when you went in there it was very Spartan you
know and unpleasant to for many so you know what I've understood from Scripture
if it was meant that everything like I do say you know certain things
specifically like getting a wife or spouse is brought to you from the most
highest in Proverbs so but to say that everything is directly that way would be
false because then we wouldn't need the law to discern anything we would just be
on remote control you see so there's an aspect of the free will part that they
don't comprehend on the scene level so that's that was extreme dogma basically
on these scenes and if you actually read out of the text let's see what they
call the New Testament I would suggest very strongly if not almost matter of
fact that Johan and the immerser or John the Baptist was raised by them at one
point it could be inferred yeah yeah so because that was the will to negative
right so so but that's neither here nor there I would just like to address the
point of asceticism as as not being anything that's that's yeah worthwhile
because it's just a real it's like Santa Claus you know everyone gets all hyped
up about and they say do it every year or you know asceticism is something you
practice as a lifestyle but I don't see it as being anything I wouldn't say
lawful or unlawful but I don't see it being within the scope of how we are
supposed to be see so it's not to lend any credibility to it we know that
there's none there I guess the broader view is to try to understand whether this
is something that was an outgrowth of the Judean culture of the time or whether
it was imported because I don't see it as being something that we can find any
origin stories for in that region it seems to have come out of the out of the
Far East I would say what I was imported especially if they were east of the
Dead Sea or just slight south and slightly east because well you can also
you can also see there was a big shift you know the effect of Hellenism on the
whole world at the time right and what I mean by that is you can go to places in
Afghanistan where there's a just absolute wilderness and you'll find a
small Greek amphitheater built by Alexander the Great you know like the
Hunza people even today state that they are descendants of those who mutinied
from Alexander you know back in those days so you have a long history of
Hellenism the the Judeans Israel everyone being Hellenized but there was
a break that happened after the the Alexandrian conquests fizzled out and
that formed the Parthian Seleucid and the entire eastern you know the Persian
which was already defeated by the Greeks but it still you know held power in that
area and it never it never released the power even even when you look into current
history you I mean in the past thousand years or so you had the Eastern Western
churches right the Eastern Orthodox that was more north but you it still has
shades of that today but you think to consider all of it was Hellenized so
when I let's go back to the asceticism of you know preaching poverty as being
beneficial to the human I would see that that was actually a shift that happened
after the Hellenism took place because that was not part of Hellenism but you
know if you actually look at some of the sects in Athens and the Peloponnesus
region of ancient Greece there were some philosophers that did teach and
preach asceticism but not on a social level but for the individual only you
know so it might have all so to tie all this these rambles that I just gave out
together it could have been that just a few of these whacked-out Greek
philosophers had a potent enough message that it permeated the Hellenic
system as it spread throughout the entire known world then well you know
East and once the Hellenic system subsided went into subsidence some of
this Greek this this philosophical asceticism sprang up because I don't see
it in the Judean culture or the Egyptian culture or you see so I'm just giving
you this is the the Greek theoretical the Greek speak theoretical moment you
know because I have no proof of that because unless one of these sects said
yeah we are you know we are ascetic because we've been Hellenized and there
was a minor philosopher that said that was the way to go no I haven't found
evidence of that but I just you know this is where I've seen it only I mean
as a sporadic thought based on this idea that everywhere was Hellenized and you
had these Greek philosophers that exercise a lot of influence I mean I come
to think of you mentioned that the earlier statues of the Buddha was
actually Greek looking figures so there seems to be this somewhat loose
connection with the Far East anyway because how would the Far East then have
ended up with that being depicted as something else that's more in line with
their aesthetic with their visuals no but they did because the only well the
oldest known bronze statue of a Buddha is a Hellenic looking Caucasian Hellenic
meaning it wore his hair and his beard and his dress the in the style of the
Hellenes which are the Greeks yeah so there seems to be some something there
some linkage right and all of this all of this was just at that cusp around the
5th or 6th century BC and then that's when the major axial periods happen
which you'll which is most aptly stated in the first chapter of Jeremiah you
know what does that mean right you know here's interesting thing get into
discussions these are like roundabout discussions because you can't just
discuss one aspect of scripture but if anyone reads the book of Jeremiah which
is by the way the only book I would suggest to anyone to read because it's
the prophet took the whole world right if you read the book itself you'll say
oh this guy's a real whiner you know there's some bad times going on no one
listens to him but they do they don't shed his authority to do so but they
don't listen to him anyway you don't get much of a feeling that this guy went all
over the world as a young man he went to every leader of every known society on
the planet you don't get that feeling do you when you read that book of Jeremiah
do you but it's clearly stated there and it's actually clearly reinforced in
other books like the book of Ezekiel like when they went to Ezekiel and asked
him to be a prophet or told him that he would do that you know that be appointed
as one he was he went into a panic and it was noticed that he went into a
panic and what was the first thing they told him after that says don't worry you
don't have to learn all these languages and speak to foreigners and all this
you're gonna stay here in Israel why would you tell him that if it wasn't if
it was not known that the guy that came before him did the world tour and it
wasn't pleasant so anyway I just want to throw that in there cuz I'm pretty
passionate about that time period you know fifth sixth century BC seventh
century you know that's somewhat well yeah that was a you know but yeah like
between 500 and 650 BC was a yeah it's a time that changed the entire world as
we know it and I think that because you mentioned it quite a few times and I've
only recently started to look into it so I won't touch on it too much until I've
compiled stuff but as far as there being certain specific things that happened
that would have created the axial shift in part we can say natural disasters and
things of that nature but I think it's also important to mention the
Nebuchadnezzar phenomenon in his role because he was quite significant as
Babylon was the first Empire in the statue and I think that the role that we
can see him playing is that Babylon had a habit of uprooting and destroying
cultures they would go out and as they did with the Israelites they would wage
war burn everything and then take the people and put them in another part of
the world right more more more at the Nebuchadnezzar the senior would have
been that position but also you have to imagine he I would suggest what you said
is correct if you he went out and wrangled just like a farmer would go
wrangle some cattle when they're out on the field on the plane to bring him back
that's what he did because the first Empire was really under Nimrod but it
was it was already concentrated at that point it didn't cover a vast area of
lands you see so bear that in mind when you look at that history because also
that history is around that time of the Axel period you notice how how come
there's you know how come there are no iPhones or cars or airplanes in
scripture right why not why isn't that mentioned you know because if there's a
very specific point here that's and I'll just say this I don't say it frequently
people try to read the book of Revelation try to read the book of
Revelation to explain the Bible it's the opposite the entire Bible all the text
explains the book of Revelation oh yeah it's backwards Revelation came first
revelation came around that Genesis verse 1 not verse 2 that's later so so
when you look at the book of Revelation it talks about a world leader and his
posse when you look at the the history of the whole world from the Genesis
through on how come Nebuchadnezzar shines as a world leader that of a
magnitude that isn't mentioned before you see when they were actually you know
ones like him prior but not exactly like him and not exactly in the same
condition so that's another discussion I don't like going into the book of
Revelation but eventually we're gonna have to to explain these things yeah I
think it's pretty clear that the Babylonians made a habit of destroying
cultures not just destroying people by transplanting people and uprooting them
and forcing them to sort of adhere to Babylonian ways and forgetting their own
cultures and that sort of explains why you don't get a lot of history beyond
500 BC because a lot of those records were destroyed by the Babylonians as they
are today there's still destruction going on but it's not commonly known in
Western cultures if you told your common oaf on the street or plebeian
that you're gonna some public records historical records will be destroyed
they'll all be up in arms but if you go to any Middle Eastern country now and
tell them you're going to do that they're like oh yeah fine that guy's an
asshole anyway it was a different mindset so as I mean there is a lot of
record destruction being done constantly so but it's it's more favorable in the
east it's considered to be admirable that if someone was considered to be
good and at the end they screwed up oh just wipe wipe his whole existence from
history this is a common thing I mean but here's the interesting part your
history that you're getting in university and on television is like
that anyway it's all it's it's all thwarted and twisted and bizarre you
know so but here's an interesting way to look at it from the you know I did a
discussion recently but there's no such thing as anything secular because you
can take an atheist or told secular person you ask him do you believe in
justice and they say yes and if you ask them what's that mountain that spews lava
they say it's a volcano well that's after the god Vulcan you'll find in in these
eight quote-unquote atheists or or secular people a third of their
vocabulary is deep deific and they have a lot very strong beliefs so there's no
such thing as secular atheists you see and that's why media is always pulling
from religious influences and whilst they're simultaneously trying to deny
that they're religious all the Hollywood stuff makes reference to religious
stuff all the time and then they misquote where they got it from like I
watched a documentary once and it opens with a house built on a house divided
against itself cannot stand and then they attributed to Abraham Lincoln they say
that's where they got it from oh my right it's like a facepalm moment because
they don't even know where the thing comes from I feel that they just kind of
go ahead it's a planet full of what well I think that they're they're all feeding
each other continuously the commercialism or commercials the Hollywood
medical they all feed each other in this big little bubble of crap that they dish
upon people oh are you their attorney are you here to represent no no are you
defending them no I'm making an observation that this is the tool that's
just a bunch of scumbags yeah okay let's just simplify it then yeah it's
just evil I mean evil meaning not good right right so yeah yeah don't make
excuses for these okay I'm sorry oh that's fine I mean you could I mean
that's how you get around with well I and you know I meant that more than
observational premise and to sit back and plead for them in any way shape or
form that would be the last thing if I do something like that I would I would
really want to be chided no what you're saying is not incorrect but the reason I
said what I'm said what I said strongly like that is to make a snap out of that
politically correct motive I'm not saying that you're considering being
politically correct but there's this forgiving element you know there's the
truth and then there's the facts the facts are not always true but if you're
going to use a truthful fact the fact that the people on this planet are
scumbags or morons or evil or to be avoided or whatever and this is what you
see as a recurring theme by the way over and over and over and over through all
of the ancient Ritz not just the biblical certainly didn't come to the trough no
no doubt about it and they're fed with this and yeah I agree look yeah from
another reality which is the real reality in a way is why not shed all of
the worst aspects of humanity now pre-resurrection so at least it's done
and over with and manifest so post-resurrection you don't have to do
it then now you notice what I just said not that it won't happen but you don't
have to do it then you know to illustrate the point you see yeah but
you're taking that lawful aspect out of there then aren't you oh yeah you know
they didn't measure that yeah but yeah this is a show I always tell people don't
take it personally this entire manifestation is not necessarily for
humans even though humans are created now it is for the gods it's their thing
they have something they have to do and get done whether it's beneficial to them
or us obviously it doesn't seem that way but it's it's a you know what I mean
by the gods is the various angelic beings demons sons of gods on and on and
on they have some kind of thing that they're doing and we're caught in the
middle of it so but because they have a very high level of economy of movement
why not they finish up what they got involved in that's not necessarily the
best and at the same time have us on the scene when this is going on so we get
battle-hardened or at least go through the worst aspects first it's a very
simple thing to once you note it you know you know you can't tell us to
someone who's like oh no one knows the meaning of life you know that mentality
you know it didn't they don't they're not they can't get it but it's very
simple don't it's just very simple you know we just happen to be through
economy of movement at the tail end of some kind of you know divine cosmic
beyond cosmic you know a cessation period because when this period ends now
this period also will end for them that the disharmony that they're having so
don't take it personally but it just so happens to be that most people are just
downright awful did you notice you know from right off from the get-go when
Elohim created the angels and the deities and all these things and then
creating man there was this flaw where they wanted to divide and go away from
Elohim and some stayed some left I just found it an interesting presence I know
what you're talking about huh you have to you have to repeat just go ahead good
you guys discuss it because I didn't quite get that but go ahead no I don't
get it like what where is that well I mean you you had the division of of the
of the of the angelic ream or Rome wasn't there a battle because wasn't
there a battle because the Elohim made man I would use battle I would use
battle in the heiress tense which means it's constantly going on okay what I
would say is that battling you have a I guess you call it an alternative
Christian dogma that has now sort of become mainstream which is that certain
people from what I know in the 18th century I can think of it's the name of
the book Earth's earliest ages by GH Pember and probably some others that
will mean the age of reason stuff no that came out that's different it came
out after that but it's it's these books written by Christian authors who have
gained some higher level of discernment than the average Christian or pastor
that's not hard to do by the way but anyway I mean compared to what we're
talking about here it's not a high level at all but compared to the average
Christian they're able to see for example that Genesis of recreation and
other things but then they take it to certainly illogical extremes because
they feel like they have to explain the purpose of evil or the purpose of Satan
and so on and so they run with the Lucifer theme that Lucifer was an angel
who rebelled because he was mad at Adam he got salty and started a war then he
got kicked out and then he went and tempted Eve and of course this is not in
the text but they'll read it they'll read into the text and so this has now
become part of sort of an alternative mainstream but there was no war at the
time of Adam that was started because he was created as far as I can see based on
text anyway I see all of Christianity I see all of Christianity is being an
alternative mainstream it's a synchronized it's like you ever go to a
public waste treatment plant they when the water comes in from all the sewers
they have someone standing there at the grate in case there's something too
large that the system won't process you see like fecal turds and sanitary
napkins hope no one's eating all the nasty stuff people throw down the drain
and including stormwater and there's a guy there with a pole and if there's
like a baby's head or something that you know it's just very unusual he poke he
pulls it out all right that's what they do to form these religions they
synchronize like just the everything that mankind has gotten into that's
abominable and before it gets processed into the sewer for everyone to drink
they pull out all the obvious bad points you know and the bad labels you know and
it's not just Christianity that's like that it's all of the mainstream
religions are like that just that you know you you know here's the thing if
the government down the street whatever or business is secular why are they
closed on Christmas so the whole planet has to put up with this crap so and I
and I mean that literally nature is tired of it and you know I had a
conversation with someone says I'm just I get everything I need from nature
instead are you sick and tired of mankind you're like no I said you're not in
touch with nature you get it anyway that's a whole other discussion on its
own I still think that if we if we're going to say that the sinkholes around
the Dead Sea that keep appearing randomly are supposed to be some active
nature and I feel like we should see more occurrences of such aberrations in
other places like you know I can only see the sinkholes well you will but it's
not time yet because if it happens in the current mindset it'll be viewed as an
anomaly that is going to distract people and create a sense of alarm the
way the way that you do these things is so they appear to be natural in other
words a natural of course kind of attitude not how shocking attitude you
see like if not I like to use the biblical references and analogies with
9-11 it's perfect example five years before 9-11 if you describe what
happened everyone would laugh at you but when 9-11 happened the plan was
orchestrated to mentally steer all of your emotion and energy into a certain
direction so it got dumped out instead of being held in and contemplated right
what was going on also you have to combine that with ignorance just basic
physics and basic structures not because just ignorance of basic physics and
basic structures in general but ignorance of basic physics and basic
structural stuff regarding certain things that mankind is involved in that
people if you mention what it is people will say they know about it but they
only know about one kind of it one type of it you see and that's nuclear and
atomic energy if you mention nuclear atomic everyone thinks of all the stuff
they've been shown the mushroom cloud and all that there is virtually no
discussion about what happens when that goes off underground none so it's the
same thing with biblical stuff why does everyone think the Christ was born on
Christmas and there's a crucifixion a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper
and all that why because they've the moment was captured when when people
demanded answers for all of these things that were going on that everyone
knew about the there's groups that were aligning themselves to create a story
but different than 9-11 that what people think about the Bible today was created
over centuries so which even lends to more inaccuracy right like you will never
see anything even gesturing to a Roman crucifixion prior to 400 or 350 AD never
doesn't exist anywhere
see so like 400 years after the fact they develop all of the facts that
people believe in now but here's the other point I want to bring up and it
was just since you brought up Gnostics earlier just like 9-11 people were
demanding answers because it was shown to the whole world around the first
century early part of the first century when the Christ was executed there were
a lot of natural anomalies and rumors and stories and things going around
through the entire world known world at the time and people wanted answers why
what was going on and here comes Simon Magus and his cohorts to create the
story for you and that's that's also who funded and created Gnosticism and not
completely totally but initially I would suggest he gathered up all of the
various Eastern writers to conjure up whatever they like telling around the
campfire as holy writ and make up things about you know people that you know
were not like that at all
also very simple
everything I just said could be validated
although it's kind of hard to validate the Simon Magus stuff
not that it's untrue
it's the only logical way to look at it
he provided, let me put it this way, there was a soup, a molten soup, a broth
that was sitting around of questions and events
that couldn't be put together because remember everything was a secret
he provided one percent of the impetus that was enough to congeal the whole
thing just done to get biblical but he was the yeast and the leaven he was like
the leaven in the the whole lump right
you ever see certain catalysts you have a liquid big vat and you put a drop of
another chemical and the whole thing goes solid in five seconds
you know
yes
yeah so he was the catalyst for it
he wasn't because look he was accommodating the mindset also right
now the reason why you have all the stupidity everywhere in every level of
society bar none is because they're accommodating because they're
accommodating the public at large because let's just say all of all of the
government all of religion all of science institutions are are they are
they not in the public eye
they are the medical he was able to read that really well and he could play on
that
yeah well that was his thing he was a magician legend remain and other other
stuff so whenever you're in the public eyes and authority no matter how much of
an authority you are unless you're fixing and going on killing everyone and
subjugating them through terrorism or whatever
haha you have to accommodate their current mindset so it ends up being a
dog chasing its tail or or a catch-22 where you're now in a vicious cycle so
mankind has goes through you know a dog will chase his tail for so long before
he has to eat drink sleep or shit so what happens is you see the society the
chasing it's like a dog chasing its tail then the society has to eat sleep and
shit and it stops for a minute or a couple years or a decade or so and if
you ask the dog or society will be doing those chasing my tail oh yeah
thanks for reminding me and goes back to it again so it's not a big deal look
if you were a god and you were you knew that there had to be a 6,000 year
curing period how are you going to keep these people that are on idiot level
busy for 6,000 years that's a lot of popcorn and aspirin isn't it a lot of
watch yeah yeah so there you go yeah and believe it or not on the spiritual
realm there's not a lot of regard for the soul and the body the highest regard is
for the spirit of the individual that's why the gods have no problem wiping out
tens of millions of people at a time physically there's their spirits are
still maintained they get downloaded into the master hard drive but it's very
hard for people to contemplate that as being what's happening they at least say
well why did God allow that you know whatever God they reference which is no
God at all because they know nothing about them so anyway in connection with
this we mentioned a certain dark period that comes about around 500 BC I think
it's also worth mentioning that it's been documented that there was a dark
period before that possibly many dark periods but we can absolutely validate
the 1177 or around 1200 BC there was a quite a global civilization collapse
that occurred and that's documented around the end of the Bronze Age the
Mycenaean Minoan Trojan Hittite and Babylonian cultures took a nosedive all
literature seized all communication slowed down and the academics don't
really know why their hypothesis is that you had these quote-unquote sea people
of unknown origin that came in and just ravaged everybody sort of similar to the
Hyksos with Egypt but that really doesn't make any sense and what certain
other people have found particularly there's a guy called Eric Klein who's
written a book on it that's been kind of well received he shows that at that time
you had a sort of a perfect storm of things that just happened which created
a domino effect of natural disasters on one hand definitely invaders of some
sort there was certain places that were toppled because they were invaded but you
also had trade slowing down because you had certain supply lines that were cut
into and completely destroyed so that certain necessary trade routes were
obliterated and other things that caused sort of a similar 500 BC event to take
place well so then you can combine it with natural disasters and the
frequency intensity of natural disasters like for example when you hear of a
lightning storm or a thunderstorm now you know people go inside and hide right
could you imagine in the ancient days of thunderstorm that actually the lightning
chased people down and zap them in groups and fried them so you'd have a
lightning or thunderstorm and 10,000 people are wiped out well that doesn't
happen today you just take cover you see so the things were different to a
certain extent I would suggest that the prevalency of the interaction with
angelic beings and gods at the time was much higher than it is now as a matter
of fact that there is almost none right now for the past 2,000 years as if you're
familiar with the ancient texts there's a time period when it all gets shut down
that's the direct interaction right or in it so except for certain malevolent
beings so there's many aspects to it I think that what's so wonderful about the
coming time period now is that there'll be more disclosure around that time
period and I believe all the way back to the first verse of Genesis within this
time period so keep your eyes peeled yeah keep your eyes you know just be
aware of things that it you know for example in archaeology is a good place
to look you've heard of parts are out of place artifacts you know they find like
a clock or a hammer or a shovel or something looks like a spark plug and
coal that's supposed to be you know millions of years old and you know it's
not millions of years old or whatever but there's going to be a little bit of
an uncovering of ancient history through archaeology because if you don't
have physical even though it's a society where evidence means nothing really when
you have that physical evidence it's already it's already been considered
that if it's archaeological and validatable it's important you see all
right so this is a piece of paper or picture where people will say look it's
photoshop so not to say that a lot of the things that you're being shown in
archaeology are falsified many are believe it or not just like you know to
go to the Louvre those are not real paintings from Rembrandt and Matisse and
da Vinci those are copies but nonetheless the subject matter is going to grow and
the evidence will grow as well and also you're going to have a new crop of
younger people rising to authority type figures to rehash the narrative you know
versus all these older farts you know not that being old is bad but these
older people have sold out you know big-time right personally I look forward
to the archaeological aspects of the things I think I'm not you know cultures
like the Minoans and the Mycenaeans have been completely brushed under the rug oh
yeah the Trojans maybe they'll talk about the Trojan War but then they'll
only talk about it in a sort of Disney sense for the sake of a movie like
Hercules or something but um but the Trojan War has been Schliemann I think
who dug that up validated it specifically as Troy it was validated to
be Troy as as such you know not that they're not just calling a dig Troy it
was identified as Troy and what's interesting about what's been
memorialized about Troy it's highly spiritual you know with the ancient gods
right there was a particular lady you know you know like Apollo the Greek God
you know he liked interacting with women in lascivious ways and carnal ways and
this one woman didn't really want to be with Apollo but she did did it with him
anyway because she wanted she heard that if you went with Apollo sexually he gave
you the power of prophecy right to see the future so when Apollo found that out
he just she just did it for the prophecy not because he was Apollo he gave her a
curse that she will still be able to prophesy but the curse is that whoever
listens to her prophecies will not believe it and she's recorded as
prophesying that Troy would fall to the Trojan monarchy and they didn't of
course no one believed her you see and this is in the the myths but it's also
you know it'll it'll become evident through you know archaeological
findings and that will really short-circuit a lot of the separation
that you see you know in the mindset of ancient world you know an interaction
with the gods right we had a question in chat will we see more presence of the
gods in the next seven year period not really just knowledge of it let me just
state it this way when when you're in the past the 20 mid-2020s when you have
this particular young man who is of a Syrian descent he's around 20 right now
and he's going to claim Judean descent by the way he will eventually claim
himself few years after he rises to power with his group as God on earth so
that question you know is will we see the gods will it be will it be in your
mindset or real and can you identify a God and also do you understand what the
purpose of the gods interacting with man are and that's a big question I just
want to throw that little tidbit in there so in the future just like 9-11
you know the people right now if you say that the whole world's gonna fall for
someone that's going to be so charismatic and they will actually
believe his statement that he is God on earth and worship him as one for a short
time sounds pretty ridiculous right now so that's that's that's where I would
take that answer yeah you'll you'll see it no there let me just say it this way
emphatically it's all shut off until everything is wrapped up there there is
no more interaction open interaction with the gods for over 2,000 years why I
love poking fun at people who say they had a dream with such-and-such and Jesus
came to him I said a bunch of demons are playing a joke on you did it look
like the one they show you in church or on TV's yeah I said oh man you felt
you're a sucker so but but there will be dreams and visions given to people much
later on again because remember there's something called a testifying or
witnessing or giving the truth you know just like when you you know the
furniture you've heard of this certain furniture called an electric chair right
before they put you in that they read read out to you and you have to
acknowledge why you're there so before the kill shots are administered they're
gonna there's gonna have to be enough people to acknowledge the truth of the
matter it doesn't mean that it's going to change anything but it will be
acknowledged right it is worth stating that at least I don't I don't see any way
how we could logically come to a head in that way unless the supernatural does
actually manifest itself in a way that's palpable because people actually
have to believe that this guy is God and he can't do that without miracles we
know that right right they'll be well sure let me just say there'll be all of
the miracles and all of the fire in the sky and signs in the sky and in the
earth to accompany it yeah but it'll be a proxy you know it won't be like a God
appearing on his own behalf it'll be by proxy this man will be doing all of this
and his group will be doing these things because they're empowered and the
shift will of the people's minds won't be like oh well these are God's doing
this no these people are the gods you see that's the screw-up you see and when
you take into account how dim-witted people are right now it's very easy to
follow that through and see that you know but I don't know exactly how it's
going to happen again the 9-11 metaphor five years before 9-11 if you said Arab
hijackers are going to turn the World Trade Center into dust with box cutters
you know of course I'm saying it deliberately because that's how
ridiculous it is anyway right people would laugh at you but now still you
know even though people under their breath city that's a bullshit story
they're all just sitting back and and just like in the future and just like in
the past people surrendered all of their ability to interact lawfully or do what's
correct because of you know the external input you see see like in
America or the whole world surrendered their ability to act how they did before
9-11 at 9-11 because no one stood up and called bullshit right whenever Knesser
was going through the world no one you know stood up and called bullshit well
they would have needed an army to beat him right right or whatever and I'm not
saying that this should be any other way I'm just saying this is the the the
math behind it in other words the mindset is either prepared prior which
you'll see in many cases and when at the event happens there is a very rapid
control of the mindset to accept it I mean look look at the confusion with
Nebuchadnezzar even today if you actually look at it in a cut-and-dried
way when he went into Israel everyone thinks you know right now just a
convention is that all the Israelites were either killed or taken captive
right that's the common you when you bring up you know to the point zero one
percent of the people even know what you're talking about that's what they
think but if you actually study the history in the text of it those that
resisted and fought against Nebuchadnezzar were the ones that were
killed and taken captive the ones that accepted his conquest were just fine I
mean in other words they were spared you know the captivity and spares did
that do you feel on me on that yeah very big big difference in what people
think even that is so and I think it should also be mentioned that with
regards to the ten tribes people think that the ten tribes were conquered by
the Assyrians and then they migrated into Europe and became the British or
some shit like that whereas if you read for example the book of James I think
James opened up his letters to the ten tribes yeah those guys have actually
already come back well maybe not all of them but it's all towards the east all
those letters by the way were written towards the east not towards the west
like Paul for example so yeah but enough of those guys have made themselves known
to the point that they're being letters are being addressed to them so if they
migrated into Britain how is James writing letters to the ten tribes yeah
that's nonsense as well oh it's all nonsense right here's the thing Sam and
I how many times have I said this if there was anything even 50% or 30% or 20%
correct I wouldn't even you and I wouldn't be having these calls I
wouldn't be speaking you would know anything about Greek speak on my
personal level I would just say here's some good links this guy's got it this
guy's got it go do this or that there's nothing there's nothing going you unless
you you're you don't mind eating corn out of someone's poo it's really a lot
of porn porn yeah a corn porn eating corn out of poo and there is no fresh
clean cut and dried good corn being served anywhere right now and it's it's
really disheartening but it doesn't have to be look on the other hand the more
people hear Greek speak the guiltier they get they can't say later they never
heard it doesn't matter if they like it or not believe it or not or whatever so
you're it now it's very cut-and-dried it's very simple pertaining to these
ancient the sort of the post Christ periods in the the BC years I think
you've mentioned before that there was a small window of time when everybody knew
a scriptural truth and sort of set up religions to try to teach people mm-hmm
what was that window well there were two windows several there were always
windows open to that you look in Genesis when Jeremiah went around around the 5th
6th century BC he spread that concept I mean there are Native American cultures
there are cultures out in the Pacific Islands that were not considered to be
discovered until early 20th century that had almost things verbatim out of what's
called the Torah and they asked them you know where did they get this and they
said well you know they're great-great-great-great forefathers you
know this man came over on a winged whatever and spoke to them do we know
what those guys are called no just do some general research I you know I found
this out just by doing general anthropological research and finding
old writings there's a lot of stuff done on this in the early 20th century in
1930s on the mythologies of these primitive peoples and actually called
them primitive peoples you know and so the writers were bold enough then and
educated enough to know scripture that they would say well this is just
something out of scripture basically how did they get it well obviously if these
people are primitive and mythological and they're giving us stuff that's right
out of scripture well guess what scripture is primitive and mythological
then right you see and that was actually by the 1930s it was there was a
worldwide movement to start discrediting the writ you know so there were no there
were no megachurches other than the old cathedrals before then you know like the
American megachurches and I think Europe might have some now too I doubt it I
hope not but you know the evangelism right but that's all right these
megachurches and evangelist morons they're just accommodating the people
it's the people that have to people like oh don't go to a 501 c3 church I'm like
oh boy where do you start with that where do you start you know it's like don't eat
hot dogs on the street you know from a street vendor yeah okay so it doesn't
mean that he'll be there because most people that's what they want yeah let's
stick with the Middle Eastern regions connect concerning Israel I think you've
also said I think I was listening to one of the older sonic events and I didn't
really understand one of your statements when you said that about the
return of the Israelites into their land I'm trying to quote it verbatim so I
don't mean misrepresenting what you said it doesn't matter that the current
Israelites aren't the real people I think it was this that is descended from
the twelve tribes and that sort of their presence in the land and the
conflict that they have in the region is really just a geopolitical issue
that keeps them relevant so that the world is aware of them and issues can
unfold so that's right so how can you be of that persuasion so so at what point
do the real price you show up and get returned to their land that these other
ones are just placeholders there's two answers to that and it's very simple
again the first answer is when you read in scripture of Egypt it doesn't matter
if if if Egypt is completely populated by Japanese it's still Egypt so when
you hear about the people let's say let's just give a hypothetical fictional
situation here let's say we read that all the Egyptians left and all it was
populated by a Japanese when even after that point Egypt will still be referred
to as the nation of Egypt it's geographical okay that's the first point
it's geographical it doesn't matter there the mind of the mindset that
Israel is a state or you can take a buy an airplane ticket to go to Israel is
just that the people that are there don't matter again on the other level is
because various sections of the book are very emphatic and very specific that
during a certain time period near the end this whole to-do about the most high
is not just going to be by the descendants of Israel but also by the
other nations this shows up over and over and over I mean I wouldn't say as much
as other things but it's enough that I get the point right even in the New
Testament talking about being grafted in the hope but most of that is much much
later so when the second part that I just mentioned right now it hasn't
happened yet that's way later that's like just that almost right before the
end right in other words this this explanation won't make won't be
relevant at that time because there'll be so many other things going on it'll
seem obvious again but the point of the let's say Israel becoming a nation in
around the mid 20th century formally or you know as formally as can be in
today's world and the things that happened with the six-day war and the
things that are happening right now like the past few weeks and things are
going to be happening in the next year and four years and seven years are all
listed for quite quite well through allegory and prophecy and it doesn't
matter if if everyone in in Israel right now left and you know Egypt and Angola
came up and took over it would be the same but it just so happens obviously
that it's not I mean if you go look for example at the quote-unquote Judaism or
the Jewish religion in Israel right now is that is that lawful no you can you
should answer that in point two seconds no you're not think about you know it's
not so what's going on how can prophecy still take place well it's there
there's a time of indignation that's going to change there's a time of
turning around there's a time of acknowledgement those things haven't come
yet and it's not it's going to be a mixed bag of people another thing I
want to throw in there when you wrote it we just mentioned the letters being
written to the ten tribes of the ten groups those people still know who they
are so you know it you'll hear general discussions well those people there are
not you know of Israel well then who are they well let me tell you this the
people that are descendant from those original people know who they are most
of them I wouldn't well let's just say enough of them know who they are that
it becomes such a broad a broad open discussion you know they're not lost
and also the words that you see lost in the New Testament that's being used is
not an accurate translation the actual word that's being used is perished so
it's referring to those who have died in most cases it's not the one where he's
writing letters to the ten tribes let's say but you know there are other verses
that say I have come from the lost of the tribe of Israel it's not like you're
lost and wandering means you're dead because he came for what to show right
that they will be what res right you get it I'm not gonna say it you know be
resurrected I'll say it because the Christ's sole purpose was to show what
happens after you die and and it could be witnessed and then after that
everything's done because we've been shown everything how to live and all
this other stuff and now the only thing that was left that we haven't witnessed
is what happens after you die so anyway I hope that helped it did you want me to
keep expanding on that or that's enough
but in connect going on with sort of this idea of Israel being lawless part of
the purpose of having pagan nations in the first place is to show the chosen
people what not to do and you know what happens if you go down that route so why
and also hold on and also a lot of the laws are there to contradict the
behaviors of the nations are almost like if you look at the Ten Commandments in
Exodus 20 which are not the ones written on stone each one is almost a direct
contrary law against typical culture of Egypt so good so what I'm wondering with
regards to that is why Yahweh only picks one small group of people to be lawful
and billions of others to be pagan to make that point because I mean what
wouldn't a 50-50 distribution make more sense and also this is supposed to be
some kind of a learning no go ahead good no it could but you also have to
remember there are places in Scripture that described that the nations were
given to be ruled over and set up by the sons of God's so so you ever see a
father play with children in a big family does he take more play pieces or
does he also just take a play piece like everyone else you know in a game when
you have you see so he's playing fair by only taking one group of people to show
that he's a you know you know when one God you take this nation the next God
you take this nation I'll take this nation so he's also he's done just one
country that way to keep the playing field more even for them that's goes
back to what I was saying earlier don't take this personal this is something the
gods are doing and we happen to be caught in the middle of it makes sense
but also I mean if that if we want if this is a sort of principle that gets
used to illustrate a point who's going to be the pagan scapegoat in the
millennial kingdom the ones that don't get redeemed the ones that the ones that
decide to go through and satisfy the debt on their own accord they don't the
ones that don't get a new identity that's like everybody like everybody but
not everybody right statistically yeah right yeah and let me just say I've
gotten a couple emails when I said this the you will be you don't know what
terror is until the resurrection comes so and I don't mean like a horror film
gore splatting but a level of fright how many times you hear fear you know God
or fear Yahweh how many times do you hear that or read that and people like
oh why do I fear why do I want because it's not talking about what's going on
right now it's talking about what is going to happen I used to make it a
point when people I knew people that were semi-reasonable which is almost
impossible to find these days that are old and on their dying bed deathbed I
would go to them and I said listen you old fool these idiots around you are
lying you're not going to die and go with the Lord or anything the next thing
you know you're going to be you know an adult body like you were when you were
maybe 25 or 30 and you're going to be around some really scary looking
creatures anthropomorphic super dynamic just keep your mouth shut you'll be
shown what to do and all this so you know I give more detail and they and
they usually look at me with a stare like holy crap and then you know they
have like you know they their family or what is he saying I'm like just get at
it give me five minutes with this poor soul before he goes you know and you
come back with your bullshit later I'm sure if he thanked you before you died
yeah I did actually I've done it with in recent memory past few years was maybe
two or three people older people and one of them was on the phone I was like
listen listen you know this is what's gonna happen next I'm just letting you
know just the main thing is if you just keep your mouth shut so yeah it's it's
it's just yeah you don't want to know I mean but you I mean you do want to know
what's coming obviously the resurrection and all that stuff and what's lawful or
not but you don't want to really get into the minds of people now you know
other words to convince them anything or indulge in what they indulge in you
know or what they consider it's just absolute worthlessness it's kind of like
you know when you drive down the street and you see a pile of garbage you kind of
steer away from it a little bit or you know you don't want to go too close
because it might stink you know this is this is all of man's society right now
you know what they're putting out whether it's scientific stuff religious
stuff philosophical what they call spiritual you know it's just stinks I
mean let me just let me just couch that to me right it's so yeah you know it's
interesting though connecting with this idea of death in the resurrection the
Christians are not completely unaware of the idea although they largely discard
it but there's this term soul sleep which is probably more known less in
the mainstream and more at the periphery but still known by some some strands
particularly I think on the Mormons do talk about it that you know the soul
goes into disanimation but it's all is your breath but yeah either way but yeah
I understand the essence of the individual yeah and that is something
that is talked about in Christian circles but then it's largely put down
or it's used as a pejorative term like when you say soul sleep it generally
means that you're making fun of that idea because how could you possibly be
that you become disanimating that you know but they are aware of it like the
scholars yeah no no but what they are you ever heard my met the analogy of a
counterfeit note you just get a dinner napkin and a crayon or a pencil and
write a hundred on it in Bank of England or Bank of Spain or Bank of u.s. who was
Federal Reserve and go to the cash it no in order to be a counterfeit you have
to make it look very close to the original right or what people will
accept as what they consider to be original so all of it all of these
religions even science they they they're all setting something up so they're
plausible again it's the eating corn out of poop idea that what that they're all
all of them are like that and then to make it you know to make it even worse
the situation that humankind or mankind is under meaning women as well is that
this is all a social phenomenon there is nothing academic or scholarly or
intellectual about it none of them know what's written in the text that they
allegedly subscribe to they'll do a little bit of cherry-picking here and
there and reconstruct something but they cannot take the anything that's been
written holistically now of course obviously things like the book of
Mormon and a lot of the later buddhist writings and the writing system are just
downright ridiculous and is not enough prozac in the world to help anyone who
believes that stuff but more SSRIs or or any kind of tranquilizer or anything
like that I'm not discussing you know the the the nitty-gritty of the really
just stuff that you can discern as being just stupid I'm just discussing you know
the general framework of what it's supposed to be based on because in most
cases even the Quran has biblical references right so and and that goes
back to the Bible believe it or not and how many people know the Bible none
statistically so but it sounds sure sounds like a lot do this is part of the
insanity of the situation
oh what was mankind particularly in connection with that though as far as
the general hopelessness of humanity you've talked about the leaders hold on
it's not hopeless at all just because you're in a piss-poor state when you see
a baby with human society well when you see a baby in its diaper and it's
totally full of the brown stuff and the yellow stuff and it's got vomit on itself
is it hopeless not unless you say that's time to throw the baby away
because it's like that no it's going to be cleaned up that's why I refer to the
end as the mop-up crew I don't I don't refer to it as the destruction crew
surfacing mopping up means you're cleaning up but what you can't say is
that that baby's mode of self-government is hopeless which is why somebody has to
take care of them so human society it's surplus it's not very self-government
when they prescribe and subscribe to justice or subscribe and prescribe
justice what self-government is that that's a pre prefabricated goddess
religion they don't have to think of anything there's not much thought in any
of this stuff these scientists are basically if you really want to know
what these scientists and medical people are doing they're just taking old
philosophical parlor tricks from the ancient Greeks and reviving them as
science the way they communicate I had a discussion by the scientific type
recently and I said that he was getting on mixing science is best in science is
good but the way you're doing it it's not science and he actually agreed just
to make this short here is that the evidence and the experiments are not as
important as the authority of the individual who's putting it out into the
world I'm going to say that again in other words part of the thing I was
saying was that you're they're ignoring experimentation and they're
fictionalized so well the experiment and the conclusions and the theories are not
as important as who is who is speaking on it basically how many pH how many
doctorates and does he have that's more important than the actual experiment
itself I mean this is where you just you know I don't you know it's just you know
you got it if you don't laugh at it it's it's really bad you wish you could bring
down fire and brimstone or what is it and when John the book of Joshua when
they're fighting they drop a 70 pound rock on his head from outer space you
know so it's really it's actually I want to just get a piece of wet newspaper
roll it up and hit him on the nose with it well the wet newspaper you ever see
how it turns into like mush I mean this is this is what you guys are allowing
this is it's the same thing like now you get in trouble if you do child
rearing if you spank a child right these older farts need to be spanked like
children and you need to put them over like a Santa Claus type statue and pull
their pants down doesn't matter how old they are and expose their buttocks and
get a paddle you know how they used to in the old days you've seen old cartoons
like that you know publicly but I don't think that should be done at all I'm
just saying why would you do that to a leader of the people that's what these
people are they're leading they're the ones you look up to but I'm just saying
in an objective lawful world that's what would happen but piggybacking off
this leader of the people thing where are you getting that the most high sets
up leaders in accordance with how evil the society is because isn't it the
opposite that the leaders are given to lead society down a certain path of
depravity we see that with Israel they did what the king did not vice versa
no the people know where I get it from is just by observation and summation
summarize summarizing it okay but I'm talking about scripture now so yeah
saying that which is that no but the king did evil and then the people
followed we don't see the people pressuring the king to be evil and then
him giving well well they had they did have a lot of internal pressures David
had a lot of internal pressures to leave the throne at one point also yeah
but he didn't do it I know but that's not the point the pressure came upon him
you know obviously do it and he and he kept it together so what others were
where others weren't able to do it because if you look there was a
consistent pursuit of all the what the foreigners were doing well I mean we see
that certain points but we also see certain people like Jezebel coming in
and saying okay we're gonna do it this way screw everybody right certain other
people just showing up and saying no I'm gonna go with this other God and the
people are like okay mm-hmm but if the king don't initiate that it doesn't
really go that way and similarly when the Kings want to be righteous they say
okay we're gonna stop doing this and the people fall in line and those that don't
are just opposed I would go back and re-examine that go back and re-examine it
more instead of just you know the tall poppy of Jezebel go look at try to piece
it all together and see what's going on before they you know the intervals in
between the Kings also you know how it starts off and how one ends and how the
next starts off I'll give an example going on right now it's like saying for
example Donald Trump started Twitter you know how for example anyone it's
hard to avoid I open I turn on the computer and the home page says President
Donald Trump of you know American president tweeted this and I'm like what
what's that you know and it'll go down in history people will say that well he
started Twitter I'm like no Twitter was around people were using it and he just
did it because everyone else is doing it now I'm not going to use that as a
direct example in scripture but I want you to consider how much of it was in
place before these other people came about and and also you will also look at
when it comes time for a leader that doesn't accommodate the people just
like you see in the 20th century all of the bloody revolutions you know when
certain dictators took over and they wiped out the large swaths of their
population