And there we are.
Greetings, everyone.
Greetings.
And I believe we should be out there.
How are you doing tonight, sir?
Hey, okay.
Hopefully I'm coming through clear.
Yes.
Beautiful.
Doing well.
Good.
And your last show was just absolutely excellent, in my humbled opinion.
Oh, I didn't get that.
Go ahead, say it again.
I said your last stream that you did was absolutely beautiful.
Oh, it was good.
Yeah, I think so.
I must say I was more alive than usual.
Yes, you were.
Thanks.
Yeah.
What's interesting about doing these things is there's not much interest to personal...
Wow, I got a lot of background noise on you.
Oh, no.
A lot of background noise.
It's loud.
That's okay.
Well, let's...
Go ahead.
Okay.
I'm trying to...
All right, there you go.
You're probably muted.
Okay.
Yeah, so the last...
I was thinking maybe of discussing a few more things along the lines of the last Sonic event.
And I was wondering if there's anybody out there who's got any comments or questions to get into at all other than that.
And maybe it's best if you...
I wonder if you're probably muted.
This is just another beta test.
I think you are muted because it sounds quiet.
So I'm not in front of any computer right now.
I'm actually in the kitchen.
I'm making my way out to the garden, and I'll be back.
Yes, sir.
I was muted, and I was going to get to the Chantangle and see what we had going there.
Okay.
People can hear us both, which is always good to know.
Okay, good.
I'm going to be just moving about until another few minutes, and I'll be in.
I'll go into the office, and maybe I'll bring up some stuff, read out some more interesting stuff.
Maybe, maybe not.
But in the meantime, yeah, it's gotten quieter by you there in the background noise, Bruce.
But, yeah, the last event, I was just noticing that it's best to just keep repeating the same stuff.
It's kind of hard to move forward and give more detail at this point.
And I'll give an example.
When you look at, I don't know, what would you say what's put out to the inhabitants of this planet, what socially people find acceptable, whether it's legal, religious, scientific, or just basic fashion stuff, it's so absurd and so ridiculous that it almost bars one from wanting to instigate more of a flow of information or concepts at all.
It's sort of a strange, illusionary aspect to your own thoughts once you start discovering things and you start seeing what everybody else is thinking about these things we're not thinking.
I got the distinctive questions.
Okay, anybody in Chatango want to talk about anything in chat?
Because we're just testing again.
I have nobody saying anything.
You're kind of iffy touch and go it sounds like, Bruce.
But when we do listen to the archive, I think it's much quieter.
Oh, there you go.
I hear myself.
Okay.
I'm going to go into the office and see what I can maybe go into chat and see what's going on.
And, you know, we could also drop this stream.
And I could also start the stream on uncommon radio and try to do a recording and all that.
All right.
And just monologue it.
This is also true.
Is the audio better now?
Yeah, much quieter.
Okay, good to know.
Ah, the hive.
Okay, I just turned on the other machine.
I'm here in the office now.
So let's see what's going on.
There's some people in chat.
Okay, yeah.
So let's just take it from the top, I guess.
The last sonic event I did was pretty much a recap.
But I always add in a little bit more detail, slightly more.
And perhaps the point was to give a few more references.
I think that came through pretty well.
It just shows you how absurd it is.
Again, I wanted to give an example.
You know, when you look how people what they call banking, by the way, you know, most people haven't noticed that all the banks are closed.
Right.
You know, but it's Greek.
That sounds ridiculous.
I go to I go to the bank all the time.
Right.
Well, they're they're not really banks.
You can go look at their financial institutions is the general category.
But they're banking associations.
They're not even really they're not even corporations, really, even though they do have a corporate side, because, you know, when they hire a janitor or so-called employees or a sign maker or whatever, they have corporate architecture, you know, but they're not that either.
What's interesting is if you study the federal laws, what 99 percent, if not all of what the banks are doing is unlawful and you're ready illegal.
But no one knows and no one cares.
Yet when you, let's say, go to apply for something and banks give legal disclosures, they tell you, oh, we have to abide by federal laws and federal law state.
We have to share your personal information and Social Security number and all this other stuff.
You ever notice how formal and prim and proper they seem.
Right.
But they're illegal as hell and unlawful.
They're so unlawful, the stench goes up to heaven.
But they're also illegal.
So what's the point here?
Well, should you not deal with them?
No, actually, no one should.
I'm not trying to promote abstinence from them because you're going to have a super hard time because we're not in a society that you could function easily without them at this point, at least most people.
But I'm telling you, it is a nasty, nasty thing.
This is not opinion.
This is actually you could prove it.
So at the same time, it's the same thing that's going on with the churches, the same thing that's going on with the doctors, the synagogues, the mosques and all this other, you know, every aspect of society.
It's just a horrendous mess.
It's just a, I don't know what you would say, it hasn't gotten to the point where it's introverting and causing outward destruction, meaning where people can't get any food or water or shelter and you see dead bodies everywhere, right?
But other than that, it's just as bad as bad can be, all of these institutions and what people are working with, right?
All of them, not some of it.
But so the interesting point here is that you're only basically a hair's width away from the point where you go where there is no food, there's no water and just dead bodies everywhere, you see?
Because everything else is so unlawful and so illegal at this point in terms of your institutions that that would be almost like a righteous retribution from another society for how you're performing.
I hope that made sense.
Yes, it did.
But it's like dropping the hammer on somebody that's doing bad things, quote-unquote, to stop them from doing what they're doing.
Society's been at this point for almost 100 years now.
I would say more than that.
Generally, on a liberal way, a few thousand years or a couple of thousand.
So it's called like the sword of Damocles.
It's something like a sword hanging over your head.
You know, it could drop at any time.
And no one really understands that aspect of it cosmically that I've seen outwardly.
There's still too much opinion and emotion and whatever.
But the irony of what I'm saying is what is true irony is just like on the last Sonic event, I was reading off some laws that were easy to access.
Actually, you could try to study the law.
Someone, I think, this morning put in chat, they're looking at the laws.
You're not going to find anything like that.
I shouldn't say you're not going to find anything.
What they do is they have so many laws that you start reading.
It all looks very benign and like everything's in accordance to what they're doing.
So, in other words, it takes a tremendous amount of work.
And you're only going to find it if you understand the premises of why there are so many laws and why everything is so illegal already and how it's hidden.
Just like I see people often tell me, well, I'm reading the Bible.
I'm reading scripture in Hebrew interlinear.
I'm like, yeah, so?
So what?
You could read it all every day for the rest of your life.
It doesn't mean you're going to understand it.
You see, it's an interesting point of view to share with someone.
They're like, well, you know, how else am I going to understand if I don't read it?
I'm like, yeah, because the interesting point here is how many people profess to work in the law and don't know the law?
Just about everyone.
And the same with medicine and the same with the religious people, the scientific people, what have you.
So there's a very, very interesting condition on the earth right now.
It's as if everyone was used to driving around or living in complete fog.
And you try to tell people, well, you see, this is just a fog condition.
They're like, well, yeah, I guess so, yeah.
But we've been, you know, this is just how things are.
I'm like, well, you know, normally it wouldn't be foggy.
Normally you should have sunny days.
So either way.
The contrast of what is really going on and what people think is going on is huge still.
And you've heard many times people say, well, you know, it's all an illusion or this is an illusion or whatever.
It really, really is.
The illusion is even greater than ever.
And it's not an illusion where, well, it's whatever you want it to be or whatever.
No, no, no.
It's an illusion in a sense that what people think is real and what is really going on in front of them is so very different that you can only call it their perception and what they think is, you know, reality, illusionary.
So not because it's really, you know, something that's fabricated as such, but because they just can't notice it at all.
So why continue?
You know, why go on with more in-depth on many other subjects and even ones that have been brought up?
You know, I don't see it.
But at the same time, I think it begs to have a continuance and a little more definition and a little more detail.
Kind of reminds me of that movie, They Live, when the guy puts the glasses on.
Yeah, why bother?
Yeah, why put the glasses on?
Then what are you going to do?
Right?
What are you going to do next?
Exactly, yes.
Well, there's a very simple solution to it.
Set yourself apart from it as much as possible.
Right?
Correct, yes.
But either way, yeah, I'd say, yeah, there's a lot of fat to chew, as they used to say in Europe, regarding any subject and just continuing on many things and doing maybe projects or modules based on things people have asked.
And, yeah, just expanding on it.
Because the whole thing is, like someone said, well, where do we go to get this information?
I'm like, nowhere.
It's right in front of you the whole time.
What do you mean, where do you go to get this information?
Like I mentioned, you know, the New Age idiots talk about, don't be judgmental.
Actually, most people do.
They say, don't be judgmental.
That's correct.
But only from the perception or the perspective that you lack the discernment as a society to be judgmental.
You're pretty good at making poor judgment.
So why bother if you know you're not going to have a good outcome, right?
But judgment is very, very important.
If anyone, quote unquote, drives a car, if you go to an intersection and see a red octagon, you just hit the gas, keep going, right?
No.
That means stop.
And what do you do when you stop at an intersection?
Judge.
You better be judgmental.
If you're traveling along in a, you know, call it a motorized wagon or engine-driven wagon, you have a cluster of gauges in front of you.
Something says fuel and has F on the top and E on the bottom.
When it goes all the way to E, what do you do?
I don't want to be judgmental right now.
You're using judgment all the time.
What's that sound?
Your stomach's growling.
I don't know, man.
Constantly making judgments.
You know, when you're walking, what you're doing, see, walking is displacing your center of gravity.
So each time you take a step, it's actually a controlled fall.
So what happens is you lift one foot and you displace the center of gravity of the body forward and the body starts falling forward.
And then you put the foot down to stop that falling action.
And then you repeat that action.
Guess what that's called?
Walking.
That's why, like in the cartoons, if someone throws a banana peel down or something slippery, when you go to stop that falling action and there's no resistance on the surface, what happens?
You can't stop the falling action and it continues.
That's why people say, oh, yeah, he slipped on that and fell.
I said, no, no, no.
What's going on is you're falling and he couldn't stop the fall.
That's why he continued to fall.
You want me to repeat that or you got it?
Nope, I think you did good on that one.
Because walking itself is displacing the center of gravity and going into a falling condition.
And the reason you put your foot out is to stop that and repeat it.
And that's how you move forward.
You're actually falling, you see.
Think about it for a minute.
That's a metaphor, a very strong one.
Well, you know, someone could ask, I've heard this, I haven't brought that up in a long time, but someone says, well, Greg, then how are we supposed to walk?
Just fine.
Just don't, when you need to, in order to have a gracious looking walk, right, you need to have a very good systematic way of controlling the fall so you can look like you're walking and not falling.
And that's what society is doing.
They're just falling out of whatever.
And they just stop it when it gets to a certain point.
So this is not to be critical on them, you know, because this is a tremendous amount of stuff that can be imparted regarding health, what's called health.
You ever hear people say, oh, that's really healthy.
You know, like olive oil is healthy or brown rice is healthy or you eat healthy.
That's not true.
It's healthful.
The body itself is either healthy or not.
The food isn't healthy or not, unless it's still growing.
So it's healthful.
You see, it promotes good health.
I'm not saying that to be an ass, in a way, like nitpicking on words, but it's just a mindset there as well.
Because I used to tell people, you know, as a joke, you know, you know, someone says, well, you know, I'm vegetarian and I eat health food.
I said, you look too healthy to be eating health food.
You know, because usually people that are into that, quote unquote, and they wear it as a badge of honor, don't look healthy at all.
You ever hear of like a hypochondriac?
You know.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, they don't look healthy.
But that's not true across the board.
I'm just saying that there's a level of mindset to that as well.
But whenever you feel you have to do something, you ever hear people say, I have to do this, right?
That's because it seems like you're doing it out of time, like you should have started before, you see.
The proper way to do things is to build on them gradually, like if you go to a gym, you know, you go in the first day or the first time, and you're sort of intimidated because you approach the equipment and you find that it's almost, well, it offers a lot of resistance, sometimes insurmountable, and you're tired quickly.
And you see all these other people around you doing much more than you are, and they maybe look more fit as well.
And it's real easy to become intimidated or discouraged, right?
You don't say, well, I should have started this a long time ago.
Well, maybe you should have, but why?
You know, just now that you are starting it or doing it, you will approach it gradually.
The body adapts to the increased stress, and you get stronger, and you keep going back.
And after a month, you're doing more, and after three months or a year, you end up looking like everybody else in there, fit and strong and able to manage and work all the equipment in the gym.
The problem with the society right now with what's going on is that they're in a static condition, just like before you went to the gym, right?
You're in a static condition, let's say, unfit, not strong, not being able to lift anything.
And this is pretty much what's been going on with society, the new people that are brought into society and all that.
For example, you approach someone in any of those entitled classes, whether it's legal, medical, scientific, or any of these things that society deems as being relevant and important.
And if you approach with proper information the people that run these places, meaning the legal society, medical society, religious society, scientific society, academic society, even in the engineers, they don't want to hear anything.
They want to be static, but yet there's change.
How many times do you hear, oh, we're improving the medical field, we're improving the religious field, we're improving this, right?
Where does that change come from?
Is it really change or is it not?
And have they ever gone back and covered all the failures and all the misgivings and all the stuff they ignored before?
The answer is no.
So that is a very simple way to accept what's going on.
As a person finally getting some of their eye open on many things and setting oneself apart, you brought up some stuff that you talked to the other fellows about, and it was brought up in chat here.
Oh, in private.
Yeah, I just saw this.
After the show was over, we sat around for another 20 minutes or so, and they were like, oh, this is, I said, you know, I'm just going to keep repeating myself.
That's fine.
This is what it is.
But there's a lot more that could be talked about, like what?
And I just covered a couple of things that I haven't really discussed or brought up in public before.
And they just got quiet.
So you guys still there?
And you could see the cross-eyed rabbit in the headlight stare through the microphone.
And that just tells me, you know, it's correct to not really discuss a lot of things in public.
Oh, so what would it be?
Well, it's not to be talked about in public yet.
Yeah.
Well, it's not like, you know, something's going to fall on your head tomorrow and I didn't tell you.
It's, of course, along those same lines in the subject matter and the mindset that I try to bring up whenever, you know, I do a sonic event.
I can tell you some of it is like, well, let's just go into it a little bit.
How's that?
Let's give a little introduction.
Part of it is what energy is in terms of plugging in sockets and all that stuff, you know, what people call electricity.
Another part is what people call ancient Ritz.
I talked a little bit about a couple of concepts there, something that was going on in the beginning that people are not aware of, even though it's right in front of them.
It's just right there, but no one really sees it.
Another thing was, let's see.
Oh, human life, human life, basically, why we're so different than everything else, but in a little more detailed fashion.
So those types of subjects.
So we could bounce around maybe a little bit on either one of those.
And, you know, either one of those, we could open up and do a three-hour discussion on stuff that I've never really discussed openly before,
which I think is best probably saved for the future once we get the radio thing more together,
and I get off my butt and get an established format to store these archives and do like a module thing,
you know, like part one, part two, part three on a subject, you know, and introduce them properly.
Yeah, but you still have time.
You know, what's interesting in terms of timing, starting this spring is a new period.
And I want to get into discussing the prophetic timekeeping also, how that works.
You know, there's four seven-year periods, but you have to overlap.
Here's something.
You also have to overlap on the four seven-year periods, seven four-year periods.
Do you see like when you take…
Do you see that, or is it…
I guess I'm a little foggy on that one.
Could you clarify just a smidge?
Well, after 1998, there was a five-year.
I think I've gone over this, but it hasn't really stuck around with many people or many people haven't gotten it.
When time ended around 1998, it was around 1999, the spring or fall of 1998 roughly, because years were lost and then they were added on.
And then so I would say it's around the year 1999, what, you know, you would measure as on the Pope's work schedule.
Well, there's a five-year period before man's system, this final system comes into place, right, because five comes before six, which is man.
Man as an anthropomorphic man on the surface of the earth.
And then you have four seven-year periods with a three-and-a-half period thrown in in the end, as long as it's all less than 40, right?
So you see you end up being like 32.
You know, when you throw 28 plus three-and-a-half, you end up being around 31-and-a-half or 32, because remember when you have your ninth birthday, let's say, you're in your tenth year?
Right, right.
So it would be 32 years, right, or around there.
So it's interesting, these four seven-year periods, you know, the number seven, right, well, there's almost like a fractal aspect, too.
Well, you can't ignore the number four.
So there's also seven four-year periods.
So you have, you know, four seven-year periods.
You have seven years as one period.
Seven years is another period and so on.
So, you know, seven years is another period.
Seven years is another period, right?
That's four seven-year periods.
But you overlap over them as points of like an accent point on certain languages.
You put an accent over a letter to give a little emphasis, right?
So well, over that four seven-year periods, there are seven four-year periods.
So you have a four-year period, a four-year period, four-year period, four-year period, four-year period, right?
So imagine just having a yardstick and it's got four seven-year periods on it.
Now you have another yardstick.
It's the same length, but it has seven four-year periods on it.
That one is divided differently.
Now when you overlap both of them, the middle of both is at 14 years, isn't it?
Because, right, you have the four seven-year periods is seven on one side, seven on the other because it's four.
But when you divide the seven four-year periods in half, well, it's 14.
So what's interesting about that, that's the point where we are right now.
We're 14 years into this.
Because 14 plus 5 is 19 plus 19, 99, 98, right, is 2018.
Do you see that?
I've been talking about – yeah, this is more – this is like part of – there's plenty of people, not plenty, a handful, that I've chewed their ear off for six hours on Skype calls years ago and even recently on these matters in private.
I'll just go on how to learn how to keep time for four hours on Skype without repeating – I think you've experienced some of that in private with me.
Yes, I have.
Right, and none of it has been discussed yet publicly because, I mean, just look, look around.
I mean, why?
Well, you know, I think the people who are mostly wanting to really open their eyes while being a curious species that we are, and I think that's what attributes to a lot of this.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so too.
So now it's a curiosity thing.
Well, I mean – I'm being facetious.
Yeah, it's beyond that.
Yeah, I guess – I think maybe if anyone's listening right now or down the stream will get their ears perked up when they hear that because I don't think I've ever really said that publicly before or with emphasis, maybe in passing.
So – but what's interesting is you ever hear sometimes, you know, when you read the biblical text, you know, why is the almond tree so important?
You know, like let's say how I could come out and say, well, you know, the Christ was executed.
He was stoned to death while he was nailed to an almond tree.
Well, how do we know?
Well, we can take a hint.
I'm not – you know, we're not that dense.
We're not that stupid, right, because if you read the biblical text, there's at least 20 references to the almond tree, something important happening, which even alludes to even the actual event.
But it doesn't quite say it like, you know, just, you know, the Christ was nailed to an almond tree and then stoned to death.
You don't find anything, but, you know, but there are all these hints, you see.
That's the difference between a hint and a statement, you see.
Right, right.
Yeah.
So one aspect of it is regarding timekeeping, I've been hinting at least for the past five years, which would be around 2020, 2012 on the pagan work schedule, that the important year is not 2012.
I was saying around there it's around 2018.
I've been saying this for a long time.
Well, guess what's approaching?
Yes, it is.
So I'm very patient about these things.
You know how many people say, oh, it's 2012, oh, you know, we're all going – it's the end of the change.
And then when it comes, well, we didn't notice it, but it did change, you know, or, you know, we're going to have a financial collapse in June, or the world's going to end on September 23rd.
And, you know, what's going on with you, you know?
And nobody says nothing when they fail.
No.
But I'm telling you this is a very critical year.
But, you know, when I say critical, if you don't know what's coming, and even if you do to an extent – well, actually, if you don't know what's coming, you'll be jostled a little bit.
You'll see there's something strange going on.
But if you know what's coming, you're like, oh, shit, there really is, let's say, a behind-the-scenes or higher forces controlling everything, you see.
Right.
And I think that's what a lot of people are trying to bring themselves to.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so what's interesting about that, that whole thing, is when you look at all the people on the planet,
when I mean, you know, not all the people, but, you know, when you're aware of how many different nations there are on the planet,
what you call race, religions, all the varieties, societies, right, of people on the planet,
it's very interesting to watch what one particular group is doing that the gods have chosen as a timepiece.
You know how you hear in Scripture, well, Israel are God's chosen people?
And a lot of quote-unquote Christians take offense to that, or Americans or whatever, you know, because they want to feel important too.
It has nothing to do with being important per se, inherently, other than the inherent fact that they were chosen to be a time marker.
Right.
So you're going to see some pretty major changes starting to take place this coming year with those people as a group, in name.
Because, you know what I mean, a lot of people say, well, we don't know who they are.
You mean the Jews?
I'm like, no.
You know that term Jewish is not a real term, even though people use it to apply to themselves.
It's a religious term.
Like, you could be a Catholic and then convert to be called Jewish later, can't you?
Or you could be Jewish and then deny and say I'm Buddhist now.
But typically in that part of the world, if you're in quote-unquote Israel, Jewish just means you're blood also.
But you see, if you say Catholic, it doesn't mean, Roman Catholic doesn't mean that you're bloodline.
But the interesting thing about the term Jewish, if you even look in what's called the King Jimmy version, it's the word Judean.
So it's really the Judeans, which are one-tenth or one-twelfth of the group to really watch.
It's just a time marker because, you know, the gods don't use the wind-up toy or the Pope's work schedule.
And if they gave you the fine points of the astronomical aspect of timing, I don't think people are aware of how to keep that.
So it's very easy to affect a certain group of people, watch their behavior, and now you know what should be coming next when something happens to this group of people.
I mean, you used to see that all the time when children are interacting as different groups.
They're like, hey, listen, when we throw snowballs at the guys that wear red jackets, then you're going to run over to the back to the basketball court and take the stuff, right?
Or the basketball, you see?
They always have a certain timing using an event.
You know, even children do it.
So what's interesting around this time is a new time period starting, but it's a center focus point.
And there will probably be some more discussions on that in the near future.
And I hope I gave a little bit of an introduction that you could sink your teeth in instead of like, well, he just brought that up and he should continue.
I think it's something people could sit back and think on a little bit more.
You know, when you brought up the topic about all the different groups, religious groups, and what they hearken back to in their pagan worship, that was an eye-opener.
Yeah, I've been kind of repeating.
If you look at all the different sects of all the different religions, why are they different?
Like, you know, the Roman Catholics or Christianity, you have Eastern Orthodox Roman Catholic, you have the Protestant and Lutheran and all that, and then you have the English Anglican.
They're all very different, the way they do their liturgy and what their doctrines are.
And then you come to South America, they're different with their skulls and, you know, the Day of the Dead and all this crap.
And then you go to other parts of the world, Asia, they have their own version.
It's just the same stuff that they've been doing geographically, you know, pagan stuff with just a new name on it.
The Muslims are a really good example for that.
Look at the various sects of Islam, right?
They're doing still the same stuff that they were doing thousands and thousands of years.
They just call it Islam now.
Yeah, it's very simple.
None of them know anything about what they're saying.
And that's a fact.
The reason why is because let's say you consider yourself a religious conscript or you've pledged allegiance to one of these religions socially or whatever religiously.
You're just as ignorant as a bag of hammers or a bag of nails or a doorknob.
Now, one of these days you might get the inkling that, you know, this is supposed to be – they tell you it's based on the Bible, right?
Let's just use the Christians.
And you start reading it in context, not just – like you ever see how they do it, there's one verse and then the idiot at the pulpit stands up and just talks about, you know, whatever?
No, no.
If you read the whole thing in context, you're going to say, well, why is it that everything that this religion that I subscribe to is doing – everything that they're doing is in the don't do section and they don't know or do anything in the do section of the Bible?
Why?
What's going on here?
I better leave this group or I better put that down because I like the jelly donuts and the bacon that they serve here.
You see?
Right.
And there's also a reckoning.
What's interesting is there's a – well, I should say a reckoning, but in America you have also generally you have the evangelical, what's called the Bible belt, and you even have the harshest part, which is the buckle, the belt buckle of the Bible belt, right?
Oh, yeah.
And that's their own cultural thing.
What they do is they do Pledge of Allegiance in churches.
Well, not maybe now, but they have the American flag in the church next to the cross, the pagan cross.
So they have their own little fashion, which is basically the military that expanded into the West across the plains.
That's what they did also, that tradition.
So it's very – it's kind of funny to watch.
I mean the planet is inhabited by, should I say retards?
Retard meaning not in a pejorative term, but it can be.
It just means slow.
Well, yeah, something has happened to the personality.
I see where you struggle for the word.
Well, the character, that's another thing people don't quite understand.
I talk about the body, the soul, and the spirit, and the spirit is the mind.
And what's interesting about that, when you combine it with what's called free will, there's a certain amount of things you can do on your own volition and your own desire, and it really is your own, even though it's still external input, because you process it according to the spirit or the mind you were given.
It's like when you hear some people say, well, I'm very mathematical and technical, and the other person says, well, I'm not.
Well, I'm very musical.
That's because they have different spirits, right?
Yes, yes.
The part, you know, you don't have free will, that you're not going to live to 500.
You're going to die.
You're going to walk on the earth.
You're not going to fly around like a bumblebee, unless you're Muhammad Ali or something.
But all these things are, you know, you could see what your limitations are, and you also see what your free will is at.
And where your free will is, what makes you you, is where you start to make harsh choices, or if you're conscious of it, to even make the choice of assessing your own character.
Like how many people can, you know, and improving it or letting it go or letting it degrade.
How many times do you hear people say, well, you know, I smoke too many cigarettes, you know, and I should stop that, right?
Or I drink too much, you know, I should stop that.
Or, you know, I pick my nose in public too much, I should stop that.
Or, you know, I'm not a very good dresser, I should probably dress better.
You see, those are all like self-assessments, you know, and you can change that.
Those are all things you can change, make the effort, and that's where you have the free will to develop your own character on that, you see.
And that's where the focus and the importance of being able to do that, A, noticing that you do have that ability, B, noticing that you can self-assess, and C, noticing that you can develop the attitude or the direction of that assessment once you've decided to.
That's what's going on, and that's what I brought up earlier.
If you look at a religious idiot, and it doesn't matter what religion, if they're sitting there and they're like, wait a second, what is this supposed to be based on?
Let me go at least look at that founding document or what's been memorialized.
They will find all of them, not some of them, that what they're doing is contrary to what they should be doing and devoid of what actually what they're doing is in the abominations don't do, and sometimes prohibition, and what they should be doing is unknown.
Well, then that's where the person might say, well, you know, they do the character assessment there, and they say, well, these guys, according to, on one side of their mouth, they say they believe in the Bible or believing in it is, and believing it could be two different things too, but it's supposed to be based on that, but they know nothing or what they're doing is against it.
I now need to make a decision because I have the free will to either stay here with these idiots or leave.
And abandon this debauchery, you see?
And doesn't that affect one's character?
Like a weak character will say, no, I'm going to stay with the group.
Whereas a slightly stronger desire to develop stronger character development will say, screw this church crap, I'm out of here, right?
Right, right.
And that goes with anything.
There's people, there are many professions like that.
I've met at least two or three attorneys, what they call attorneys that were groomed to be attorneys because they grew up in a family of them and went to school and immediately got placed in, let's say, they didn't get entry-level positions because they had contacts or connections, as they say.
And after a few years they quit because they actually looked into it and they saw what they were doing.
They didn't know any law.
That's why I say attorneys don't know any law is because I've gotten this from other attorneys, right?
They don't know any law.
And also what they're doing is illegal and unlawful and just downright immoral.
And a lot of those attorneys that discovered this made a character assessment and said, I'm going to leave here because this is not correct.
This is not right.
The same thing with people in the clergy and the same thing with people in the medical field.
I had met someone who used to be a doctor and wanted to deny that he was because it was such a joke.
If you ask him what he did, he says, well, I worked as an inspector in this firm and I did this and that.
You had a couple of beers and you sat around and he would start bringing up some points that you knew only someone that went to medical school would know.
You're like, well, did you study medical?
He says, medical, academic stuff?
He says, well, look, I don't like talking about this, but I went to medical school and I got a Ph.D. in medicine, but I found that what they do is repulsive.
And I denied the whole thing and went on a different course of life.
You see, that's a character again of the individual.
Correct.
I do a lot of shin-kicking of these guys, priests, rabbis, imams, doctors, attorneys.
I don't get onto the politicians too much because they're just like clowns, really, if you really want to – and I mean clown in the truest sense.
They put on a face and they go out with the big shoes and the horn and the funny color.
The entertainment.
Yeah, I mean it's like tits on a bull.
You can't get anything out of them, but you like teats.
Most animals, both male and female, have teats.
A male dog has teats.
I remember being very young and naive once.
I had a puppy and it was around flea season and I'm getting a tweezer and I'm pulling on his teat.
And someone says, well, males have teats also.
Well, what are they there for?
Why do they have them?
They're not doing anything.
I mean they're never going to have to use them.
I thought it was a tick.
Yeah.
You see?
You know my point?
That's politician.
It's just teats on a bull.
But the reason why I knock these entitled leaders over – I wouldn't even say they're leaders because leadership is actually cosmic so much.
It's because I actually know them and I think I've brought this up several times.
It's not like I formed an opinion because I read a Bazooka Bubblegum Rapper or I had a little short antidote about them.
It's because I actually know these people.
Well, I don't know them like in a way where we hold hands and take windy walks together, but I've come across them for many, many years, and I started noticing the similarities by using discernment, the similarities within each group.
And then just actually literally lifting a finger and approaching the reference materials that they were supposed to use as educational material and also the guidelines that they are supposed to work and live by, which I've showed I think on the last Sonic event a few.
And literally one of these days we might do a Sonic event where I do go through all the 50 codes and then maybe do a YouTube on it where you have the list – not a YouTube but something where you have a list and you have a hyperlink within the – a link that jumps to it based on time.
So if you have 50 codes in a one-hour audio in the description, you show this code is from 1 minute 20 to 2 minutes 15, and then from 2 minutes 15 you click on that.
It brings you to the next code like a reference book.
You have a hyperlink within the video.
A hyperlink within the video would be great to do hyperlinked reference stuff.
But actually this stuff I was in a recent discussion with someone regarding some legal stuff.
I said don't – you can't get hyped up on going after these guys just because you hear me talk about something because they will eat you for lunch because they don't go by any laws.
They are vile and – they are violent and vile.
They feed off of people's desires to go after them, you see.
They are very vile.
They will kick your butt.
Yeah, they feed on that.
So you have to do it in a very tactful way and you have to do it properly.
And there's no reason to go after them because they are actually accommodating the masses.
I think I brought up the point how what's called illegal drug possession, narcotics and all that has been decriminalized.
It means there's no jail time for that, right?
It's a civil matter.
I think people can figure out in a judicial system what civil and criminal is, right?
So I brought that up.
So if you bring up to anyone – let's say to go to someone's grandma or someone's priest or someone's doctor or just someone and say, hey, this guy was caught with a duffel bag of cocaine.
What should the authorities do to him?
Oh, he needs to go to jail.
That's criminal, right?
All the people think that, don't they?
But the codes – yeah, that's because of the people, the way the people think.
So I try to make that point.
Just because you know that the law says the opposite, like Federal Reserve notes, right, Title 12, Section 411.
Go out to the merchants, all these idiots with stores and businesses and try to bring up what a Federal Reserve note is.
They're going to laugh you right out of there.
Some of them might get mad.
There's no reason.
So actually, you're in a position right now in society that doing the right thing is destructive.
So what is your only option?
You get it?
Set yourself apart.
Right.
And how do you fix society?
And if doing the right thing is destructive to society, and if the right thing comes, what happens to society?
It gets destroyed.
That's why when you read the ancient writs, all this destruction that is brought upon mankind in quote-unquote the end times, who is it being done by, the malevolent forces or the good guys?
It's the good guys doing it.
And you've never gotten that explanation before, ever.
Because you're at a point right now where the people are incapable of doing what's right.
Incapable.
I think I've said they're irreparable.
And I don't mean you specifically, listening or whoever.
I mean the society as a group.
And I mean 99% of the society.
Not like 50-50 where they vote someone in and 51% gets it.
No, no, no, no.
99-99%, 9-9-9%.
It's irreparable.
If you go back and think about how long it has taken to bring mankind to this dumbed-up position that we are currently in, it boggles the mind.
They always were like that.
Here's one thing I haven't got on.
It's very easy to swim along when you do these sonic events.
What I mean by swim along is bring up a topic that you know people will readily accept and discuss it.
Not because I'm taking them for a swim or something or whatever.
Because I know that it's easy to listen to.
Well, for most people, not all people.
But what's even more difficult to listen to, believe it or not, is from a cosmic level and a spiritual level, man has always been this way.
Because we like to say, oh, yeah, we're dumbed down now.
Or dumbed up.
One example would be what's circulating on the Internet, which is true, is an 8th grade final exam from 1890-something.
And even your best academics can't get 10% on that test.
Have you seen the 8th grade final exam from 1892 or something?
No, I have not.
It's online.
Put in like a late 19th century 8th grader final exam, one-room schoolhouse.
I mean, there's very few people alive who could even complete half that exam today, right?
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, even if you have five college degrees, you can't do it.
So you could say from that perspective, yes, people are dumbed down.
But I can go back and show you how they've always been this way.
Just reading the ancient, you know, reading the, well, I hate to say this word, even the King Jimmy, you can see how people were way back in the day, and it just boggles the mind.
Well, what do you mean, back in the day, in what way?
Well, okay, back in the Canaanites, back in those days.
Yes.
Oh, in the setting of the Bible, the biblical setting, let's say around Judges or something?
So 3,000 years ago, something like that, you mean?
They were already like that.
Yeah, they were.
My, my, my.
Now, it's actually from the beginning, what's interesting is one of these days, one of these days, maybe in the next year or less, we'll do a discussion.
I think it has to be done in several parts on what's really being said in the Book of Genesis, not because I said so, but because it's right in front of you and you're not noticing.
You know, and just read, has anyone ever read out of the Book of Genesis, read out of it?
I would say no, not really.
Yeah, there are those who have.
The ancient sages that comprehended Genesis said that if you comprehend the Book of Genesis,
B'Deshith, right, the Hebrew text, you should keep it to yourself
and only discuss it with others that admitted to have understood it and can prove it, you know,
by saying, hey, and those that don't know need to just accept that they know what they know about it
and shut up and sit down and not dig into it.
This is what the ancient sages used to say in the rabbinical culture, by the way, even back in the day thousands of years ago.
Now, I think there's a time to start cracking that open, right, don't you think?
I mean, it's right there in front of you.
A beautiful subject, for sure.
And I have bits and pieces.
Now, the thing is, do I comprehend and understand it?
If I say yes, do I sound cocky?
Well, too bad.
Yeah, it's why.
Why can't I say I understand it and comprehend it?
Because I'm reading out of it.
I'm not reading into it.
It's like approaching something objectively is the only way to walk away and say, yes, I see what's held within it, right?
Right, right.
Just a subject on light alone, just the very first few verses of that, you could spend months on that.
Well, here's the thing, yes, but here's the thing, the subject matter is brought up in a certain context, but it's not elaborated on because there's no reason to elaborate it on, because the setting of that text is to set a lawful precedent when a certain group of people came out of Egypt.
Okay, yes.
Yeah, it would have been very easy for the gods to give you a manual or a cookbook on how they did everything or how it's done.
It would be very easy for them to show up every 100 years and tell everyone, get on your knees, we're the gods, and you better do what we say or we'll be back in 100 years.
How hard would it be for them to do that?
Not hard at all, right?
Yeah, exactly.
So you have to understand the context of it, and it says what it means and means what it says.
And when people read the Book of Genesis, they go, oh, here's the Book of Genesis, I found out, I heard about, it's called Genesis, and there is a man and a woman and a snake and an apple, and there's light, and it was good, and this and that.
And before they even read anything, they start thinking about all the things they were told about it in TV, church, synagogue, their parents, the movies, right?
No, wrong.
If you could wipe, you could sweep the mind clean completely of anything and look at it like, what is that G-E-N-S, S-I-S, or even an interlinear.
Now at this point what I'm saying, it doesn't matter if you're looking at the interlinear or not.
How many times have you ever seen me, private or publicly in chat or audibly or whatever, tell someone, oh, that's great, you're reading the interlinear, that's really great, that's good, good for you.
Never.
Or do you hear me say, so what?
Doesn't mean you're going to understand it.
The reason I stress the interlinear is at least you're not going to get, you're going to see the omissions and the mistranslations, right?
I never said you're going to understand it.
You can get plenty of understanding in the King James, plenty.
But after a while you're going to start to see that there's a contradiction here and there based on what you know already about the language.
How can someone say, my name is the Lord, when you can go in England right now and they have the House of Lords, and if you go to the House of Lords and ask them, what's your name, do any of them say, my name is the Lord?
No.
So there's something, there's an anomaly here.
This is beyond reprehensible stupidity.
So then you've got to say, okay, this is such an obvious prank that if I continue with this mindset, it's no one's fault but mine.
It's obvious.
That's why when you hear these Christians, I'm going to the Lord, and I'm like, oh boy, just walk away, just walk away.
Don't bother for a second talk.
When you mention that about the buckle of the Bible belt, I know a few in my time, and yeah.
Oh, space heaters, they're the deluxe space heater.
They have the extra long cord and they've got the several settings on their dials, you know.
Oh, yeah, when they get their cord kinked, they'll let you know it.
Yeah, and they might even have an automatic shutoff on the space heater for safety.
You get it?
Yes, yes.
These are deluxe space heaters, you know.
I mean, yeah, yeah, you don't want to, yeah.
There's not, just don't even bother with that.
Here's the thing.
Even in ancient texts, you know, see, they're molded into that like concrete.
Let's say you make a mold, a form, and you pour concrete in it, and you come back a month later.
What's the only thing you can do to change that?
Smash it.
Yeah, yeah.
Can't change it.
You can pull it out of the ground and roll it down the street.
It's going to look exactly the same, right?
It's cast in concrete, isn't it?
Oh, yes, it is.
So how can you change that with a jackhammer or a stick of dynamite or whatever?
Ain't going to happen.
So most of these people are molded just like concrete.
Once it sets, it's it.
It's finished.
This is not a condemnation.
It is a very, very simple objective observation.
It would be a condemnation when you said you have to be destroyed because you can't change.
No.
I'm just saying walk away because they can't change.
You know, there's a difference.
The gods are going to take all of that, and the gods are going to do all the banging around and smashing much better than many men can do it.
I'll assure you that.
So this is a very violent reality we live in, by the way.
Most people don't realize that.
Not that you should.
You should be the opposite.
If you're going to set yourself apart, you have to act peacefully.
So by design, we have by design from the very get go, we have had this manifestation in our lives.
And yes, yes.
From Genesis.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, people, you know, there's an interesting and we'll be able to show it.
It's right there in front of you.
You just don't see it.
But because people don't understand the mechanism, just like when people say God, there's no God.
Because there's many levels on the way that that other side is communicated.
You know, the angels are also called gods in some instances because they're part of that society.
Just like if you're a general or a ensign or an officer or an enlisted man in the army, they say, hey, he's in the army.
He's in the army.
But as the conversation develops, rank might come up, training and position come up, and they're a little more important, you see.
But what's interesting is, I'll throw out a hint that could be discussed.
Just because one can comprehend and understand Genesis doesn't mean you know exactly how to place all the information that you now comprehend and understand.
I just want to put that out and think about that for a minute.
Let me give you an example of that.
Let's say you know a lot about car engines.
I mean, you know about the timing and the piston bores, and you know the bearings.
I mean, you have the bearing number for the piston rod memorized, right?
You've got the spark plug.
You've got all this stuff memorized.
If someone shows up with an engine block, it doesn't mean that you're going to be able to put it all back together and do all that, right?
And even someone can do that.
Every time they do it, it's a little bit different.
But they do – it's a finite – but the engine is a finite thing.
It's finite.
It's not infinite.
It's all there.
It's just that every time you take it apart and put it back together or want to do it, it's slightly different every time.
And sometimes, you know, you might do it differently.
So it is possible to comprehend and understand, let's say, the book of Genesis.
But what do you do with it now that you comprehend it and understand it is another level of difficulty.
That's why very often I refrain from getting into the details and saying this is like that.
And I just say, well, look at the things that are easy to comprehend and easy to place, which is, you know, you have a human anthropomorphic.
Then you have the gods.
Those are easy.
That doesn't change.
I'd like to discuss the things that don't change as your understanding increases, you see.
Right.
But as you get into a comprehension of what is really being said there, you're like, uh-oh, what do I do with this now?
I see it.
It's pretty clear, but what do I do with it now that I know it?
Right?
It's like back in the day.
You say, well, that and $2 gets you on the New York City subway.
So what?
Right, right.
Whether you knew it, whether you knew it or not, you still needed $2 to get on the subway, right?
So big deal.
But it is a big deal because it does set an aspect of the mind.
You know, the curious part, like we said earlier, is now satisfied.
It's kind of like come home and the dog's barking because he's hungry, and then you feed him.
He stops barking.
Well, you know, he's going to start barking when he gets hungry again, but he's not barking now.
You know, all your work is done, right, regarding the dog, let's say.
So the curiosity being like a pet aspect.
Yeah, the curiosity of what's being said in scripture can be satisfied, but now what do you do with it?
Right.
Well, maybe we'll get into that, and I'll show you.
It's right in front of you.
I mean one of the trademarks of Greek-speak is talking about not the stupid stuff everyone else does, and yes, I do mean everyone else, but talking about what is within arm's reach, what you can see or access yourself.
I'm not going to talk about stuff that you need a high-powered microscope or a high-powered telescope that you'll discover none of those things are there when you look there anyway, or all this crap that you hear.
I'd like to talk about things that are pretty flippin' obvious.
And that's the same, and I actually learned that from studying scripture.
It's pretty flippin' obvious what's going on, but no one sees it.
So, I'll give you a little hint.
Well, actually, let's just save the hint for another time.
Actually, the hint was a detail, but before we get, I might do it, maybe not, but let's just say this.
We ever heard like the scripture or the Bible says what it means and means what it says, or you should say what you mean and mean what you say?
Right.
Just keep that always in mind, even when you're reading something that's a metaphor.
Like a metaphor would be, you know, when the potter goes to the pot with an iron rod and smashes the pot, right?
You read that in, let's say, the book of Shefer Yimeliyahu or the book of Jeremiah, right?
You read that, you know, and he says, well, that's what I'm going to do to Israel.
Well, that's a metaphor, obviously, right?
You know, I'm going to smash you or I'm going to spill this out like a cup.
That's a metaphor, obviously, you know.
But even then it means what it says and says what it means.
You have to know what it functionally entails to, let's say, smashing a pot, what it functionally entails to pour out a cup.
You see?
So it gets like, for example, when you're pouring out a cup quickly, doesn't it get to a point where before all the liquid hits the floor, it's still up in the air, but you can't get it back in the cup?
Or maybe you could if you reverse the cup real quick.
OK.
I'm not saying this.
I'm not saying this because there's parlor tricks in this.
I'm just saying there is a flow that develops when you pour out a cup, let's say, isn't there?
Right.
You can actually see that.
But that flow just means that it's beyond management now because when it's stable in an upright cup, it's very manageable, isn't it?
Yes.
You see the description.
So when someone says, well, here's a metaphor of, you know, of pouring out a cup.
Oh, I guess so.
So let's go back and examine what happens when a cup is poured out.
And there's your detail.
And that's why the metaphor is laden with description.
But everyone just passes over it.
Now, do you see that mindset I just gave?
Yes.
Very clearly.
Yeah.
That's how when you go to the first, when you read Genesis, and also you read it without chapters and verses, and you'll see where the story or the information should naturally stop and then the subject matter change, not where they put the numbers for the verses and the chapters.
Right.
You get it?
There's a flow.
Yes.
And as you're receiving the information, just like anything that's in context or done right or well, it naturally tells the mind, okay, we're ending this topic and starting a new one now, right?
Right.
And you're not going to get that.
There's so many details scattered throughout the whole book relating to the subject that if you wanted to pursue it, you'd have to pick up on it later on to get more.
Yeah.
Speaking of picking it up later on, we've been on for about 45 minutes.
I'm going to take a one-minute break because I'm just going to have to come back.
If you want to play some music or something, here's your opportunity.
I was just going to mention that if we wanted to take a little break, we could keep the Skype line open, mute out, and come back in a little bit.
I'll do that.
I'll see you in about a minute, two minutes.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Okay, so we're back.
Yes.
So, yeah, there are things that could be discussed in the future.
Perhaps they should be.
Well, they should be and they will be.
And, again, yeah, this is just another beta test, I guess, we're doing on the streaming until things are just developed a little further.
So.
Working our way towards it, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't think there's any urgency for anything.
I think to some degree the truth gets even more disturbing as time goes on, but the matters still should be known because it's for man to know certain things when the time is right.
But on the other hand,
if there's a mindset that people can adapt or be aware that exists that they
can use, let's say, what I mean by mindset is not information,
just how you think, called discernment, for example,
or can you discern things, that could be actually helpful to some,
albeit, you know, it's like an electrical shock sometimes to realize certain
things that are just, you've been interacting with your whole life,
that whether they're good or bad, that you are now seeing them more clearly,
you know, and then you recover from that shock,
but you're probably not going to get shocked like that again regarding that
thing, you see.
Right, right.
You know, you'll get shocked again, but maybe based on something else.
So, yeah.
And again, just, today I spent a little bit of time on what they call the rectangle, looking around, like what's going on, news and what people are saying, mainstream, independent, you know, looking at some reference material, it's still just really pathetic.
It's like, how can it be?
You know, sometimes I just got to do like the double, the double palm face thing, you know?
Right.
And it seems to be getting worse.
Yes.
You know, it's only worse because what they're doing is they're increasing the speed and the features on the rectangle.
Yes, oh yes.
Yeah, but essentially the people are just the same as they were a while back.
I wanted to bring that up earlier.
You know, in scripture it says, you know, it's foolish to say that there were good old days back then.
You hear that all the time.
Oh, yeah.
You're actually better, you're better off now.
That's romanticizing stuff that wasn't even there, you know?
So, yeah, you know, when you actually learn the real history, when people say it was the good old days, it's because of the false history or the lies that you're told that what happened then, it really wasn't so.
And you're still just as dumbed up.
It's not worse.
Right.
You're better off now.
But the problem is, well, not a problem.
There is no problem.
The issue might be, a cognitive issue might be, well, how can we have so much more available to us, right?
Even just like plastic.
Just think of when you go to the store or what's called the shops or commerce or market.
You have a lot of things available to you because they're made in plastic.
They're, you know, molded and, you know, and they're cheap, right?
Years ago you didn't, before you had these petroleum-based plastics, you know, that appear to be solid, you know, artifacts or whatever or articles that you use.
They had to be made of wood or stone or metal or leather or fiber, you know?
You know, just even take like clothes hangers.
They had to be metal wire.
Now they're just mostly plastic.
You're not going to get a metal clothes hanger unless you go to a, you know, high-end, get a high-end clothing.
They still have a wooden and metal clothes hanger, right?
Oh, yeah.
But they're all plastic, you know, your containers and all that.
So you have all of this stuff being made available to you.
You have more and more and more and more functional things through plastic, right, believe it or not?
Right.
And asphalt, too.
You know, you're able to make roads very quickly.
They have machines now where they're grading the road and pouring the asphalt at the same time at a rate of like two or three miles a day, you know?
So you have so much available to you and it seems impressive.
And I think on the last Sonic event I said people are easily impressed by edifices.
You know, look how big those towers are.
Look how fast that plane goes and all that.
That makes them better.
You know, so this opportunity to maximize or I should maximize, yeah, sort of maximize, I should say, the material world through manufacturing commerce has been misinterpreted as an advanced society because the actual component, you know, the actual human or person in the society is really crap, you know?
And you know that there are malevolent forces running the world because they try to tell everyone that they're great, right?
That means they want to get something from you.
So there's a very interesting aspect to that right now where it wasn't so before.
See, that's where it's different.
See, years ago people were told they were crap and they were subjects, and if they even thought whatever, they'd go to the gallows or they'd get tortured, you know what I mean?
It was more like you never had, you didn't have this instance where I said, oh, this is a free country or you have rights or all that.
No, that was never really discussed.
People are outwardly told they were crap unless you were, you know, of high, you were of high birth, like the English would say.
Right, right.
You know, or whatever.
You know, people, you know, if you even look at old literature, even old films are quite accurate.
You know, they're going through the countryside, let's say, setting 300 years ago.
So someone would say, oh, I'm just a lowly, ignorant peasant.
You know, you see that in literature, right?
Yes, yes.
People would introduce themselves that way.
And in movies, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
But now they don't do that.
You run into anyone, oh, I'm just an ignorant worker.
You get that to a certain degree.
The other one was living the dream.
Right, right, right.
So that's also different because you've been coached into thinking you're advanced and you're better because of all the plastic things you can buy now that were, you know, once had to be handcrafted and all that.
And all the edifices that you see and all the roads and the fast planes and the drugs and the TV and all the rectangle and all that.
That's where you know it's coming to a height because the actual character of the people, again, is getting worse.
And that's one of the things before things start to get wrapped up, the character of the humanity is going to be let go, and let go meaning unrestrained, just like you see now.
There's all these various groups, you know, left, right, political, left, right, gender groups, right, left, right, religious groups, all this stuff.
They're letting go of their character.
Oh, here's a group that I associate with.
I'm going to go with that.
Forget about, you know, human character, you know.
So it's just going to be vileness all around.
And then when they start just deciding to kill each other for whatever reason, you know, that's when you really have to get out of the way.
Okay, right.
So what else is on the burner that we can discuss?
Otherwise, maybe we'll just make it a short event.
What do you think?
I was just checking the channel out and seeing if there was anything on it.
Nothing that has appeared yet.
Okay.
Yeah.
So we'll see how things sort of pan out in the near future.
What I'm planning on doing is redoing the Uncommon Radio site and getting a way to put archives and things up and getting the Uncommon Radio stream going.
We've been using Question Everything stream for now and doing some little beta tests here and there, which, you know, we could just start.
But, you know, or, you know, the Uncommon Radio streams could start in a schedule, could be put up soon.
But it just hasn't happened yet.
As always, still working things out and a few things that we should probably discuss behind the scenes and helping each other out in some respects.
Yeah, possibly, yeah.
But getting into some of these topics, though, I think it should be done in a module form, you know, bring up a topic and really expand on it more than ever before because I think there's more of a focused audience, perhaps, because, well, here's the thing, and not to be facetious, this is actually true.
If you focus on anything and just stick with what's been memorialized about the subject and approach it with discernment, you're going to provide a banging, you know, sonic event because what everyone else is doing is just crap.
Right.
And I really mean that.
Yeah.
Yeah, just with discernment.
It's real interesting.
I've seen, you know, sometimes, you know, not with hope or even false hope or any hope at all.
I'll just bounce around.
People send me links and, you know, independent media interviews here and there, and I really, I mean, you get like five minutes into something and you're like, they've already contradicted themselves or they're not even, where are they getting this from?
This is not what it's, this is not what, you know, they bring up a certain subject.
I'm like, wait a second.
Why are they saying what they're saying?
There's nothing, that's not true at all.
And you look down at.
And, you know, something else, it would help give people practice at what discernment is and how to utilize it and build the strengths and help the character.
I think that's a really good approach that you mentioned.
Yeah, but it is, but here's the thing, then you won't be able to listen to anything on the Internet, really.
That's a good thing.
I just wanted to bring that up.
A lot of that stuff is dangerous for you anyway.
Or even college textbooks.
They are the worst.
It's a joke.
It's like worse than a comic book.
Now, if you look at any recent college university textbooks, they're either completely unintuitive or false again.
The other thing I wanted to bring up is years ago, you were able to do sort of fairly good research on the rectangle.
When you're looking at institutional research like government websites and institutions and industry.
And right now they're all lying.
I think I brought this up recently again.
I used to be able to go to UStreasury.gov or any website, Federal Reserve or AMA or National Institute of Health, and you're able to access fairly decent reference material, which is if you know how to read, you just say, oh, wow, it's amazing what they're disclosing, the truth.
And this is the opposite of what everyone knows about it because it's on their website, right?
But now when you go to their websites, it's all lies, all bent, twisted, whatever propaganda people have in their heads.
And that was a wake-up call a few weeks ago.
I started researching some laws and things, and I went on certain government websites, and I'm like, what happened?
What happened to the material they used to offer?
And look at the way they're presenting themselves.
This is totally the opposite of what they are.
I'm like, wow, what's going on?
There's been a major change here recently.
And now I say recently, it's been maybe half a decade since they used to delve into those things to put information together.
So maybe, you know, it's more gradual over five, six years that it's been changing like that.
But right now, it's gotten to the point where there's even the, quote, unquote, official stuff is all crap.
So it's interesting to see where it's going to go.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, the way they got it going now, it's only, as you mentioned, going down worse.
Well, yeah.
It's going to get aggressive in other ways in the future.
Because remember, you have this seven-year period that's going to be starting in the spring, is going to build up to the point by mid-2020s, which is just not too far away, two years away, let's say.
Well, I'd say that period of where we had it in our face, I think a beautiful way of putting it.
It came out of nowhere and it stayed.
Oh, you mean the recent one or what's coming?
I'm just, I guess I'm with, from the Clinton area on, it seemed like it was all in your face.
Oh, I see.
From the political attribute of, yeah.
The people kind of followed afterwards, you know, slowly, but they did follow.
I think it's, yeah, it's been going on for, you know, because they used to do in your face in print back 100 years ago.
Also.
I know that.
Oh, you'd be surprised to see some stuff that was in regular newspapers even 150 years ago in your face.
Yeah, that begs looking at it.
Yeah, interesting approach, yeah.
Yeah, that's, but that's all right.
Yeah, regardless of who's in office, they're not going to be good because the people are not good.
And I guess I was, I guess I left that all kind of weird, but.
Yeah, to say that you have, the people have bad leaders is an oxymoron.
They have the leaders of the gods, the gods put over them, you know.
And for example, if someone, if you run into someone that says, well, I have a bad president or a bad governor or bad, whatever, you're not paying attention to the man on the street.
You need to get out of the house and maybe walk down the street and talk to people and you'll see that they fit perfectly.
Yes, yeah.
They're corrupt and vile and lying and malintent and ignorant and just as, yeah, across the board.
It wouldn't work.
If you had, if you had a good people and a corrupt leader, that leader wouldn't last but a couple of days.
Yeah, he'd be gone.
Yeah.
It'd be very easy to do that.
But the people, just because of what they say.
Don't look at, don't listen to what they're saying and how they're saying it.
Actually, it's how they're saying it.
You know, people get caught up emotionally.
Oh, yeah.
It used to be a great country.
Look, this guy passed this law.
How can you do that?
It's against the constitution.
Or look at, oh, we need a better president.
Oh, this is terrible.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Look at what they're saying, what they're saying, not how they're saying it.
You know, we have the left wing, the right wing, the protesters, you know, the ones that think that this isn't righteous or whatever and then none of them are.
No.
And if you're in that society, well, sorry to say that you are because this is an interesting time period, the past 6,000 plus years to be born in this mess, in this war zone, spiritual war zone.
I'm sure later on there will be a veteran's approach to this, meaning that much later on that some people will say I lived and was born originally on the earth during this time period and the newly born beings will say, wow, man, I'm really sorry to hear that.
You were born during those ages, you know.
Because, yeah, there will be people being born and new spirits and souls coming into this existence after the gods come and rearrange and take over again, you know.
Right, right.
We had one in the channel that mentioned something.
Any funny prophecies he's willing to share?
Funny?
As in ha ha?
Well, any fun prophecies, yes.
Oh, fun ones.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the whole thing, remember, when you're reading what's coming, it's operating on a, using the K-12 analogy, it's coming on a 30th or 40th grade level.
Because whenever you read these ancient writs, especially ones that have been legitimately inspired by the gods, they have an IQ, let's say, of 2 million compared to men.
So when you're reading and trying to get information from it, you're getting, that's their baby talk.
When you read scripture, that's like the baby talk.
But they don't act in futility.
You know, they want you to understand it and it seems incomprehensible.
So it's all funny from that perspective, you see.
Their level of communication based on their intelligence level, which is way higher, and their ability level, which is way infinitely higher than us in comparison.
When I say infinitely, most of them are finite.
All of it's funny.
When you comprehend their ability and level of intelligence compared to ours, and the communication that they're giving us, it's all funny, really.
If you try to comprehend the contrast there, you know.
Right, right.
Yeah.
Like I said earlier, there's stuff going on here that is counter-spatial.
Well, not earlier tonight, but earlier other times.
Counter-spatial, not inter-dimensional.
There's only one dimension, right?
Everything is in this one dimension, but it's just seen or unseen.
But some things are counter-spatial.
Yeah, it's just counter-spatial.
You were going to start on something like that many times about counter-spatial, longitudinal, how that actually works.
Yes.
Yeah, like, for example, when you're longitudinal and counter-spatial, it would be like if all you knew, your whole universe was in a fishbowl, and it took you X amount of time or a really long time to go from one end of the fish tank to the next and all that, right?
And you started measuring your whole cognitive existence based on those distances and all that.
Well, here comes someone in the room and picks up the whole fish tank at once.
That's a counter-spatial thing, you know.
Okay.
Because no matter where you are in the fish tank, the whole thing got lifted up and moved.
It's like, how can your whole universe move across to another place in the universe instantly like that?
Do you get it?
Yes, yes, wow.
Yeah, so that's what I mean by counter-space.
It's where we start measuring things in time, you know, progressions of distance, progressions of time, progressions of energy, you know, going from high potential to low potential, things wearing out, let's say.
They're able to bypass that whole progression and do it all at once.
You see, that's a counter-spatial issue.
And I have never – you have to give at least 100 analogies of counter-space where people can start relaxing into it.
And that's how the gods work in a counter-spatial way.
How else can you show up and disappear and be all-powerful comparatively?
I remember one time you said that they're 1,000 years to one day of us.
Yes, that is regarding the end times, yes.
There are other analogies, other time analogies we'll get into in the future where it's even less than that.
Oh.
It's even – yeah.
Or 1,000 years is like a watch in the night when there are three watches in the night or four watches in the night.
So, yeah.
You know, with the Earth – well, there's a relative aspect too with the Earth on that.
I think on one of the sonic events – I don't know if it was recorded or not or we made an archive – was what spins the Earth?
How does the Earth go round and round?
Yes, I remember that.
That was from the night that it didn't – well, something goofed.
Needless to say, the event that never was.
But, yes, if you would love to touch on that.
That was a beautiful discussion.
Okay.
What makes the planets go around or any of these things?
Not necessarily the stars because the stars are not really there.
We only have a concept of the sun and the star because we have an atmosphere.
If you wipe the atmosphere – before we get into the planets – if you wipe the atmosphere, you don't see the sun.
You only see the sun come through maybe where the atmosphere is.
But if you're looking up at night – I mean during the day, sorry, not at night – and you see a blue sky and you see the very bright disk of the sun that you can't look at because it's too bright, right?
Well, if you remove the atmosphere where you're seeing the sun through, the sun disappears.
The rest of the sky appears to be blue.
And now whatever intensity of light where you've wiped out the sky becomes black.
You don't see the sun.
But you have a very interesting shimmering edge.
So you have this big black spot in the atmosphere in the sky when you look up.
And at the edge where it becomes blue again, it's very bright and shimmering.
But where you've removed the atmosphere, there's no sun because you only see the sun or the stars.
Because of the atmosphere, all the astronomers know that.
That's why – you remember the Hubble telescope?
They put it out in space and they didn't really communicate very well.
And then they had to go and fix it.
Remember it said it was like giving someone glasses because it couldn't focus?
That's total bullshit.
What happened is they had the wrong diffraction lenses on it.
So if you have a crystal lens or a crystal window in space, you could be staring right at the sun.
You don't see it.
But you'll see the light on the spacecraft in your spacesuit in your hand and on the planets.
But you don't see the sun.
And if you look at that black part of space where the sun is supposed to be, it will damage your eye.
You just don't see it.
Oh, yeah.
You know, once in a while now you're starting to see more and more pictures of space where it's looking out over the Earth and there's just absolutely nothing in the background.
Well, that's because they're using clear quartz lenses and nothing with a diffraction.
Now, that's why you see the spacesuits.
They have the gold tint, the visor and all that.
That's so they can see the sun.
So when they put the Hubble telescope up, they were like, we're not getting any images of the stars or anything like that.
Well, we had the wrong diffraction lenses.
So they had to go up there with a bunch of window tint, just like the window tint you put on a car.
Yeah.
And stretch that over something that looked like a carousel that rotates to give different aspect ratios and lenses.
Right.
So they decided to put some window tint on everything for it to work.
They're not going to say that to you.
They're going to tell you, well, it's out of focus because of the speed.
If you know about telescopes like a Dysonian, you know, we have secondary primary mirrors.
Right.
We had a software glitch.
Yeah.
They're going to tell you they're not going to tell you what's going on.
I mean, it's just ridiculous how what they get away with.
I mean, they lie to people more than people lie to dogs.
You know, I've I've watched it.
I mean, the officials and people lie to each other more than they lie to their animals.
So anyway, moving on.
So moving on.
But to get to the point with this is I'm not discussing the stars and the sun, because that's really what you hear.
Most of the discussions of outer space are about the stars.
There occasionally are planets.
Now, planets are more of the solid material that is discernible as such as being solid, you know, and you see it when there's light.
So what what rotates?
I just did a famous Greek diversion there.
Right.
But about the sun and the stars.
But anyway, just to go back to divert a little bit more.
There's ancient writs that talk about the sun going black and the moon turning red.
The sun is always black.
When you when you read in scripture, the sun goes black.
That means your atmosphere is being sucked out.
And yeah.
But yeah.
In other words, your fish tank is being drained.
Atmosphere to humans is like water for fish.
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
So that's why I remember earlier we gave the slight analogy.
You hear a metaphor of a cup being poured.
And so the cups being poured and they keep going.
Well, wait a second.
What happens when a cup is being poured?
Are you familiar with what is going on?
What does that really mean?
You see, what does it really mean with the sun turning black?
No, the sun is not.
Your atmosphere is being pulled.
Bad news, folks.
Especially if you time lapse that thing and you can make it go really slow over a period of time.
Yeah, there's a whole lot going on there.
So there's your little fun prophecy note, which if anyone wants to think about that.
And that's never been said before, by the way.
And so a lot of these things that were not, you know, on a sonic event or wreck.
And this is just a very simple way to start discerning things.
And you're like, wow, you know.
So what makes the planets rotate?
Yeah, what makes the planet turn, yes.
What makes the planet rotate, the earth and anything else?
Very simple.
You have something called a vegetative layer.
Not vegetables or vegetation, but it's an ethereal vegetative layer.
What I mean by ethereal, it's primacy.
It's prior to what we call energy and matter, which is secondary.
And all of these things that are called planets that are actually of manufacture have a vegetative layer.
Like, for example, one can describe on the earth, there's something called the tree line.
You know, when you go above 10,000 feet or so, the trees don't grow anymore typically because they call it the tree line.
The tree, the vegetative layer for the earth is roughly from the surface or slightly below the surface.
There's many types of layers, but generally the surface of the earth is about 10,000 feet or 3,200 meters or something, right, is what they call the tree.
That's the vegetative layer.
That's its band.
And one day we'll discuss trees.
So you'll see something about trees that you haven't seen before.
But right now we'll just stick to what turns the planets and the earth.
So that vegetative layer on the earth exists.
That tree line ability, for example, that we discuss on the earth, that exists whether there are trees or not, right, whether there are plants or not.
This is an ethereal energetic field that's on the planet.
Now, when you understand that plants are secondary because they're material, right, they are governed by this primary vegetative layer.
Or field, let's say.
One of the basic things you could look at the characteristic of any plant is that it moves towards the light, right.
So if you move a plant away from the light, its body will actually move towards the light, the leaves and all that, right.
And then once it gets enough light, you'll notice that it tends to want to now, it's saturated with all this light energy.
And it kind of like wants to droop down or move away.
But, you know, because they can't get up and walk, they kind of like don't seem as perky.
The leaves kind of droop down a little or curl inward or inward a little bit.
But but there's sometimes if there is a side of the plant that is not in the light with a side that is overcharged, it starts to kind of like bow down a little bit.
Well, the side that was not in the light wants to now move into the light and wants to like twist itself around.
So what's interesting is that when the this vegetative layer on the planets and on the earth, when it's facing the sun, that side of the planet is lit.
And it gets to a point where it's overcharged and it no longer wants to attract itself or be in that position.
And remember, the backside of the planet now is not in the light.
And just like a plant, that vegetative layer wants to turn it into the light, wants to go to the light.
So the side that's in the facing the sun is sort of saturated, had enough.
And the side that is not in this facing the sun wants to go towards it and starts turning.
Right.
And then that dark side gets into the light, gets overcharged again or saturated.
And the side that was in the light now is dark and is ready for more light and wants to go back into the light.
And that's what keeps the planets going round and round and round is this vegetative layer from an ethereal point of view.
So was that sort of like a lot of power to it?
Yes.
Tremendous power.
And all planets have that.
All planets that do rotate on an axis have that vegetative layer.
Now the axis is something different.
That's almost like putting a skewer or an axle through it.
It rotates on and that is another aspect to that.
And that axis or axle is really stronger than steel, believe it or not.
But it's thinner than a spider's web.
It's stronger than a 400 mile wide bar of steel.
But it's actually smaller than the finest laser you can imagine.
That's an ethereal counter-spatial issue to discuss in the future.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's ethereal again.
It's a pivot.
You ever see on certain devices they have pivots and they come to a very sharp point?
Yeah.
Just imagine that very sharp point projecting through space and without it coming as an apex.
It's always that thin and narrow.
And those points can be disturbed very, very easily even though they're that strong.
So anyway, about rotating the planet.
Did I do enough description?
Yes.
Very nice.
Excuse me.
Very good.
In an English way, yeah.
So that is a simple way to wrap the mind around how these things are turned.
Now, for example, if Mars, let's say, rotates.
You'll say, well, that's the vegetative layer on Mars that is rotating it.
You may not be aware of vegetation or visibly to see it or whatever.
Now, the Moon is an interesting thing.
The Moon, they say, well, how does the Moon, why don't we see the back of the Moon and all that?
Well, that's because the Moon doesn't have its own orbit.
It's locked into the orbit of the Earth.
So if you understand planetary mechanics or how things rotate, if you understand how to build a planetary gear, it will very simply explain why you don't see the back of the Moon.
It's not a mystery like most people try to pose it as such.
Tesla wrote a good article about it.
Tesla, over 100 years ago, got tired of hearing about people saying, well, how come we don't see the back of the Moon?
He wrote a short little treatise on why, and he put it in the New York Times, so anyone could look it up.
I did see that.
That is a good article.
Yeah, the Moon doesn't have its own orbit.
It's locked into the orbit of the Earth.
That's why it acts so, quote, unquote, funny.
So, yeah, it's amazing the stuff that people come up with.
We had another question.
Were the malevolent gods always malevolent?
No, no.
Apparently, they were not always, no.
Apparently, this new kid on the block, and I don't mean a goat,
but I'm just saying it just kind of in a semi-pejorative way,
Adam, was given a decree or stated as being one of the most,
well, the most important being in the universe,
like the most high is making a family,
and he's, Adam, now bypasses all the other spiritual beings that are around
for time immemorial, and they didn't like that idea.
And that was the beginning of the separation, then.
Right, right.
Now, here's the thing.
I once saw a History Channel thing a long time ago, God versus Satan.
That's the dumbest shit I've ever heard in my life or seen ever.
That's some of the dumbest shit.
Because none of these entities are against the most high.
They're against man.
But because they're against man, they're against the most high.
You see?
I don't get it.
They're following marching orders.
Either way, it comes back to their fight against the whole process.
Yep.
We're caught in a crossfire.
Right.
And it's semi-indirect.
It's about as indirect as you could get without being direct.
Exactly, yes.
If they got direct, they'd take you out.
One of those malevolent entities can kill every man, woman, and child on the planet, and all things living, if granted the go-ahead.
And there are more of them than us, quote-unquote, people.
The whole story and the actual scenario and the truth of the matter is very comprehensible and cognitive.
I mean, it's not beyond anyone's understanding.
It's just that the reality of these things is so far different than what we've been told in every venue, every aspect, whether it's the media, government, school, religious bodies, whatever.
It's all false, everything that's out there about it.
Now, occasionally, there might be a little bit of something true coming out.
There'll be another going-into-the-pagan-holiday-season, and you'll watch a documentary, and they start off almost all Christmas documentaries.
Well, everyone knows this is a pagan holiday, but blah, blah, blah.
Here's the Christmas thing here and here and that, right?
They always say that now.
Only the most ignorant, awful people will say, well, that was when the Christ was born.
I don't know how much of that is still going on.
Yeah, it's still out there.
Wow, that's pathetic, not just sad.
It's just pathetic.
Someone needs to pull the handle on the porcelain bowl.
But anyway.
It's been sitting a little too long.
Oh, yeah.
So, anything else, or we should maybe give it a wrap?
No, I don't see anything else in there at this point.
I'm trying to think of some subjects that may be.
Oh, there's lots of stuff to discuss.
Yes, there is.
Well, it's up to you, sir.
Oh, I think we should just do a wrap on it, yeah?
Maybe we'll do a couple more of these, and then maybe the Greek will get serious on doing a schedule of some sort and doing these things more regularly and perhaps doing a good solid archiving.
By the way, the server, we could talk about this off the stream, but everything's going okay with the server?
People are accessing it.
Anything you want to tell people about it?
Occasionally, since I don't have a lot of bandwidth, if it gets overwhelmed, it will only accept a certain amount of people on at a time.
So be patient.
It does work.
Right.
I haven't linked it to the Uncommon Radio for that reason, because it's limited in that aspect.
So right now it seems like there is a – probably when the schedule comes together, it will be on the Uncommon stream and most likely archived on a Podbean site.
Yeah.
And it will be linked, and there will probably be an embedded player on the site, or you can do it off-site if it's less bandwidth.
That way I'll figure it out.
And I'm going to most likely archive them in a 44K or 32.
So you don't need to have like 100 and whatever megabyte.
It could be 40 or 50 megabyte.
There's no – I'm not playing music here.
It's just voice.
I noticed that when you go below 16, what is it, 16K or whatever, then it starts to degrade.
It gets a little iffy then, yeah.
Yeah, 32 might be good.
So you keep the files kind of small and easy to stream and download and all that.
And then also, of course, there's the subject matter and the context of all these things.
Right, and categorizing it and, as you mentioned, different episodes on more thorough explanations.
Yeah, I think it should be done, yeah.
The concept of having a private membership and all that is on hold.
I don't know if that will really happen.
Again, I've always been looking back and forth to perhaps that is a good idea, but I just don't really – it doesn't sit well with me for some reason.
I understand.
Yeah, but it should be – like for example, on a private – if a multinational corporation or a monarchy got in touch with me, yeah, they're definitely going to get more information than I'm putting out generally.
I'm not teasing anyone or lauding anything over anyone because they're in a position to do so because then I can make a living doing that with them, right?
Right, exactly.
Yeah, and I have not yet considered to do a full-time dedication to putting out information in public.
If I did, then maybe – how else do you do in exchange with the public other than, quote-unquote, selling to them a membership or information?
That's what professors and authors and writers do, right?
And people in the arts, they want to produce what they produce and then put it out on the market, right?
Exactly, yes.
So I haven't gotten to that point with that.
I should – someone says, Greek, you should be doing that.
I'm like, yeah, there's many things I should be doing, but – or put it this way, it could be done, but to do it out in open in public and to go full-time on it and all that, no, I don't see that ever really happening in the near future.
But I am open to a monarchy or a multinational corporation that needs some proper consulting.
Yeah, then I would go full-time and all that, but of course, they'd compensate me as well.
And on the other hand, the thing is I noticed that most of the people at large are on the student level, and perhaps one of the things that I would say is that I've said before is I'm only speaking publicly because no one else is saying these things, and it's just a cry in shame.
I mean how could there be so many people and no one is actually saying anything right?
Not one word.
Yes, so if I don't say anything, I'm going to be culpable later perhaps, maybe.
Maybe not for sure, right?
But let's just cover that base.
And the other thing is I'm not looking for students or newbies.
I'm looking for teachers.
There's a big difference.
I'm not looking to give people fish.
I'm looking for fishermen.
You see?
So because every time you project or let's say go out and give information to people that are on the student level, well, every time you encounter these people on the student level, you need to keep starting from the beginning and just like a class, right?
You present the entire thing from start to finish over and over and over, where if you put the information out to people who are teachers, now they can do it.
You see?
Now they can just go out and talk to others, speak to others.
And one of the things I mentioned on the Sonic event was I've been speaking, giving more than hints on things, and no one is still coming around and taking these subjects.
Not that they should.
I'm not expecting it.
But no one has furthered any of this stuff with precision and accuracy.
So it makes me wonder.
It's like, okay, what's wrong with you all, right?
But nothing.
I mean, I'm not saying there's anything wrong with wanting to hear something novel and interesting that happens to be precise and accurate in almost all cases.
It's just a matter of there really isn't anyone out there that can articulate this subject matter.
Not to mention the fact that you need to get yourself a good pair of shoes that you can run in.
Yeah.
So from that perspective, yeah, there's got to be someone else out there that can do this kind of talk.
They just haven't come around.
And until they do, I guess I'm the one that has to do it.
Oh, poor me, right?
No, not at all.
I enjoy it to a certain degree.
But I do understand that I assess myself and the audience constantly.
How?
Well, I can assess myself privately.
But the only way I can assess the audience is publicly, see what's going on in chat, what emails I get, who else is – if you do a, quote, unquote, search or look around at what other people are saying.
And you get to see what level people are at with the stuff that's been expanded or expounded on.
And so far, again, just to say it again, no one's able to go out there and articulate the subject matter like this across the board.
So I have to somehow – not that – I mean I could just fall off the face of the earth and not talk again, speak again, or communicate with anyone.
That was just as easy to do as anything else.
But I'm – and I'm not saying I'm being hopeful or waiting for someone else to, let's say, grab the ball and run with it on these subjects.
I'm not expecting it.
But it would be pleasant and a good surprise and very fit and proper if someone else did.
So anyway, that's just the overall assessment of the condition of this whole thing.
And heaven forbid that there's a Gustave Le Bon type group around this type of thinking because it's not – I think one of the things I brought up with the last Sonic event with the two hosts, the young boys, is when one of them said, well, where can we go to read about this stuff?
It's not about reading.
It's about discernment.
So it doesn't matter what the subject is or whatever.
It's just can you discern what's going on or not.
And right now there's very little discernment.
So at least the people that are putting microphones in front of their faces or writing websites and books and doing YouTubes and stuff, there's – I don't see anyone out there really putting a good foot forward in the discernment category.
There's a big difference about what's being put out there in the world these days across the board between what they want to talk about and what can be talked about.
There's a big difference to that mindset.
Yeah, I guess you nailed that one right on the head.
Yeah, like most of the stuff you see out there is what people want, and that's what they've chosen.
That's fine.
Want to discuss or disseminate information, which even then is 99 percent not accurate or precise anyway most times.
Even on the academic and scientific aspect, come on, man.
Protons and electrons, calories.
I mean, come on.
What's wrong with you people?
Get over it.
So even then on that level, what seems to be academic or what is standard, they're still putting out what they like to put out, not what can be put out regarding the subject matter.
That's another world of existence right there.
Hence the reason that you've got the president that you have, a clear representation.
Well, it doesn't matter.
The president is very irrelevant, actually.
It's the county, the locality.
In this country and in most countries, it's the actual local government that controls it.
You could study in many places.
The president would represent the leader of the centralized government, the federal government.
You can research this on your own.
There are many local governments that have exempted themselves or banned certain central government practices.
You ever heard of prostitution being legal in certain places or gambling being legal in certain places where the central government says it's illegal?
There are localities that have their own jurisdiction and what they decide to impose.
It's all local.
It's a big distraction to think that the president is the be-all and end-all.
It's quite the opposite.
He's just there, like I said, put on the big oversized shoes and the funny nose and whatever.
I'm not disparaging them because they're perfect for the society.
Even if you look at, for example, some of the historically heinous leaders you heard in Russia or China or Europe or whatever, no one ever says, oh, the poor Russians or the poor Soviets or the poor Chinese or whatever.
Those leaders were fully in line with the people, no matter how heinous what they did was.
It's things to think about.
No one's really discussing it that way.
When you hear of certain dictators killing millions of their own people or tens of millions of their own people, how did they do it?
They had at least 20 percent of the population doing it.
Easily.
Yeah, and it was part of their culture.
Don't buy the boo-hoo, ooh-ha, whatever stories.
Look how bad it was then and how good it is.
These are the same people still today.
They could break into that kind of modality at any time.
Okay, so speaking of breaking into or out of modalities, I think we've been on for almost two hours, right, or something like that?
Almost two hours, yes.
That's quite a bit.
It went by really fast.
It doesn't take much time.
Well, thanks for doing this.
We'll catch up.
We'll do it again soon.
Yeah, we'll do it again soon.
Thanks.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
Bye now.