You see, yeah, most high.
Yeah, we keep and I think what Sam is has is trying to contend with is the grammar is the semantics of saying the most high if it's lateral.
No, no, what I'm asking, what I'm asking specifically, is there are certain structures that are in place that indicate how things work.
Right?
There is an example of a hierarchy or system of leadership or government that eventually destroys it.
Sorry, I'm going to interrupt.
Hold on interject this when you're ruled by Satan.
Even most people are going to walk away saying we know how things work.
But because you're ruled by Satan, that is actually a deception.
You see, and I'm not trying to be adversarial in that aspect.
I'm just trying to tell you that in this world, people don't know how things work.
They're just buying time.
They're just biding or abiding time, I should say.
Do you know how anything works?
Yeah, but on a sure, I do.
And in many cases, I actually, I'm sorry to say that.
Yes, I'm sorry to say that I do.
But on a cultural and a societal level, they don't know how it works.
No, but we're not talking about them.
We're talking about what is observed.
No, we're talking about what's observable to everybody.
Yeah, what's observable.
But here's the thing, what's observable to anyone is, you know, you have a reasonable modicum of peace in society, right?
Not everyone is killing you.
You know, it's not like gone into complete darkness yet.
Even you know, spiritually it might be.
But what I'm saying is, hardly anyone knows anything about anything.
And you all seem to be getting along just fine till now, right?
As a matter of fact, the things that don't seem fine are actually instigated by, you know, secret forces behind the governments, right?
Like no one's going out killing other people unless they're made to, you know, for industrial reasons or whatever.
It's very rare that you hear about crimes of passion, even though they do exist.
You always hear about the ones that are propagandized.
So my point here is very simple.
It's, and this is why I've been speaking, no one seems to know about anything about anything.
But everything seems to be fine.
And I'm telling you, it's not fine.
Right?
Have you ever listened to Greek speak cover?
Maybe a dozen different subjects, and they're very easy to comprehend.
But there are very stark contrast to the common understanding.
Oh, yeah.
And it's not as I'm not being esoteric or sublime.
So you know, no, no one knows what's going on.
No, I can't say they do.
I mean, we're not talking about them.
I don't know why you keep bringing that up.
That was whether you it's right now, just forget about them.
Just go get a random five people from anywhere in the world.
They don't know what's going on.
I'll bet that they don't.
The chances of you getting five random people from any society, and anyone knows anything about anything is so rare, that I would bet that none of them know anything about anything.
This is how sure I am about this, by the way.
Yes.
And that is not so not to extend.
Now to extend that ignorance and stupidity, whether it's a micro or macro scale, it's the same.
So no, there are no wise kings.
No, there are no, you see that no one knows what's going on.
It's a miracle.
You want to know what a real miracle that we're all here in the in the fat way that we are.
Yeah, you really think that when I say wise King, I'm trying I'm talking about an actual wise person?
No, no, you're giving an example.
Oh, yeah.
So why do you keep acting like I'm not doing that?
Or that I'm talking about a concept?
It's a concept, but here's a concept that's so far removed that even if we use the colloquial wise King of Solomon, did he end up being fairly wise or not?
No.
So I see what you're saying.
But I don't see but I don't see how it would it would work in this in this incarnation meaning of this reality.
Okay, well, then that is what I'm getting at.
Like, does scripture indicate that there's an incarnation where it does work?
And does it offer the technical alludes to it?
Yeah, that's why Have you ever heard me say that scripture is not finished?
The scripture we have is finished a long time ago, but the actual acts?
Okay.
You like, for example, the Book of Acts?
Why is it called the Book of Acts?
Right?
Just a record of acts, right?
Or events, right?
Do aren't there going to be acts when the gods come back?
Oh, let's see.
overtly?
Yeah.
And do you think anyone is going to take the time or there might be in the in the, you know, the God government?
A position for recording these things?
Yep.
Yeah.
You see?
So when I say scripture, not the scripture we have, but there is going to be a writ record in the future as well, records will be kept in the future.
So we in other words, we have very little information on those records.
There is one who knows what those records will be like, right?
But we have no information on that.
Okay, there's very little information, by the way, about anything that we consider to be a necessity now, in scripture, believe it or not.
Where does it talk about the biological vacuum and you don't absorb anything?
Where does it talk about how to make a fire?
Or, you know, or specific, you know, child rearing specifics, which is, you know, child rearing is one of the most important things that a man can, you know, humankind can do.
Right?
That would be like saying, going to a factory that makes glass molds or clay pot molds.
And, you know, oh, it doesn't matter what the mold is like.
Of course, it matters.
The rearing is the molding, right?
What tools you're giving, right?
There's not, there's very little information on that.
We're basically given so little information that we cannot screw up the plan.
But given enough information that later on, we can't say that we didn't have any information.
I don't think we, I think all of it is there, and various degrees of technological formats that we don't understand.
You know, I think I've explained that, previous sonic events.
I don't know, Bruce, have I ever gone public with the, the Hebrew and Greek letters being Morse code?
Do you remember that?
Or maybe I don't know if Sandy...
Yes, and as you elaborated about, if you were to put a piece of paper across, on, and just read the top row of the dots, it's like a Morse code, a straight edge, right?
It'd be like a Morse code.
And didn't you say something about that?
God, how did you put that?
That it would actually create a picture?
Or...
There's enough code there.
If you if you go across the letters, top, middle, bottom, the number of the letter, what is the alphabet, the number of the letter in the word?
Yes.
The spaces between all that, you're going to get a few minutes of video on each page.
Yes, there's enough.
Yes.
Bits and bytes.
Yeah.
And I ran this when I was out in LA and other times running into people that did MIDI, digital analog to digital conversion, and they looked at it and actually compiled that?
No.
Well, I've been sort of semi-public about that for a little while.
There's nothing on it.
My goodness.
Yeah, I don't know.
I can't be the only one who sees that.
But I don't see any information on it.
And I would be surprised if it's it's already been done and not made public and actually being used against people.
True, true.
But I don't think the, you know, but anyway.
Wow.
So otherwise, why are they so adamant about the preservation in those languages when we know there are errors in it?
Yeah.
You see, there's a, right?
Because at different times, it was not preserved in that it was preserved in, you know, what they call paleo Hebrew, which is different.
They didn't have that format for other reasons.
You know, like, you know, people say the Jews versus the non-Jews or whatever.
You know, they need to wake up at what they call Hebraic script and Hebrew and all that stuff.
That's all borrowed from Babylon, right?
Or developed.
Yeah.
So all this bigotry and hate and race is really an instigation.
And, you know, so.
Somebody's working overtime to keep that going.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The Hatfields and the McCoys, you know, kind of thing, right?
Big time.
Do they have that metaphor out there in Europe, Sam?
Not really.
It's just families that are fighting and so many, so much time goes by, they forget why they're fighting.
They just know that they have to fight.
No, I've heard of it.
It's probably another archetype or something.
Loose, cultural, piss-poor, low-level, you know, stuff.
I was explaining to someone, by the way, in terms of the law, brought up, like, you know, they say, love your enemy.
Do you know what that means?
And I said, yeah, but you don't.
And the guy says, what an arrogant fuck, right?
I said, well, let me explain to you.
He's speaking, he doesn't say, just love your enemy.
That's stupid.
Because if you do that, the enemy is always looking at a weakness to take advantage of you.
Stupid.
That's not what it means.
Everything that's said in the New Testament is context with the biblical law.
And, of course, because the demons that run the religions and the churches don't want you to look at the law.
Can we come up with, is there a law anywhere that states about, love meaning do the right thing, agape, right?
It means without breach.
Do you know that in the law it states that if you have an enemy based on boundaries or whatever, and their animals come across to your land, that you are not to kill them, that you return them back to him?
That's what love your enemy means.
Do the right thing to the enemy.
How do you know, what's the right thing, you know, like, you know, in Scripture, when you go and do war, what do you, you don't tear down fruit bearing, fruit bearing trees, right?
But if you notice now, they're doing that, right?
Don't they do, when they do war, even in the Middle East, don't they blow up olive trees and burn them down and stuff?
Yeah.
So that's love, you know, I mean, people don't, forget about the word love, you know, that's what I like about Jack Fresco, the word love is bullshit, you don't know what it means, right?
So, again, if you read the news, you know, turn the other cheek, you know, if someone slaps you, it's usually you're not, it means you're not a moving target.
Well, if you get hit, if you get hit because you were not a moving target, maybe it's better that you are a moving target now, because, you see, turn the other cheek, get it?
Time to move.
Yeah, it's not, this is, it's amazing how stupid people are, not stupid, they can't see the plain example, because they don't know the whole story.
What I was saying with Ocelli was, you know, can you imagine going to college level math and they say, okay boys and girls, you're in college now and we're going to do math, so two plus two equals what?
No, it's cumulative.
You see, when you get to the end of what they call scripture, the New Testament, that is PhD level stuff.
If you don't haven't done your homework and the rest, you will not understand anything in it at all.
Guaranteed.
Which is self-evident.
Yes.
Let's just wrap up this hierarchy thing a bit, like what you were saying before about the rats in the cage.
So you're, you would say that, I mean, normally, if you know, in human society, there's an ethic that's associated with leadership, that is not, you know, a mere consequence of having power.
Like, just because you're the boss doesn't mean you do whatever you want.
I'm going to interrupt you again.
Have you ever heard the saying, true power is never known in leadership?
True power is never known.
Look, if you were really in power, would you want to go out in the world and tell these idiots you're in power?
Are you going to put the janitor in president's uniform and say, this guy is your leader?
Of course.
Yes.
This is, I mean, this is planet Earth you're talking about, right?
Not some other planet, right?
Okay, so the idea is that all leaders are corrupt and there's no ethic.
No, no.
I didn't say, you keep using that word corrupt.
Like, like this other guy the other day was saying all the attorneys are corrupt.
Okay, all leaders are malevolent and there is no ethic.
You know, they're doing exactly what they're doing according to the God that they form their society under.
Yes, but even within the context of this deception or the misdirection, people still have to adhere to the fallacy.
So when they say that your leaders have an ethic, people still have to see that.
They don't have to adhere to it.
You could be in, scripture tells you to be in it, but not of it.
I'm not saying you could be a fly around the fly.
You don't have to get stuck on the flypaper.
Okay, listen, so I'll just like ask it simply.
Is there an ethic associated with leadership?
Well, ethics is a really difficult thing to define.
Oh shit, come on.
Ethics, the sense that you have to act a certain way, that you have to adhere to a certain display of benevolent qualities.
It's not that simple.
Yeah, again, there's so many levels to it.
One is if you understand the current intricacies of showmanship, like for example, modern world leaders, why don't they just have actors?
Just go to Hollywood, forget about the other political side.
Just put actors in there, right?
Supposedly they'll be better than the ones they're putting in now, at least in performance.
Or you can go to the spiritual side and say there's an entity behind it.
Or you could say, where's the wisdom in being a leader?
Because these people are, who wants to rule over idiots, right?
There's got to be something wrong with you, unless you view them as food or pets.
So there's so many, what ethics?
This is complex.
Remember again, I know this is not where we were going, but when you're dealing with the gods, you're dealing usually on that level with beings or creatures or create parts of creation and then the most high that has IQ in the millions.
And I don't like to use that metaphor, because you know, if you have never discussed the IQ test, I don't know if anyone's taken, you know, it's basically time versus how many problems you solved.
These gods would solve the IQ test before you handed it to them.
That's why I mean it's an IQ of 2 million, right?
Or whatever.
As you hand it to him, he'd hand it right back to you and say, it's done.
I didn't even see you do it.
It's all perfect, in no time.
So where's the ethics there?
I mean, what level of performance are you looking to judge what is really going on?
Because what is really going on is really emanating from that primacy.
So the rest of it is what you would like to see, Sam, from it.
What I would like to see is the ethics.
We're talking about the primacy as well.
Okay, put aside the man society shit.
Even in their kingdom, you have a boss, the most high, he runs everything, and he gives his followers or his subjects the choice.
Do you want to follow what I'm doing or do you want to go and rebel?
Right?
And some of them rebel and some of them follow.
Right, yeah.
And yeah, it's his plan or whatever, but they still have the agency to say, I'm gonna do what he says or I'm not gonna do what he says.
Right?
And I'm trying to see, okay, so you have some of them that go with the plan, some of them that go with the instructions, some of them that don't.
And perhaps the ones that don't have determined, well, we don't like this guy.
Forget him.
We're gonna do what we want.
Alright, I'm gonna stop you again.
Just do this thought experiment.
Let's go into the future when the gods are on earth and ruling.
Do you think that question would be relevant?
No, because the bad guys have been deposed.
They've already lost.
Right, so we know that for sure.
Okay, so if we know that for sure, can't we act that that's been done already anyway?
You know, so I give the...
But it doesn't change the social dynamic.
There's still gonna be a rebellion.
The thing is to avoid that dynamic.
But there's still gonna be a rebellion.
The dynamic is always gonna be present.
A thousand years later, you're gonna have hundreds of millions of people that do another rebellion.
That doesn't change.
So the act of how social being works is not going to change.
There's a nature that's built into the creation.
But there's a dynamic that we don't know until it's experienced because of the limiting factors that we have.
Like for example, when Satan is unleashed back on society, some people go for it, some people don't.
No, it says that no one goes for it, right?
But actually there's an army that is...
Isn't there a battle?
But it's put down very quickly.
But the only way that you can predict the future is if you have certain fixed references that do not move.
Right, I call it an inertial plane of reference.
Actually one of the projects I'm working on is to establish an acoustic inertial frame of reference and that just like every engineer...
So we're talking about 75 year old engineers now, people that are very well...
can't grasp it.
And it's a child can grasp it.
So do you want to go down the route of the...
So in other words, okay, let me just summarize up until now.
Not only are we discussing this or you're bringing it up from a, let's say, see what's valid or invalid, but ensuing perhaps at is there engineering involved and how much of it is engineering, how much of it is happenstance or, you know, or is it just all metaphysics?
In other words, we can't get a grip on it for measuring and managing, but we can get a grip on it cognitively.
I don't know if I actually simplified or made things more complicated by saying what I just said.
But I would suggest that at this point that when you're...
you cannot go purely secular on this...
on this...
on the attributes of the hierarchy.
Can't.
That's just admitting we're going to be ignorant.
You know what I mean?
I don't know that I'm being completely secular.
Like, what do you mean it's secular?
Like, if I look at...
if the couch is red and I see that the couch is red, it's neither secular nor anything else.
It's an observation that something is the way it is and it functions that way.
It depends on how much light...
it depends on how much light you have on the couch.
Years ago in cycling, when people used to buy red cycling gear, I said, at night that looks like black.
And recently someone here came...
they were wearing something red and it was dim.
I said, is that black?
No, it's red.
See?
So, in other words, there's so little light in the world, and that sounds philosophical, that we can't see the true color anymore.
I mean, I'm not saying it's not possible to see true color.
Of course it is, and heaven forbid you do.
The reason why is because your life will be miserable.
Look, if they're having violence and war there, what do you think you're gonna have here?
How would you act?
Like, how would you...
would your mindset be different if you're in Europe during World War II right now?
Do I know everything that I still know, or am I just...
No, in other words, your current mindset, what would it be like if there was war in Europe, like World War II?
Actually, believe it or not, there were still people going on vacation during the height of the war, right?
Like, it was no big deal.
Just depend on where they were dropping the bombs, right?
Right.
You see what I mean?
So, there's always a place, even though it sounds categorically, oh, Europe and World War II was a nightmare.
No, it wasn't.
Sure.
I mean, one of the core things that I'm trying to see here is if there is something outside of the consequence of being the most powerful guy in the room, because clearly, Yahweh is the most powerful guy.
I mean, even if you look at, like, kingship on...
I don't want to say a secular level, but let's just say that, okay?
The way the kingship works is that sovereignty requires legitimacy.
You said that.
People don't just follow the king because the king said he's the king.
They have to see him as being legitimate, and then they get behind him.
Otherwise, you have revolutions all the time.
So, it was overtly known in ancient times that the king had legitimacy because the god was behind him.
So, what gives the gods...
if you go one step higher than that, what gives the gods legitimacy?
Specifically, what gives Yahweh legitimacy as king?
Is it just the fact that he has all the power, and the rats are in the cage, and he's like, fuck y'all, you're in the cage.
So, stay there.
Yeah, because there are certain things that occur that just can't be changed.
So, we're all in the cage, and so is everybody else on the other side.
Yeah, you could say that.
A spiritual cage would be of no relevance to the physical world, other than its imposition.
You know, if it wants to start coming in, and a physical cage in the material world would mean nothing in the spiritual world.
So, then everything is the result of a power dynamic.
Right.
Ultimately.
Dynamic, yeah.
Power dynamic is like saying power power, because dynamic means power in Greek, but yeah.
But of a power situation.
So, the guy with the most power rules is the fundamental understanding here.
Oh yeah, might makes right, correct.
And the most mighty makes what's right.
Okay, well, in that case.
I mean, do you want to explore that either in, you know, here or there, or, you know, it's the same.
No, that's fine.
You know, again, this is a world ruled by Satan, or the adversary, let's just say.
So, the things that people are striving, like for example, if you ask someone, are you striving for good?
Yes.
What is that good?
And they explain it to you.
That's mostly evil, evil stuff to the gods.
And if you strive to what the gods consider good, most people will say that's pretty evil.
Right?
Yeah.
I mean, think of a phaser.
You know, I said, I wish I had a phaser.
Why?
Oh, it's for landscaping.
You know, the Star Trek phaser, you're just pointing it at someone, they turn into a pile of dust.
You can't tell them well, because it's neat and clean.
They'll say that's evil.
Right?
Anyway.
Well, that does it for the hierarchy stuff.
What else?
But hold on, the hierarchy works the same way electricity works, it works the same way magnets work, works the same way water works.
In other words, those things I just mentioned are natural forces that appear to be ever-powerful in this realm.
Right?
You know, water, no water, forget it.
No electricity, you're not going to have anything doing anything.
And no magnetism, there won't be any material.
Once you start understanding these material things, you'll see that there's a relationship in the spiritual realm.
You can't change those things.
You know, that's why, you know, if you study the Greek philosophy and metaphysics, it's not translated.
You know, you're not going to, the current mindset can't grasp what's being said.
Right?
Because what they're telling you is there are things that don't change, and the more you understand them is you'll understand why things do change, because the things that aren't changeable are rotating around the things that don't change.
It's like the concept of the atom is completely misunderstood.
And, you know, when I started looking into some of the Greek writings, I'm like, this is not what, you know, when you look at what the English professors are writing about, I'm like, that's not what's being said.
And I can do that.
I'm not educated, and I don't have any special training in that.
Except you know Greek.
Well, ancient Greek is different, by the way.
Just, you know, I mean, if you want to start qualifying it, you're going to have to learn it.
But what I found by learning the ancient Greek is similar in all languages.
You know, you have pre-root meaning of word, you know, you've seen that in Strong's Concordance, root meaning unknown.
That's bullshit.
Right?
If you know the letter, you know what it means.
You have prefixes and suffixes, right?
That are undeniable.
Like, you know, I usually give the example when you see a in front of a word it means without the root meaning, right?
Like amoral means without morality.
So you see the a that means without, you know, pro means running with, and para means with, pro means for, towards.
So you know, you have certain methodologies to develop, and once you hold on to those basics, which don't change, you'll start to get a definitive communication versus a version.
Again, that sounds familiar when you're studying scripture.
I mean, you know, here's the thing, just for shicks and giggles, like they say, and fun, I still occasionally will pull up an e-sword and various things and look at words that I would, you know, if I meditate on scripture and say, does that word really mean that?
And I look it up and it doesn't, you know, and I've done so many of them right now that I can actually meditate on scripture properly and see how simple it is, its simplicity.
You know, recently I was explaining to someone the word sin, you know, the Christians like to use that a lot.
You know, it just means missing the mark, and just being in front of the computer I quickly went, I just did a search, Strongs, you know, Strong apostrophe S, Greek, sin, and Bible Hub pulls, you know, pulls up the meaning of the word, shows you what's being used, and it actually had in the definition, which is not in the other, in the e-sword, very clearly it says missing the mark.
Amartya, right?
And I was like, perfect, it's exactly the metaphor I gave, I showed this individual, I said, basically sinning is like going to a shooting range and you say you're gonna hit the bullseye and you miss, you just sinned if you don't hit the, you know, the bullseye.
It's missing the mark.
So here's the interesting part, you ever read the book Catch-22?
I can't even say that I, I did read it, but I didn't read it in a state where I could recall it, it was a very long time ago, and I didn't think it was important, but one of the guys in there in the beginning of the book was, I just want to be bored because I found out, someone said that if you're bored you don't age, right?
So he attached one thing to another, right?
So basically if you have no attachments or no desires, can you sin?
No.
If you have no desires to do anything or pursue anything or attempt anything, can you sin?
No, because you're never gonna miss the mark, because you're not doing anything.
Hmm, it makes sense.
It was the Christ without sin because he had no desire to do anything other than what he was sent here to do?
Think about it.
You can't say he had no desire other, there's still a desire there.
Well, because he's a man, but what I'm saying is the, what he accomplished was exactly what he was set out, set out to do, so he's without sin, isn't he, is he not?
Didn't, wasn't he put to death and resurrected, is exactly as planned from the promise from the beginning?
Very simple, why he's without sin.
These are simple concepts, very, very simple concepts.
Remember the scripture is baby talk to humans.
It's their baby talk, which, which I find reviling because, you know, I've, if you've listened to maybe some, I used to press on with this when I was doing some sonic events back in the day.
There should be no separate child cult society.
Children are just small people.
Should be no happy meals and children's, you know, subculture, children, you know, shows and children books and that's bullshit, right?
Something I like about frescoes is children are a pain in the ass, you know, until they, until they, you know, they get it, get their act together, right?
Or, you know, when they're not, when they have assholes raising them.
Let's just look at the language thing real quick since you brought that up, because ever since coming across Greek speak, I've been making adjustments to certain aspects of my mindset, but it's common to run into real-world situations that challenge some Greek speak conclusions and the issue of language is one of them.
So now I sort of pay attention more to etymology than I used to, but I find that when I overly focus on it, I run into other problems which raise some questions.
So if I were to say, like, in general, what's the purpose of language?
It seems that the purpose of language is for communication, right?
Irrespective of values or accuracy of speech or virtue or whatever, there's a whole range of things that could be communicated across any of those.
Yeah, but Sam, when people, you think people are speaking to each other, they're grabbing words and trying to attach them to pre-downloaded files, right?
They're not really listening.
No, okay, so it's not effective communication, but it's still communication, I'm just saying.
Because they can't rationalize.
And let's go back to the Tower of Babel, when their languages were, their tongues were mixed up.
So what?
I know they didn't have Babelfish Google or whatever.
Well, I don't know they didn't.
I wasn't there.
But what, they couldn't develop a sign language in a method of a translating or a bridge?
Of course they could have.
It mixed up their rationale.
Because, you see, they couldn't rationalize anyway other than, right?
Right now, if you were in wherever you were, and all of a sudden everyone spoke a complete different language, does that mean the world's gonna end?
You won't be able to get anything done?
Bullshit.
Of course you can't.
But that's presuming you can be rational about it.
But if you go into a panic, no, you're not.
You see?
And also, when most people are speaking, they're just thinking about attaching certain words, every other word or whatever, not the articles, you know, or whatever, but, you know, to previous, right?
Like, you know, discussing with an acoustic engineer.
So he's like, yeah, I know what you mean.
And then I try to go back and he really didn't.
Yeah, yeah, okay, fine.
So there's inefficiency across the certain mindset.
Because people can't be rational, right?
It's part of the cosmic censorship.
Look at the, I use Jeremiah as a reference all the time.
When they come to him, they say, we know you're a prophet of Yahweh, we'll do anything you say.
And he tells them, well, don't go to Egypt, don't stay here.
Oh, we don't like that, we don't like what, no, we're gonna do it anyway.
But you know that there's rationality within that irrationality, right?
I don't want to say it's called psychology, you know, put it inside the field itself.
Yeah, there is no chaos.
Yeah, there is no chaos or irrationality.
That's why I use the term cosmic censorship.
And, you know, if you're ruled by the adversary and you don't know that, constantly, you know, adjusting like some kind of, you know, ship or plane through the fog.
You know, usually you could pilot a ship or a plane, but when there's complete fog and zero visibility, you're relying on instrumentation.
And most people are not relying on the instrumentation of their, you know, the instrumentality of knowledge that's been gained.
They're impulsive, you know.
So language is fine the way it is.
It's the way people are using it.
Like a hammer is a great thing, but you could bash someone's brains in with it.
It's a murder.
By operation of law, a hammer can be a murder weapon.
By operation of law, right?
This is the murder weapon.
He's holding up a hammer in court.
And you're like, no, that's a hammer.
That's for carpenters and other things, you know.
But how did it become a murder weapon all of a sudden?
By operation of law, by operation of the rationale, by operation of being led by the adversary, by the operation of cosmic censorship, language is ineffective.
Sure, but at its primary, in its primary functionality, it's meant, it's simply meant to communicate.
It doesn't have values built into it.
You impose the values.
So whether you want to use it accurately, or you want to use it adversarially, that's your business.
But the purpose is to communicate, and to open up a range of communicative potentials, right?
So having said that, I do understand that in order to formulate things, you would need language to initially be fixed.
Like in order to serve that function, it has to have fixed references, like any objective thing.
It has to have substructure, valid syntax, vocabulary, grammar, clear etymology, literary devices, and so on.
But then there's, of course, nothing to stop you from later on down the line, violating those frameworks and doing whatever you want.
But you could still be communicating effectively, even if you violate the original parameters.
We see that with like pigeon languages that develop in certain...
Or religion, religions, they say, what's your religion based on?
It's based on the Qur'an or whatever, you know, they say that, right?
But is it?
No.
But it's used against people.
Like, for example, have you heard of the the New Order of Barbarians?
Dr. Day in 1968 at the Pittsburgh Pediatric Society did a speech to other doctors about the coming world in 1969.
He talked about all these things you have now, you know, let's promote homosexuality, and we're gonna call it gay, right?
So, and anyone who's against it is phobic of it, you know, they already planned all that stuff, right?
So, or let's, we were gonna have them do this, and he was discussing things that, you know, were not even, you know, in the public eye at all.
So, I mean, depends on, you know, there's a level of engineering behind it, you know?
Like, when somebody said, I want a phaser, why?
And I'm not gonna, you know, tell them because it's very neat, because I'm gonna use it for landscaping, cut the grass easy, yeah, right, you know, sure.
Right, but anyway.
Let's put aside the cultural aspects, like, just the language for a second.
You can still communicate effectively even if you violate the rules, right?
We see that with pidgin languages, we see with mental health victims who create their own way of communicating, we see it with pop culture where everything is dumbed down to sub-Neanderthal levels, and people still speak to each other.
Now, you can say that they're not effective or whatever, but things move forward, and people still talk to each other, and, you know.
Because they're allowed, they're allowed that level of rationale to continue the society where, for example, at the Tower of Babel, they were not, that rationale was not allowed to continue.
So it was not just the languages, the language was enough to stop the rationale.
Right.
By the way, you know, language will, there's a promise of restoring a more pure language in the future, by the way.
I've come across that, yeah, I haven't thought about it much, but, okay.
But what I'm trying to get to eventually, maybe I should just give the punchline first and stop all this shit.
The Greek won't let me get to the point.
So even though etymology determines the memorialized meaning of a word, we know that usage in context is what determines the social-cultural meaning, or, you know, in real-time conversations, what people think it means.
So realistically, you can't pull out single words out of a conversation stream or a text and assume that it has a bounded definition that's self-evident because you know what the etymology is, right?
Well, hold on.
Unless you are determined to deal on a level where people mean what they say and say what they mean, I use the analogy to bring up, here's the thing, I'll pat myself on the back, I'm one of the few people in the last decade who's made a big point about that.
I'm the only one I've ever heard bring up a lot of these words and it's actually spread and I'm glad to see it, but even though it's not going to help anyone.
When someone says my kids, I'm like, wait a second, you have goats?
I know exactly what they mean, but is this person speaking to me about their kids?
Do they say what they mean and mean what they say?
In an accepted reality, on their social level, it does, but from a more objective point of view, it doesn't.
So, in other words, this person who's telling me about their kids consistently, using that term, is going to have problems objectifying other things.
That's a pretty good scenario to put them in, to project that on them.
That's what I'm trying to say.
So when you find people are not using words properly, it's very clear that they don't say what they mean and mean what they say within an objective point of reality.
So it's about objective, but they're purely, they're totally normal within the society, right?
Because you turn on the television, a very popular television network is always using the word kids and this and that, everyone's very, you know, they make billions.
Everybody knows kids means that, you see, but can they objectify?
No, they're going to show you paper-thin aluminum planes going through steel towers and everyone's going to believe it.
You see, I mean, this is what one, this is what it leads to.
As a matter of fact, going back to Scripture, isn't it say somewhere if they're not interrupted there will be no life left at all?
So, that's what it's going to lead to.
Yeah, you do have to specify who they are, you can't just say that generally, but objectifying means that you're using references to show how something is constituted, right?
By referencing the references and using measurements.
So, are you saying that usage and culture is not a reference point?
No, well, it's not for if you're going to jump from one through time or from one culture to another and it doesn't work.
Yeah, but language doesn't exist in the other, English doesn't exist in Italy as a language.
Yeah, that's...
Go back a thousand years, there's no English, so you can't, so we're not talking about jumping cultures.
We're talking about modern English, it doesn't exist anywhere else outside of the past couple of hundred years.
So, words have an etymology, sure, but they also have a position within a phrase which is in a sentence, which is in a paragraph, which is positioned within a contextualized discussion or exposition, and you have to triangulate all of that simultaneously to extract out the meaning of the words as they're being used.
If you take the singular word and only look at the etymology, then you decontextualize it from the social cultural setting.
Right.
So, unless you're saying that the social cultural setting is not a reference, I mean, who said you're allowed to do that?
If the purpose of words is to communicate, if the purpose of language is to communicate, who says you're allowed to decontextualize the setting and say, this is the etymology that determines what it means.
No, you do it because, you know, when someone, you know why you do that ultimately in this society or any society that you know is going to change?
If you live in a house, don't make it out of glass, because, you know, what you're basically doing is throwing rock at the window when you do that.
And is it, you know, when a rock is thrown through a window, is it deserved?
Well, sometimes it might be, right?
Yeah, basically throwing rocks.
Is it correct?
Yeah, it's correct.
Is it, is it incorrect if it, you know, takes it out of context?
No, but if it's a society, if these people are idiots and they're not going to get, you know, anything done anyway, why the hell not?
I mean, you can't use that sort of rhetoric to rationalize the situation, because you can't tell people that they're idiots.
Sure, I do all the time.
I was having a conversation a couple of times, I bring this up, George Carlin, the comedian, right?
He'll, he'll have an American audience, he'll spend a half an hour saying how stupid Americans are, and I'm talking about deep cutting comments.
And there and he has a result in deafening applause.
Right?
But that's okay, because it's just comedy.
But if you look at him on stage, he's deftly serious, you know, he's not joking.
But the setting is a come, you know, comedic stand up.
So I guess it's just hits home so much, right?
But if you stand up in a courtroom or in public in a series that they'll cut you to pieces if you say the same stuff.
So I guess the context in which it's being done is important.
Also, you know, or the venue, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so context can be objectified as well.
Right.
That's why the best way to get a point across is through show business, cause, you know, comedy or movies, you know, how many times have we even discussed, you know, maybe they're showing you how they're showing you stuff in movies, right?
That's going to happen.
So context is valid with what you're saying, as far as communicating in different forms.
Why is context not equally valid when it comes to language in the sense that the con, like, I'm not, I'm not trying to, I'm not somebody's lawyer and I'm trying to defend them.
But if people are using the word kid in a certain context and the context explains how that word functions in that setting, why is that not valid?
Why then say, well, it doesn't mean what you're using it for.
Yeah, but in the context, it does though.
Yeah, it's valid when you establish if you were to contextualize or memorialize that event, you know, or, you know, let's say you were to do a transcript of that conversation for memorial purposes, put it away so it could be retrieved later, right?
You know what I mean?
The summary would be, well, here, I'm having a conversation with a moron and this is the words that he's using.
These are the words, no really.
Okay, forget it.
No, no, why?
It's true.
No, this is just, this is just pejorative soft realism.
Like I don't, the fact that morons is neither here nor there.
We're talking about the language.
Look, attorneys do this all the time.
Give you an example.
If you go to any government office anywhere in the world and start bringing up, I want to speak to the attorney here, works in the government, right?
Why you guys are doing this?
They don't answer anything you're saying.
They say, you keep going because you're going to go to jail.
That's what they always say.
They don't want to address anything that you're saying.
What the hell, what they're basically telling you is you're just an underling scumbag.
We control everything.
Get the fuck out of here.
Right?
So, I mean, you know, um.
It's just that when you try to, when you try to tell people.
When I call, when I tell people, call people morons, I'm not using that as a put down.
I'm using it as an accurate statement.
It's actually a much higher, it's much higher than what they really should be called.
But that's another discussion.
No, it's a put down.
Even though, even if it's accurate, it's still a put down because most people don't understand what you're saying.
That's their problem.
I just don't want their problem to be my problem, right?
Okay.
But the point is, I forget the point because I'm getting tired.
No, that's fine.
But look, this, when I, very often when I speak, it's not within a culture of a specific geographic location.
No, what I was going to say is.
I speak on a worldly level.
I'm trying to be more worldly.
In other words, when I say moron, I'm applying it to Iraqis, Russians, Colombians, Canadians, Americans, Spanish, Italians, Greeks, all of them.
Sure.
You know, Libyans.
But the thing is, you run into people and you try to explain this, the language stuff and they always fall back on social cultural usage.
And you have to negate that if you want to move forward with the etymology understanding.
Right.
So speak a more worldly, worldly, speak in a worldly sense.
Why don't you give analogies and metaphors and things that affect the whole world?
Very often I say, what if we visit a planet where Kevlar underwear is the biggest industry because they have a tradition and custom across the planet to put thumbtacks on their seats before they sit down.
I didn't say one country.
When I say surface dwelling earth inhabitants, is that one culture or the you say, no, it's worldly.
It's the entire group.
There's implications when you go from culture to culture, even, you know, you'll see inconsistencies in etiquette and tradition that might make someone seem vile from one culture to another.
Like if you go to certain Arabic countries, if you sit down and cross your leg and show the bottom of your shoe, the bottom of your foot, that's like the middle finger in a Western country.
Or if you run into like someone from the Ukraine, let's say this is, I'll give you an experience, someone moving, a Ukrainian woman engineer, she needed some help moving and all these Americans went over to help her and she wanted things stacked and moved a certain way.
She had them labeled in, you know, Russian basically and they couldn't read if it was dishes or whatever, right?
So I said, well, how did it go?
And she goes, yeah, they're all strong like bull, but smarter like gorillas, right?
Well, because they couldn't read in, you know, Russian.
Yeah, pretty stupid, right?
To her.
You get my point?
Yeah, that's less of a cultural thing, more of a social thing.
Obviously, dishes don't, you know, they go a certain way.
She labeled everything, all the boxes in Russian and, like characters.
No, well, she was expecting to move it all on her own and she needed some help.
We went to help her and she's yelling at everyone about where the boxes, how the boxes are being stacked.
Can't you see this is dishes?
And we're like, that's just scribble to me.
You see?
So there's your language, there's your perception, there's your worldly, you know, I wasn't there.
If I was there, I'd say, what is all your breakable stuff?
Put it aside, you know.
First, what is breakable?
Because I've experienced with moving, right?
If it's not breakable, it's less of a, right?
So ask questions first, right?
Not later, you know.
Yeah.
So she considered everyone to be smart like gorilla because they couldn't read that she wrote dishes and, right.
When she would, that was the truth, wasn't it?
No.
Yes.
Yeah.
No.
They're supposed, if you're going to go help someone who writes in Russian, you better know how the Russians label, you know, they, what they should have said is we, you know, we don't know what's, you know, what's, can you please, they should have anyway.
Oh, they should have.
Okay.
Yeah.
We don't know what, you know, why are you, oh, I'm sorry.
You know what?
The help should have.
Oh, the help should have.
Yeah.
All, but look, you know what that means?
Well, neither one should have, and they all should have, but it's called working.
It's called working together.
You get into a situation where everybody has to work together is the best situation, right?
So you walk into a room and you know, you're moving stuff and you don't recognize the labeling.
The reason there's a label is to communicate.
So in other words, you're walking into a situation where you won't be able to communicate.
How about resolving that first?
Goes back to your language.
Communication is very important.
Now I could read that language, but I don't know what it means.
Just like, you know, if you don't know, let's say Italian, you could read, if you know Roman letters or English, you can read the Italian newspaper, but you don't know what it's, you know, what it means.
But these guys could look like foreign symbols to them completely.
You know, they didn't understand the Cyrillic characters.
And so there's two levels there removed.
That's why I'm saying that most people are sounding words without comprehension.
They can read.
I mean, at times you heard me say they're functionally literate, illiterate.
I don't know what these words mean, but ultimately it breaks down to rationale.
It can't be rational either.
How can they?
They were not raised to, you know, the culture doesn't promote it, promotes the opposite.
You know how it does that by, well, I shouldn't say confusion alone, but because you have so many choices that you can't make any more choices.
But conveniently, when you want to make a choice, because there's so many choices, it's very easy to, and I'm telling you, you have no choice.
There are no choices.
It's an illusion of choice.
Oh, well, we're all doomed then.
No, you're not doomed.
Well, if you believe what the adversary has set up, yes, you're doomed.
That's where the doom lies, because doom is a realization of an unfortunate ending that was not expected.
If it was expected, it's not, you know, it's a tragedy.
You know, you knew it was going to happen anyway, so.
No, I'm just joking.
That's why I say, you know, if the bad news is you've got 14 years left and you know what the good news is, you've got 14 years left.
Anywho, we can wrap up or we can attack one more thing.
Yeah, so it's up to Bruce and if we're, are we still streaming?
Yep, we're doing fine.
That's fine.
I have coffee and cigarettes and I plugged in a power supply.
If you're tired, we can stop or if you want to do one more thing, that's fine.
You there?
Let's see.
Should be.
Bruce, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you fine.
Oh, you're breaking up the same towards me.
Does Bruce sound like he's duplexing or break intermittent?
I'm definitely breaking up.
Yeah.
Hello?
Yeah, go ahead.
I was gone or did, was I not?
I don't know.
No, you were gone and Bruce is breaking up and am I coming through clearly?
I can hear you, you know.
You just messaged, I can't hear anything.
Oh, but now I can hear you.
What was the other thing?
Uh-huh.
What was it?
Do you want to do one more thing you said?
Oh, the other thing.
Well, that was sort of the idea of natural, sort of the natural rights fallacy that comes along in the enlightenment period.
So despite the encroachment of certain Eastern religions and the philosophical influences of that in the 19th and 20th century, Western civilization has predominantly been shaped by two pillars of tradition, which is the Judeo-Christian and the Greco-Roman.
And that saturates everything from tradition to culture to laws.
So to narrow in on that, over the past 400 years or so, movements like the Reformation, the Enlightenment have produced a consensus of morality that's predicated on certain presuppositions that have organized society.
And part of that is, obviously it's not in the Bible or in scripture, but it's something like the divine, that there's something divine or sacred in all human beings.
And that's a presupposition that's embedded in the legal society, in the idea of natural rights.
And basically the result of that idea of natural rights is that society claims to value the individual above everything else.
So it puts sovereignty in the hands of the individual.
That's what the adversary teaches.
There is nothing sacred in the individual.
But go ahead.
Right.
So like I'm looking at the Enlightenment period, and you see that pop up a lot with people like John Locke and Jacques Rousseau, and stuff like this.
And this is where the Patriot movement gets there.
The individual is sovereign and this sovereign blah, blah, blah.
Right.
They're idiots.
Yeah.
They're full of hate and stupidity.
The Patriots, the minute you see that.
Yeah.
But in addition to that, the Enlightenment stuff, since the 60s counterculture revolution, people have been further indoctrinated into the idea that their lives center around freedoms and rights.
And through a ramp up in consumerism and Buddhist philosophies and stuff like that, it's really gone kind of far.
The Buddhist religion, not the Buddhist writings.
Yeah.
Which is like Christianity versus the Bible.
Buddhist religion has nothing to do with the Buddhist writings.
They're a bunch of assholes, the Buddhists.
But go ahead.
So in general, I'm just trying to examine ways of discrediting that in a rational way.
Like, even if I didn't, if you don't get to mention scripture once, because you're talking to somebody that doesn't know it.
Is there like a Greek speak way of just approaching that I'm trying to find?
Regarding speaking regarding from a platform to someone without referencing it?
Sure.
I do it all the time.
Yeah, in trying to...
How can you not?
If you comprehend scripture and meditate on it, everything, it will change the way you speak.
Yeah, that's fine.
But I mean, talking to a Mormon.
Don't say we don't talk to Mormons, because we do.
But I mean, it's impossible not to.
Unless you're by yourself.
So if you sort of wanted to explain that how there are no such thing as natural rights.
Oh, I see what you're saying, discredit that fallacy.
Yeah, I want to discredit the whole notion.
Well, before you get into, well, if you want to discuss natural rights, so basically, if you can define nature, if you can define rights, you know, I mean, but then again, that might sound like you're being, you know, sidestepping the issue.
You know, natural rights is very simple.
You could say, if we go out to that pond over here and take out some water, look under a microscope, you're going to see all the organisms are fighting each other.
If you look in the jungle, you know, one, the larger animal eats the smaller animal, usually, and the smaller animal learns instinctively to avoid the larger animals.
Right.
So yeah, no, there's still order there.
If a person is hooked on natural rights, if you there's two ways to do it, you know, when I have time with a Christian or a Muslim or a Jew or a Buddhist, if I have a lot of time and I know I'm going to dedicate time, I tend to seem agreeable and let them tell me as much as they can about what they know about what they believe in.
Right.
And instead of saying, well, that's stupid or that's whatever, I start, you know, working in to see, you know, how much they really can back it up with the rationale that they've been taught from other areas as well.
To give you an example, a negative way of doing this is when I discuss with people regarding how the body works, I don't want to hear them say, are you a doctor?
Oh, you're not a doctor, so you're not qualified to tell me how the body works.
Then I say, are you a doctor?
And they usually say, well, I don't know anything about the human body.
I'm not a doctor.
And then, right, then you have to walk away because then, you know, they cannot, they lack the rationale.
They, you see, it's like going to a headhunter and ask him, are you upset that you have five shrunken heads?
And if he says, yes, because my brother has 20.
And then how do you deal with that?
You know, how do you begin to inform them?
Because there's no way you're going to have a conversation with him on his level.
So if they're going for natural rights, one thing, you know, it depends on the individual again.
Like the word nature means God in ancient Egypt.
So God, right, and the gods don't give rights, they give laws.
I would say maybe there are more laws than rights.
Like the laws of nature, maybe.
Yeah, but we can't maybe our way through it.
And frankly, ancient Egyptian language is not the end-all be-all for etymology.
So you can't keep saying that.
No, but the reason I say it is because it may be it's a good way to stick a crowbar in that loose piece of plywood and get it off.
So you can put a fresh piece of plywood on it.
But it is true, by the way, the niters.
It's not even nature, it's niter.
Yeah, in ancient Egyptian.
N-T-R, it's constant, there's no vowels.
It's N-T-R, if you were to really spell it out.
But I would just suggest that it's sometimes better instead of doing one-on-one, do it in a group setting.
But if you're, okay, if someone is in a natural law or natural rights, natural rights is really, that's almost like an oxymoron.
I think that there is no pat, simple answer.
I think a lot of it takes work.
And essentially, this might sound superstitious or supernatural.
But if you have a keen observation of humanity, you're going to have to be inclusive of the cosmic censorship and be able to discern and recognize who the gods want to see this and who they don't want to see it.
And that means making very rapid, swift judgments that you don't etch in stone, but you hold as a reference point.
Right?
So.
Yeah, right.
It's simple.
I mean, what part of cosmic censorship don't you get?
If the gods don't want someone to see something, you can torture them to death, they still won't.
That has nothing to do with it.
I'm trying to, it's about a certain type of rationale that can be used to explain something in a way that the only way to oppose it is to be arbitrary and to just deny what somebody is saying.
It depends.
Again, Sam, this is not being whatever, but you're trying to bring, you said, rationale to the irrational.
And that's valid to say that.
How do you bring rationale to the irrational?
You're saying it like it can't be done.
Of course it can be done.
No, I didn't say that can't be done, because if you discern those that can accept it, from a cosmic point of view or spiritual point of view, then it can be done.
You know, very often, I'll give you an example.
I'm out at the shops, and you'll have a big store, you know, a food store, and they'll set up these demonstration tables.
You might have seen it, you know, where they're giving samples of products.
And if I, you know, if I have time, I'll stand there and start doing Greek speak.
And before you know it, there's five, six, seven, eight people all crowded around.
They're not interested in Sam, they're interested in what I'm saying.
Right?
And some of them are not, some of them are, but some of them get really excited about it.
And they're like, oh, how do I get in touch with you?
This is great.
You need to write a book, blah, blah, blah.
I said, okay, are you going to email me?
Here's the email.
And I said, when do you think you're going to email me?
Oh, in about an hour.
Guess what?
They never do.
So there's that level also.
What I mean is, you might have a conversation and have a breakthrough moment, and you can get past the natural rights and evolve.
And then, then so what?
They might say, well, good Sam, I want to stay in touch with you.
And they do.
Or they might say, Sam, I'm going to be in touch with you.
And they never do.
Are you going to be attached to that?
No.
Nobody's attached to that.
So the thing is, all right, well, no one is or no one isn't.
But this is irrelevant.
What I'm saying is, you do what you do.
And if it happens, it happens.
It's like panning for gold.
No, no, no, no, no.
You have to do what you do in a certain way.
You have to do what you do.
I don't want to say effectively, because it's not about the outcome per se.
Because like you said, they can go either way.
But you have to do it in a methodological way.
I'm not saying that right.
Methodology.
You have to have a methodology that is valid in the way that you do things.
You can't just say, I went out and I talked to people and it didn't work.
Well, maybe it didn't work because you suck.
And you don't know how to communicate.
And you didn't pick the right words.
And you're not eloquent.
You don't have any charisma.
And you were impatient.
Like that's your problem.
As long as I hit all my...
It could be a personal problem.
Like maybe you don't want your self-development to be along those lines.
It could be a temporal problem.
Like it's not time yet.
But for you to be able to learn how to communicate...
Not for you, for anyone.
Like the steam engine was around 2,000 years ago.
But Fulton was the one that made it in industry.
What?
Something new?
Light bulbs were around 300 years ago.
Electricity was around 300, 400 years ago.
500 years ago, 1,000 years ago.
But we have electrified cities.
It wasn't time yet for that.
No, but there were people who knew how those things worked.
And they used it for their own personal gain.
So kudos to them.
The society, the fact that they didn't have it is their problem.
So I'm talking about you need to learn how to communicate for your own personal gain.
As a point of self-development for yourself.
Personal gain would go in...
If you keep pushing the issue of personal gain, for example, you go into the commercial realm.
Now it's about doing commerce.
Who says you have to do that?
Well, no, if you push the realm of personal gain in this society, it's commercial.
No, you might just want to power your house or whatever.
That's your thing.
You don't have to push it.
But how are you going to power your house without getting wire and all the other necessities?
Are you going to make it yourself?
That's fine too.
But by the time you make a generator from scratch, you'll be so old, you won't need it anymore.
Well, but it's not about setting up an enterprise to sell stuff to anybody.
No, but acquiring it, you're going to have to find, you know, depending on the level of...
What level of convenience are you willing to accept or not accept?
Like, for example, if you lived in, let's say, 100 years ago on the Polynesian islands, your level of convenience would be a straw hut, and that's fine, right?
Sure.
So what level of convenience...
You know, this is another example.
A lot of people say, I want to live off the grid.
I'm like, why?
It's going to cost a hell of a lot more than being on the grid.
And anyone who's ever proven that out found it to be true.
Electricity costs three to five times as much than being on the grid.
Well, I don't want to be a part of the system.
What if it closes?
Well, it's super cheap to, you know...
I wouldn't, I can't...
The point is, from a heuristic point of view, which is, you know, quick problem solving, for example, you don't have to have a problem to solve it.
In other words, there's a mindset behind that, right?
But the problem sure helps, you know, the mindset exercise that problem-solving ability, right?
You see?
You know, like creativity.
What does a crisis create?
You know, problems create creativity, you know?
And also the concept of accidents, you know?
Most of the people that I've met that are inventors with patents and things like that, their inventions are not stuff they ponder.
They're things they discovered by accident or through failure.
So when you bring up, you know, how do you communicate this or how do you do this?
Why don't you try and come back and report how effective it was?
If it wasn't effective, tell us it wasn't effective.
So now we know as a step on the ladder that, you know, that's a step on the ladder that we need to keep walking on.
Don't dwell on it, right?
That's why very often is, but how does this work?
Or should I do this?
I don't know what to do and report back.
But it has to be consistent.
If you're engaging with people on how to do this or how not to do it or what if, if they don't report back, where's the accumulation?
Where's the evolution of the matter?
There is none.
So it goes back to communication, reliability, proximity.
If someone says, well, you know, I don't know what it's like to do this.
And you say, I don't know either.
Are you willing to try?
Yeah, I'm willing to try it.
Well, when you do try it, let us know how it worked out.
If they never come back, it's as if that conversation never happened, right?
Even though they did it, you have to come back and report.
You know, once that is established as, you know, see, that's another thing that's going on, you know.
That's part of the censorship, by the way.
We, again, back to scripture.
You know, we read about the end time scenarios, you know, Antichrist, all these macinations, all these events.
I'm telling you, when these things start unfolding, they're going to be a secret.
You see the rationale behind that, I hope.
Because if they're happening and everyone has access to exactly how they're going to happen and when, they're all going to shout foul, aren't they?
But the scripture says they're not going to shout foul.
That means that they're not going to know.
Just like when the Christ came to earth, how many people knew who he was, even when he was standing in the room with them?
Not unless he allowed them to.
Spiritually, mentally, you know, from a cosmic or divine level, right?
When he opened the scroll in the synagogue, let's say, the study hall, I call it, was he acknowledged as the Christ?
Or just some guy with a bunch of followers who was popular that they got really pissed off at?
The latter, you see?
So, this is a very interesting...
Here's another thing to recall.
Once you see that something works, don't be so, don't just stick with it because you're stubborn.
Keep, and don't be happy with because you found out how it works.
Keep investigating it so you get the fine points also, so you can make corrections where needed, right?
That's why very often, you know, like for example, I did the thing with Ocelli and very often I bring up, you know, things from the past that I know are going to happen again and again.
Just not to say that, look what I did, but because you can do it too, and this is what's being used.
I remember in 2015 with Ocelli, I was saying, the spring of 2018 is when you're going to see movements in the Middle East that are going to be for sure, you're going to see the transition of change, and for sure, it's going to be the precursor to the Middle East Union, you know, like you're going to watch what's happening in Israel.
And Ocelli comes up, says, I think it's 2017, not 2018.
And I'm like, well, why?
What are you basing it on?
He's like, well, no, I just think it's 2017.
And I'm like, no, it's 2018 because the seven-year period ends in the fall of 2017.
In the spring, there's going to be, you see, planting and then growth, right?
And there's going to be, was I correct?
Yeah, I was correct.
Is it my just like, oh, great, I'm glad I'm correct this time.
And I, you know, no, because I can give you all the reasons why, you see.
So again, when you interact with people about natural, right, or natural, are you prepared to give them all the reasons why they, you know, from their point or another point, you see?
And once you understand the details and the fine points of all of it, there's nothing to, you know, it'll work out or it won't.
But you know that you don't have a deficit, right?
You know, it's not like shooting dice.
Yeah, that's part of it is trying to overcome the deficit or trying to fill that to a point of surplus.
Which is still a process.
I mean, I can do it partially, but very definitively.
A very simple thing is, you know, do the animals have a problem with natural law?
No, because no one's really had a conversation with a bear, you know, or a dog or a cat or whatever about natural law specifically.
So maybe is it natural law as it applies to man?
And why are there so many different types of law?
But you know, even though there's an appearance of so many choices, you really there is no choice, right?
So, you know what it boils down to eventually?
This is all of its entertainment.
How do you keep a society multiple?
Honestly, society is in plural preoccupied for 6,000 years because the society is not important.
It's the 6,000 years that's important, right?
To pass.
So you have to make sure they have fire and they have genitalia because without those two, they're not going to be around.
That's it.
Pretty simple plan.
And then the rest is entertainment.
What?
You don't think the world religions are entertainment?
Of course it is.
Do you think there is ever entertainment where people were thrown to the lions or munched up in machines and killed for no reason?
Sure.
Is it possible to have entertainment where people lose their lives?
You ever heard of something called the theater of war?
Right?
Yeah, it's all entertainment.
The gods have no qualms in wiping out billions of people.
They don't care about your body.
Not because I say so.
It's because they say so.
So, you know.
It's harsh.
It's harsh because you have a body.
Physical body.
That you can't shed, you know, at will.
Or dematerialize and appear somewhere else if you wanted to keep the body.
That's why, you know, years ago, I used to run into a born-again Christian.
I remember a conversation.
I won't forget.
He's in the parking lot.
Well, I'm born again.
I don't have to believe in what you're talking about.
I'm like, oh, you're really born again?
Is there a parking lot across the street?
Can you just show up right there right now?
But don't move from here.
Just, I want to see you in that parking lot across the street.
Can you do that?
Yeah, I'll be right.
I'm going to walk.
No, no, no, no.
Just go ahead and, you know, you're born again, right?
Okay.
You're a resurrected being.
So go ahead.
Let's see you show up across.
Just one demonstration.
You see how stupid these people are?
Yes, that is already evident.
Yeah, yeah.
So if you're born, you can do that, right?
So anyway, this is, yeah.
So is it entertaining?
No, but yes, it's bad entertainment.
Is there such thing as bad entertainment?
That's a really big one.
We still, I make a joke.
I was trying to make a joke.
Like we have this thing called Chick-fil-A here.
It's a thing like Hobby Lobby is another one.
They pride themselves as being closed on Sunday for worship, right?
And it's a chicken.
They serve chicken and I always joke around.
That's the born again chicken sandwiches, right?
You know, we're the born again hobbies or whatever.
You've heard of Chick-fil-A?
Not to mention.
Yeah, I call them the born again chicken sandwiches.
I love that.
Yeah, yeah.
These are idiots.
I mean, these are, you know.
I mentioned that to a Christian one time.
That was probably a rather uneasy moment.
Oh boy.
And everything is uneasy with them.
You have to be more honest.
I just couldn't help it.
Yeah, I mean, Satan's laughing his ass off at these people, you know.
He's laughing his ass off at us right now, I'm sure.
I don't think he cares enough to be listening to this.
But, you know, I'm sure that everything is being observed.
And taken into account.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd say the depths, what is it?
The depths is immeasurable.
Because look, what we see as being unattainable or infinite is very finite.
Once you, you know, you're not bound to this material realm, so.
I think I'm good for this one.
Yeah, this one.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, thanks.
We haven't done this in a while.
Thank you, Sam and Greek.
Okay.
Beautifully articulated by both of you.
A lot of Greek information.
Greek just spent the whole time just shooting my stuff down.
That's funny.
We're shooting it up.
No, no, I think interjecting is fine.
It's a, you know, why not?
It adds dynamics, right?
It does.
I could sit back and be quiet and listen.
But I think interrupting might be good, too.
Interrupting is fine.
We just want answers.
This is all I'm saying.
Yeah, well.
Maybe I have to think about it a bit more.
Yeah, yeah, think about it.
Yeah, I think when it sinks in, you're just going to, you know, wonder why bother.
I'm telling you, food, clothing, and shelter, man.
If you don't know that now, eventually, you know, food, clothing, and shelter, and good conversation.
Fire and genitalia.
Yeah.
Without fire and without genitalia, there's no human race.
Yeah, you're done.
As it is.
No fire, you've got nothing.
No genitalia, it all stops.
Okay, so simple.
There's your answers.
Thank you, Greg.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Carbon as usual.
Thank you, Sam.
You'll get over it.
All right, guys.
Yep.
Thanks again.
All right, later.
See you all, guys.