Greetings folks, we're on live with the Greek and how are you doing tonight?
Greetings.
Okay.
Yeah, we'll do a another short sonic perhaps sure and keep it Yeah, it's a it within the theme of it being midsummer here mid mid year it's past mid year it's also the You know for the folks that are upside down.
It's midwinter.
So yeah, I would suggest it's around the fifth month We're well into the second week going on we're going into the second week, right?
So almost middle of the month of the fifth month and what's interesting is, you know when you think about you know, the theme of the middle Middle of the year, you know middle of the summer middle of the winter.
However, you know you where you are when you're listening to this
it's
It's an interesting concept because that's the time when you have maximum maximum growth and
You know if you've listened to any Greek speak
You know summertime is when things grow and and just in a Greek speak
I bring up the Middle East Union a lot and I'm not saying this is when it's going to start right now
But it's all being prepared.
I looked at the what they call the news and China supposedly, you know, China is a fictional juristic thing, but you know the government there or the They're suggesting to do 20 billion in loans to the Middle East To rebuild it and it's funny how they didn't give them the 20 billion to defend it, right?
Right, which shows you how you know, just humans are just idiots and no one's really paying any attention
That's that's why you know the setup that the gods are putting on is so simple
I mean a child can do it even you know
It didn't have to be in other words
If you were to set up mankind for a scenario, you don't even have to be a god
That's how stupid people are but and no one would still notice or very few would and you can discredit them
but in essence most of the discussion is that gods have a plan and it's basically
Described if people look at ancient Ritz the majority of the ancient Ritz talk about the end of that plan and a little bit of
Information on what happens after but being the fifth month, you know
It's interesting whenever you want to contemplate lawful time go into some ancient documents or not
So ancient documents and look up, you know timekeeping
well, I'm sorry not look up timekeeping, but
Because there is nothing much there isn't much on it.
Just like there isn't much on why the sky is blue
But look up for example, you can you know with the mini television or the stupid rectangle, you know, you could look up
You could look up
What they call biblical search programs biblical search
searches queries and just put in fifth month in and search that in a Bible and
You get to see, you know things that are happening within the range of the time that you're in right now
You know in terms of the year and it's kind of interesting to compile certain things and also understand when you're compiling
Let's say the days that you might look up and let's say what they call the scriptures
those the ones that
Are themes that parallel a world events are when those world events will happen
You know
So you can parallel that as well
But you know if if you read scripture, of course, and it says, you know, it was the fifth month the 10th day.
It's not May You know, it's not any an unequal calendrical system.
That's funny.
It's still it shows me the cons of censorship and most people still Don't understand what I've been doing sonically and I say most actually I don't think anyone really does yet Why because I'll give the example, you know people still when I just you know that I've been listening to Greek speak for a long time You know, they'll still say oh, yeah, it's a lunar calendar and I'm like, oh boy.
There is no calendar You know them they don't understand it.
Most people still don't get it that it's an observational thing
so
Yeah, yeah, it's it's sad but there I think there's I think it's there's a little value still
I mean, there's a lot of value and what can be said or discussing things of high value
But there's not a lot of value of being public with it and I've tried for a long time
I don't mean to sound disparaging but it's just the humans are just not ready
Just like I've said this kind of stuff is for the next society not this society
But it doesn't mean you shouldn't do it, but I am petering out a little bit, you know
Like lately I've been past few months been saying like why bother
Right, you know just why bother right?
So So but in essence, you know again just to go back.
This is the middle of the year Let's it you know, and I would still stick to saying summer In more in a stricter sense because you know what the other the other hemisphere where it's winter It really is not a factor in prophecy and in Scripture You know, it almost makes you wonder if anyone really should be living there, right?
I think it just shows it shows the dichotomy of how things can be in how severe You know that one side of the planets in midsummer the other side of planets in midwinter So for for most of the discussion when I bring up seasons, I I'm negating the southern Aspect, you know where it's backwards.
So So I'm speaking more on the latitudes that are along the middle, you know The central part of what's called the Middle East, right?
Also if most people have Any done any research which most have not so, you know, I have they kind of like hang on the what I'm saying Very rarely do I see people spin off on the topic and bring new stuff, but where does lawful time begin?
it begins around somewhere between let's say Iraq and the Levant and that can be measured by using Astronomical location specifically the moon Which is one of the easiest things to see its phases, right?
So the moon actually becomes full when it renews initially at that point somewhere between Baghdad Babylon and Jerusalem It's initially cited as being full.
So that is your true datum line Right.
So usually we know when I'm discussing seasons.
It's based on that datum line You know and also what's interesting is if you are living down under where it's winter right now You will notice the full the moon does keep its phase as the northern Part of the world does even though it's the opposite season, right?
All right.
So I just wanted to bring that up that they're not completely out of the loop down there only seasonally.
All right, so
So with that said what's interesting is this is the first year in this particular seven year period
That I've spoken about for a few years that was coming
around the fall of 2017 spring of 2018
I've gone on record discussing this for a while
and what you might consider is the apex of this period occurring around
2021, you know the three and a half year mark, right or the fourth year of the seventh year period
Usually and it'll build up, but you know in the next couple of years, but what people can consider
is
Which won't be a big deal by the way when it happens
But you can consider by 2025 around there 2026 the spring the Middle East Union will begin
Right now it's every it'll be I would say almost in full swing, but not in full swing yet
You know, but it'll be there'll be no doubt that there is a Middle East Union by that time, right?
You know or unification and all eyes forward, you know to that and that being the front So, you know and it's it's interesting to discuss this when it's still just this this particular period is just starting to take form right Being the first year of the seven year period where?
Would the events that you see now are going to be very different than the events that you had in the past seven years
Which I've also discussed
The last seven year period I was saying you notice how things don't change
It's missing airplanes a lot of talk about corrupt politicians and financial crisis and right over and over and over and over
Still going live and strong except for the missing airplanes.
Not not as much Yes, but the corrupt politicians.
Oh, yeah, never an ending.
Yeah Keep in mind the politicians are officers of the government the government's a corporation So just like any officer, right?
They they are behest to the wills of the shareholders, which we don't know who they are We we know who they who their financial brokers are, you know, all the central banks and their ties Going back.
We don't know specifically who we could you know, they do expose who they are based on Their financial brokers, you know the central banks.
So, you know the government the the government officials are just Regular, you know morons or schmucks or whatever that you that the rest of the population is and they just bring them up Based on you know, they're how well-known they are or to fit that position, but they have no no no No say that's why very often you you'll see they'll make a promise and then they'll switch and do you know?
180 or 120 degrees right or 90 degrees or yeah, because they're just And I'm glad that Dimitri on the on the videos Dimitri Kalazov did a little bit of a talk on it I used to be more into that kind of research, but our research But the research showed me that these are just common morons like everyone else The government officials.
I mean presidents prime ministers all these guys also just like the rest of the people They're not really the power ones that are the power behind what's going on It's the gods, but then if you go from the gods, you know the principalities who?
Their human agents are those are secret.
You see the part the political agents are not secret.
They're just You know clowns or whatever, you know, the circus puts in front of you and it is a very it sounds pejorative But it's true.
I mean, there's no other way to say it
and that's what they're focusing on those people being corrupt and those and if you understand the reality of it those people that they're
Saying are corrupt or angelic compared to the shareholders the ones that really are in control
Yeah, yeah the Clintons the Bush's all the corrupt politicians that they're talking about are angels
They're not even there are Cub Scouts and Girl Scouts
We you know compared compared to the and so it's that's why very often
I've said it's better off not to know you really don't want to know what's going on because
You could look up on the rectangle
The most outlandish
Conspiracy theories are the most horrific things that are and in the reality is even worse than that
So it's it's not something that you people should be putting in their little pea brain.
Just stick with the stick with the corrupt Clintons and Bush's and whatever politicians and corrupt judges Whatever they whatever show they put in front of you because the reality is way way way way way worse and and I and I say That in a very sober way that people can't handle it Not as a general way, but a very clear way.
They lack the
Maturity to handle it not just I'm talking about physical maturity about the mental maturity spiritual maturity to handle reality
you know, so
It's best that they don't know and that's why I never really have gone publicly on
Discussing the traces that I've discovered, you know who really runs the world, but it's if you
Act with discernment when you're doing research, you know, I'll say that again
You have to act with discernment, which means that when you're doing research don't get caught up in a dummy load, right?
So you have to keep discerning what you're doing constantly look kind of like walking on ice
You ever notice you could slip a little and you catch yourself
But if you slip a little if you get to a point where you can't recover and you fall
even though you're trying to
Most research is like that as well
But if you really here I'll throw out a hint if you really want to understand who runs the world
Go look at who?
Who was behind the major conquests
through world history
and I mean all the way back from the Babylonians all the way to the barbarians and Attila the Hun and all the way to
current times and you'll see what they all have in common and
and bloodlines and
movements, you know and strategies
and also look at who the
The royalty and those that you were told were in control feared
Right, that's why I kept bringing up the Magi
Right.
It's people run over that point where you know The Magi just walked in Kings court and he was afraid of them.
Usually when someone's in your backyard You make them afraid you see so yeah, they were in his backyard and he was afraid of them So who are they the descendants of Abraham a strong implication doesn't say in Scripture They are but we're not that stupid.
We can take a hint
by the way, I noticed that
One of the different definitions of someone being stupid is they can't take a hint
They're really, you know a little bit of information doesn't you know
It's kind of like, you know
When you have something wrapped up and you can't figure out how to get it and they provide a little tab like pull here
Right, like stupid people never find that tab, you know
but anyway, so the the point is
The
The okay
What you've been told about the new world order or the way things are to be art is false, right
But there's another level to that the real powers that are behind the world
Don't know what's coming either and I had a discussion with this recently
With someone actually I've had on and off discussions about this.
Well, maybe they're using the Bible as a playbook Well, yes, that's possible and a safe presumption, but what's not True about that is they don't understand the biblical text.
They don't understand the scriptures So they can try to use it, but they I'm telling you they don't comprehend it.
I Know that sounds kind of crazy, right?
I'm not talking about the politicians that you guys are doing about the people that hire the politicians, you know The power is behind the powers, right?
Which is very interesting How do I know that?
Well, guess what?
It's in Scripture.
You could find it yourself So and this is I'll give you a hint on how to find that in Scripture.
It says that the wise will be confounded Right these people that control the planets Do they go and say let's just hire somebody that might be inspired in knowing the scriptures Let's go find the experts that should know it That are the wise Hmm the latter that's what they do.
Yes.
That's why they don't understand scripture So in other words that people that listen to Greek speak and other things like this, ha ha ha Know more about scripture and what's coming than the powers behind the powers that you know about That's a very powerful thing.
How many times I use that word power, right?
It's very very powerful.
Yeah, and the thing is it's nothing to be proud of in this sense actually Spiritually it is if you read the book of Jeremiah He talks about bringing people that are proud down It's not good to be proudful and the Christians use that a lot, right?
But if you read that when you find that in what's called the book of Jeremiah, you'll see that there's an exception It's okay to have pride But it's not pride of what you know, but it's pride of what you know about the gods Are you familiar with that?
What those verses by the way?
Not right offhand not no
Yeah, look it up look it up you do in the book of Jeremiah talks about you know
The proud will be brought down low and it's not good to be proud and they use you've heard of people especially in Christian circles
Use that well, certainly, but they never they never they never do it in context
They never look at the next thing that it says based on exception
The exception is it's but it's okay to be proud if you are proud of knowing the gods
Right your knowledge based on the not on your own stuff what their stuff is
So there are things to be proud, okay
So I just want to throw that out there because it's still the beginning times of the of this of this season
Keep your eyes and your ears open about what makes what's coming different
Meaning now that you know that there's going to be a Middle East Union when you see what input you're getting from media
Keep your eyes and ears open about what can apply to the Middle East Union that's coming
That's kind of going under the radar
And what will
Allow the establishment of the Middle East Union to happen and it'd be no big thing
Right.
Everyone will say well, yeah, of course, it's pretty All right expected.
Well right now it's bizarre You know So I think about these things and again I would suggest also to the people that are younger when you get older, especially past 35 or really past half a century years go by very quickly and It's very easy to say.
What did I do for the past five years?
I don't you know, how did it go by so fast?
Right where when you're less than 35 or 45 years is a long time and when you're a teenager, you know That's a really long time right right a child.
It's that's your entire existence.
Yeah.
Yeah So again, it depends on where you are, but the setup is in I see it every day.
I see People you can say they're under a spell and I mean in humanity at large And I'm using that term loosely You can use that term.
You can use the terminology of a spell, you know
Curse would be the same thing very in that wall on those lines
Cosmic censorship and external influence that right, right
Okay, they're still under that and it's thicker in one ways but expect but well
The cause and all that is thick very heavy right now
But expect it a certain exceptions to be made where the censorship is opened
so people at least, you know, the
Determination of their society will be deemed lawful, right?
Because if they're completely ignorant
you know, it's unlawful to come in and execute the
Judgment on their wrongdoing, you know, usually the the assailants always told why they're being you know
Whatever reprimanded
Always so there's gonna they're going to come into understanding of that which is going to be interesting to watch as well
so
so that's pretty much all I got basically considering, you know, it's very subtle and
Yeah, I think last week you said
something the effect that it's pretty quiet and I'm like that means that
There's a lot going, you know where it's noisy
It's bullshit right and where it's really quiet as real stuff that's going on
So if it's quiet in general, it means that they don't have any bullshit to cover up
their their stuff
You know what's going you know
What could be in their stuff meaning what what they're doing that could be that they don't want people to know
It could be in the yeah
I've noticed that by turning on the browsers the past few days as they've been plugging the
Bunch of young boys in a cave in Thailand being rescued.
Yes.
It's so obvious that how stupid, you know They know the people are stupid.
They so they're still keeping the youth The peril to the youth the children.
Oh how you know when rescues that is still doing that stuff
Meanwhile, you know, they're killing millions of without but children by the thousands every day, you know
And so it's just bizarre
So used to you can see the distractions and all the stuff that they do they have no value
They have no value attached to human life other than a warehouse inventory and even less to children
So but that's what they use against you
So whatever they're telling you there's value and is what they have no value in right, right
They tell you about children take care of the children means they have no regard for children.
You know, it's all it's all backwards Which is there's a place in Isaiah, by the way where you read about the inversion Are you familiar with the verses in Isaiah?
He talks about what they do is inverted.
Are you familiar with those?
It's not right offhand.
No, I'm I'm still the process working my way through Okay.
Well actually, you know here remember these are speed bumps that you don't want to go over at highway speed either
Right, right most people that read scripture
Read it and they without comprehension
So, yeah
But they still got the separation of children down in
Ones that the immigrants had tried coming here
Yeah, they're just lunch
Right, and there do you know by the way, I know this is
Most people don't comprehend this but it's commercial
Remember the governments are commercial entities, right?
Right.
So what do you know about something called Admiralty?
Admiralty Admiralty and Maritime is on the ocean and Admiralty is when you're on land, correct?
in Admiralty or maritime what they do is they
You gain well you do commerce which is exchange, you know with money and barter and trade actually money and trade
Or you can acquire goods by claiming them
Right now you even have even if a pirate
Seizes something he can't really use it
Until a certain amount of time goes by where it's claimed as where that when that time is going by by that
Those items are whether the animal human or material are considered to be abandoned
Right, and they sit there and then they claim them after a certain choice as a monetary
monetary play on their part
Right, so what they're doing is they're separating the children considering the declaring them abandoned in secret, you know
But they have the paperwork to show it sure for they have to be held on to for you know
14 for it's usually three days
Then it's seven days and it's 10 days and 14 days and 21 days all those legal days that you receive
You have to answer in 10 days or 14 days or then 30 days and then 60 days and 90 and after 90 days and 180
That's for sure.
They can do whatever they want.
So that's why they separate stuff Very simple, I mean most people think it's oh, they're separating children breaking up There's nothing to do with that if there was no commercial value in it.
They wouldn't be separating the children And also they're they're abandoning them not only from the families But those children if they have birth certificates in another country that country has to come back That country has to come back with a claim on those children.
They hold the original title, right?
You see so I'm not going to get into this too much Because most people are too far removed from You know the base knowledge of commerce So but that's all commercial.
Yeah, if you want a real nightmare go through blacks law hmm Once you understand this you could have fun with so-called government agencies like the Treasury Department and Homeland Security You know when they see well, you know when they seize property from people and then they have the auctions Well, most people don't know what's going on.
They're like, oh, it's government
Let's just wait for it to go on auction
Why because when they seize it get a list of what was seized then just claim it right before it goes to auction
But you have to you can't just walk in there and say you have to know how to do it
All right
And when when you start on pulling around with that process you get a call from an attorney and they say well what you're doing is
Not evil, but you shouldn't be doing it.
You know, in other words, you're messing with our game.
You're doing everything the right way It's scaring us, you know Mm-hmm.
So the best is you know when they seize like cash and you're like I'd like to see the cash and you record all the serial numbers then you claim it that way that really freaks him out But that's another That's another I mean, yeah, so but this is you know, this is Satan's community Satan's sons and daughters, you know You want to you know play with these idiots?
so Okay, any anything else otherwise, I don't have all so much to get into the No call-ins or anything and it's actually been very quiet in the chat for since the last sonic events Little here.
Okay Okay, do people know that there's another chat.
I don't think I've ever invited anyone here to there is another chat It's a very exciting.
I did post I did post That we were online Okay, the other one I think you just missed what I said, oh, but there's another chat that I don't think you know about Bruce Oh, no, I probably don't mean unless you're Unless you've gotten an invitation.
Ah, no, I haven't been invited yet We'll see what happens Okay.
Yeah, it's very it's a very harsh one.
That's why ah It's not harsh on a personal level where we talk about be what it's very harsh to regarding some of these topics.
Oh, okay Yeah Okay, I shouldn't have said that now You know now you feel like a vessel of insufficiency now No, no, no, I seldom worry about anything.
Oh good
Yeah, I would just suggest that
Food-clothing and shelter as usual and
Yeah, you're this is not you're not in a good situation and no one has been in a good situation for thousands of years
so
If there's if that's it, I mean that that's it if there's no questions or anything
I just wanted to come in and maybe do a little bit of a sonic like this stir things stir the pot a little bit
Was it yep, not a lot of broth or anything in it, but and
Yeah
Okay questions or anything.
I nothing on the email.
So Okay, well, thank you again, yes, okay great and we'll see you guys next week then.
Thanks Bruce.
Hey, you have a good night No, take care.
Bye.
Bye