Alrighty folks, it's live with Sam and myself.
Greetings.
Hello everyone.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Okay, well this seems to be a weekly affair with Sam and Bruce, so what's going on?
And otherwise, we were having a little bit of a discussion about how the moon anomalies will be noticed when you're paying attention to it, and they've been going on since what they call, I noticed, around 2005.
It seemed to be pretty ripping smooth in 2003,
2004, and when I say those numbers, those are in between
numbers, because obviously these morons think it's the beginning of the year in the middle
of winter, and so when you give a number like that, you're
you've really much included
the whole year, which is from spring to fall, but you've excluded
the part of the winter, you see, which is another chunk.
So the year basically goes from fall to spring, you have that whole winter chunk,
and then you have another chunk, the other half, let's say, but it's
hard to say they're halves, but they could be represented as such from spring to
fall again, and all the measurable years for the
certain events that are in scripture are obviously between those months,
even though there's some traditional ones that go outside those months,
and I've explained the seasonality of it prior, but you will notice
that usually the Sabbaths will start to go
back and forth, and that's a sign that's described in, let's say, some
books, like the Book of Enoch, it tells you in the last days the moon will
err in its ways, uses the female version,
and this is, remember, the Book of Enoch, just to recap,
is a compilation in the annals of the thoughts
and the oral traditions and the science of the temple priests,
those that were in the temple grounds, let's say,
and what they discuss, kind of like, you know how
when they go to work, they go to work for 40 hours straight overnight
and all that, or 50 hours, you know, they stay over for a few days, right?
You know how that works?
Or certain fishermen, when they go to work, they work straight through several days, that's how many of the temple people were at the time, actually in most temples in the world, and when you were a priest, you went to work, let's say, you know, beginning of the week, and you didn't come home until the end of the week, so you stayed over constantly, and there was a lot of time...
Whoa, what happened?
So, I didn't have such detail...
Okay, are we back on?
So there's no reason to have those kinds of details if you're not going to use it as a way to find some kind of reference in a record, right?
So that's why I do the biblical timekeeping, because when it gives you certain days and months in Scripture, well, when are those?
You know, the Scripture is a completely pared-down, detail-free, strip- bare-to-the-bone narrative.
It really is.
So, when you consider that as the theme or the structure behind the Scripture, it's about as stripped-down and bare-bones as any narrative could ever be, and they throw in something like the 24th day or the 9th month, you're like, I can't just pass over that not knowing what that means.
That's just the way I've seen it.
Like I was giving the example, other people will see something else they want to obsess on.
I didn't say I'm obsessing over time, I'm just saying that is something that you can't find referenced anywhere.
It is avoided like anything could ever have been avoided.
And one of the reasons is because people are still engaged in timekeeping, and what it'll do is it'll show a contrast.
Now, other people have gone in great depth with other aspects of Scripture because it doesn't seem to come in and infringe upon whatever convention they have adopted.
So, if you're researching the foods and the weaving practices and all that, well, you know, you feel so much better about researching that because obviously you're so modern and much better now, aren't you?
But the moment you start researching time, it makes the general human very uncomfortable because you will see the fraud in the current system.
In other words, it's unlawful and it's arbitrary.
In other words, if you understand the Julian dating system, their months and weeks are arbitrary.
It's strictly day numbers.
I think it was like 2 million whatever days.
But I'm also seeing that the Julian day counts is different from the Julian calendar, which was enforced by the Pope Gregory.
Those are two different things.
Well, essentially it changed when New Year's was.
That's the big thing.
And calculations are centered around what day Easter will take place, essentially.
There are many interpretations, many versions of explaining it, but that's the general crux of the matter that they put out initially for forming the Gregorian.
Two things.
New Year's Day not being affected and Easter not being affected.
And also, which year has Sunday, when is the first Sunday of that year being designated a letter?
I looked at it so much that I'm ashamed to say that I have.
I don't want to talk about it.
It's like talking about the liturgy of Catholic Mass.
Yeah, I know exactly what they're doing and all that.
I could teach people how to do liturgy at the Vatican.
But I'm embarrassed to say that I know that crap, because that's what it is.
Well, we can always move on to another subject.
Yeah, but the timekeeping is very simple.
You want to see how simple it is?
When you read any day, I didn't say date, but day in any ancient document, it's not just scripture, anything old that says the 24th day of the 9th month, oh really?
How do we know that day?
What does that mean?
You don't.
And you won't.
As the typical thinking, even the best investigative thinking that I've seen out there falls flat on its face when it comes to an overall perception of lawful timekeeping.
So anyway, let's continue on.
What have you got, Sam?
It's the Sam in Greek show with Bruce at the helm.
As I said, I'll be trying to be quiet to not disturb people in my room, so please excuse that.
Last week's talk, I think, saw the Greek kind of grow wary of what he presumably perceived as me being long-winded about facts and scholarly stuff, and you did suggest that, or low-key insist, that I give the end of the script first instead of a linear build-up.
And I just want to say because I thought about it a bit, that it's easy to sort of give the ending to your pitch when you're talking to the dummy load producer or the studio CEO who knows very little about film and just sits in a chair all day smoking cigars and hitting on his secretary.
But when you're reading it for the script writer or the lead actor, it's kind of a different matter.
So those people tend to be hands-on with the project and they want to know what's actually in there.
So as much as you might be nudging me to, I don't know, view you as the CEO, I feel like it does reduce my utility to these talks to do that.
No, no, it's not upper or lower, remember?
It's lateral.
If I punch you, yeah, I could jab you in the ribs, but if I jab you in the ribs, you can't say I drop-kicked you on the head.
Go ahead.
I will say that at this point my thinking is kind of linear with these kinds of things because I'm not as familiar with the material at an in-depth level to sort of bounce around.
So if I jump to the end, that's going to turn a 20-minute conversation into a five-minute conversation.
No, no, don't do it.
So I'm going to concede and be somewhat realistic and make adjustments, but the division of labor here has kind of always been clear.
I broach a subject matter in a methodological way and you expound on it and then I assess that and ask some questions and stuff.
But feel free to tell me to stop if I'm going overboard.
Gotcha.
All right.
Granted.
Agreed.
Sounds cool.
So unless you're totally disinterested, I kind of think we can take a bit of a look at Melchizedek again.
Okay.
Because I think that there's stuff there.
We left it off the table because we used up the three hours the last time.
What have you got on Melchizedek showing up anywhere else or anything else around that time period?
I think one way to figure out more about Melchizedek, notice I didn't say figure out Melchizedek, was to see what was going on in the surrounding environments, right?
And one example would be, well, the example I can give many, let's say certain loose-fitting examples about understanding any ancient writ when you understand the general history and you start narrowing down on the location.
And it does include customs, it does include folklore, it does include legend as well.
If you go around saying that there's a 14-headed purple monster eating people at the shopping parking lot, that legend will not stick with society as if you said there's a guy that lives in the bushes that comes out.
Because you won't remember the 14-headed.
Because someone living in the bushes coming out assaulting people in the shopping parking lot is more plausible so they remember it more, so it's probably more accurate also.
Something could have happened.
So that's what I mean about myths and legends.
It doesn't mean we're relying on it, but to consider them is important.
If one starts looking at, let's say, for example, the age of the heroes, which was around that time, by the way, to consider it might have been slightly after or before or around, I wouldn't say exactly centered, but yeah, the age of heroes in Greek culture.
So there was a mindset.
And people were very different back then in certain ways.
Well, if you imagine that the degenerative aspect of the gene, hereditary from a biological point, the level of mutation that is acknowledged in humankind right now is far greater than it was even 500 years ago.
So it's another story, but go ahead.
I think one of the last things that we said last time was the Jebusites.
I think you sort of mentioned that in passing before we ended that.
They were the pre-Israelite inhabitants, and you'll often hear that Jerusalem was previously called Jebus because of a passage in Kings.
I don't really subscribe to that per se.
I have an entry from Anchor Bible Dictionary that says that Jerusalem was the name from the early times, being mentioned in the 19th century Egyptian execration text and some other places, the Armana letters also.
And we know that the Assyrians called it Jerusalem in their siege of it in 701.
So the Jebus thing, I wouldn't really put much weight on.
But there are people called the Jebus, and you could loosely fit them close enough to that area, but I wouldn't identify them completely with that.
If you couldn't identify anyone there, it would be a mixture of the Canaanites and the Philistines, like it is today.
Lebanese and Palestinians.
The fact that they were living in Jerusalem, I think we can nail down, but I think that they called it Jerusalem also.
This idea that it was called Jebus really, I can't find it anywhere.
But then you also have this makeup of the name, Jeru and Shalom, with Jeru being to establish or to create, and then the Canaanite deity Shalom, which is mentioned in Ugaritic mythological text, so we know it's a deity, and not just this random piece, whatever.
Right, just like justice, people use that for law and morality, and it's a deity.
We still haven't really reconciled, and I think you and I diverged last week, we haven't reconciled the presence of the name Zedek and Melchizedek, with the fact that this is also a Near Eastern deity of some sort.
I don't know if we want to adopt a let's wait and see mentality to that.
I don't particularly lean that way, and we can find quite a lot about Zedek.
One thing that I looked into was the delineation of the gods.
If you were to visit this planet, like in sci-fi, they'd call everyone a human, and that's it.
We know that there's different based on the social classes and various quote-unquote races, creeds, and colors of people, we don't use that term like it would be used coming from afar.
So when you come back in to look at this character from that point of view, and you start thinking the Zedek was probably a deity, well, can we classify the deity?
Was it angel worship?
Was it an elemental god, like a ball?
Was it an Earth type elemental creature?
So those things I like, but just saying it's a deity, yeah, of course.
Most names have deities behind them, people's names, I mean.
So there's an interesting aspect to see what's been brought forward in history.
Is it angelic worship or is it bonafide ball worship?
There's a big difference there, right?
Or sons of God, you see?
Well, I don't know if I can say necessarily anything about the specific class of Elohim ontologically, but we can parse sort of where this deity ranks by looking at different things.
Like if you were to tell me that there's a particular deity that sits on the council, you know, I could feel satisfied with that, even if I don't know exactly what type of gods those are.
I know it's pretty high-ranking.
Or determines the national interest, like the sons of gods were supposed to.
So there's this kind of I would say it's a very impressive piece of literature called the Dictionary of Deities from the Middle East, and it has a Zedek entry that I'm going to read a bit from.
I'll be selective about what I'm thinking to save time, but by all means...
Give us the source of that document.
Is it an Oxford or Cambridge publication?
One second, one second.
It seems like I'm bugging my roommates, so I'm going to check out for a bit and see if I can find a spot.
Okay, why don't we take a break?
Bruce, I'm going to take a break, also make some coffee.
Okay, I'll put some music on and we'll be back in a little bit, folks.
Stay tuned.
I could leave Skype on and make coffee.
Oh, that's neat.
Okay, cool.
Bruce, are you there?
Yes, I'm here.
We're back now.
Okay, so Sam, you bring up a reference, some reference material you want to read out of it, and I remember, let me just preface, I like to leave my opinion out of this, and I like to leave my own personal stuff out of it, but I don't like what academics have done, right?
So you make it minimal in terms of what did they figure out to let us know?
By the way, let me say one more thing.
They like to write a lot and read about what they wrote versus giving anything that we use.
You see what I mean?
So what can we use from it?
So yeah, I'm being selected and I have no interest in pagan gods, only the information concerning them, because then I can use that to learn more about their society.
So I will focus on what I think is important here.
So reading from the book which is called, sorry I got the name wrong before, The Dictionary of Deities and Demons in the Bible, which is pretty good.
Yeah, how old is it?
Let's see here.
Early 20th century, yeah.
No, sorry, 1995.
But it's still good.
Oh, that's kind of late.
Okay, go ahead, that's fine.
I bet you the majority of the material is research that they did out of other stuff.
There was a big movement towards this in the late 1700s and then picked up again in the mid-19th century.
So anyway, go ahead.
So, under the Zedic entry, which is sort of at the end, starting with Zed, the West Semitic deity Zedic righteousness is found in the Bible only in the personal names Melchizedek and Adonizedek, both Israelite kings out of Jerusalem.
Zedic is probably to be identified with the deity known as Bar among the Amorites and Kittu in Babylonia.
So, we know that different people assign different names to the same gods based on their function.
So that's legitimate.
Picking up on the thing again, the cult of Zedic appears to have been well established in pre-Israelite slash Jebusite Jerusalem and a number of texts, righteousness with a capital R appears as either a member of Yahweh's court or as a personification of Yahweh's concern for righteousness or justice.
Evidence for the West Semitic deity Zedic is mostly indirect but nonetheless compelling.
Most decisive is a statement by Philo of Biblios that the Phoenicians had a god named Siddic or Zedic.
Philo noted that the Phoenicians numbered among their gods Mysor or Siddic.
Mysor and Siddic correspond to the Hebrew Mylor, justice and Siddic, righteousness.
Siddic is not directly attested elsewhere as the name of a deity but indirect evidence comes from two sources, the Amorite and the Babylonian pantheons and West Semitic personal names.
The West Semitic god Zedic seemingly corresponds to the deity known as Kittu in the Babylonian pantheon.
In Mesopotamia, the preservation of truth and justice was considered to be the particular domain of the sun god Shamash.
Truth or right, capital T and R, was personified and deified as the god Kittu.
Kittu was often invoked together with Misharu, justice.
One or both of these deities were described as seated before Shamash, that is Shamash's attendants or the minister of Shamash's right hand.
It appears that the deity known as Kittu in Babylonia was further known to the West under the names Gar and Siddic, all three names having essentially the same meaning but different linguistic communities.
Okay, so my question is why are all these personal oh right, there's a little bit at the end here that's probably important to read.
The West Semitic personal names containing the root Zedic are attested at many sites including El-Ammar, Ugarit, Rimah, and Mari.
So if we have a situation where these personal names are being found, then we know that the entity exists because they're constantly being referenced.
I think that's an undebatable point.
Moving down into another point of the text.
Melchizedek is not only identified as king of Shalem but also as priest of God Most High El-Elyon.
One hypothesis suggests that Zedic is to be identified with the god Shalem, whose name is embodied in Jerusalem.
Support for this hypothesis may come from the Ugaritic personal name Zedek Shalem.
A long-standing cult of Siddic at Jerusalem could account at least partially for the fact that even during the Israelite period, Jerusalem had laid special claim to such titles as city of righteousness, which you can also find in Isaiah 1.26. So to not ignore that, it does specifically call itself that in Isaiah.
How did Abraham interact with Melchizedek again?
There was a performance of bread and wine, wasn't there?
I believe Melchizedek brought the bread and wine and Abraham gave a tenth of his spoils from the war with the kings like a tithe.
So if the narrative is minimal, we do get enough detail not to wonder about how they interacted.
I think what you're asking about is who was Melchizedek and examination of the label or the name itself etymologically or source.
In other words, why is he Melchizedek?
I'm not trying to get so much at the guy himself per se, like his personal life or whatever, but it's more of this idea of how it ties back to the society of the gods.
I wanted to interject something.
He was called out of Ur for reasons given, light reasons again, minimal, but he was called out and he went out with others.
You notice what's interesting, sometimes what's not being said can inform you on what you're looking at, what is being said.
One thing, when he was called out to go where?
East, right?
He'll show him where to go.
He didn't say he would be alone.
He took his household.
No, no, for the purpose.
So Melchizedek, in other words, when you give tribute to someone, there's purpose there.
Even people that do it begrudgingly do it out of fear of penalty.
There's no fear of penalty here.
This is a willing thing and it was reciprocated.
In other words, the gesture was reciprocated.
So, I would suggest loosely that this Melchizedek guy was sort of a target feature on the location that we're discussing for Abraham going east.
If you know what I mean by target location.
It's like, you know you're there when you start interacting a certain way.
And that aspect is not only for what went on there, because we're going to learn a lot more about that time period as time goes on archaeologically, apparently.
And it also lets us know that there's a spiritual support, or he'll find some kind of, it's almost like a, how would you say it?
I wouldn't say sense of purpose, because the purpose was defined through a covenant, believe it or not, where the Most High was the one that was going to perform.
Not a lot was put on Abraham after the covenant was made, right?
He just had to be there and have children, which he had.
So, the performance aspect of this was all put on the Most High, let's say, on the covenant for him to perform it.
So, you have this Melchizedek guy there that's sort of like a, I don't know, I wouldn't say fulfilling any purpose.
Well, come on.
No, I wouldn't say fulfilling the purpose for Abraham going there exclusively, but sort of like letting him know that you're here, and you've made it this far, and this is how things work here, and you don't have to go anymore, you know, kind of thing.
Because when you think about it, he pretty much stayed in that area, north of the Dead Sea, and north of the Kekar, north of the plain.
No, we don't know that.
No, we don't know it for sure.
But we don't see any annals of him moving to Egypt, or going back to, you know, we know he sent his sons back to the east.
But it's an interesting thing to think about, because the details of the narrative are so minimal, that I think what you're doing by looking at that is good, because I think that it's minimal doesn't mean absent, right?
But it's also an issue of seeing how one thing correlates to another, because I'm not trying to myopically just stare at the Melchizedek character.
The name infers a bunch of other things that you can use to gain understanding about the society, and that's kind of what I'm in on here.
So if I just zone in on sort of the core part of the presentation...
Let me just say one thing.
If anyone had a name like that today and meant it, they'd be in big trouble.
Think about it for a minute.
It would be politically incorrect to have a name like that, and to operate under that name.
Yeah, I can see that.
Although I'd have to wonder who's going to call you out when most people can't interpret the meaning of any name.
But it would have to be a pretty high-level individual that knows ancient history.
Right, and like we've said before, you're not going to find anyone like that, unless they come to you.
So going into the dictionary entry again, Tzedek and Yahweh are found in synonymous parallelism.
Looking at certain verses like Isaiah 51, hearken to me, you who pursue Tzedek, righteousness, who seek Yahweh.
Another one is sacrifice, sacrifices of righteousness, and trust in Yahweh.
Psalm 4.
At other times, righteousness seems to be used as part of a compound name, which I find very interesting.
Yahweh, righteousness in Psalm 17 verse 1, where it specifically says, hear Tzedek, Yahweh, listen to my cry, give ear to my prayer.
Now, I know that in modern Hebrew, this is not part of the entry.
In modern Hebrew, they use commas and punctuations and things, but I'm not aware in Paleo-Hebrew that that's there.
I don't see any commas when I look at the interlinear.
It's the word Yahweh followed directly by Tzedek.
That looks like a name or title to me.
When you read it in the Scriptures in 98, they put a comma there, but I don't see that as being really correct.
Reading again from the DDD, in some instances, righteousness, capital R, appears as an embodiment of the divine sovereign's invincible right hand, which is interesting, by which he rules the world and protects his devotees.
So reading from Psalm 48, righteousness fills thy right hand.
Or Isaiah 41, I, Yahweh, will support you with my right hand of righteousness.
Open the gates of righteousness, I will enter them, praising Yah.
Psalm 118.
Poetic parallelism here allows no doubt that the gates of righteousness is the semantic equivalent to the gates of Yahweh.
Jeremiah 33 also declares that in the end time, Jerusalem will be known by the name Yahweh is our righteousness.
So are we still going to hold, end quote, are we still going to hold to the idea that Yahweh and Tzedek are so unrelated that we shouldn't examine these correlations?
I mean, I think we can be concrete about this.
Yahweh's right hand gets called Tzedek directly, right?
Is that a name for his body part?
I don't think it's as observed as a modern person would think.
Yeah, but you know, think about, okay, think about how real the angels were then.
They came in threes, right?
They came in a three-party, a three-person party to Abraham.
That was scripture supports, through scripture, that that was the most high himself in authority.
Right?
You know, later on we figure out through hints and allegory and just certain details that, well, you know, he has angels that do his work, and then within those angels he has some that are almost like a body double, right?
In a physical form.
And then, of course, he has others that take on the various other personages that still do, you know, his work.
So, the thing is, am I suggesting that Melchizedek is an angel?
No.
But the thing is, we don't know for sure, but I believe that if he was an angel, we would get that detail.
But he does, what's an interesting thing about that time, this is post-Flood, and the Flood was in recent memory still, and many things that we consider to be, you know, just nominally, strictly biblical events that everyone knows about that happened in that time period.
I would say that we don't really, even myself, let's just say even myself, what am I, right?
But I don't have a very strong grip on that entire time period about really how prevalent the gods were interacting with people.
You know, how common was it, you know?
I would suggest that from stuff that I've looked at, that goes from the mythological to legendary to reports about ancient writs, that they were very, very prevalent.
It was not unusual to run into an angelic-type being, and proven to be such.
You know, like walking through walls, disappearing, and doing miraculous things.
So, when I start thinking, when I start reading that time of Genesis, and I see a character like Melchizedek, I kind of blow a fuse, because on one side it doesn't say that he's anything else but a man, so I want to believe that.
But on the other side, there is so much supernatural and ultra-natural and spiritual activity going on at the time that if he had a name like that, and Abraham was giving him tribute, I don't think he rolled around town very humbly or loosely.
I think it was very well known that he was backed up in many ways.
And that's just another side of the thought, and I can't prove either one.
No, it's fun.
In other words, this is a very, very different time period than we can imagine at this point, until we get more down this time period that we're in, to get more accurate information about it.
But just to be clear also, what I'm looking at specifically here is the Zedek concept.
So there's Melchizedek, I can't really say much about him, but I'm reading stuff out of his name, that we have this entity that we can then link back to Yahweh, because it says that he serves the Most High.
But you have to account for this other thing also, that there's obviously a theological statement being made in the Psalms and in other books when they're calling Yahweh by other names, like El Shaddai or Yahweh, El or Elion.
And you can say that's not his primary name or primordial name or whatever, but they're trying to illustrate something that has to be deciphered.
Now, I don't have specifics, but I do know of creation myths where the chief god makes the other gods out of his body parts, or as embodiments of his attributes.
Even in pop culture, you'll see that in certain Marvel movies or stories and things like Full Metal Alchemist, and things like that.
Or the Greek Olympian gods, yeah.
But also, if you look back, just to interject something for thought, if you look at the, let's say the limited analysis of the names used for Yahweh, they always strike on two chords.
And one chord is militarism, and the other chord is law.
You know, righteousness as in law.
When you were reading what that fellow was writing about righteousness and justice, it should have been righteousness and lawfulness instead of justice, you see what I mean?
But anyway, go ahead.
So it's militaristic and lawful.
Is a simple way to, the names, right?
Like what is it?
El Shaddai is Angel Army, head of the Great Almighty, right?
Isn't that the one he provides?
Well, let's look at that one again, because you could look at what the letters mean, right?
Okay.
But I would suggest that it's the two aspects of his names are usually militaristic and lawful.
You know, lawfulness or righteousness.
Where does righteousness and morality come from?
Law, right?
What if you have a law that it's okay for men to dress up like women?
Is that righteous?
No, you see?
But that's how it's considered righteous, when it becomes law, right?
You see what I mean?
When something becomes law, people start to hush up about countering the idea, because now it's quote-unquote law.
But the idea that Yahweh could sort of spin off a god that's named after his right hand or his left foot, or make a god that's embodied of one of his attributes is perfectly legitimate.
Like you said, you know, the Greeks do that.
I mean, every ancient pantheon has one thing in common.
All the gods have essentially one core job.
They might have smaller jobs, but they have one main thing.
God of war, God of love, God of justice, whatever.
Well, here's a real crazy one.
You know that a woman was made from a rib of a man, right?
Oh yes, and there's that.
But this idea of them having one essential attribute, and you know, maybe 500 years later they're doing something else, but in the beginning having one core thing, where are you going to get that mandate from?
Like these guys can't do more than one thing at once, and you know, how do you make anything if you're the head god and you're primordial?
You need raw material.
So where does Yahweh get the raw material to make these Elohim from, if there's nothing in the beginning?
Doesn't he have to take that for himself?
Well, to define nothing, you need something.
And the something that we have to say was made out of nothing is incorrect.
Well, there's no one.
I mean, presumably.
Well, that's a good question.
This is not a cop-out, but you know, it's a maturity issue, don't you think?
I think I've mentioned before, if you give too much information to mankind, what do they do with it?
I've got a couple of four-year-olds.
I've got a four-year-old, a five-year-old, and an eight-year-old, let's say, and we're going to give them a five-room house with a handgun loaded.
It has a safety on, but no lock.
Some matches and some swords.
And we're going to leave them there for three days.
And they're well-trained.
That's not going to end well, no.
I didn't say they're incompetent.
I said they're immature.
I didn't say monkey in a gun store.
There's an element of immaturity here.
We have no idea how they interact or what they do in their realm of being.
We do a little bit, because it's very similar to what we're doing.
They plant gardens and they make wine and they have horses.
You know what I mean?
Literacy is important to them, because they're always telling you to write stuff down, not remember it.
The truth is important to them.
Where it's not important to men, no matter how much they usually say it is.
They like creating.
Right.
But that's what Sam is bringing up.
What is creating?
I mean, there could be an architecture of development, but we just have no clue.
If we're mirroring an aspect or multiple aspects from that realm, there's an element of transmutation.
I have firsthand experience on transmutation, turning one thing into another at a very high percentage, where it shouldn't be there.
Let's say if you transmute iron into platinum, you're not going to get like a cartoon, the entire block of iron to turn into platinum, but you're going to get 3% by weight.
Which is not a lot, 3% is not a lot, but you know, a hundred dollar lump of iron now is worth a quarter of a million dollars because 3% of it is platinum.
So, if you have nothing, because the something that we can relate to even cognitively, we only compare it to something completely intangible, let's say the realm of the gods, so that means that they have nothing.
I don't think so.
Well, you do think that seriously.
No, I know, but we don't know what that something is that we think is nothing.
But, is it not that the scripture shows kind of clearly that Yahweh subsumes all of these various characteristics, which by the way are the names for gods in the Canaanite culture, let's not pretend that Shamash wasn't a real Babylonian sun god, that Yahweh subsumes them into himself ultimately?
Right, storm and water and wind.
Or whether it's justice, or whether it's destruction, or pestilence.
Disease, death.
Ma'at is a god.
Well, what's the Hebrew name for dead?
Ma'at.
Or Mut.
What's the god of death?
Ma'at.
Mut.
Not Ma'at, that's a different one, that's an Egyptian one, but still, she was encompassing that, you know, Ma'at in Egypt, she measured your heart against a feather, it should be lighter than a feather.
Oh, heavy heart.
Well, here's the thing, you know the element, the concept of transmutation, and real science, even they tell you they can do it with a nuclear reactor and all that, but they don't talk about how, see, nowhere in any physics department they'll tell you that lead can't be turned into gold.
They say, sure it can, but it costs 100 times more than regular gold, so that's why it's not done.
But they won't deny it can't be done.
So they put in front of you, well it's too expensive, and then the other thing they say it requires too much energy, you can't do it in your kitchen.
So if you figure out how to do it in the kitchen, with low energy, well then they have to deny it, you see, because then it destroys the value of gold.
If we figured out how the gods created stuff, would we destroy creation?
Very good chance.
Now we're getting philosophical.
No, it's not philosophy.
Actually I did a little thing there.
It's not philosophical.
That's actually proven.
We'd do ourself a hell of a lot of damage.
And it's been done before, and we don't know the details on that, fortunately, because when you know the details of something, you try to do what?
Reenact it.
Let's just put it this way.
Let's just say I'll cop out and say that I'm happy with knowing that I don't know how they do it right now.
But most people don't.
Maybe because personally I've gone through the excitement of growing gold on silver or turning iron into platinum and other things, right?
Or carbon into iron.
Just carbon.
You go to a landfill and burn the garbage.
Here's an example.
Go to a landfill and you have all this burnable waste.
Go ahead and set up a double forced air furnace so you don't have smoke coming out.
It's very efficient, right?
And you carbonize all that crap.
And while you're burning the fuel, you're making electricity with a turbine.
And in turn, that electricity gets put back into the carbon in a certain way to turn the carbon into steel or iron.
So now we're producing iron out of burned garbage for almost no cost.
Because remember, the fire is making the electricity, you see?
Great.
For me, that's no big deal.
When I tell people that they're like, it's so excited.
No, no, no.
You're absolutely right.
It's not exciting.
Let's be real.
But let's just go back to the gods we're creating.
It's exciting for us now, but it's not exciting for them.
And you know how I know it wasn't exciting for them that much?
I'm giving you another perspective on it now.
How do I know it's not that exciting for them?
Because they didn't give us the details on it.
And you know how I know why they didn't give us the details on it also?
Because we lack the maturity to handle it properly.
I give two reasons there that are very pretty sound and maybe profound on how they did it.
But hold on, let me say the last part here.
The last part I want to say is that, okay, like bringing up the analogy of how the Olympians did that.
You know, it was Athena or Hera come out of Zeus' head and this and all that stuff.
Now we're going to lean on mythology and legends.
Yeah, I didn't say that to accept it as holy writ, but you can lean on it as much as you want, but it's fragile.
It'll break if you put your weight on it.
But it doesn't mean it should be ignored.
Because the last thing you want to do is, let's just say hypothetically, is that you read all the myths and you know them and how these gods came about.
And then later on, after the resurrection, you do find out that it was very similar to that.
You're going to look like a real dummy, aren't you?
Because somebody's going to come up to you and say, wow, you know, I read that in Greek mythology.
And you're going to be like, oh, I didn't.
Well, where were you?
You had access to that too, didn't you?
Do you see my point?
Yeah, absolutely.
So it's good to look at all of it.
Yes.
When you don't know, that's what you do.
Look at good forensic analysis.
The reason you embark on such a campaign is because you don't know.
If you do know, why would you go on a campaign to investigate?
Right?
Unless you've got a lot of...
you've got to eat up the whole budget, because if you don't, you won't get anything next year.
But I'm just talking about typically these things are done out of a need to know and want to know.
Want to know, not need to know.
So anyway, that's all I've got to say about that.
As far as the excitement thing, if you're going to compare this creation thing to the transmutation of elements, in the grand scheme of things, no matter how novel that might be in today's sort of clueless society, that is banal and sort of trite.
If you can show me how to turn a dog into a cat and call that transmutation, I think that'd be fun to look at.
Gold into whatever, I can't really do much with that.
So there is a level of excitement to it once you progress into something else.
And I wouldn't be surprised if there's technology to turn a dog into a cat.
I mean, if you can turn a staff into a snake, then these things can be known.
I want to interject this, and I've said it many times and I've been saying it for a long time.
Later on, mankind will discover what separates us from the gods is technological stuff.
The stuff that we call miracles and all this is a technology that they have that we don't have.
And what I mean technology is, I don't know, etymologically probably also, it just means a knowledge and techniques that surpass what we have.
Because right now you say technology, it depends on the current age.
Right now it's information.
When you say technology right now, people are thinking smartphones and computers and communications, where 50 years ago it would have been aviation, and 50 years prior to that it would have been what they call the engine-driven wagon or automobile technology.
And prior to that it would have been industrial machinery.
If you can go over that mindset, what I mean by technology is an overall technology that is bound within their society and not here, unless of course you access it through what they call magic or you're given the ability to perform miracles.
Here is another interesting bit from the DED.
Sedeq and Mysor as attendant deities of Shamash in the Babylonian mythology, also have their reflexes in Yahwism as dual deities of the God of Israel.
Isaiah 11.4 says that the spirit of Yahweh will possess the Messiah with the result that he will speak, he will judge the weak with righteousness and he will defend the poor of the earth with justice.
Psalm 45.7-8.
We also read he judges the world with righteousness, he judges the people with justice, and so on.
So, end quote.
Ancient Near Eastern deities By the way, you know the word justice is not it.
You keep saying that.
Is that really?
Okay.
Are you guys in there?
Okay, I lose you.
No, I'm here.
Can you hear me?
Sam is suplexing or is it me as well?
No, you're fine.
Both fine to me.
Oh, okay.
I'm getting a break up on Sam.
Okay, that's fine.
Can you hear me now?
Yeah.
So, I was going to say, the justice thing I'm just reading straight from the quote.
The Ancient Near Eastern gods, as far as I can see, if you look at it through the context of Scripture, often at times they're shown as qualities or servants of Yahweh all the time.
And we see this with, for example, Dever and Ketev in Psalm 91.
You are not afraid of the dread of the night, of the arrow that flies by day, of the pestilence, Dever, that walks in the darkness of destruction, Ketev, that ravages the midday.
So, for people who aren't familiar with Near Eastern references and how it's been completely obscured by the English versions, the arrow that flies by day, known as Hez, is an actual demon or god for disease or sudden pain.
Dever and Ketev are also Elohim.
And they've been rendered as nouns of natural material, but it's a pretty false representation.
So, the Canaanites felt like Dever and Ketev were these big-time gods or whatever.
But you could read very clearly in Habakkuk 3.5 Yahweh is on a war mission or a war path against a certain nation and is said to be preceded and followed by, respectively, Dever and Rephesh, which are similar to the picture of the two divine attendants who escort major gods in ancient myths.
Rephesh means plague, and he's talked about also in Deuteronomy 33 and Psalm 78.
So, it's a theological statement, like I said before, that's being made all over the place, that these gods either serve him or are absorbed into him.
The Pentateuch was written by Moses and compiled by Ezra with the rest of the Old Testament.
And they knew the Most High as Yahweh, and they called Him Yahweh.
Okay, fine.
He's Yahweh.
But in the same way that cities were named in the text with different names than what they would have been in the time period that they're talking about.
Like Ramesses, the city of Ramesses didn't exist when the Israelites were there.
Why is it called Ramesses?
That's an editorial thing that comes later.
So, if you would have gone back to Melchizedek and asked him, who do you serve?
And he says, the Most High.
And you're like, no, no, that's not a name.
Give me a name.
If he said to you, well, can't you see it's in my name, the Most High, it's Zedek.
You know, is that unfeasible for him to do that?
No.
You're not violating any theological sacred cows by saying that Zedek is Yahweh.
Well, here's the thing.
There's a certainty element here.
If you want to really drag this element really to the gutter, like I could do it here for just a second, a very simple yes or no answer would be, has the Most High used pagans and other gods for his purpose?
Very simple.
Yes.
And even in ways that you wouldn't expect.
I mean, you can ask the same question on who was Yethro?
Who was Moses' father-in-law?
His media knight, right?
I mean, he rolled right along.
He rocked right along Moses, didn't he?
And as a matter of fact, Moses even took his advice.
So, yeah.
I'll give you another aspect to it, and it's very simple.
It depends on how serious one is about what they think they know.
And what I mean by that is, for example, when you look at a lot of, especially in the Christian community or the Jewish community especially, I should say, they can't be around any other deification at all.
It just freaks them out, right?
They think it's, you know, Scripture, it is unclean to go inside the temple where they do their rites, you know?
But some people have just taken it a little bit too far.
And a quick example of that is I was at a temple once, not in the temple, but at an adjacent annex building where they had, it's called Govindas, and it's a vegan food, all-you-can-eat, and it's delicious high-quality food for like eight bucks, right?
And you sit down, and these monks walk around, and they have all these Ganeshas and all these various gods from that part of the world, and they explain to you what the god is.
And someone that was with me once, I said, let's go there.
He says, no, no, I can't go in there because of those gods.
You're just visiting.
You're just a little immature in this idea of Scripture.
But I'm in there sitting with someone else, and I let him explain, you know, let's say who Ganesha was, right?
And I'm nodding and nodding.
I said, yeah, I got it.
I know who that is, but tell me what you think about it.
So he's telling me what Ganesha is, and I stop, and I say, can I tell you about my god?
And he's like, sure.
I said, well, my god made the wood that you made your god out of.
No big deal.
You see my point?
Very casual.
Where other people that are, let's say, new to Scripture, and they're sort of, let me just say it, but not say it dogmatic.
Oh, I can't go in there.
There are idols in there.
Oh, really?
And what does that have to do with you?
You see?
But there are suggestions that it is unclean.
Let's say you go into their inner, you know how they have a temple, let's say, like, I'll just give a personal example.
I won't go into a church where they have the pews and the altar, but I'll go into an annex building.
Some churches have annex buildings next to them, you know?
And that's no problem, but I'm not going to go where they do the deed.
You know what I mean, right?
So there's an aspect that today it's very, today there's many that have the posture that everything was clear cut.
And if you, let's say, were dedicated to Yahweh, you couldn't even wave at anyone who wasn't.
You see my point here?
I'm trying to relax the mindset around this whole thing.
There's a lot of hang-ups about people reading Scripture, and they think that everything in it is good.
There's a lot of bad stuff in there, too.
You know how they call it, the good book?
Really?
I'd say about half of it talks about some pretty downright wicked evil shit if you want to get down to it.
Within the good and evil aspect.
Are you mature enough to handle that, or are you going to turn a blind eye to that?
All this, as I said, is for the mindset, not exactly about Melchizedek.
I'm not saying Melchizedek was a pagan, or this or that, or whatever.
We're investigating the etymological source of the name, I think, at this point.
Because culturally, we don't know the stripped-down, bare-bones narrative details that we get in Scripture.
If we went back there right now, we might see the terms Sedeq written on everything in that area, or within a certain dedication.
You know what I mean by dedication?
It's what you do to a god, right?
For sure.
In other words, that possibility does exist for sure.
Is that exactly what's going on?
Once you get over what's called a hang-up, I'm using that term loosely.
When someone has a hang-up, they don't know why they do something, they just do it because it's either fashionable or belief-based without substantiating the belief at all.
Like I said, there's a lot of bad stuff that's going on in Scripture, and you can't turn a blind eye to it.
Again, have pagans, quote-unquote, or let's say non-covenant people, non-MOTs, you know, MOT is a member of the tribe, all this other stuff, been involved directly influencing people that were patriarchs and others?
Yes, of course.
Can you be a pagan and be righteous?
Yeah, you can, when you think about it, of course.
Yeah.
We're not talking about allegiances now, so...
Right.
As far as digging up stuff on Melchizedek, you have the Old Testament sort of as a source, then you have what the New Testament says in the book of Hebrews, but you also have this sort of in-between layer, historically, of the Second Temple period, where you can look at the resources that they put out concerning him there, like the Qumran texts.
When you say Second Temple, that's Herod around that time, like the first century B.C.? Well, the lead-up to that, so between Malachi and Matthew.
Yeah, after the Persian, and build-up after the Persians, because the Persians had a very big influence for many years.
Which, by the way, in order for them to be so influential, they were, quote-unquote, influenced by Yahweh themselves.
So that's another thing, a heads-up for people, to find that in archaeology, which right now, modern-day Iran, or media, you know, the area of Kurdistan and all that, if they find anything that, let's say, a piece of pottery, or stone carving, or a statuette, or anything that memorializes the name of Yahweh, you know what they do with it, right?
Or, well, it would be good if they just hid it.
They actually destroy it.
This is the type of people that have, in other words, this is the type of mindset these people have, I should say.
I'm sort of content to let the presentation lie at this point, because I'm still looking into the Second Temple stuff.
This is kind of the Old Testament stuff.
I think it's interesting that you can garner that these deities have sort of a complex matrix of existence, and you kind of have to understand where the Most High exists and all that.
It's not just this sort of top-down, he's at the top, everybody's at the bottom.
There are things that sort of spawn out from him in different directions, and you kind of have to tie it together.
But I'll leave it that way.
Well, yeah, let's interject something here for the mindset of people, because I think mindset is very important.
Throughout man's history, scripture included or scripture aside, 99.9999% of all deific interaction with the gods, angels, and all that was not directly with Yahweh, or any of his direct agents.
Yeah.
It's like, let's say you have a large sack with gray marbles, it's as big as your waist, and it weighs 100 kilos, and I'm telling you there's one red marble in there, and that's the Most High, let's say, because he's interacting on an equal basis, let's say.
When you open that sack, all you see is gray marbles, you've got to keep digging and digging, he's in there somewhere, you know what I mean?
That's why a lot of people in the academic world, I've noticed after a while, they're like, oh yeah, I look at the Canaanite god El, who's a storm god, and he destroyed the enemies with a storm and hailstones, and Yahweh does the same thing, so he must be the same.
No, you know, if the French army goes and blows up England with tanks and bullets, and the Americans go blow up Iraq with tanks and bullets, it's not the same army.
That's why, you know, how many times have you heard me, I don't want to get into a rant in academics, they're very stupid people.
They sound smart, and they do a lot of grunt work.
In other words, they're being quote-unquote compensated to spend most of their living days accumulating literary works, whether it's of their own or writing about what someone else wrote.
That's what they do.
So, I'm not throwing them out, I'm keeping them objectifying who and what they are, which is ignorant, stupid, and have done a lot of ditch digging, a lot of grunt work.
So now, the metaphor of sifting through poop to get fine edible corn applies again with these academics.
Again, don't just, you have to, you cannot, look, grunt work is grunt work.
And if someone's got to do it, and just be thankful that you didn't, you know what I mean?
If the grunt work has already been done into sussing out, and I'm not talking about the censorship and obfuscation where they hide stuff.
I'm talking about the general subject matter.
If you look at a body of knowledge and it's been compiled by academics for a period of a hundred years, you have to look at it.
You can't ignore it.
No, granted.
Yeah, and you have to do it with an open mind, but not so open that your brains fall out if you lean over a little bit too.
So, anyway.
Speaking of ancient cultures, you mentioned Persia.
Let's take a look at Babylon, because in the last week's stream, I brought up the subject of Nebuchadnezzar and his role as the head of gold and intervention in the course of world society in the 500 BC era to sort of create a global empire that threw a lot of other civilizations off and destroyed them.
And there's more that can be looked at at that specifically.
Although the archaeological discoveries can give us information back to,
say, the 8th or the 9th centuries BC, and I think the Egyptian accounts go back
further, though they're more sparse, it's difficult to
comprehend where many of those records belong chronologically, which is
why you sort of need a standard historical document, which scripture kind
of is, and even the secular institutions have voiced that it's a pretty
good guide for parsing ancient history.
So the Old Testament gives us information about Israel, which was directly in the sort of the center between Egypt in the south and Mesopotamia in the north, and at one point was actually a bridge between them.
So we can use that to glean accounts of what was happening in those areas around that time.
I think that there is, I think it's the 11th edition of the Encyclopedia Britannica from the early 20th century.
It says that there's, in there, it says that there's very little that is systematically known about world history before the 9th century BC except what we find recorded in the Bible.
For example, the modern historians believe that Nebuchadnezzar's kingdom was very limited in its extents because they can't find any records anywhere or any archaeological anything that shows that he was anywhere other than the Middle East.
I've heard that there are records in, some records in Assyria, Syria and places like that but also very sparse.
Let me just put it this way and do this with a bated breath, I guess.
Let's say we're living in an alternate reality and you went to a Native American museum and not only did they show you the wares and artifacts of Native American culture through the years here, but they also showed you they had cylinder seals and writings in Babylonian cuneiform.
Wouldn't that be interesting?
Now let me just couple that with hearsay of Jesuits raiding and robbing artifacts in the 15-1600s from Native Americans, and I'll leave it at that.
So, I don't, you know, this obfuscation started 500 years ago here or more, or you know, within that time period.
So I just want to leave it at that, and one day I'll dig up some more information on that and show you.
That would make a lot of sense too.
Well, there's who is it, Klaus Dona, who goes to Columbia the country, and through caves, and they find shields and brass work and all this, it's clearly Babylonian and he walks right through the airport with it, you know, leaving with and they're like, well, aren't you guys upset that I'm leaving?
They don't give him a hard time at all, and they're like, oh no, take it, because this does not agree with our pre-Columbian history.
I remember you saying that, yeah.
And I'm glad he's come forward, because if you stick within the archaeological realm of the grunt work body of knowledge you put together, you're not going to see that kind of report in it.
Right.
There's no academic that's going to write, oh yeah, a bunch of Babylonian artifacts were taken out of Japan, and the Japanese government says it's fine because it doesn't conform to the pre-whatever period, you know, the pre-Columbian period.
Pre-Columbian period, yeah.
Or for Japan, or anywhere.
Yeah, academics aren't going to tell you that.
Look, I'll give you another example.
There's a in mining, a crowbar is a stick of dynamite, right?
And there's a guy here, and he's passed away now, and when you're a small mining company you're always, like farmers, if you have a bad season, you're out of business, your whole family will be destitute.
So these small miners are doing
hard rock mining here in Arizona, and sometimes they'll blast
and keep blasting the rock, and all of a sudden there's this huge opening, and they go in there
and they find these 12 and 13 foot and 11 foot
skeletons with baskets that are woven so tight that they pour water
into it, the water doesn't leak out, all this strange jewelry, and
some of them had red hair or whatever, and they're like, wait a second, what are we
going to do?
Because if we make this public or go to the government or the university, they're going to shut us down, take the land, and they're not going to compensate us, and we're done, because we've invested everything in mining here, right?
And they knew this from previous
experiences, so they would call old Joe, and he shows up with his
truck and a whole bunch of crowbars, and he puts them
in there on what they call a Friday afternoon, and they go back to work on
Monday, because when you blow a cave up with dynamite
it takes a couple of days for the dust to settle, it's not like outside where the wind sweeps it
away, and they all go back to work.
But in the meantime he was able to pocket a few interesting things, and I'm not going to say anymore on that subject.
So this is the real world that I'm talking about now, not what the academics are talking about.
Hmm, interesting.
I would say that kind of form of corruption goes on all over the place, different forms, different forms of corruption.
Initially the miners, they didn't want to be corrupt, they were excited, but they found out that they would get screwed.
What they would do is they'd come and put them all in separate jail cells, and they're like why am I interested?
Well, you've got to tell us what you saw.
And they'll say, well we saw some 12 foot skeletons, and they're like, wrong, you're going to stay in jail.
They come back four days later, and they say, well what did you see?
I saw a 12 foot skeleton.
Oh, wrong, you're going to stay in jail.
They come back another couple of days and say, what did you see?
I didn't see anything.
Great, you're out of here.
So who's corrupt?
Where's the corruption?
Well, it goes all over.
And it's one thing to read about stories like this, and it's another thing to sit down with someone who was there and did it.
That had to hurt.
You get over it.
If you're a small picture type of person, you don't know reality in a bigger sense.
In other words, if you've never been in a helicopter, it'll eat you alive.
But if you see the big picture, in other words, been in a helicopter, you rise above it, and you see the beginning and the end of the parade in one shot, you kind of relax into that thought and say, of course, it makes total sense that shit's so fucked up.
Anyway, sorry about the medical term there.
So going back to the Babylonians, in the 6th century, it's kind of clear to see that things changed.
Scripturally, you can see that the Greek and Russian sort of went from one country to another, and Jeremiah talks about it quite a lot.
He's the main prophet at the time.
I think his calling directly is to tear down former civilizations and build up new ones.
But let me just use this metaphor, and I keep using it, and this is a helpful tool for when you're reading scripture.
When you're reading specific things like that, when someone is given something that seems general, it's about this particular god.
So when it's to break down, what is he breaking down?
Stuff about this particular god?
No, because they have other gods.
Okay, and what is he building up?
Oh, just a different set of gods again, or just about this god?
You get it?
So, for example, when you read the book of Daniel, no one understands it, very simply because they're taking it literally out of context.
When you read, for example, in the book of Daniel, and knowledge will increase, people say, oh, we're in that now, because you see the knowledge is increasing with the internet and the printing press and all that, right?
Really?
You're joking, right?
When it says knowledge will increase in the book of Daniel, it's knowledge of the gods.
They're writing about themselves, by the way, when you read scripture, you know what I mean?
It's not your knowledge, it's man's knowledge of the gods.
So what Jeremiah was tearing down was knowledge of Yahweh.
No.
What was the precondition before he tore down?
No knowledge of Yahweh, or in other words, they had set up, before the time of Jeremiah, do you see temples of Yahweh everywhere, or you saw temples to various gods?
A ladder, right?
Yeah.
And then after that time, how many temples were built and dedicated after the time to pagan gods, major ones, or even semi-major ones, after Jeremiah?
Almost none.
Well, the Greeks are their gods.
Yeah, they did.
But around that time period, stuff started to go downhill.
Yeah.
So, one thing you were saying earlier, I was thinking, it's the obfuscation of knowledge of the gods and knowledge of their identity that's been going on for over 2,000 some odd years.
2,400 years, I'd say.
I mean, put it this way, if that had not been done,
what happened in the first century would not have been such a mystery
and you wouldn't need all these conspiracy theories from Simon Magus
and all these other types, and the Samaritan crew that he rolled with,
and all the other groups that came hundreds of years later to develop Christianity
and all this other stuff, which is all conspiracy theories, right?
But if that had not been torn down, because right away all of the people would have wanted rapid and succinct identification of all these events going on with which specific god, right?
They were so loose.
I mean, you had some pretty educated people.
Tiberius Claudius Caesar had some pretty...
He liked accuracy and precision.
He wanted to know which god was responsible for all those events in Judea in mid-first century A.D., or let's say around 30 A.D. He wanted to know what was going on and which god was behind it.
Specifically, he didn't want to hear no stories about it.
He wanted to get the real scoop on it, which he didn't like, by the way.
Because he was the emperor.
How come they didn't come to him?
He didn't deny it, though.
There's a lot of stuff that was on the internet, is not on the internet.
I guess if Claudius Tiberius Caesar was around that time period, he was a historian.
He was a strange bird for an emperor.
I don't know if he was ever deified, by the way.
I think he was.
It's a tradition, yeah.
But I think you might have found it...
Personally, from what I read about him, he would have found it distasteful, but it was done anyway.
If you were to sit down with any emperor, or if I were, let's just say, it would be him, and have a coffee talk.
I look into it.
So, when Nebuchadnezzar becomes the head of gold in the statue, the Book of Daniel says that he was to be the head of a new civilization, technically that would last until the end of man's society.
So you could say that we still live in the Babylonian system that began in 6 BC, because it spun off the subsequent Persian, Greek, and Roman ones.
With a predominant influence of the Greek, which is noted through science, math, and philosophy, and government.
Yeah, and well, since the Greek time, that has stuck.
Although, I don't know, I don't want to get into this because it's kind of a side note, but I'll just bring it up lightly.
So why don't you agree that the legs in the statue are the Romans?
You keep saying that they're the Greeks, the Greeks are the belly.
The legs are the Romans.
Well, if you look after the Greeks, you have divisions, right?
Yeah, you have East and West.
Is Eastern Roman?
Byzantine?
Is it Roman?
Yeah.
Is Roman Roman?
You see, there is no Roman.
Show me something in Rome that's uniquely Roman.
No, show me something in Greece that's uniquely Greece.
The Greeks took from the Persians.
That's all Persian stuff.
Well, then other people might argue that the Greeks, want to argue that the Greeks took from the Egyptians.
No, they were there parallel with the Egyptians.
They were sister civilizations.
Right, sister cities as well as sister civilizations.
Yeah, they shared just about everything other than language itself.
So I would suggest that if we're going to trace things, the Greeks stole from the Persians.
I mean, when we talk about Alexander the Great, he wanted to be like the Persian kings.
He jacked them one to one.
I don't know what he wanted to do other than chase little boys around.
Yeah, he didn't die the way they tell you anyway.
So he was a little too friendly.
But let's just put it this way.
There's an order that's shown from the statue, right?
In prominence and in value.
But it's a descending order through time.
You see.
Well, why are there two feet with five toes on each one?
Ten toes and two feet.
Are the feet part of the legs?
Well, yes, but the whole body stands on the feet, doesn't it?
You're not going to do very well with no feet.
And then you get to the very bottom and it's the least stable of all, structurally.
Yeah, I just think that it's worth making somewhat of a distinction that the Romans had their own thing which spun off from the Greeks, yes, which spun off from the Persians.
Well, let's just go back to the Persians real quick.
Zoroism, Zarathustraism, I think is a contrast to the Greek pantheon.
And the philosophy is a contrast.
And there's a definite east-west division that was maintained.
And the irony of it is, in this culture, we think that after that time period, meaning the Greek period, that the west was the prominent power.
And I would suggest the latter.
I would suggest the eastern was prominent.
And that was not really settled until about the 5th century or 4th century AD.
Yeah, I can agree with that, sure.
Pantheon Seleucids and all that.
And believe it or not, there was a lot of people from Alexander's army that adopted into those eastern cultures.
So, I don't know.
I would suggest an overall more objective view of east versus west.
I would suggest that the stability of the
eastern empire was probably a little more
had more integrity than the western empire, with the Roman
expansion trying to get the northern part of Germany, which they never really
got, and England, where the
eastern empire went all the way out to Afghanistan and all those
in India and settled in very, quote-unquote, let me say this in English,
nicely, where the western didn't.
So, look, I'll take chicken tiki marsala over spaghetti and meatballs any day.
But anyway.
As far as the Greeks spinning off from the Persians, there's also a geographical aspect.
The only reason that Alexander got this great big empire that people want to laud him for getting is because it was already the Achaemenid Empire.
The land was already there.
He just took somebody else's land.
He didn't go out and conquer a hundred countries.
So, geographically, he took their stuff.
Sure, he did it politically.
Yes, in the sense that he took cues from them.
The Persians wanted to create a unified world empire and they did that through entertainment, by marrying into the culture.
You often make that mention of Alexander doing that, but he took it from them.
That was their idea.
He told his military people to go out and marry wives from conquered territories.
But Persians were already doing that.
Just to simplify it for the listenership, in the Western convention right now, when you go into scientific, medical, philosophical and government documents, not now, but as far back as you want to go, even a thousand years, it's all going to be metaphorically Greek prefixes, Greek suffixes in all the technical terms and an underlying Greek-ness or Hellenic influence throughout all of that.
None.
Very little Persian.
Where I see the Persian influence is in Saturday morning cartoons with the superheroes.
Let me put it this way for the listenership.
The concept of someone coming out of your society with unique powers to save society, like the Batman and Superdog and Superman, those are all concepts out of the Persian philosophies by the way.
Look it up if you understand Zoroism.
And Manichaeism.
As you went further east, it changed.
And as you got further west within the east, it changed again.
But initially the influence was similar.
But you don't see that now.
You see Greek influence everywhere.
I don't see Persian or I don't see Farsi type.
They're not Arabs.
I don't see that language being used in technical, philosophical, even religious.
Look, put it this way.
Even the quote-unquote Judeans got Hellenized more than they got Persian-sized or whatever.
Or Zoroism.
They see that right away.
So I would differ, not because I want to differ, but I would differ only because it's glaringly obvious that the Greek influence is much greater than the Persian.
Whether they got it from the Persians or not, I would say the archetypes were different as well.
The Persian archetype from the Greek archetype.
Even though you mentioned the entertainment.
When you go out to Afghanistan in the middle of nowhere sometimes they'll dig up a small amphitheater.
That is strictly Greek with Greek inscription, not Persian.
So whether it was gotten from the Persians or not, it was established as Greek.
And still is today.
Everywhere in the world the whole world wants a democracy as it's being peddled in the media, the propaganda.
I don't see them peddling an Ayatollah, let's say.
So it's still the Greek meme.
I'm not saying that it's cut and dried and this is it and that's it.
No, I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying the leanings.
Let me just fast forward for a moment.
When we get into this Middle East Union, I keep saying it's not going to be like the European Union.
It's very different, but that concept of a union, yes, will exist, but not like the European Union.
I always preface that.
It's going to be very loose and you won't know it's happening and you won't know that it's taking over because of its looseness.
Right?
Imagine the debates on there.
Imagine 10 years from now, is there a European Union?
No, there isn't.
Well, yes, there is.
Yes, there is.
You see?
That's going to be an interesting one.
So, going back to the Jeremiah bit, if you look in Jeremiah 25, there's a rundown of all the nations that are intended for destruction in geographical order, I think, and the list starts with Judah and Jerusalem.
Jerusalem and the cities of Judah and their kings and their chief officials to make them a waste and a desolation.
And then Pharaoh, king of Egypt, and his court, and all the mixed multitudes of the kings of the lands of Uz and the land of the Philistines, and Ashkelon, and Gaza, and Eschron, and Edom, and Moab, and blah, blah, blah.
And it goes on, and then at the end it says all the kings of the north, the near, and the far, each after his brother, and all the kingdoms of the earth.
And then, at the end, Shishak, he shall...
Well, wait a second.
Wait a second.
Go back.
What was that?
All the kingdoms of what?
Of the earth.
Yeah, say that.
Go back up, and what does it say before that, and say it real slow, like this.
Do me a favor.
Please.
Just do that for me, Sam.
All the kings of the north, the near, and the far, each after his brother, and all the kingdoms of the earth, that are on the surface of the ground.
Hmm.
Okay.
Interesting.
Does anyone need help with what that means?
Anyway.
No.
But this is talking about that time, though.
It's not like it's talking about what's coming.
Uh-huh.
This is talking about the 5th, 6th century BC.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's fine.
But either way, it's a very tall statement.
Either way.
You can more specifically place that when we go into the interlinear and we see the context, whether it was strictly for that time, but I just want the listeners to consider...
You've got to have a real set of cajones or balls to make statements like that.
So anyway, go ahead.
So yeah, there was to be a total overthrow of all political systems in the entire world, with only Babylon being prophesied to survive in a social and religious sense, until eventually that was overthrown also, thanks to the Medes.
But the Medes would also get overthrown prior to that.
So then from Babylon, as the head of the so-called New World Order, would develop the civilization that predominates the world currently that we see.
So it's quite clear in the Old Testament that Babylon in the 6th century pretty much ran the world.
I think it's interesting, like you said, it's a tall statement and Nebuchadnezzar went after everybody, but we can't really find any records of it that are publicly available.
Yeah, and I think it's pronounced Nebuchadnezzar.
Yeah, I'll just say it.
That's fine.
But here's one thing about the Babylonians.
What and how they differed, other than geographically, from the other cultures, whether it was in their height or not, but let's say around their height because that's when you have the most freedom and wherewithal to do things, would be that they were into hot couture, hot cuisine, hot technology, like high fashion.
You see, other cultures had fashion, but the Babylonians had high fashion.
Everything they did, to a certain degree, was embellished and was considered the peak of like you would say Ferrari for cars or Chanel for clothes, or Zegna, or whatever.
You see what I mean for shoes?
They were into the not in a brash, garish way, but it was considered the standard for high fashion of their time.
What's that?
Nothing.
Sassy, yeah, okay.
But I would say they had better taste.
Let's just say they would do it in good taste.
So this was something that would be considered that many people you know, because right now when you go out to the community or the people at large, you say, Babylonia, that's bad.
That's about, you know, it's deception, it's evil and all this.
Well, yeah.
But, you know, they really don't understand.
If there's going to be a repeat of some assemblage of a repeat, let's say, of this thing, they're not going to see it coming because they lack the awareness of the qualities that they were pursuing.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
So, both Jeremiah and Ezekiel did say that Nebuchadnezzar, if you read it, says that he would conquer all of Egypt, which is in Ezekiel 29, and Jeremiah 46, and Ezekiel also went on to say that he would conquer countries which I think correspond to North Africa, though I have to look into that a little bit, but it seems to correspond to that, Ezekiel 30, and the rest of the most of that chapter.
We also have historical records which are interesting.
There's this guy called Megasthenes.
He's an ancient Greek historian and diplomat in the 4th century BC.
Repeat the name?
Megasthenes.
Spell it.
M-E-G-A-Mega, S, Megas, and then Thenes, S-T-H-E-N-E-S.
Oh, okay.
Megasthenes.
I don't know if I'm pronouncing it right.
That's like the root name for Thomas.
That's okay.
Go ahead.
So he's the guy who wrote a book called the Indica, which is what you would call India.
He's a guy who did go to India quite a bit and document a lot about that.
The book itself is said to be lost, but it's been partially reconstructed from writings of other authors who quote it a lot because it was highly regarded.
In that book, he does show that Nebuchadnezzar figured kind of prominently in the history of India and that he conquered India, as well as North Africa and even Spain.
Also if you read Josephus, Antiquities of the Jews, I can try and quote a little bit for that.
As regards to these things, one must consider as reliable the report of the Chaldeans.
Indeed, in the ancient records of the Phoenicians, accounts in agreement with the things reported by Berossus have been written about the king of Babylon, that the ruler subdued both Syria and all of Phoenicia, Tyre, and goes on to talk about the majority of Libya and Iberia, with Iberia being where Portugal and Spain is.
So Mediterranean Rim countries, it's North and South they call them.
So there is some kind of documentation for it, but it's really sparse and you kind of have to dig a lot.
Well, the last thing anyone wants to do is pull that out archaeologically to prove it at this point.
I mean, no, actually, let me just say it like this.
At this point, we will see perhaps more evidence of that, but we have not, if anything like that was dug up, you know, like hard evidence of it, it would have been put away.
Because they have established the history of the known world since Roman times very well, and how academically it needs to be procured.
Anything that jumps up in that is really a problem.
That's why, for example, let me just interject something.
In the Western world, if they find, let's say, Chinese artifacts that are very old, they're negated.
And in China, if they find Western artifacts that are very old, they're negated, because they don't want to show, they want to express that it was xenophobia of the Chinese, no interaction until Marco Polo, you see what I mean?
The propaganda story, right?
I mean, you see, so the people that, you know, there's no cross, instead of cross-pollinating the two artifacts and saying, hey, you found Western stuff in China, we found Chinese stuff here, let's see, let's work together, because maybe there was a period of direct and frequent interaction.
No, no, no, no.
I mean, one story about this you could look up was 30, 40 years ago, they found the oldest mummies they announced found in China, and they announced it too soon, because then they found that they were not Chinese, they were, quote-unquote, Caucasian with red hair.
So now they have to hide it, you see?
And it wasn't until 2003, 2004, until they published the analysis, because they can't, you know, and the same thing when the Western world, whenever they find, you know, Far Eastern relics, it's like, oh, we found some great relics, oh, no, they're Chinese or Asian, oh, well, what about those relics again, oh, never mind, we'll talk about those later.
It's just like, if you know anything, yeah, any subject is like that these days, because
of the level of distraction, see, back then, actually, they had a level of intensity within
their daily lives, you know, you didn't have, you couldn't, it wasn't common back, let's
say, 100 or 200 years ago, for someone to spend three quarters of a day every day for
a few weeks behind a computer terminal researching.
Back in those days, you had people support you, or you had to go out and earn, you had to work for at least three hours a day to make sure you ate and had a bed to sleep in.
So what I'm saying is, information was hard to get, so it was very easy for them to hide it back then.
Now it's not.
Right now, a crew on site could find something, and they have those silly phones and stuff, they can immediately videotape or photograph and have it uploaded and Twittered and Facebooked or whatever for many people to see within the same day.
I could even say within a few hours.
So how are you going to hide that now?
So this is the time for that.
That's why I keep saying the purpose of the Internet is not what you think.
It's a tool to validate what you heard about or read about in ancient societies.
Anyway, I've discussed that before.
And it can't be screwed with.
That's right.
Right.
Well, it can be.
It can be.
But not with things that can be easily discerned like that.
Right.
And if they try to hide it, you can GPS it now, right?
It's also worth mentioning that Nebuchadnezzar did all this stuff at Yahweh's instruction as his servant.
I don't know if he served him directly or if he knew what he was doing, but he was moved to do that because Yahweh told him to.
So from what I'm seeing, it also seems to be that there was a historical illiteracy
that spread around that time where these people were not able to perpetrate their national
existences as they had had them before the conquest, in that Nebuchadnezzar adapted a
policy that I think the Assyrians who preceded him had used, which was that you take people
away from their native lands and bring in, you know, the elites from Babylon to occupy
or some other country to occupy, and then you transplant the natives, which is what was
done with Judah, obviously.
But with that situation, they did leave the poor people of the land to be vinedressers and husband men, I think it says.
But it's also worth noticing that because of their rebellion, even those poor people were finally removed, I think in Jeremiah 52, and that left the place vacant for several decades.
Because the conditions were, don't fight him, and you'd be chilly chill, right?
And you know, it's like, you'll survive.
But let's say the mindset at the time was the pride and the way of life that we're used to, which resulted in the impulse of, we should fight.
But it's very clear when, one of my favorite examples, I'm just going to paraphrase, there's trouble obviously at the walls and Nebuchadnezzar's army is going to prevail.
And the people come to Jeremiah and they soup him up, right?
You know what I mean?
And they say, oh, Jeremiah, we know you truly are a prophet, and we'll do anything you say.
So what should we do?
And he says, well, don't go anywhere, he says, we want to go to Egypt, right, and all this.
And he says, well, stay here and don't fight.
And they're like, oh, no, no, we don't like that, we're not going to do that, you know?
You see what I mean?
So this is the mindset that you're, and you remember the interaction, it was like, what are you talking about?
We prospered under Ashtoreth, we worshipped Ashtoreth and all these other gods for generations and we prospered under them, what do you mean we got, this is the god that's doing it to us now?
You see what I mean?
So there's this mind, you could really, in other words, the reason I'm saying this is because you get a good read on the mindset of the people, right?
They're a bunch of assholes, sorry, I'll say it that way.
So just like today.
Okay, so make a point on the people being killed, like you said, I think bears the truth in scripture, you rebel, you die, or become captive, that's all.
Oh, so let's do the math on it then.
If I don't rebel, I don't die and become captive, yeah, that's right, put an equal sign on that, see?
And you will find that to be true.
But how many did not rebel?
Very few.
Because remember when they came back from Babylon into Jerusalem with, you know, getting help from, I think it was Cyrus and all this, and the other, there were several kings there that helped, you see that there were already people there.
And it was the temple that was destroyed 10 years after the conquest, or maybe more, and the walls were broken.
But there were houses and there were, you know, fixtures and, you know, there were people there.
But eventually even those people were deported.
I'm trying to find the verse itself, it's kind of hard to do two things at once.
No, what I'm saying, ultimately, when they started returning back, you know, let's say after the time of Daniel, right, and within the context.
Oh, then, okay, yeah.
Yeah, there were people, they went, you know, like, in other words, I'm referencing Nehemiah and Ezra now, right?
Even during the time of Malachi, which I think is, I think Malachi was in that time period, I think Malachi was Ezra, but we'll get, we can look at that later.
Well, that's another question, then, if Malachi is Ezra, why is he Malachi, and then Ezra, you know, why isn't Ezra Malachi and Malachi Ezra?
So, but that's another point.
Why is Shishak Nebuchadnezzar?
You can code names, but.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can.
Well, let's just say we have to investigate something that seems anomalous, just like when the New Testament states, as written by Jeremiah, and we don't find it in any of Jeremiah's, we find it in Zechariah.
So why?
Well, it's very simple.
He just said it.
It means that there are writings in Zechariah that were actually performed by, guess who?
Jeremiah.
Get over it.
Too bad.
You don't like it?
That's too bad, you know?
I mean, that's what it is, right?
Simple.
We don't have to blow these things up into whatever.
So, in other words, what I'm saying is the best evidence sometimes is taking a relaxed, succinct, rational approach.
So if you say, like, this guy is that guy, let's just look into it.
It's not impossible.
As a matter of fact, let's investigate that, right?
It should show itself.
That's one thing.
If you've got a lot of, I tell people, if you've got hang-ups or unfounded beliefs, just leave any ancient writ or anything ancient alone.
You can't bring the mindset that you've been raised in into stuff that existed in the past.
Sorry.
I don't care how many history channels you watch, you know, shows you watch and all that stuff, or how many degrees you have.
It doesn't work.
This is a very heavily propagandized, censored society.
So just chill, relax, have a good time with it, right?
And you'll learn more that way about everything.
I mean, to give you an example, you know, people say you're into Scripture.
You know, you get this, like, prudish mentality.
I mean, when I do sonic events, I like to make at least one lascivious comment every time, just to show that, you know, this fake morality that, you know what I mean, people attach to these things, you know what I mean?
Three comments.
Yeah.
Remember, I used to say it on air, I want to make at least one or two or three lascivious comments.
That's right.
Yes, you have.
Yeah, because you know what?
Yeah, this is for mature audiences only.
Great.
Please.
Very well should be.
Oh, you can also took a program of re-educating people.
I mean, in the case of Israel, they had to learn and use the Aramaic, the Chaldean language.
And I think it says in Ezra somewhere, Ezra 8, that they lost the ability to speak Hebrew somewhere.
But I have to look at that.
Yeah.
Several, several references to the look what you're speaking.
Yeah, he was a, let's see.
Well, Nehemiah was, he'd be in federal prison maximum security if he was alive today.
He would go out in the street and he didn't like the way you looked in terms of, you know, Babylonian fashion language and thought and speech.
He just pulled out a club and bashed your head in on the spot.
It says it, you know, he beat them, smote them, pulled their hair out of their head.
Now, you know what I mean?
It takes at least a 30 or 40 pound shock load to pull someone's scalp off, you know, with your hand, you know, with the hair, you know.
So, yeah, I think Disney will be avoiding Nehemiah.
Presumably most of the literature they had in their libraries, religious artifacts were also destroyed.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, some of it.
I heard religious artifacts, libraries, yes.
Yeah.
Presumably that's also destroyed when the temple was, so it seems as if Nebuchadnezzar also had a habit of taking people's literature away from them, you know, burning it so that they couldn't just connect to the past.
We do know that representatives from these different countries that he conquered were brought back to Babylon because it says in Daniel 4.1, peace addresses all the nations.
Hold on a second.
Bruce, is Sam coming through clearly?
He is periodically in and out, yeah.
No, he's not coming through clearly.
He's breaking every other word.
Every other word, yeah.
What I mean clearly is crystal clear, no breaks.
Is he coming through that way or are you having trouble?
No, he was popping in and out.
Okay.
Well, you got to let me know.
Yeah, that's why I just stopped you.
Yeah.
So what I got out of it, just to repeat, Nebuchadnezzar was obfuscating people's access to information, their history, and other things.
Yes.
Sounds like the American, or it sounds like any other modern culture.
So from that perspective, you could say it is Babylonian still.
Yes.
What I wanted to ask is from, would you say that, because I think in the book of Luke, it says something about the times of the Gentiles, right?
The nations.
Yeah.
So could you say that from the 6th BC onwards where a Gentile nation sort of becomes a world empire and then successive Gentile world empires, is that the time as far as from that point period up until now in the end?
That is the time.
Well, the intensity of it builds up, and that's why it loses integrity also from that perspective.
I mean there are other deities who would like man to believe that integrity is going up and all this other stuff.
So here's the other thing I want to interject about scripture.
It's a strategic manual or an op manual.
You know in the military when they develop a strategy to use in war that includes tactical, they form it in the form of a book or a manual for that.
That's what scripture is when you look at the battles, the destruction of nations, and all this other stuff.
It reads like a war manual, right?
Like an op, yeah.
Yeah.
And you know the winning side.
Like if I said, for example, you're going to play a game on the field and there are two teams, Team A and Team B.
Team A is definitely going to win, and Team B is definitely going to lose.
Which team you want to play with?
Most people are like, oh, I don't know.
Maybe Team B.
I'll say, well, you're a terrible strategist and a terrible tactician to do that, right?
And you don't even have to be a strategist or a tactician.
You're just playing stupid to pick the losing side.
I mean that's when you distill all the information that we get about the events on Earth, that's what it boils down to, doesn't it?
Right.
Yes.
And it's voluntary.
That's why what the Christians are doing is totally unlawful, going around trying to convert people and all this other stuff.
That's completely unlawful.
I wouldn't say there's a law against it in scripture, but it has to be free will.
And the used car salesmanship on all the mythology they put on people about being born again and knowing this J-E-S-U-S and all this other stuff is not founded in scripture at all.
And that's obviously the losing side, but that's okay.
Let me just say it this way.
Any world religion is the losing side if you're going to invest your cognitive ability into it.
Notice I didn't say what you believe or your faith is, right?
Because usually most people have released and abandoned their cognitive abilities when they subscribe to a belief or a faith.
That's okay.
They're just being used.
Someone today went in the chat, put in a thing about a robot, and I'm like, damn, robots, I got nothing against.
I prefer robots, especially anthropomorphic ones.
Why the hell not?
Because they were never made with flesh and blood.
It's a robot.
Of course it's going to be cruel and stinky and whatever in manner and character.
Humans are worse because they're made of flesh and blood, and they have a heart, and they act like they don't.
They have a mind that has far more ability than any of these robots, and they act like they don't.
So who's worse, the robot or the people?
It's easier to get scrap parts from a robot too than a human.
I'll wrap up on my Babylon thingy.
The literature thing I think is interesting.
Am I coming through clearly?
Yes.
Okay.
Let me know if I start to break up.
So if you look at the Daniel period, I think that Daniel 9-2, I might have to pull it up.
I think it says that he became, I think it says that he became head of what remained of Israel's early literature, as in their library stuff, the stuff that was not.
Daniel.
Yeah, this is what I meant.
I think they put him in charge of the books.
Yeah, he had all knowledge of Babylonian science, magic, astronomy.
So it says in the year of his reign, whatever his name is, the king of Persia, Daniel understood by the scrolls the number of years which came to be, which came by the word of Yahweh to something, something.
Basically, it's saying that he had access to the Jewish scrolls that showed him what was going to happen in the future, which he would have never have been able to access unless he was basically put in charge of those books.
So, yeah, whatever they had.
So there are references that are scattered throughout the Old Testament to show that many of the prophets and the priests and the kings had their own writings.
Isaiah wrote a major history of the kings of Judah that you can see in Chronicles chapter 32.
Both Nathan and Gad had their own separate histories of King David, which is attested to in Chronicles also.
And I think even before 100 years before David, the Canaanites had a city called Kirjot Sefer, which means the City of Books or City of Letters that was almost entirely devoted to literature.
Yeah, Sefer is usually means scroll today.
So where's that as far as I know, it's all of that stuff is gone.
And what I'm trying to say is, Sam Holm, what I want to keep pounding maybe on this sonic event is even if they did find evidence of it, you ain't getting it, you meaning the public at large, up to this point.
So go ahead.
So it doesn't mean because they haven't found it means it doesn't exist, because you have to take factor in who's running the show right now, even from a people point of view.
True.
And there was Solomon.