I'm one of the last people to work with him to take his methodologies, which were from Reichensteiner to advancing it.
What you see on YouTube and a lot of methodologies were like cell phones in the 80s or 90s, and now we've taken it up to current advancement.
It got to the point with Trevor that I was sending him devices and he says, well, I don't know how it works.
I mean, I don't understand what you're doing, but it works even better.
So it got to the point where the student, you know, the master was now the student.
So I felt very humbled and at the same time exalted to be able to take it to the next level where at this point, we have full spectrum dominance over the weather on this planet.
And I say we, whoever we is, you know, you can guess, I've done demonstrations for quote unquote, government people, and they just give you an example.
I did 15 demonstrations.
I drove a couple of colonels back to drinking because they had bet that if I did, I got three out of the 15, that was the real deal.
I got 13 out of 15.
So demonstrations, you know, like, you know, they pick a city and then like make it rain here and it was the middle of the dry season or, you know, there's rain here, stop it or throw down a tornado here or make a hurricane there or stop a hurricane here, you know, and it's like, OK.
So, yeah, I just I don't mind saying at this point, you know, because it's just everything is just so ridiculous at this point that anything that's sane or duplicatable, technically accessible, that sounds fantastic.
You know, it sounds ridiculous.
So but it's it's about being a technical, technically accessing, you know, anyone can do it, you know, if you know if you know what's going on.
So, yeah, but someone else they could speak up if they want to introduce themselves or just listen either way.
Hey, my name's Matthew.
Hey, Matthew.
Good to have you.
Cool.
Thanks.
I'd rather just listen if that's all right with you guys.
Mm hmm.
OK, so I just want to give a little bit of a spoiler.
Some of the stuff that I had kind of penciled in to discuss only because about 90 percent of the emails that I get privately are regarding explaining what's called scripture or Bible and things like that.
And again, I was prefacing earlier, I think it'll it'll show up on the audio that it's just the most amazing thing to be amazed about is how you go on something called the Internet or the stupid rectangle or whatever.
And you notice how no one has picked up on what is obvious yet.
I mean, all the stuff being discussed is just a dummy load.
And also, I just want to, you know, I appreciate Chuck Ocelli's, you know, putting up with me for 60 hours and all that, you know, for him to get away from the dummy load he usually delivers and go go to something like this and then obviously go back to it.
It was a big jump for him.
You know what I mean?
So but it put out quite a bit of really good stuff.
It's just sitting there and, you know, and here's the other aspect of it is there's a lot of, quote unquote, academia that doesn't get a lot of play on the it gets a lot of play on the Internet, by the way, academia.
But even if you go look at the academic circles about the subjects brought up in Greek speak, they fail miserably as well.
So I'm just trying to get pieces together on how to continue presenting things, anything or any things in a very simple way that anyone can, you know, be edified by it.
And I get stupefied myself when I see how little information of quality there is being put out, you know, in public or on what's called the what I call the stupid rectangle, you know, the Internet, the computer.
So, you know, from that point of view, then, you know, why not to start hitting on the things of order of importance?
Now, give you an example.
A few weeks ago, there was a group of people that met in what's called Idaho, and they demonstrated not one, not two, not three, not four, not five, but about six what's called free energy devices that work.
And the one and the one that's the most easy to access of it is the the energy machine of Joseph Newman.
You know, so this stuff has been around.
It's provable and all that.
Right.
But still, you have people looking for free energy.
You get my point.
Yeah, it exists.
I mean, it's just that do you want to get into it?
You want to go down and let me just share an experience.
Could you imagine that you could read between the lines?
It's about one or two a.m. in the morning and you get a knock on the door and you look outside and there's like a semi SWAT team type cops, heavily armored body cams, the whole thing.
And they're like, well, we got a suicide call from this address.
And you're like, well, that's not possible because there's no phone here.
Well, it was from a disabled cell phone from about 300 yards in this area.
Really.
So this is the only house that you decide to knock on.
Interesting.
This is what we'd like to come inside and see if you look around because it was a suicide call.
Right.
So you're like, well, OK, why don't you come on and look through?
And they just march on through, you know, with all their heavy armor and machine guns and all that.
Yes.
And then walk out and say, well, thanks.
Have a good night.
So this is the kind of stuff you end up to read between the lines and who that happens to.
Right.
So so this is the type of society you live in because, you know, eventually, you know, you could be suicidal anyway.
I'm not going to I'm not a conspiracy type or whatever, you know, thing.
But that's already been shown.
So so the thing here is it's all just one big kind of like prank prankaliciousness that I call it, you know, from one level to another.
So, again, one thing that the reason I've been holding back is just I've got to just wipe my brow and say, like, what the hell is going on on this planet and just take a break?
And again, just to reiterate, I promised a sonic event soon after the solos I was doing on AFR.
And then I said, well, let me take a week off.
And I started looking around.
I said one week became two weeks and three weeks and four weeks.
And I know there's interest.
I know there's plenty of interest, but I don't really see it.
And I think that enough has been said that even if no more was said, it would be pretty honky dory, like they say.
But I think more should be said, because like I mentioned before, I've had a I remember listening to an old radio broadcaster from the 50s.
He says, never share more than 10 percent of what you found out in public, you know, and but you could hide all of it in the public library.
Right, so so let's let's just continue, I wanted to just throw another spoiler, perhaps, on the biblical text, and because it has nothing to do, I think if anyone spends 15 minutes researching the history of the biblical text, you'll find it has nothing to do with any religion on the planet right now.
Right now.
Now, notice, I didn't say that there are other religions that have hijacked it.
No, but there but the text itself has nothing to do with any religion.
Now, there's plenty of evidence that there are other religions that have hijacked it.
Plenty of groups of religions and sorts that have hijacked it and are telling you things that are supposed to be out of there that you will not find in their characters, events or anything.
So I just want to make that clear.
And and and I never recommend that anyone go and read or study the biblical text, contrary to what most people say.
And the reason why I never recommend anyone go read it or study it is because if you tried, you don't understand a dang thing in it.
So why would I tell you to do that?
But you see, so the other point here is why not start having a legitimate, rational discussion on what is really there and then see what happens.
Right.
So one of the spoilers, again, I wanted to give is how to comprehend prophecy and the same way you understand if you're, let's say, traveling on the earth in a motorized engine driven wagon, which is a car, if they want you to slow down, they'll show you a sign showing a very low speed limit.
And if you miss that sign, they'll put a speed bump in front of you to make you feel it that you should be slowing down.
Right.
And that's what happens very often when you read a lot of these ancient texts.
I wanted to give an example and explain it just to kind of like see how people would expand in their own studies with it, because there's many examples I can give.
I'll just give this one because it's pertinent, because it also ties into what's called geopolitics.
Now, let's just call it a verse.
Now, I don't like if you ever heard me discuss biblical texts, I'll never give chapter and verse like these, you know, who's do because they sound like preachers, McMinisters, like you when they they all they always shout a verse at you.
And it sounds like to me when they start shouting verses and chapters, all I hear is two old beef patty, special sauce, cheese, lettuce and a sesame seed bun.
That's all I hear when they start all these, you know, Christian, I call them pastors, McMinisters, Mick, whatever, Mick churches.
That's what it sounds like.
Oh, yeah.
You ever hear like Matthew 25, 17, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm like two old beef patties, special sauce.
I was like, what the hell are these?
You know, if you want to, you know, you know, if you want to do your demonology, go ahead.
But, you know, say it is so, you know.
But anyway, that's what it is, by the way.
When they do that, it's a form of spell casting.
They don't know it.
But but so the verse or the part that I'm going to be explaining is in what's called the book of Isaiah.
It's around the first chapter.
And I know I don't study it in chapter and verse.
Very often when I have conversations with people on the biblical texts, I'll say like, you know, in the book of Isaiah, such and such.
And they're like, well, what's the chapter and verse?
I'm like, heck, I don't know.
It's around the middle somewhere of the book, you know, because that that's how it's supposed that you either know it or you don't.
You know, how many times people watch a movie and are like, remember in The Matrix at exactly one hour, 32 minutes and 43 seconds?
Like who talks like that?
Right.
It's like, you remember in The Matrix or on the office building or whatever, you know, yeah, I remember that, you know, you know, one, you know.
So one thing I tell people is you either know it or you don't.
And forget about this, this demonology that's been put on humanity for hundreds of years.
Or the McPreachers, the McMinisters, the two old beef patty special sauce, you know, cheese kind of crap.
And not to use McDonald's as a reference.
But yeah, they and the only reason I use McDonald's as reference is because their own CEO publicly says they're crap.
So if he says they're crap, I can say they're crap, I guess, you know, even though I'm not a stockholder.
So let's go back to the verse.
It's in the first what's called the first chapter of Isaiah.
And if you look, I think it's in the middle of that chapter, down the middle or a little past.
It says something like, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges or your judges of old.
And then you will be known as a righteous people.
Now, let me repeat that.
That sounds very benign, doesn't it?
Most people will just read over that and keep reading.
Right.
He says, when I return you into the land, I will restore to you your former judges or some version, say the judges of old.
It's actually pretty close to the original text.
And then he says, and then you will be known as a righteous people.
Right.
So let's just look at that.
So they meaning the Israel as a political group, you know, where they set up borders known as Israel.
And they're going to be ruled by judges like they were in the past.
Like, in other words, when they went into the land, they were not ruled by kings or ruled by judges, as you see in the Book of Judges.
Right.
And as long as they have, you know, and then they will be known.
In other words, after this period of judges, they will be known as a righteous people.
So that means that during this period, they will not be known as righteous.
Right.
So if we look at the verse again and how it's prophetic and geopolitics now, by the way, I get a lot of flack.
Well, the people that are in Israel now are not the real Israel.
So that's not the point.
The point.
This is a geopolitical issue of how the people are viewed, whether they're in Israel or not.
You see.
So let's go look at this again.
When I return you back, this is in the first chapter of Isaiah, near the end somewhere.
When I return you back to the land, I will restore to you your former judges of old and then you will be known as a righteous people.
OK, let's go look at this now.
So they're sort of established as a nation again in around 1948, 49, actually sooner than that.
But let's say 48, 49, commonly accepted.
And they're ruled by prime ministers.
Now, a minister is a judge and a prime minister is a head judge.
So whenever you see a country ruled by a prime minister, that is a judgeship ministerial position.
Now, for example, a country that has a prime minister as their top dog is also has a president.
But you don't hear about it because they have that the president signs all the executive orders.
If you look this up on your own, you'll see, like, for example, who rules Israel?
It's the head of the party, Netanyahu, who is the prime minister.
But if you research who is the president of Israel, they will show you there is also a president.
Most people are not aware of this, right?
Because the president is the president that signs the executive orders for the corporation and all that.
So you could look it up.
I don't know who the president is right now, but he's some bloke sitting there, you know, doing, you know, pen.
OK, so Israel is now being ruled by prime judges or prime ministers.
Now, what's interesting is if we go back to the prophetic aspect of this, when Israel initially went into the land with the Book of Judges, they were ruled by a roughly 14 to 16 judges.
That means whether, you know, you count Joshua as one of them or Moses or such, but not really.
So we say specifically around 14 to 15 judges ruled ancient Israel.
Now, if we look at the judges of ancient Israel, we will see something interesting because the first three were men.
And the fourth judge of ancient Israel was a woman, Deborah.
Now, if we look at modern Israel, we will see the first three prime ministers are men.
But the fourth one is a woman, Golda Meir, Grandma Moses.
And the only woman to ever be prime minister of Israel, because Israel never had, only had one woman or female as a judge, you see, or a prime minister.
So we have a repeat.
Now, Netanyahu is the 12th position.
So we have one more, and then we have the 14th position, which was Samson.
Now, what's interesting, if you read in the Book of Judges, a lot of them only get one or two verses attributing to their judgeship or ruling of Israel.
But when you get to Samson, he's like the bulk of the book, you know, in terms of what's dedicated and like Samson and Delilah fame.
Right.
All right.
The Nazarene.
So so the Nazarite oath and all that.
So with the hair, you know, everyone, even storybooks have been made about it.
What's interesting about Samson, it was all about the engagement with the Philistines.
When I say engaging the Philistines, I don't mean like fiancee getting married, but there was a lot of dynamicism between them.
OK, so what you're going to see in the next, not Netanyahu, but the next prime minister and the one after him will take the position of Samson.
That's why very often I've said there is going to be carnage in the Middle East between the Israelis and the Palestinians that has never even been imagined.
Forget about what you what you've seen in the past.
Right.
And he will probably also perish.
And then the prime minister that comes after that one will probably be very spiritual, more like someone like Eli, because what I'm trying to say is the prime ministers of modern Israel are a repeat of ancient Israel's judges.
Now, here's the kicker to the end of the verse.
Remember, the verse in Isaiah says, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges and then you will be known as a righteous people.
Now, as long as Israel has prime ministers, they will not be known as a righteous people.
How many times now do you hear, oh, the Jews, oh, the Israel, the Zionists or this or that constantly, no matter what they do, they will never be held as a righteous people.
So roughly you have about three more prime ministers left in modern Israel before they have, I would say, not a civil war revolution, but a political turnaround almost overnight where they're going to install some form of a loose monarchy.
OK, so this is do you see how this very benign statement in Isaiah that says in chapter one, it says, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges and then you'll be known as a righteous people.
That's very benign.
But do you see how when you look into it as a speed bump, slow down and say, wait a second, you know, what do you mean when I return you back and I will restore your former judges?
What's going on?
You know, yes, they are back in the land.
And what's going on, you see, and you see the repeat.
There was only one judge that was a woman, Deborah, in ancient Israel.
And there was only one woman who was going to be prime minister of Israel, which was Golda Meir and also in the same position, fourth position.
Give you an example on how accurate and powerful this is.
A few folks remember the not this previous election, but the previous one when Netanyahu was going against Tzipora Livni and she was about 90 percent in the polls a week before the election.
They were ready to paint her name on the door and people were coming and saying, hey, Greek, you know, that prophetic stuff doesn't seem to work.
I said, it doesn't matter.
She's not going to be in.
It's going to be Netanyahu because there's only one prime minister that's going to be a woman.
So everyone was like, oh, no, Tzipora Livni, she's ready, she's in, you know, she's 90 percent in the polls a week away.
She's got it like, nope, she's got nothing.
And what happened?
She didn't get in.
Because I'm not following what CNN says or the media or alternative media or the people even on the boots on the ground, I'm not following what I'm not looking at their stuff as the BL end all.
I'm listening to what they're saying, but I'm saying, no, it's not going to happen.
And guess what?
It didn't.
And they're only she's, you know, so so this is very powerful stuff once you understand it.
Also, as long as Israel has prime ministers, they will never be considered a righteous people.
And from discussing and having discussions with people in Israel, a lot of the negative stuff that you hear coming out of there just isn't true.
Like, I wouldn't say all of it, but a lot of it is not true.
Like, for example, years ago with the war with Lebanon, they had put they had blamed Israeli troops for killing a few hundred Lebanese prisoners.
Now, that wasn't true.
What really happened, this is I spoke to one of the guards, the Israeli guards that was stationed there at that temporary holding area, was that there was a group of Lebanese that pleaded with the Israeli guards to let in some more Lebanese.
And they ended up being a rival faction of Lebanese, the same people.
And they started killing their own people.
But then but internationally, it was the Israeli guards that killed them, you see.
So and this and there's a lot of stuff going on with the Palestinians.
Now, there's all this oppression.
If you look at how much money the Palestinian Authority gets international aid and how much of it gets bought and distributed to the people, it's less than one percent.
The rest of it, the rest of it goes to buying the Palestinian Authority, uses it to the current Palestinian Authority, is it for personal investments?
So, you know, there's a lot of interesting stuff.
And also they breed in Palestine what they have, you know, how years ago in America, they used to have the Pledge of Allegiance.
Right.
Well, in modern day, like the Gaza Strip and places like that, all the school children are pledged to kill an Israeli every morning or Israel will be doomed, you know, just just for the hell of it.
This is the pledge.
So you don't hear this stuff.
So it's very biased and skewed.
Now, I'm not for or against either one of those groups.
I'm just saying what I see and what can be said about it.
So they're not going to be known as righteous people as long as they've got prime ministers.
So as long as you see prime ministers in Israel, they're always always going to be the Zionism.
Oh, the Jews are faulty.
Oh, it's Israel or this or that.
And how much of that do you still hear?
Quite a bit.
It's not going to go away until another several prime ministers.
Now, the prime ministers have a term of roughly four years, but it is possible to exchange.
I think in the late 90s, they went through three prime ministers in four years due with due to assassination illness and I think a short vote or something.
So you have quite a bit going on.
So anyway, I just want to recap that very benign verse in the first chapter of Isaiah, which states, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges and then you will be known as a righteous people.
How that is a very strong geopolitical prophetic statement hidden within a very benign language of that chapter.
So I just wanted to explain that.
I hope that makes sense from one level to another.
So, again, one thing that the reason I've been holding back is just I've got to just wipe my brow and say, like, what the hell is going on on this planet and just take a break?
And again, just to reiterate, I promised a sonic event soon after the solos I was doing on AFR.
And then I said, well, let me take a week off.
And I started looking around.
I said, one week became two weeks and three weeks and four weeks.
And I know there's interest.
I know there's plenty of interest, but I don't really see it.
And I think that enough has been said, you know, and but you could hide all of it in the public library.
Right, right.
So so let's just continue.
I wanted to just throw another spoiler, perhaps on the biblical text and because it has nothing to do.
I think if anyone spends 15 minutes researching the history of the biblical text, you'll find it has nothing to do with any religion on the planet right now.
Right, right now.
Now, notice I didn't say that there are other religions that have hijacked it.
No, but the text itself has nothing to do with any religion.
Now, there's plenty of groups of religions and sorts that have hijacked it.
They are telling you things that are supposed to be out of there that you will not find in their characters, events or anything.
So I just want to make that clear.
And and and I never recommend that anyone go and read or study the biblical text, contrary to what most people say.
And the reason why I never recommend anyone go read it or study it is because if you tried, you don't understand a dang thing in it.
So why would I tell you to do that?
But you see, so the other point here is why not start having a legitimate, rational discussion on what is really there and then see what happens?
Right.
So one of the spoilers, again, I wanted to give is how to comprehend prophecy.
And the same way you understand if you're, let's say, traveling on the earth in a motorized engine driven wagon, which is a car.
If they want you to slow down, they'll show you a sign showing a very low speed limit.
And if you miss that sign, they'll put a speed bump in front of you to make you feel it.
They should be slowing down.
Right.
And that's what happens.
Very often you read a lot of these ancient texts.
So I wanted to give an example and explain it just to kind of like see how people would expand in their own studies with it, because there's many examples I can give.
I'll just give this one because it's pertinent, because it also ties into what's called geopolitics.
Now, let's just call it a verse.
Now, I don't like if you ever heard me discuss biblical texts, I'll never give chapter and verse like these, you know, who's do because they sound like preachers, McMinisters, like when they always shout a verse at you.
And it sounds like to me when they start shouting verses and chapters, all I hear is two old beef patty, special sauce, cheese, lettuce and sesame seed bun.
That's all I hear when they start all these, you know, Christian, I call them McMinisters, McMinisters, whatever, McChurches.
That's what it sounds like.
Oh, you ever hear like Matthew 25, 17, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm like two old beef patties, special sauce.
I was like, what the hell is right now?
If you want to, you know, if you want to do your demonology, go ahead.
But, you know, say it is so, you know.
But anyway, that's what it is, by the way, when they do that.
It's a form of spellcasting.
They don't know it.
But but so the verse or the part that I'm going to be explaining is in what's called the Book of Isaiah.
It's around the first chapter.
And I know I don't study it in chapter and verse very often when I have conversations with people in the biblical texts.
I'll say, like, you know, in the Book of Isaiah, such and such.
And they're like, well, what's the chapter and verse?
I'm like, I don't know.
It's around the middle somewhere of the book, you know, because that's how it's supposed to be either know it or you don't.
You know how many times people watch a movie and they're like, remember in The Matrix at exactly one hour, 32 minutes and 43 seconds?
Like, who talks like that?
Right.
It's like you're in The Matrix or on the office building or whatever.
You know, yeah, I remember that, you know, you know, one, you know, so one thing I tell people is you either know it or you don't.
And forget about this, the demonology that's been put on humanity for hundreds of years.
Or the McPreachers, the McMinisters, the 2LB patty special sauce, you know, cheese kind of crap.
And not to use McDonald's as a reference, but yeah, they and the only reason I use McDonald's as reference is because their own CEO publicly says they're crap.
So if he says they're crap, I can say they're crap, I guess, even though I'm not a stockholder.
So let's go back to the verse.
It's in the first what's called the first chapter of Isaiah.
And if you look, I think it's in the middle of that chapter, down the middle or a little past.
It says something like, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges or your judges of old, and then you will be known as a righteous people.
Now, let me repeat that.
That sounds very benign, doesn't it?
Most people just read over that and keep reading.
Right.
It says, when I return you into the land, I will restore to you your former judges or some versions say they're judges of old.
It's actually pretty close to the original text.
And then he says, and then you will be known as a righteous people.
So let's just look at that.
So they, meaning the Israel as a political group, you know, where they set up borders known as Israel, and they're going to be ruled by judges like they were in the past.
So, like, in other words, when they went into the land, they were not ruled by kings or ruled by judges, as you see in the book of Judges.
Right.
And as long as they have, you know, and then there will be known.
In other words, after this period of judges, they will be known as a righteous people.
So that means that during this period, they will not be known as righteous.
Right.
So if we look at the verse again and how it's prophetic and geopolitics now, by the way, I get a lot of flack.
Well, the people that are in Israel now are not the real Israel.
So that's not the point.
The point.
This is a geopolitical issue of how the people are viewed, whether they're in Israel or not, you see.
So let's go look at this again.
When I return you back, this is in the first chapter of Isaiah, near the end somewhere.
When I return you back to the land, I will restore to you your former judges of old and then you will be known as a righteous people.
OK, let's go look at this now.
So they're sort of established as a nation again in around 1948, 49, actually sooner than that.
But let's say 48, 49, commonly accepted.
And they're ruled by prime ministers.
Now, a minister is a judge and a prime minister is a head judge.
So whenever you see a country ruled by a prime minister, that is a judgeship ministerial position.
Now, for example, a country that has a prime minister as their top dog is also has a president.
But you don't hear about it because they have that the president signs all the executive orders.
If you look this up on your own, you'll see, like, for example, who rules Israel.
It's the head of the party.
Netanyahu is the prime minister.
But if you research who is the president of Israel, they will show you there is also a president.
Most people are not aware of this, right?
Because the president is the president that signs the executive orders for the corporation and all that.
So you could look it up.
I don't know who the president is right now, but he's some bloke sitting there, you know, doing, you know, pen.
OK, so Israel is now being ruled by prime judges or prime ministers.
Now, what's interesting is if we go back to the prophetic aspect of this, when Israel initially went into the land with the book of judges, they were ruled by a roughly 14 to 16 judges.
That means whether, you know, you count Joshua as one of them or Moses or such, but not really.
So you say specifically around 14 to 15 judges ruled.
Ancient Israel.
Now, if we look at the judges of ancient Israel, we will see something interesting because the first three were men.
And the fourth judge of ancient Israel was a woman, Deborah.
Now, if we look at modern Israel, we will see the first three prime ministers are men.
But the fourth one is a woman, Golda Meir, Grandma Moses.
And the only woman to ever be prime minister of Israel, because Israel never had only had one woman or female as a judge, you see, or a prime minister.
So we have a repeat.
Now, Netanyahu is the 12th position.
So we have one more.
And then we have the 14th position, which was Samson.
Now, what's interesting, if you read in the book of judges, a lot of them only get one or two verses attributing to their judgeship or ruling of Israel.
But when you get to Samson, he's like the bulk of the book, you know, in terms of what's dedicated and like Samson and Delilah fame.
Right.
All right.
The Nazarene.
So so the Nazarite oath and all that.
So with the hair, you know, everyone, even storybooks have been made about it.
What's interesting about Samson, it was all about the engagement with the Philistines.
When I say engaging the Philistines, I don't mean like fiancee getting married, but there was a lot of dynamicism between them.
OK, so what you're going to see in the next not Netanyahu, but the next prime minister and the one after him will take the position of Samson.
That's why very often I've said there is going to be carnage in the Middle East between the Israelis and the Palestinians that has never even been imagined.
Forget about what you what you've seen in the past.
Right.
And he will probably also perish.
And then the prime minister that comes after that one will probably be very spiritual, more like someone like Eli, because what I'm trying to say is the prime ministers of modern Israel are a repeat of ancient Israel's judges.
Now, here's the kicker to the end of the verse.
Remember, the verse in Isaiah says, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges and then you will be known as a righteous people.
Now, as long as Israel has prime ministers, they will not be known as a righteous people.
How many times now do you hear, oh, the Jews, oh, the Israel, the Zionists or this or that constantly, no matter what they do, they will never be held as a righteous people.
So roughly you have about three more prime ministers left in modern Israel before they have, I would say, not a civil war revolution, but a political turnaround almost overnight where they're going to install some form of a loose monarchy.
OK, so this is do you see how this very benign statement in Isaiah that says in chapter one, it says, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges and then you'll be known as a righteous people.
That's very benign.
But do you see how when you look into it as a speed bump, slow down and say, wait a second, you know, what do you mean when I return you back until I restore your former judges?
What's going on?
You know, yes, they are back in the land.
And what's going on?
You see and you see the repeat.
There was only one judge that was a woman, Deborah, in ancient Israel.
And there was only one woman who was going to be prime minister of Israel, which was Golda Meir and also in the same position, fourth position.
Give you an example on how accurate and powerful this is.
A few folks remember the not this previous election, but the previous one when Netanyahu was going against Tzipora Livni and she was about 90 percent in the polls a week before the election.
They were ready to paint her name on the door and people were coming in and saying, hey, Greek, you know, that prophetic stuff doesn't seem to work.
I said, it doesn't matter.
She's not going to be in.
It's going to be Netanyahu because there's only one prime minister that's going to be a woman.
So everyone was like, oh, no, it's Tzipora Livni.
She's ready.
She's in, you know, she's 90 percent in the polls a week away.
She's got it like, nope, she's got nothing.
What happened?
She didn't get in because I'm not following what CNN says or the media or alternative media or the people even on the boots on the ground.
I'm not following what I'm not looking at their stuff as the BL end all.
I'm listening to what they're saying, but I'm saying, no, it's not going to happen.
And guess what?
It didn't.
And they're only she's, you know, so so this is very powerful stuff once you understand it.
Also, as long as Israel has prime ministers, they will never be considered a righteous people.
And from discussing and having discussions with people in Israel, a lot of the negative stuff that you hear coming out of there just isn't true.
Like, I wouldn't say all of it, but a lot of it is not true.
Like, for example, years ago with the war with Lebanon, they had put they blamed Israeli troops for killing a few hundred Lebanese prisoners.
Now, that wasn't true.
What really happened?
And this is I spoke to one of the guards, the Israeli guards that was stationed there at that temporary holding area was that there was a group of Lebanese that pleaded with the Israeli guards to let in some more Lebanese.
And they ended up being a rival faction of Lebanese, the same people.
And they started killing their own people.
But then but internationally, it was the Israeli guards that killed them, you see.
Right.
So and this and there's a lot of stuff going on with the Palestinians, how there's all this oppression.
If you look at how much money the Palestinian Authority gets international aid and how much of it gets bought and distributed to the people, it's less than one percent.
The rest of it, the rest of it goes to buying the Palestinian Authority, uses it to the current Palestinian Authority, is it for personal investments?
So, you know, there's a lot of interesting stuff.
And also they breed in Palestine what they have, you know, how years ago in America they used to have the Pledge of Allegiance.
Right.
Well, in modern day, like the Gaza Strip and places like that, all the schoolchildren are pledged to kill an Israeli every morning or Israel will be doomed, you know, just just for the hell of it.
This is the pledge.
So you don't hear this stuff.
So it's very biased and skewed.
Now, I'm not for or against either one of those groups.
I'm just saying what I see and what can be said about it.
So they're not going to be known as righteous people as long as they've got prime ministers.
So as long as you see prime ministers in Israel, they're always always going to be the Zionism.
Oh, the Jews are faulty.
Oh, it's Israel or this or that.
And how much of that do you still hear?
Quite a bit.
It's not going to go away until another several prime ministers.
Now, the prime ministers have a term of roughly four years, but it is possible to exchange.
I think in the late 90s, they went through three prime ministers in four years to do it due to assassination illness and I think a short vote or something.
So you have quite a bit going on.
So anyway, I just want to recap that very benign verse in the first chapter of Isaiah, which states, when I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges and then you will be known as a righteous people.
How that is a very strong geopolitical prophetic statement hidden within a very benign language of that chapter.
So I just wanted to explain that.
I hope that makes sense.
It does.
And by the way, just to interject here, Reuven Rivlin is the president right now.
Right.
They do have a president.
He's not acknowledged like the prime minister, but they do have one.
Yes.
Reuben Rivlin, you said?
Yeah, Reuven Rivlin.
Rivlin.
OK, there you go.
But you see, why isn't he acknowledged as a top dog?
Because it's not it's not meant to be.
Because they're not ruled by the rule by judges, as it is prophetically, so.
So just a question.
Do you feel that the people of Israel have a grasp on this?
No.
Hold on.
No, no.
They're very censored on their own also.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there's some I do communicate with some people from Israel and, quote, unquote, you know, of that national heritage.
And what I've gotten from them is they've been discouraged their whole life to stay away from the Bible and just read the mystical writings like Talmudic stuff.
Really?
Yeah.
I've even read I've even met a rabbi's daughter in California, and I said, you know, I study scripture and all that.
She goes, you mean the Talmud?
I said, no, no, no, not the Talmud.
Scripture goes, well, I only know the Talmud.
I don't read the rest of it.
I don't read that Bible stuff.
No.
Wow.
OK, and also the highest percentage of atheists are in Israel right now.
If you were on a bus in Israel and you public bus or a public place and you said, well, how many of you are atheists?
About half the people would raise their hands.
Without thinking about it immediately.
I say really now, maybe it's about a third.
But I remember someone discussing this with me that was there in the 80s.
So that was clearly half.
But I think that was a third.
But still, that's very significant.
Yes.
They're under some heavy censorship still.
But now remember the point of this of them is, you know, I've listed before a various sundry list of what the how the gods work.
And one of the ways is if they give you too much information, you don't want to jump off this rock and be like them.
So they have to hide the information and limit it, but still have to make it accessible.
So what a better way to hide it and limit it by not giving it originally to some people that everyone is going to dislike.
So the moment you want to go and study it, they're going to say, oh, that's those people's book.
Oh, I don't want it, you know, because they're so unlikable.
You see, I'm glad that you brought something up.
I've got it.
I had a question.
And when you mentioned about Assyria, how much are they going to play?
Because they were a very hardy little warring machine.
Well, a very big, a very big part, because they they are.
It's important that they're geo geographically and geopolitically in place, which they are coming.
Right.
And then they're going to take land from Syria and Turkey.
But when they're in position, they they're they're going to satisfy a spiritual request also.
Also, the there's a figure that is going to be known as a world leader type in the near future.
He's about 20 right now, 19 or 20.
He was born around 1998.
He is of Assyrian extraction.
Right.
And I'm not saying the name, I'm not saying what, you know, the title is even biblically, but if you know what I mean, there's a world leader that's coming on the scene.
It's not going to be him explicitly.
He's going to have a group around him that's going to be very important in the late 2020s and pretty much be known as an international world leader.
And he is of Assyrian extraction.
So that is the importance there.
That is, you know, how can you be a world leader of Assyrian extraction and you and your country is in shambles or you don't have a country?
Right.
You see.
So that will be established for that reason and many others.
Because remember what when the Assyrians come together, they're also going to be reviving much of their culture.
Right.
Most most people now are not aware of their culture, who they are.
As a matter of fact, even today, if you if you discuss the Assyrians, people think you're talking about the Syrians.
They don't know about the Assyrians.
Yeah, they were a bad mofo crew when it came to war.
That was their industry.
You know how various countries have industry, their industry was war.
Yeah.
And I have.
Yeah, I have a personal, you know, statement, opinion, which I don't give much is that if they were not, let's say, eliminated as a group, as they were, they would.
I don't think there'd be anyone on the planet left today because they would just be munching everybody up.
They were they were bad.
Now, do you feel that they're going to come to the aid of Palestine?
No.
No, not at all.
What will happen if you want to get into a little bit more prophecy?
What will happen is with this, not the next prime minister, the current prime minister, not this one, not the next one, but the next one is going to heavily engage the modern day Philistines, which were which are the Palestinians at large.
And they're going to be completely expelled from the West Bank completely.
Most of them will perish because there's over 150 or 200,000.
The Gaza Strip will be expanded and that will become a legitimate nation of Palestine, you know, with a political.
And also when that happens and the prime minister that will be responsible for this will probably lose his life just like Samson did.
Oh, right.
Right.
And, you know, we're talking, you know, tens of thousands, if not 100,000 Palestinians being slaughtered over a very short period of time, matter of days or weeks.
Yeah.
And this is coming.
You know, this is, you know, I'm not I'm just stating what I've discovered is, you know, want to believe it or not, that's their prerogative.
But it's worth banking on and it's worth filing away for sure.
Banking on it, meaning you'll get interest on it later, you know, kind of thing.
I mean, because you'll be able to discuss what the results when these things start to begin, you will be recognizable.
Well, after all of this happens in the Gaza Strip is expanded and becomes a formal aspect of Palestine and Israel is more formalized.
Israel and Palestine will become extremely close allies to the point where they will be going into wars and doing squirmishes and battles together.
As allies.
Oh, yeah.
So it's going to be a major, major change.
But since 1989, on the Pope's work schedule, people have been used to very sudden major changes.
You know, if you discuss the the Iron Curtain and the Soviet Union in the summer of 1989 and you said, well, in the next few months, it'll completely go away and there will be no Iron Curtain by next year.
People will say, great, that sounds ridiculous because it took 30 or 40 years to put in place almost 50 years.
And there's no way it's going to just go away overnight, probably maybe and maybe in 20 or 30 years it will.
Well, what happened in 1989 in the fall?
Right.
It only took a few weeks.
So, yeah.
So, yeah, these sudden changes also with what's called 9-11, which is a small axial period.
People even use the term, the definition of an axial period regarding 9-11 accurately because they call it a post 9-11 world.
An axial period is a period that changes the entire world view.
Right.
That happened almost overnight.
I mean, if you told people what would you know, the the the apparatus that will be put in place on September 10th, 2001 on the Pope's work schedule, what would be in place in a month or two?
They said that will never happen.
But after that event, it did.
It was readily accepted.
Right.
So you're going to see quite a bit of that.
That's why I don't get attached on commenting on political things and views and stories.
I think I said recently, you know, people define the news as things that are changing.
Well, why don't why isn't there news about things that don't change?
Right.
Yeah.
So.
So anyway, I hope that I gave a little bit just to reiterate there's an explanation of how the geopolitical world is seen prophetically and simple, benign versus like the one you'll find in Isaiah, which is when I return you back into the land, I will restore to your former judges and then you'll be known as a righteous people.
I hope that gave a pretty clear explanation on how to attach that and read out of it.
What's going on with a very simple, benign verse like that.
And there are many other verses, actually, most of it of the scripture where you can hear Marcus prophetic as about things that need to be, you know, looked into so you could read out of it.
But I hope that it did.
It was very good.
When I listen to you and Seth talking about scripture and things, and he brought up how he's taken a week to two weeks on a on a small couple of verses or verse, I found myself doing that.
And just having you almost have to.
You almost have to run a lot of that stuff.
Well, you do in the beginning.
And then after a while, when you get an idea of the history, both past, present and future, because history is constantly happening, you know, the and you understand how the scripture is put together, you know, about a certain it's like explaining a Swiss watch.
You don't have to explain the chair and the and the and the floor and the ceiling lamp or anything like that.
When you read scripture, it's really talking about a clock.
Really, if you want it, that's another way to explain basically what you know, what's going to be happening to mankind, because they've already tried a life expectancy of a thousand years.
And that didn't work out.
That ended up with killing most people with a flood.
And they tried out, you know, leaving angelic beings and other demonic beings to communicate openly with men.
That didn't work out too well because then they had to, you know, confuse all the languages.
So they're like, you know, we're just going to batten this thing down.
We're still keep the some of the information out and we'll just make it distasteful.
Well, it harkens back to the statement you made one time about how the the battle was that matter could be corrupted.
And matter, matter or life, the creation could be corrupted because it was made of matter.
Right.
And, you know, how true, how true.
Well, it's about combining a certain combination shouldn't be done.
And anyone that's worked in even the co-academic chemistry labs, you know, they have certain acids and certain compounds in double or triple boxes, you know, not just on the shelf.
So, you know, but it's like, why is this thing in three boxes?
Well, so you're thinking, you know, as you're getting it out of all these containers, you got lots of time to think about it.
You know, what do you is this what you really want to reach for?
Right.
Yeah.
So there's certain kinds of acids that are extremely dangerous and things.
So so there's things like that.
There's attitudes, there's behaviors that are like that, that mankind engages in.
And see, now it's OK.
It seems it's being let out more because there's a the goddess religion has got a very heavy influence.
And what people don't understand when the spiritual realm now, or especially the past 2000 years, influences mankind, it's more hidden.
In other words, it's more covert.
You see, they don't that, you know, the people aren't going around and saying, well, I'm doing this because I'm a follower of the goddess religion.
They don't know what they're doing at all.
But if you understand how the characteristics of the goddess religion or the one that this is a particular malevolent one, you will see that this is as obvious as day that what's going on, the influence on society and individuals.
Yeah.
So, OK, so you think we had enough just for a short first little Skype deal?
You know, I think I'm I'm grateful again because you keep my curiosity on many things.
And I look forward to my my time of search.
Yeah.
Great.
And go back and read that that verse in what's called and ponder it and then, you know, keep stay on your toes.
You know, don't, you know, fall asleep behind the wheel, right?
It's like speed bumps, you know, just don't slow down when you see them.
Well, I'm I'm I'm very grateful.
Greek.
Same here.
Been very enlightening.
And I look forward to any time that you got a few minutes if you want to rub together, I'm available and can fire this bad boy up anytime you want.
OK.
Looking forward to it, then.
All right.
Well, we'll call it.
That's it for now.
And we'll we'll do it again soon.
You take care.
Thank you.
You're welcome.