Alrighty, folks, and we're back.
And let's see.
Yep, we're good to go, Greg.
We did have another question.
I had another curious, just in the future, will the actual location of the temple be recognized?
Well, if there's a temple on it.
Pretty close, huh?
And then also some talk about vegetation later on the earth.
Not sure what it was.
Let's go back to the temple.
That's an interesting one, because obviously, prophetically and historically, what they're calling the Maha Sharif, or whatever they want to call it, Mount Moriah, or, you know, Golden Dome, all these various terms to explain.
And the place where all the religious, quote unquote, Jews are banging their heads against and all that, that's not the temple by far, right?
Because prophetically we know because it's standing, you know, prophecies in two places say that one stone will be on another, meaning an official stone.
Another place, an older prophecy said that Jerusalem will be plowed like a field.
They'll try to run a plow into those 20 or 40 ton blocks.
Also, there's the work of Ernest L.
Martin and two other men.
Actually, I have them in my notes way back here.
If I could find them, I'd try to bring them up.
I emailed them to myself.
I don't know by the time I get to that.
I think Bollinger was another one.
And another guy, let me see if I can remember from memory, it was about two months ago, a guy in the 30s who talked about it.
Anybody, well, you might be able to look it up.
He wrote about a little thin book about how the temple became known as the temple today, you know, which it's not.
So the actual location is, I think I've done once on chat, I did a somewhat of a...
Some type of discovery, yeah.
Something was going to be discovered there.
Where the Ark of the Covenant?
The Ark of the Covenant, yes.
I don't want to get into that.
It's really unofficial, but that's the most likely place.
And there's laundry hanging over it now.
In the Google Earth, you can see where it is.
And why?
Because it's opposite the Giheung Spring.
And that's the true location.
And all those large stones, well, the foundation stone that they find way deep by the Giheung Spring is not from the Citadel, the original Citadel.
Actually, it could be, but it is also one of the footing stones for the temple itself.
It's actually not even a footing stone.
Let me retract that statement.
It's part of the bedrock.
You see, the reason why the bedrock was cut in a way is to accept the stones, and they think it was cut that way to accept the Citadel, but it was, and it wasn't.
It was a threshing floor.
So, that's the location of the historical temple.
Now, if you read the Book of Zechariah, Zechariah says that in the latter days the temple was built on the highest mount.
Now, if you're in Jerusalem, and if you ever look at photos looking down at Mount Moriah where the Golden Dome is, it's from the Mount of Olives.
It's higher.
So, some people, including Martin, said that it's going to be built on the Mount of Olives.
There's a problem with that, though.
You're going to have to exhume all the dead bodies that are buried there.
They're going to have to go down to bedrock.
Now, I don't know if they're going to go down to bedrock on the Mount of Olives.
So, I would suggest one of the things, other than, well, several things have to happen for the location of the temple.
One is to acknowledge where it was lawfully.
Two, the other thing is the Gihon Spring needs to be gushing.
That's what it means.
Gihon means to gush forward a sufficient amount of water.
And the other thing is, again, the third thing is to not be on top of any buried bodies, dead bodies, right?
Now, the interesting thing, the location of the City of David goes right up against that location, and there is a very, very high good chance, if you understand the renovations that were done to the temple by Herod II, that King David was buried very close to the southern wall of the Temple Mount, where it was.
So, to rebuild it in that same location, they have to almost admit to the discovery of an access way to David's tomb.
And by the way, where they say David is buried is not where he's buried, but that's okay, too, at this point, because we know it's accurate.
So, there's a few little, I would say, mild conundrums, both political, religious, and archaeological, that have to be overcome if the temple were to be built where it was originally, Solomon's Temple and onward.
And the conundrum to be overcome over the Mount of Olives is that they're going to have to go down to Bedrock at some point.
Now, geologically, if anyone wants to do a study, how high does the Bedrock come up into the Mount of Olives, I'm not aware if it does.
And also, there's no water source there.
Now, with modern technology, of course, with pumps and pipes, they could bring it there, but they could have also, back then.
So, that's all I can say, officially and unofficially, about the temple.
Okay.
And, you know, in one sitting, I should say, or a 15-minute sitting, I should say.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
What was the other question?
The vegetation layer on the earth.
And I know you've alluded to this before, which is always an interesting topic unto itself.
Well, that's what rotates the earth.
It's an archetypical…it's an ethereal archetype, let's just say.
And what's interesting, just like any texture, when you look at…you've heard me discuss plants or valves, valving systems.
Right.
Trees.
Yeah, trees, grass, you know, monocots, diacots, and on.
They exchange terrestrial and atmospherical, you know, terrasphere and atmosphere energies.
The ethereal texture, meaning geometry that they have, because there's a geometry to it, is the various plants that you see, and the various purposes that the plants have.
But the actual rotation…see, all the planets have that vegetative layer.
That's what rotates them towards the star.
And, you know, I think just to recap, like a plant, the dark side wants to go to the light, and when it gets into the light it overcharges, but it still has a dark side, which wants to rotate.
So, you know, when it rotates to the light it overcharges, doesn't want to be in the light, but the side behind it wants to be in the light, and that's how it keeps it moving seemingly perpetually, as long as there is a star or a sun.
So, let's just…let's throw this out here unofficially.
If you're a real son of a bitch, and you want to really stuff the Earth, just figure out how to put a real light source on the dark side of the Earth, you know, when it's nighttime, for a minute, about three hours, and you see what happens to the rotation of the Earth.
Yeah.
What do you think will happen?
It'll stop.
I would think it'll stop, yeah.
Yeah, so let's say you get into an object…get into a train or a car, moving at a thousand miles an hour, and stop it abruptly.
What do you think is going to happen to everything inside?
You know, this goes back to something you mentioned one time about the day that the Earth stood still, when time moved backwards.
Yeah.
What does that bring a whole different…
It's very simple to stop the planet from rotating.
And I shouldn't be speaking like this, but I'll do another 30 seconds of it.
Technologically, it's not difficult to do right now.
Right.
I just want to bring that up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so, okay.
So the vegetative layer is just about that.
It's an ethereal component.
And when I say ethereal, it's what you, you know, let's just tie it back to simple things.
But how much you know about the human body, or anything that's alive, you know, back to the human body, let's say, ask any scientist or contemplative person, what allows you to stand up from your chair and walk across the room?
How do you do that?
Yeah, they're only going to give you descriptions if you're some kind of hydraulic electrical machine.
They cannot define life, where the life force, how it's being imbued on living things.
Right.
And how it's being used.
Yeah, and once you start to explain it rationally, and how you can also not only explain it, you're ready for this?
You can access it.
Oh boy, just explaining it to these people, meaning you know who these people are, whoever they are.
They get like Wilhelm Reich said, they're emotionally armored, and they get very nervous, some of them get very aggressive, some of them just start laughing, some of them go into ridicule, everyone has their own expression of this, of this, you know, you're getting in too deep now, you know, they're, you know, it's affecting them.
Stop, stop, stop.
Yeah, the discussion part you know once you show for you know you're usually not going to get to the point but some people can take that discussion and then if you get to the point where you can access that field that then you weed out the other group again because they just freak out I've had.
Well, I'll say this again officially I was doing an experiment once, and had a guy who was getting this is not let me just give you a little background on who this person was.
I didn't like talking about it, but he was getting his permitting for demolitions.
Right.
And it was in working with high speed chemistry if you know what I mean.
And he was a consultant and all this so this is not someone who's squeamish or, you know, he makes things go boom, you know, mountain sides buildings bridges over.
That's what he does.
Anyway, we're on the roof of a building.
And one story and you know how you put like a painters ladder like a 20 foot ladder on the side of it.
So I'm doing experiment.
So just look at this part of the atmosphere right here you ready watch this, and I did something.
And he just froze and he ran down the ladder you know how you turn around and face the ladder and go down.
Yeah, well he didn't run down the ladder that way he ran down forward.
Like it was a pair of steps or something.
Yeah, yeah, he missed the last five.
I mean the last five or six steps he couldn't and he ran and all I heard was the key in the ignition and the car took off.
What the hell do you do to him?
Right, because just but you know so well it well I just explained emotionally.
He could handle the discussion but when it came time to showing it to him he couldn't handle.
Now can you imagine going down a painter's ladder on the side of a building.
Yeah, not turning around, falling down.
You're not going to do well but he made it and it took off.
Okay, so, and this is not just you know quote unquote a sissy of a, you know, this is someone who's works on the edge.
Well no actually he was he, he worked for government blowing stuff up.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah.
And my work you know minds you know anyone, you work for it.
Yeah, he was a demolition guy right and you know, so, yeah, you don't know and then you know you'll have like a 13 year old or, you know, a 15 year old, you know, whatever you know watching and you're like oh that's the coolest thing I've ever seen.
Right, you know or an eight year old you know it's the coolest thing I've ever seen.
Right.
So, so discussing this archetypal acts well discussing it is good if you can have discussion, or the audience.
Then when you go to the next level, where you can demonstrate it that then you weed out that audience again further.
See, so this is a topic that is tricky let's just go to another aspect of it.
Okay, this is real stuff you know you can surround objects moving objects with it right.
Okay, so what do you think if you did a demonstrate you know how you have companies that make ballistic that's right.
You know that companies that make things to, you know, ballistics.
Right.
Well, can you imagine, pulling up and doing a demonstration where you shoot a tennis ball through the side of the house, using, you know, this type of concept tennis ball through the side it goes right through.
Okay, now, now, that's just tennis but imagine if that was a military great armament what he could do.
Right, right.
That house in the next house in the next house in the next house.
And, well, do they want that kind of stuff.
They say they do but when you show it to them they don't want it.
Right.
So, same with it.
Let's say you have a jet of water shooting out of hose, you know, garden hose or something what you might go 2530 feet up in the air.
If you got a lot of pressure you.
Oh, maybe a little bit more that's a lot you know what could you imagine you know surrounding building a device just a passive around the water jet that makes it go 200 feet, the same pressure the same.
Right.
What does that do your physics and your laws of physics and you see because now you're working with primary stuff right that's why I keep discussing with the bot life force what do you, what do you see that all living things have in common there.
Well they're tightly wrapped they don't leak too much and if they look they do it deliberately right or there if they're injured they'll leak right right.
What do all things have in common to maintain a slight sub pressure.
Right, you know plant has a slight vacuum and cut it you know it.
Right.
Your body has a vacuum in it you know when you soften the skin.
It shrivels up.
See, the Earth's atmosphere.
Even though it has a positive pressure we measure it in kilobars or one bars 15 psi whatever 15 point whatever.
And, but it actually represents a slight vacuum compared to outer space but physically, possibly not because they might say well space is a vacuum if it's a vacuum why doesn't it suck the atmosphere into space and make the atmosphere and ability.
See, so the atmosphere is on a slight vacuum compared.
This is totally radical I don't even want to go on record saying this kind of stuff that tonight is the unofficial Greek speak right right because it's like proof.
Well you know that's that's like the guy running down the ladder forward you know facing forward you know and not making it, you know, so, or stopping the planet, you know, but just by putting a, you know, if you put a small satellite with a small nuke and a reflector gets enough to anyway.
Yeah.
So the idea is, and also the maybe like the size of a gumball drop right and we're not talking about, you know what you guys more people are used to thinking.
So the point here is this kind of talk.
Well most of the Greeks because not for this society right because number one, it's, it doesn't go along with people are aware of.
Number two, it sounds too outlandish and to like you like you were, it sounds like it's beyond our ability, right and that's not none of this stuff is.
So I keep saying well you know the easiest way to really say this is not the kind of talk for this kind of society but what you can do is you know that's why most of the time I do speak I try to bring forward.
What is the simplest that you can do for yourself right now or someone next to you that you have to buy anything.
And you can add you don't have to go you know just just do it right now it's you can access it immediately.
That's why we discuss.
I've given some hints on chat and other privately on weather ops and things like that how to do it.
Also, you know, that's why I always discuss eating seasonally the bodies of vacuum, understand lymphatic system understand the vacuum in the body.
These are things you can access right away.
So, what does that have to do with tying it back to the vegetarian layer of each planet.
Because when you say that VEG prefix veg you know people are thinking you know green stuff stuff that grows when you water it and light.
Yeah, yeah, that's, that's, that's what's also behind that.
But this is a similar type of ether that's behind us as well but it's not us.
It's inverted because we're like upside down plants right.
The head is the is the root ball.
The limbs are like the limbs and the genitalia is the flower so we're like walking around on Earth upside down right so it shows you archetypal relationship.
We have a different type of ether that we tap into, but the planet itself.
You know when you look at plants and vegetation you know there's air ferns that just require light, water them we actually, I was, you know, given some recently in the pool I was like okay let's just try it out and they look the same like they did, you know, when I got them.
So, just air for so the light aspect is very important so if you're going to sum up the vegetative layer of any planet.
It is dependent on light, and it is a dynamic layer and it's a, it's.
Well it seems to encompass these solid objects we call planets and Earth, you know.
So, and the sun is a different story I think I dropped an image in Tango that I did from a screenshot from the ISS, about two years ago where they were pointing a camera at something that's the full sun.
And when they snapped another camera didn't have the diffraction lens and you see there's no sun there, except for the little slither that goes through the atmosphere, right, can that they were saying they're showing it will had a deflection lens on it first shows the sun, because you know, but the courts camera that they switched to didn't have it and you see, obviously, with visible light, there is no sun, and I caught.
And that was, I posted that I think you posted on a dropbox.
Yeah.
Okay, so, so there's many aspects to this vegetative layer meaning it's a part of the ether.
What do we say ether right, can it be defined well it can only be defined as well as you can comprehend it through accessing it and under and seeing evidence, you don't you'll never see the ether you'll never see the vegetative layer.
You just see its effect it's kind of like the.
You don't see the wind you just see the dust and the you know the, the furniture being blown over or whatever.
So if you study the effects of the thing you'll never really know exactly, but you know consistently what it takes are you learn more about the thing kind of like the bear.
We don't know what air is but we know about it.
Right.
So that's as much as I could say about the vegetative layer without, you know, getting too outlandish I don't think about it too much in itself, but, yeah.
It's okay.
So, we had a fellow that this may seem somewhat simple but keeping an open mind please consider that this topic what's, what's there to look forward to.
Is that it.
Well, one way to look at it is what's behind you.
You know, in other words, you know the concept of stacking you know when you get to the top it's the top thing or the current part of the stack is based on what's below it right so what came before.
What's the opposite of for backward what have you seen behind you.
And do you want to is is that the is that the way that it's going to go.
Otherwise the simple answer that is, you better learn to understand what's coming and see how you can fit yourself into it.
No, there's not much to look forward to.
In the moment, or the next year or five or even a decade.
I think the thing to look forward to is what comes after this incarnation.
And that's not being escapist or defeatist.
I'm just saying, most people are going to be in for a good surprise or a big surprise about it.
You could be terrorized for a little while there but when you do find out.
But again, the simple that sounds it's a pretty broad question I see the question now.
It just depends on what you've seen before.
You know, a simple example is like, you know, this show that people will come back from the military that are shell shocked the call PTSD.
See because the bankers.
If you're going to put a hospital or medical institution and monetize everything.
You can't monetize shell shock but they can monetize PTSD.
One thing you'll know if it's being monetized it's always an acronym.
Because you know when they monetized the states you know it went from New York to and why.
We went from Montana to M.O. whenever you see these abbreviations.
No, that just means it's being monetized when you see abbreviations like that.
Yeah.
So, so my point here is what is a person that is like that the shell shock or PTSD just got back from some conflict.
What do they have to look forward to?
Right.
Well, what about someone who's been locked in the basement for a year beaten and raped every day and finally they get let out.
What do they have to look forward to?
You see you ever notice from the point I'm trying to make it.
How much of an influence does one past have on what they're looking forward to.
Right.
Yeah.
You know, what about you see what if you grew up in the lap of luxury.
What do you have to look forward to.
All right, what else to see living I see another question.
Living by example I show my young children a life living more lawfully is more and more set apart from society at large, but the little ones just want to have fun and be like everyone else, especially in the somewhat challenging time of the year.
So, yeah, but that's, that's a tough one but you have to realize it from depends.
There are many ways to look at it.
Yeah, your boots on the ground is a military analogy.
You have the boot on the ground in a foreign place then you have the, you know, the paratroopers that haven't landed yet they're up high right there flying over and then you have the ones in a completely different world a different nation looking at it.
You could look at it for me on a three ways those three ways.
If you feel like your boots on the ground amongst it, it's tough.
If you comprehend for example that this is what the gods the gods have blinded them and the gods have decided this is what they should do.
Think about it from a primacy point of view.
And also, by the way, just one thing I want to bring up.
There's an interesting separation you know when we say about setting ourselves apart, and all this right.
We're not better when you set yourself apart and you want to be lawful you're not better than the ones that are not set apart or unlawful.
Yeah, you inherently better but you know what your behavior is better.
Your, your spirit is better.
You see what I mean?
Exactly.
What makes you better off is not very tangible or material.
It's like when you ask someone, what does it take to walk across the room they can't answer other than a meme.
You're this world, we're not any better off than they are.
So think about that for a moment.
You're not any better off.
And children are better.
And children at that age, especially young, are easily distracted.
I know that giving them the truth for what they can handle for their tender years is a good thing.
But at the same time, you can distract and take them on to the path where you want them to go.
This is also, yes, but this is personal in a way also meaning that each individual is personal.
Like for example, I was communicating with someone for years, and I finally met them.
They had with them someone who had accompanied them that had also been with them for years, and I was shocked to find out that the person that was with them didn't know any of this stuff.
Like this person initially wanted to be more lawful and set apart, but they didn't share anything with the people around them.
So when I spoke to the acquaintance of this person, they didn't know anything.
I was like, wow.
So what I found out was your ability to verbalize this or communicate this is what the whole situation is dependent on.
Right.
True.
So if you – depends on how you defend it or apologetic means to defend or to edify, to educate.
That's a very, very, very, very personal thing.
Like there are some people that want to be set apart and lawful and change their ways, but they can't communicate it in a way to the people around them, whether they're siblings or brother, sister, parent, children, friends, neighbors.
They can't communicate it, and whatever they do, it comes out wrong.
Or either the people don't understand or they get upset or they just pass it off.
I can relate to that.
There are other people that can communicate it in a way, and the people around you understand it, and they'll either make a choice to do it as well or just respect your space about it.
So it depends on – it's two things.
It's how you can communicate it, and it's also the setting of the people around you.
And believe it or not, both of those are beyond your – for example, the concept of faith.
If it is meant for you to poorly communicate this, and if it is meant by the gods for the people around you to poorly accept it, so you have such a hard time that it's part of building up your character, so be it.
Yeah, yeah.
But I would always suggest, especially if you read in later parts of what they call the New Testament, there are a lot of tips there and hints given on how to be a good communicator.
What to do when you're asked.
What to do when you're in a situation.
You see?
Right.
It seems philosophical.
It seems about love, but it's not.
It's about how to communicate what's going on or what you're trying to do or say.
Right.
You see?
So remember, these are – this is a time where also people are very ignorant.
Like, for example, if you go back into the – what they call the Middle East 3,000, 4,000 years ago, or let's say 2,000, 3,000 – everyone there, everyone around knew Yahweh.
If you said Yahweh, they all knew who it was.
Mm-hmm.
If you said Moloch or Baal or Asherah or any of the – everyone knew what it was.
Everyone.
I mean, I shouldn't say everyone, but it was very, very, very common.
Commonplace, yes.
Yeah.
Now, if you say any of those things in modern society, they'll go, what?
Say, what?
Oh, I might have heard that.
What is that?
So how are you going to – you see?
Right.
They don't understand the concept of lawfulness.
They think legal.
The attorney – they're all – this is the children of Satan.
Sorry.
Because if you – in Scripture it mentions a few places that you're a child of a certain spirit, right?
Mm-hmm.
Or the son does the will of a father, right?
So whosever will you're doing, meaning not biologically, but through information or guidance or law, that's your father.
Or spiritually.
So the majority of the people right now on Earth or all societies, their father is the adversary or Satan.
Right.
Wow.
See?
Yeah.
So that's – and the concept of spiritual father is pretty universal.
People can grasp that, but they don't grasp what's going on.
So what's interesting about that is, yeah, it's cosmic censorship.
It's ignorance.
It's what was meant to happen.
But believe it or not, just like the cruise ship, remember, you can't change the ship.
But you can change what you're doing and maybe those around you to a certain degree, right?
But the thing is with the children, you can catch – here's some advice, and I do give advice.
It's usually good.
Otherwise, I tend to refrain from it.
Children are in a position.
They're like – you've heard they're like sponges, and they have their play time.
They have their sleep time.
They have their – the times, the disciplines, like brush your teeth and all that.
They understand a routine.
And also you have to understand the children themselves.
Personally, they're all different.
When do they have their learning time?
Because you'll see children will come and ask you sometimes.
They're genuinely on their own.
They want to know.
So when you understand their learning time, when that is, then you come in with some history, you see.
And believe it or not, even at that point, saying like Santa is bad or evil and this is good or whatever, the child gets mixed emotions because he wants to expand his sphere of influence socially.
He already has his other friends.
He wants to fit in.
He's going to be confused.
Yeah.
So the thing is a really good history lesson and maybe the broaching on how actually Greeks speak, believe it or not.
I don't want to recommend it to children because I think I try to keep most of the things that I say on sonic events clean enough for a mother-in-law, let's say, to hear.
I know my grandson is fascinated with your sonic episodes.
But also I do use some terms, but that's okay because if you're carnally minded and you find that it's done in the wrong way, then it's not for you.
But the intent is to just be straightforward.
Because here's the thing.
I've said this before.
The higher the criminality, the harsher the language.
Right.
So anyway, I really this is a difficult position with children.
But on the other hand.
The history lesson isn't bad to know, though.
The history, yeah.
Because you have to also know their time.
You know, it's a two-way.
You know when they're hungry.
They'll have a little time in their day when they want to learn or when it's acceptable to learn.
Also, there's many ways.
Actually, I don't like to recommend it, but I'll have to in this case with children.
Especially if you could find something that's clean and short on the rectangle a university something that's what the history of, you know, these Christianity or these holidays is you could show them that, you know, just something because, you know, there's children are still fascinated by the rectangle.
So, and also what part of the world are you in the person who's asking the question, because that makes a big difference you know like if you're in Spain, or Italy or Portugal.
You know parts of your forget it, you know, that's actually if you speak out against anything that's going on out there might even give you a fine.
The state jail time.
Yeah, it's pretty harsh.
So, if you're in the Bible Belt, it's just as bad socially or culturally.
But they won't you won't be fine.
Yeah, yeah.
So hopefully you're not in Spain or Italy or, you know, parts of their find you their Greek they'll find you down there.
Yeah, or the Bible Belt if you then you'll be a little a little better.
Yeah, yeah, they'll find you.
Those are very ungodly Yeah, what do you mean the fight will find well you know when when you're speaking out against the Bible down in the Bible Belt, they will find you.
Oh no no not against the Bible against the culture against the Bible.
No, they're the ones speaking out against.
There.
There, you know how the scripture the scripture says that they're hard headed stubborn.
Oh yeah.
What was it?
Well, that's another thing.
Yeah, wouldn't head it's not a scripture but yeah, but how they they're, they're stubborn they want to do things that way not the way the gods want it.
Right.
That's exactly if you ask any Christian or really why they do this the way we do it.
That's the way we do it.
Yeah.
Okay, so they're inconsiderate.
So, yeah.
What else you got.
Last thing there.
That was about the full extent of that one there.
Okay, am I coming through okay or no just a just a slight interruption here and there.
You're still audible and but I noticed a little fluctuation.
I thought you might been out in the garden again.
No, I mean, I have a motor that needs to be damped out and I think it's giving us at EMF.
Okay, put a capacitor across it.
You know what I mean to dampen out a little.
Yeah.
What do we get a little bit of Genesis talk how to stop the planet from rotating.
Yeah, you've been all over the map, but there was quite a lot of enlightenment shared again.
And yeah, what a wealth, but a wealth of information.
And we're about just a just about the two hour mark again.
Nice and fast that goes well.
Okay, this is something that folks slide, you know, this ad-libbing or, you know, there's just having a conversation is the way we've been doing it for a while, you know, back when I was on a Friday.
I was had the maybe this naive desire or whatever to actually put something together like, you know, like, you know how tonight up the official story of the Parthians the unofficial story about the Magi and all that, you know, what about actually if I dig into some notes and go back and find what and just put it all together and make a list and actually talk about it, like, you know, I find it gets more pedantic, but I'll try not to be pedantic because I'm going to do it the way I do it.
You know, I think I'm, you know, but, you know, instead of burying people with all the details when if you're, you know, just because people if you think it's important is going to want to sit there with a notepad.
So blurry in the head is good because if you keep it simple, the you remember it as a story and you remember it as just a general juxtaposition of the matter, without going too many details but again just to cross over and what I've seen in chat.
My fellow I do appreciate his support also about doing the I opened the mouth and said to do this would take about eight hours, at least actually more than the extra if you're going to do Genesis it could take you a month of oratory events, but I think eight hours is a good amount to cover the various things that are going on in the in Genesis.
What is how it was compiled and evidence, just citing evidence of it being true is, I can do that right now, by the way, just like I gave, for example, the, when you do a search you want to know what's going on put in Middle East and past 24 hours on a browser.
So, you go, you don't have to go look at whatever they're in front of you more control.
Here's interesting thing to have.
You know how I mentioned, I think I put this in chat this week also.
The interesting thing about Scripture other than the prophets, which is mostly prophecy, or third you know straight up.
It's going to give you the geography of the place going to give you the people.
It's going to give you where you know when it happened, right, based on you know what came before.
And why the people what they're doing and why they're doing it and what the outcome is always it seems to be the case ever mystery about that.
Right.
So, what's interesting about that when you piece that together when you go through something like Genesis let's say you have a fleeting thought of finding out for example, Joseph.
Okay, did he exist.
Well, what you do is you go find archaeology right in Egypt.
Look, it did you know just do a basic search I haven't done this did archaeological proof that Joseph of the Bible existed, and see what you come up.
And there, it's there, you know, it should be there there's a statuettes and names and, you know, things and descriptions that have been found, you know, archaeological proof of Moses, you know, and that's a hard one because they.
The, a lot of people can't decide on, you know, a 500 year period or 30 year period.
It's down to I've got it down to less than a hundred year period of when it was and I posted that information.
A week ago, you know who was the fair, and other.
Yeah, so go look for that I mean, you can go look at.
Right.
So, so that means that if you, if you have a fossil, or a lump of coal or some, something that has carbon 14, still in it, it means it's less than 100,000 or less than 6000 years old.
Right, so you know all these dinosaur fossil carbon 14 of them right.
So, that means they have to be less than 80,000, and definitely I mean definitely less than 80, 100,000, and definitely and usually hovering around the five to 6000 mark right but you know obviously.
No one knows about these simple facts on carbon 14 and they get it you know that's why the scientific community is getting away with the agenda that they are.
Right, so you're going to have to also have a little bit of this and a little bit of that, you know, like, because you'll see you can, you're going to come across mass spectrography mass spectrometry carbon 14 dating.
So get familiar with archaeological terms that's one thing I've never really stressed and I'm not going to stress it but if you want to get familiar with dating scientific dating, and that doesn't mean dating a scientist because you're not going to get invited to good parties anyway.
Right.
You're, you know, looking at these basic terms so they don't you know pull wool over your eyes and, you know, with the agenda that's out in the world.
So, remember, the, the flip over was like before King James if you were caught with a Bible you were killed.
Right, unless you were meant to have one.
And then after King James basically that killed the Bible.
You want to look, and then don't believe all the stuff that came before the Jiva and all these other things, but that it, no they were translations either but I'm just saying that it was allowed in a certain capacity that just, you know, it's still not allowed.
Right.
So, so, well, also you're not really going to get much out of what's called the Bible unless you find yourself a particular if you're reading what's called the scriptures or the Bible let's say King James or anything, and you're particularly interested in a particular book or a particular time period, focus on that you must go back to the original languages or the language of preservation you must do that.
And then dig around some more and get familiar with archaeological technical terms, so you can understand, you know, whether you're being lied to or not, you know, because if someone says, this is dated at 5 million years and it's carbon dated to that point you're like, that's bullshit, because carbon dating doesn't go back to 87.
You see, very few people know that, right?
Right.
And they don't even know what it is.
So just look into it a little bit, and various basic chores, I call it mind chores, you know, it just goes as simple as how did you feel when you first discovered what the word nice really means.
Right, right.
Shocked.
You felt smarter now, yeah, all those things, the shock value.
So there's a shock value in all of these things because, again, as we started the conversation tonight, if you're going to study any of the ancient writ, especially the scripture, I am telling you for sure there is nothing you can bring that you already have that will help you understand that, you know, from what you've been told about it meaning.
Right, right.
You know, from church, Sunday school parents, movies, TV, or even your own study.
Well, it's a lot of deprogramming too, you know, you've got to get away from it.
Yeah, let's go to the Sherlock Holmes kind of scenario.
You can have 100 investigators going in and out of a crime scene room, 100 of them, it doesn't mean anything.
Sherlock Holmes will go into the room and look at all the things that everyone's missing.
Not with a microscope or underneath something but right there in front of everyone you see.
So what is right in front of you that no one is paying attention to, or they acknowledge that it's there only after you bring it up but they can't go any deeper than that.
So let's see, one more thing popped up.
Could you do some talk about the trees Greek, the meaning of them?
Oh, trees, they're vowels actually.
What's interesting about trees is they're nuclear power plants.
They have the ability to take the energy from mineral and water in their environment and light and turn it into cellulose or starch.
You know, there's a tremendous amount of voltage going through them.
That's what, you know, you know, ether is heat, light, electricity.
Let's see what else.
Now you sort of valve in the valve between the ether in the air and in the earth.
It's just like it's an ethereal.
It's an ethereal valve.
Yes, hold on.
It's always going between the terrorist fear in the atmosphere.
Right.
And that's why when, when, when the earth gets, when the earth is discharging, it's summertime.
Everything blooms, shoots out.
You hear, you know, shooting out in the spring.
And the winter time, it shuts down because the earth gave up everything.
And now it's the sky's time to be down on the earth.
You ever notice that the sun is always hotter in the winter than it is in the summer?
I didn't say hotter.
I said harsher.
Right.
Sunlight is harsher.
There's like a sting to it.
Right.
Like, you know, if you have the sun in your eyes in the summer, let's say you're being in a motorized engine driven wagon down the street.
You could, you know, but in the wintertime, if you see the sun in your eyes, you've got to put on glasses or the visor.
It blinds you more.
Yeah.
So very simple.
But trees are the more robust form or more robust manifestation of this archetype of a plant.
And of course, you also have to consider that they're under a vacuum because they're alive also.
You know, completely sealed.
Right.
Yeah.
We were doing bimetal experiments where we were getting voltage from a tree.
It was an interesting thing.
That brings me back to Stubblefield and the story that was left with him one time where he was wrapping cables around the root of a tree and brought it into where it was two plates.
And this is something concerning his death, of course.
And it was basically a story that's been told out there.
There's no real good hard evidence of any of it.
But he was generating heat.
That's right.
Well, it's part of the ether.
Yeah.
You could generate light.
You can generate electricity.
You could generate heat.
It's just some force.
He had some interesting.
Well, he's friends with Tesla back in the day.
Yeah.
He preceded Tesla.
Yes, he did.
You're a fascinating boy, he is.
Is that T-Bender?
Is that more talk on trees?
Yep, that was T-Bender.
It was a little bit of a delay to catch to him.
Yeah.
And then, of course, to consider the shape of the tree is based on its altitude.
If you look at the low near sea level savanna type tree, it's shrub-like, flat top, broad.
They could be large, but they're typically not very tall and broad.
And as you go higher in altitude, the trees become more round and taller.
And as you go even higher, they get taller and skinnier, right?
As you go higher in altitude.
I think it's a hyperbolic relationship with trees.
You know what a hyperbolic, parabolic curve looks like?
A hyperbolic, it looks like a straight line, and then it very quickly starts to curve out.
So if you take two hyperbolic curves and just turn it upside down so the point of the hyperbolic is at the top and the funnel, open funnel, is at the bottom, based on altitude, logarithmically, the trees fit exactly in that hyperbolic curve.
So an upside down funnel is wide at the bottom and pointy at the top, right?
Right.
So you notice when you go to the higher altitude trees, the trees are very pointy and almost vertical, and just a little bit wider at the bottom, like a funnel, upside down funnel.
And as you go towards the middle of the funnel before the opening, you have more of a rounder tree.
It's still tall and almost vertical.
It's wider actually in the middle, not at the bottom, you know?
And then when you get down to the savanna, the bottom where the funnel is open, the tree is very low and squat and very broad at the bottom.
You see?
Yeah.
So the etherical movement, as they say, is a vortex, but it takes a hyperbolic form.
Shawberger talked about the hyperbolic form of a vortex.
If you look at the vortex, you know, it looks like a margarita glass, kind of, right?
Very wide at the top and then it curves and then it suddenly becomes very narrow and continues to get narrower as it goes.
And then the trees in Africa, of course, you know, their plumage is very spread out at the base.
Right, and they're lower altitude, typically.
Yeah.
This is like, you know, there's also the ability to transplant them.
Like you could be down in the savanna somewhere and plant an evergreen.
But I'm speaking of where you find them without a cross.
I mean, I mean, trees can't get up and walk away, but you have to plant them somewhere else.
You know, just like you find prickly cactus and cactus in the desert, but it originated, you'll find it in the rainforest as well.
If anyone goes trekking through the rainforest, you'll be walking around all these, you know, huge banana leaves.
And you'll say, well, it's this, a prickly cactus.
Wow, I haven't seen that since the last time I was in the desert.
You know, what's it doing here?
You know, well, the other way around.
It started off there, you see.
And then migrating birds pooped out some seeds, perhaps, or it was brought over.
Or possibly it could have been more of a rainforest condition, and those are the ones that survived the desert.
Yeah, that's true, too.
Tree of Knowledge.
Well, that is an actual tree, but it is not a tree that you find on Earth.
Is that Tree of Knowledge, and what could be explored there?
Well, it's a knowledge of good and evil.
In Hebrew it would be etz yadah tov, and what's the word for evil?
But, yeah, so it shows you how much Hebrew I've been reading lately.
That would be another really great subject, Hebrew, and what the letters mean when you're putting a word together.
Yeah, learn the letters and then put them together.
Tree is etz, knowledge is yadah, and good is tov, and I forgot the word for evil.
It's not temay, it's something else.
But I just need to see it, and I'll remember it for the next six months, and then I'll forget it.
Unless I go back and read, you know.
It's kind of like, let's say you visited a country and you lived there for a little while, then you left, and a few years later you're trying to remember how conversational you were.
It kind of hurts the brain a little.
But nonetheless, the Tree of Knowledge of good and evil is an actual tree, but you have to remember where it was, right, and also who, where, and the Tree of Knowledge of good and evil, as the Tree of Life, were both in a very extraordinary place, which is also mentioned in other places of Scripture, by the way, if people had first-hand accounts of it.
You know, it's mentioned as if people had first-hand, or heard it from someone who had a first-hand account.
It was a very good account.
I'll leave the homework for someone else.
If someone else wants to get into that in Scripture, they'll be interested.
Yeah, you'll be shocked to see who else is talking about it.
So, I'm not shocked, but it'll start to put things in perspective.
Not only the tree, but the garden and all these other things.
So, you'll say, wait a second, I've read this before, how come I didn't read it, right?
Well, you're not looking.
Are you really seeing it, or are you really looking at it?
You're either hearing or listening.
Yeah, I wasn't there the last time I read this, right?
So, knowledge of good and evil was what was reserved for the gods, right?
Remember?
Right.
And also, knowledge of good and evil is wisdom.
Right?
Like, you know, people in the legal movement say, well, you have no first-hand experience.
That's no good.
I'm like, that's bullshit.
You know, you see these fingers?
You know why I have them?
Because I know that blunders are dangerous.
I don't need to put my hand in there to prove it.
You see, that's why I still have these hands, right?
So, you know, there's only so much, you know, that's the wisdom.
The idiot will put his fingers in there and wisdom in the blender, and the wise will say, no, I don't have to put my fingers in there to know that will chop them off, you see?
So, that's where wisdom, because how do we know there was wisdom in it?
Because the scripture says that Eve saw that it had wisdom.
There's no apple, by the way.
You know, there's no, the fruit is the, is the, what it gives off.
You ever heard, by the fruit you'll judge them, right?
Right.
There's metaphors to this throughout.
Hmm.
So, what it really was, was something that was defined in scripture loosely in the Psalms.
You know, where is the, where do you get knowledge?
Okay.
The beginning of wisdom is, you know, it's the fear of the gods, right?
Fear is in love.
I think I've discussed this on one of the previous Sonic events.
Fear and love, and, you know, they hand in hand, right?
Not the secular, what people, satanic fear that you've been taught, or the satanic love people have been taught.
I think I did a discussion on fear and love before.
But, in essence, it's knowledge that the Elohim has, and the Elohim tell you where you get their knowledge that brings wisdom, and you get that from understanding and comprehending scripture.
Right?
Because at this time, they're not going to come to you and knock on your door and start, you know, pontificating all the stuff that has been written that's not meant for you to understand anyway.
Think about it.
So, if you're clever enough, or wise enough, or given the ability to comprehend what's in scripture, you will gain a level of wisdom that those who can't comprehend it or get anything out of it don't have.
So, you're operating on a different level.
So, either way, no matter how much you look for what the tree of knowledge of good and evil is in scripture, you will find that it refers back to the scripture itself, based on definition.
Based on the tree of knowledge of good and evil was good for giving wisdom.
And the scriptures itself tells you you gain wisdom by knowledge of the gods.
And where do you get knowledge of the gods?
Through scripture, at this point.
And remember, it was Eve who did it.
Adam didn't have to do it.
Remember?
But he did it because he loved Eve.
So, yeah.
I guess he didn't want another rib taken.
Right.
Yeah.
And this was known.
I've had discussions with someone, hours of scripture, not recently, but recently, I should say a few months, about, well, so he knew it was going to happen.
Of course.
It's a setup.
Yeah, you've been set up.
You'll get over it.
Don't take it personally, even though you're personally suffering the consequences.
Yeah.
It's kind of like, look at it in reverse.
You know, these people came before us.
They're patriarchs to us, or predecessors, and higher in authority because of that.
But look at it in reverse.
You have a child who plays with matches and burns the house down, and you come home and you see the house is burned down.
The child is still okay, but the house is burned down.
Well, don't take it personally.
You get it?
Right.
The child didn't say, well, I'm going to go and burn the house down because I'm mad at Mommy and Daddy.
That's not going to happen because they were a child.
And did you know that if you left the matches out, that would happen?
Yeah.
Not that it would happen, but the possibility was very high.
So, you know, see, so, yeah, it was known, of course, the gods knew this was going to happen.
But don't take it personally, because it wasn't to you, it was to Adam.
But they also knew that it would be to all those that followed.
So, how can you not take it personally when you're suffering the consequences?
Well, I shouldn't say suffering.
Suffering means you're willingly doing it.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of people just walking around that don't even know.
Yeah, and if you don't know, then why do you know?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
I think it's a good place to leave it off.
What do you think?
Two hours plus?
Yeah, we just did two hours just like that again, Greek.
I'm much enlightened again.
Oh, good.
Good to hear that.
And I really want to thank you for coming forth and doing this again.
I know that your time is worth something.
And hopefully it shows, and I'm internally grateful again.
Well, thank you, and thanks for everyone who's sent some support.
That's very kind.
And we'll do it again.
We'll probably give less of a space for the next one.
Yeah, and maybe a little more heads up, and that way we can make sure that we get more people that can participate, which is always helpful.
Yeah, maybe a day in advance next time.
Yeah, that wouldn't be bad.
Well, you have yourself a great night, sir, and I appreciate it.
And I'm sure everybody else out there does also.
Great.
Thanks.
Thanks for doing it, and everyone be well.
See you.
Okay.
Be well, Greek.
Bye.
Bye-bye.