Greetings everyone.
And we have Bruce as usual and the Greek as usual and we have a caller and a guest, I guess, to some extent, have you noticed?
And the floor is yours.
Where do you want to take us?
Yeah.
You're speaking to me, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
I'd like to speak up where you and I left off maybe a little over a year and a year ago.
Okay.
On the radio.
On AFR where I had called in about the dreams and how your dreams are not your own and your actual thoughts are not your own.
Right.
And that's a hard thing, issue for people to think about or even consider.
Yeah.
But you've got to realize people have been, I won't interrupt you much because you've got a lot to say.
When you meet people or talk to people, other than being, you know, whatever, living creatures, they are subject to thousands of years of conditioning, not just in their own formative years in their own lives, but thousands of years.
So I just want to put that up.
This is what you're witnessing when you hold up what you hear on the sonic events to what other people think, what they think is product of thousands of years of conditioning.
So I just want to bring that up.
Yes.
I've talked to a young girl.
She's in her early 30s.
I had spoken to her about dreams and she had also been affected by dreams, thoughts, nightmares, etc.
I think as a lot of people have in their life and she got to thinking about it and talked to me and she said, you know, I think you're right.
And she was, she came off of work one day and called me and said that someone had said, oh, I had a dream about you and your son.
And she said, no, please don't tell me.
I'd rather not hear that.
And I thought, great, great.
You know, if you can get through to one person, it's a help.
Yeah, that's what I said for a while.
But you get over it real quick and you realize you just go right back to where you were.
You know, you're around people that are unresponsive to the truth.
Yeah.
So it is rewarding to help one person.
I agree.
But then you just go right back to what the hell am I doing here?
Well, I know, but what are we doing?
You know, I mean, we say that, but...
Yeah, taking up time.
Taking up time, but, you know, we're learning these new things at the very end of the experience or the...
Existence, yeah.
Existence.
We're coming through.
You know, let me just throw something in that might be helpful because you brought up the dreams and all that.
A couple of things.
One thing is when I studied the ancient writs, it never mentioned anything about dreams being your own.
You know, sourced from your own or having any meaning on their own.
They were always, let's say, documented or recorded and reported as being a message from the other side.
And, you know, of course, it's not like what they call the dollar bill God.
There is no God.
It's the gods and they go all the way from the king to the street sweeper.
And on their side, they also have their nut jobs and they're homeless looking people and they're, you know, see?
It's just like human culture in a way.
But not just like it because they're, you know, they're gods.
So I started discounting the cultural aspect of, you know, like the pagans love dream interpretation.
They take it very seriously and they've taken it out of context.
So I started discounting all the dream stuff and I realized what the simplicity is.
If we're being plugged with an image and a variation of, let's say, animation experiences while we're sleeping by a spiritual being, then you have to say, well, do I want that?
Or, you know, do I want that in my life or do I not want it in my life?
So you start going through basic what I call scientific experimentation.
I'd like to not have it, you know, see if I can control it, right?
And then, of course, if they're malevolent, which is the second point I want to bring up.
Working with someone right now for a few months who has a child and they got really...
The child was having night terrors or what they call night terrors, really bad dreams and they couldn't remember them.
And the person got a little aggressive.
He started screaming and doing the usual, you know, clearing the space by claiming the space in a way.
But they got worse after a while.
It stopped for a while, then it came back and it got worse.
So what they did, obviously, is they sent a more powerful demon, you know?
So instead of just the scumbag in the Navy, right?
The scumbag is the low guy.
They sent more of a sergeant type.
So what happened there was a reach out to, what do you do next?
They said, well, this is still susceptible.
You know how you see in the cartoons the elephant is afraid of the mouse, right?
So not a sense of the demon being afraid, but I know that environmental rhythmic actions like playing instruments or music or leaving a radio on low or a TV set down low in the background.
A TV, preferably not.
Just a radio is enough to distract them.
And that's been going on now for two months and they report back.
He reports back every month that everything's fine.
Wonderful.
Yeah, because the other stuff didn't work.
He got a little too aggressive, also overzealous.
So just to throw that out there, this is, what do you call it, therapy?
When you start realizing what reality is, when you start applying it, it's a form of therapy.
It is a therapy because you can't let it go if you know it.
That you know that it's true, you have to apply it.
And that's the therapy.
If you're responsible enough to, yeah.
That's the therapy.
Yeah.
So the dream aspect, there's many other things, by the way.
The problem that I've seen with discussing it is clarity and confidence.
Most people still, you know, they might hear like some Greek speak or something and apply it.
Then they listen to other stuff and they don't know how to discern the other stuff to see whether it's contradicting or, you know, compatible.
And they try to do that even though it's not compatible and then things fall apart.
The reason why I want to bring this up, I recently got, recently, like three months ago, someone was communicating with me who was studying demonology.
But not demonology in a sense like Satanism, but it's a field, it's called demonology where you study the spiritual world and how people are possessed and oppressed and all that.
And this person, even though they were studying this for, I'd say, maybe two decades, they still think, they've mixed like the religious mythology, like when you die, you go somewhere and you have another existence.
They still believe that, you know, they don't know.
In other words, even though I say they're still being fooled because they think when they see a ghost of someone who's died, it's really the person that died, they still don't know that it was a demon playing a joke on them or a prank on them, right?
And they don't think that they can go and communicate this with other people that they're studying because it goes so contrary to what they've been taught, you see.
And this person has been involved with, which is very rare, by the way, for someone to be possessed, it's a very rare thing.
But very common is oppression.
Possession is when a spirit takes over the body and the person goes into disanimation.
So let's say someone is possessed by a being for a week.
When they come out of it, they don't remember anything, right?
Oppression is different.
Oppression is still external input and they're just basically oppressing you.
It's like someone, you know, putting itching powder on you and swapping you around constantly.
And that's what most people are experiencing.
And that's why, let me just tie this all together.
Dreaming is a form of spiritual oppression, okay?
It's a form of oppression.
Yes, it is.
Even when you think it's a pleasant dream, on the other side, they're laughing their ass off that they got you to believe it.
So, yeah.
And then you can't sleep well, obviously.
Well, you let it in, you let it happen.
Well, if you let it in, you have no choice.
But if you relax about it and you don't, you know, no control, what happens then is you...
What is it when you allow yourself to be manipulated?
Gullible, naive?
Gullible, yeah.
You know, I was just going to ask you, Greek.
What about those people...
Did you ever catch yourself where you knew you were asleep but yet you're awake enough to know that you're asleep?
That's possible as well.
Yeah.
But that's the switch.
That's just like a different, like a very relaxed state.
Actually, I've been trying to be in that state for the past decades because I don't want to be too awake in this shithole of a society.
But anyway, yeah.
You can control your dreams and yet not have any.
And those also that are in your home, children that are in your home, that is going very well.
They have not had any problem or issues since.
As you had stated, they'll try to come in, you know.
You might remember a little snippet that you disregarded and you deal with it when you wake up.
Right.
Because they don't stop.
They, at some point, you know, they come back or try to...
Well, they're hypersensitive to our behavior and our thoughts.
But they can't read your mind.
For a while back, I'll just give a little bit of a document.
Let's just give a little sonic on...
I've experimented with this.
I've thought of things and asked for a dream and did not get it.
And then I actually try to manifest things by writing them down, you know, like going to the Bahamas or going online and researching that.
And then I would ask for a dream and they would actually give me a dream of that, you see.
So, what I'm saying is they can't do your thoughts but they can do what you manifest.
Like, if you pick up a magazine and see a picture of a green ice cream truck, they know that you're doing that.
And they also have a hive mentality.
Anywhere in the world one can communicate about anybody else, you know, so if they want to pick on you about your great-grandfather or your grandfather that you knew as a child, the one that wants to give you the dream will put out a call and say, any of you guys know we're around when this guy's grandfather was alive and give me that image so I could plug him with it, right?
So, it's not always what I mean by that.
They can't read your mind and it's not always the same spirit.
And I noticed the flavor of the dream changes.
And after a while I was like, I'm going to stop having these dreams.
And they stop.
And occasionally when they do try to bring on a dream, I'm like, I'm not having it, sorry.
And it goes away.
Yeah.
I have control of it because it takes, we want to call it a martial art or a form of discipline, you know.
Yeah, something you have to work at.
Yeah, and it can't be done, it should not be done silently.
It should be manifested either with a pen and paper or verbally, yeah.
Because they don't read your mind.
Now, I'm not going to go out on a limb and speak about other things because there are ones that can read your mind and those are not the lower ones that are the typical dream makers.
That is from the very, very high office.
Only the office of the most high can read your mind.
And that's stated in scripture.
He knows what's on the minds and the hearts of man.
Yeah.
Where the other ones don't.
And with that, my interactions on that level, I keep private for several reasons.
Okay.
So, for instance, within a family, group, would you say that the emotions play a part in dreams?
The emotions, the interactions of, say, a family together or a group together, of course they know what's going on and they can play on that as well.
Oh, yeah.
You mean because they're out, yeah.
In other words, the emotions are part of the communicative display.
Oh, yeah.
And they'll weaken some and strengthen others depending on, just like people if they want to keep an argument going or instigate something or just make the whole group depressed or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
They're just like people.
In other words, when I say just like people, they're not because they're not physical corporeal entities.
What they are is their motherboard, their wiring is just like ours.
But they don't need a body to animate.
Well, we do.
So when we lose the body, we go into disanimation.
You know, like someone asked, you know, this is like a Jack Fresco thing, I'm glad he said this, and I used to say it a long time ago, and I'm glad that Jack Fresco brought it up.
When people ask you or anyone what happens after you die, it's like, what were you thinking about 500 years ago?
That's exactly what happens after you die.
And there's still a lot of people going out in the world saying, oh, I died and I saw myself on the operating table.
No, you didn't.
You didn't die because if you died, you wouldn't be here to tell us.
Yeah.
Yeah, I read an article the other day about, oh, when people have trouble after they're possessed, their souls are, the souls are coming back, they're inanimated souls, but that's not true.
The spirits, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the spirits.
The soul is the breath, yeah.
Well, they can't even get the terminology.
Yeah, they use the wrong words.
They use the word soul.
Yeah, they don't even know.
Yeah, I actually spoke to a young Greek woman several months ago and, you know, I was asking her this about the soul and spirit.
Oh, she said, oh, yeah, when you die, you lose your spirit, you know.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, and she should know better.
Well, she's human, right?
Your average surface-dwelling person, they come in all flavors, Russian, Greek, Irish, Italian, German.
You know, they come in all flavors, but they're the, you know, ice cream.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to say it that way, but there's been a conspiracy a long time ago to make sure that communication is inaccurate.
This was done for, actually in the beginning it was done as a protection mechanism, and then it became a control mechanism, and then it grew as a control mechanism and a protection mechanism, and right now it's so ingrained that, like I said, most people are unrehabilitatable.
They're ready for the scrapyard.
They have to be recycled.
You can't fix them.
And I had, still I have people saying, well, they're people.
How could you say that?
I'm like, well, what kind of an emotional bullshit are you caught up in?
You know, they can't rationalize that.
And on the other hand, I've never discussed the concept of slavery much.
I'm glad, you know, I posted some Dimitri Calswell of YouTube recently.
He talked about the sovereign state and how you enslave people by creating a state that they sign up to as property.
And if you read Scripture, slavery is a legal condition, and it is lawful, but what they're doing, most slaves in the ancient world, if you ask them their status, they tell you I'm a slave or not.
Now most people think they're free, but they're actually enslaved legally.
So whether they know it or not, it doesn't matter.
But I'll tell you, lawfully, you can do to a slave, a human being, the same thing you could do to a chair or a refrigerator or a car.
It's not criminal to do that.
Now, it depends.
Now, there are laws regarding that.
There is a level of criminality that can be achieved.
But you can kill a slave as your property or for financial reasons, and it's totally, you know, acceptable, right?
Yes, and it's all in Scripture.
Yeah, it's in Scripture.
There are a couple of laws that have fine points about beating them, and, you know, if you beat them and they lose a tooth, you let them go.
If you lose an eye, you let them go, and all these other things, right?
So what people don't understand, that's why I brought up police brutality, that is, once you get brutality in a society, whether it's police or whatever, that never diminishes.
It gets worse and worse until the society collapses.
Yes.
So in America, where you see police brutality going up, it's not going to get better.
It's going to get worse and worse until the society collapses.
And when I mean collapses, I mean, like, you know, the buildings don't have roofs, and there are very few people around, and there's no power and no water running.
You know, I mean, total collapse.
And no police and everyone.
And no people.
Yeah.
But no people to form a society as you know it.
There's still a few people.
But you can go fly over the Amazon or the Congo, and it doesn't look like there are any people down there, but if you go down there, walk around for a few days, you'll run into some people.
Like that, right?
So what the, quote-unquote, the state, the corporate state is doing, is lawful, by the way, to a certain degree, because you're a slave, evidenced by birth certificates and registrations and things like that.
And, um, but what's not lawful about it is the people don't know it.
But that also adds proof positive that it's satanic, because Satan does the opposite.
If Satan tells you you're free, that means you're a slave.
If Satan says you're a slave, that means you have a possibility of freedom.
It's backwards, you see.
But you can know it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it can be known.
But the thing is that people have now become that satanic element now, you see.
Yeah, OK.
The people in general.
So, for example, here, if you go out in the street and start saying, well, supposedly, no, you're free, but once you start dealing with the, quote-unquote, authorities on a private level, so you're just a slave.
Yeah.
And if you say you're a slave to certain people, they get angry because they only know the slave meaning one thing.
Right.
As in what happened 200 years ago, right?
And very often, that's why I don't, I've had requests to do interviews, and I used to do a thing with Ocelli, and I've done some other interviews, and there's no reason to go.
Because when you listen to people, not to disparage those people, but they think because they like something, it's right.
Like, very often, I've been in a conversation with someone, and I say, well, I don't agree with that, so?
What does that mean, you don't agree?
It doesn't mean anything.
So, most people still think what they agree with is right, and what they don't agree with is wrong, and it doesn't exist, you see?
So, that's why I'm saying there's nothing going on on the Internet, because, you know, where, if you're going to go on the Internet to get information and listen to people talk, let me ask you, where are they from?
They're from planet Earth, for starters, right?
And second of all, where did they get their education?
Where did they get their thoughts from?
They're operating on a very, very low level.
So, what happens is, I'm giving that as an example, because no matter what you try to do, even if it's sonic events on the Internet, or go read classical literature, or turn on the TV, or speak to authorities or wealthy people, it's all garbage at this point.
It's accumulated.
It was garbage thousands of years ago also, but now it's just, you know, the landfill.
Have you ever been to a landfill of a small town?
It's not that big, but if you go to a landfill of a huge city, it's huge.
And right now it's all this huge landfill, and it's very, very wasted.
So, back to the definition, it seems like we've gone away from dreams and all that, but it's very simple.
I think I stated your mind, your spirit, which is the same thing, your consciousness is wholly dependent, unless you have major assistance, which I've never really gone into, which you would call the after-death experience.
People that come back, they haven't really died.
I'll be right back.
Hold on.
Go ahead and take this call.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hi, Bruce.
Hi.
That was fascinating.
Yeah.
Yeah, no.
Yeah, the dreams...
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
So, when you look at the script, the way we were made right now, this particular, the survivors of Genesis is what you see on the planet right now, except for a very small group that are non-identified.
When I say Genesis, I mean, you know, Noah, right?
And on.
We're made in a way that your spirit consciousness is wholly dependent on your physicality.
That's why, for example, it feels good to drink or smoke pot or do drugs, because it changes that consciousness, right?
The future, after death and resurrection, I believe will be a different relationship, because after the resurrection, you don't need to have a body to be conscious, you see?
You can shed that, and right now it's in paranormal, supernatural.
But, see, on the other hand, once you understand this, it's quite an advantage, because it's very narrow.
You don't have a lot of options, right?
So, you know, like the zombies, you know, you kill the brain, you kill the head, you kill the zombie.
You know, like the zombie, remember, they shoot the arm off, so it keeps coming, you have to kill the head, right?
So, it's the same with people, you know, there's people that have had their full amputations and they're still gone, but once the head is removed, and the body, you know, from the head being removed, then the spirit goes to disanimation.
So, the reason I stated all this, even though it might have some gory detail, is very simple, because it is very simple.
So, once you understand that, how you are actually almost prey to the spiritual world at this point.
Like, if you ever see all the deer in the forest, not the ones that get used to being fed, you know, I've been in places, camping, where I see the deer come up to the people, because, you know, for generations, people fed them.
I'm talking about real prey animals, you know, when you watch like zebras and all that stuff, you know how they all huddle together and a lion comes by, or a fox, or whatever, and they all run, right?
Because the only defense is to run, or kick.
So, you know, humans are, can be easily predated upon by the spiritual world at this point.
And this is a very simple point.
So, all these points that I'm making are very, very important to understand the simplicity and the foundation of your composition, because how can you work on something, right?
Both positive and negative, if you don't understand its composition.
And by the way, for every, not the people, well, your average people, not those, but there are people listening to this kind of stuff.
So, for everyone that listens to what we're really made of, there's, they want to do something positive, there's another three or four that want to do something negative with this information.
That's why I don't talk about a lot of the poignant points, and it wouldn't be prudent.
And I've discussed, there's several people, like, there's a guy named Ibrahim Karim, he's from Egypt, he doesn't know a lot, he's very censored, but he knows a lot about biogeometry, like drawing a symbol that can change the environment, you know, we're not talking sigils in evocation.
And having a discussion with him a few years ago, he mentioned, for every, there's about one or two laboratories that are experimenting with symbolism, biogeometry, for health reasons, to mitigate electromagnetic stuff, disease, and all that, but there's over 50 labs researching it to weaponize it, in a negative way.
Okay, so, yeah, this is the same with, I've met people that were very good at chemistry, full scholarships, even though it's a bullshit, you know, standard.
Nine out of ten of them, once they graduate, go into companies that eventually make weapons.
You see, so this is, what I'm trying to say here is, whether it's information, concepts, processes, the majority of the consciousness, or the people that are on the planet right now support the negative outcome, or weaponizing, or using it for bad instead of good.
You see?
Yes.
And that's in scripture as well.
You think it's a piper plane?
Could be.
Yeah.
I can't, I can't, I can't go in.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Yeah, we were just talking about the weapon idea.
So, I can't go inside.
Well, that's fine.
Yeah.
Now, Next.
How much, how much, do you think, or not think, but when a person wants to know something, is it more easily for them to learn it if they have that gumption, or they have that interest in learning something that they didn't really know before?
Well, you also have to bring in cosmic censorship.
If the gods, especially the higher, don't want you to see it, there's nobody that can make you see it.
Even if they put a gun to your head, you still won't see it.
Now, is there, okay.
Cosmic censorship's a bitch.
Yeah.
I mean, a female dog.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Because how can you differentiate that?
I mean, if someone wants to know something for their own good, you're saying that they may never know it.
Right.
Well, for sure not now.
Like, you know what an ah-ha moment is?
Uh-huh.
Before you even finish telling them they get it?
That means they're wide open, and they're not censored on that subject.
Okay.
You know, like if you just bring a concept up to someone before you, and when you're halfway telling it they're finishing the sentence for you, it means they got it, and the other side is permissible for them to know.
And there's other people that you can tell, and they just shrug their shoulders, and whatever, they're censored.
We're not talking about everything now.
We're talking about the truth.
The truth, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
The truth is it's not open for whether it's appealing or desirable.
That's why, again, if you've ever heard me on other sponics, other interviews of other people and stuff, it's all about what they like.
Who cares about what anybody likes?
Yeah, because Sing the truth.
Yeah.
The truth, well, seems to be not that desirable, actually.
Well, also you've got to realize the truth is very, very detrimental to the powers that be.
You can't be a slave if you know the truth.
There's a couple of...
Right, right.
There was an old book where there was...
they had a slave that kept beating him up, and they'd find out, like, well, why are you always being, you know, beaten?
And he says, well, I can't...
I don't make a good slave because when I was young, I traveled a lot, and I learned a lot of things.
So I don't make a good slave.
So when you run into, like, higher-ups in your society, Harvard, Princeton graduates, doctors, engineers, and all that, they're good slaves because they never learned a lot of stuff, you see.
You know what I mean?
And you can't graduate from those schools unless you're proved to be a good slave.
There's no way.
So the more knowledge...
When I say slave, I mean...
Okay, let me just put it this way, because most people still don't understand.
How many times have you heard me say, how many people in the world ever heard of the book of Revelation?
Raise your hand.
How many people heard of the Antichrist?
Well, if everybody knows about it, aren't they going to cry foul when it starts happening?
Yes.
So what it means is that it's all secret.
Even when it's happening, they won't be able to discern it, you see.
Everything in Scripture is still secret.
When you say Abraham to someone, have you heard, yeah, show me a picture, what do you think?
It's all wrong.
It's all still secret.
Like the character of Abraham, the character, especially, of the Christ, and all that.
All of that is a secret.
Still.
Big, big, big, big secret.
Yeah, because when someone today thinks of Abraham, they think of all Christianity, Islam, that's all they think about.
And I understand that.
Yeah, they don't understand his character either.
If you study Scripture, you'll see the man had a character.
And you wouldn't like him if he was a relative.
Let me just put it that way.
But, nonetheless, let's just say, we'll leave it at that.
I've got a lot of notes on biblical characters that one day I'll share, or someone else will share.
And I'll suggest that it'll be quite an eye-opener.
So, if all of these things are secret, right, when you read in Scripture, let's go back to what I was saying about being a slave, the leaders or the kings of a people and all that, it's not the politicians and the people you see on TV or in the history books for a long, long time.
Those kings and leaders of people are people behind the scenes that you do not know and you will probably never know.
You see?
So, when you read about the king of the north and this and that, that's not talking about some puppet president.
There's no president in ancient writ.
They're corporations.
There's bloodlines that run.
So, who runs, who owns Egypt, who owns Israel, who owns the U.S., you do not know.
And you will not know because they're very good at keeping those secrets secret.
So, when you read Scripture about these leaders moving around and things happening then you will not see that.
But you will see the effects of it.
Kind of like the wind.
Yes.
The ether.
Yeah.
Right, the ether.
So, all of these things are so simple yet one thing that you need to do is tell people if you are a thinker especially if you contemplate the truth if you're a good thinker you will contemplate the truth you're going to have to eventually phase people out.
In other words, let it not be important to you to have discussion and conversation with quote unquote friends, family and acquaintances just because they're there.
Right.
Just because you have people around you whether it's co-workers, family or friends if they're not open to it and industrious about what you're discussing in other words they want to help and learn more just phase them out when it comes to that subject.
So, if you're at work just talk about you do work things you're at home watch TV with them or whatever or whatever they're interested in but don't because what that will do is the energy that you could be using on studying and contemplating and meditating on the truth will get muddied up with the emotional responses internally and externally because they can't understand it.
And you can't be so eager to say oh, I want to help people because it's too late.
You can't really help people.
You can't do it.
Well, here's the thing.
You know how they say the will of the gods is more important than the will of man.
The gods already are very clear saying that you're nothing like, let me just like shit in the street.
Yeah.
Of course it is.
Not even yeah, we're not talking about shit in the living room floor we're talking about the shit in the street is what the gods think of humanity at this point on a major group and of course they pull out and choose selected people here and there to do certain things.
But this is the level you're like dung.
You know.
Or another if you want to graduate to a higher level you're like grass or in the field.
How many times do people feel sorry because someone put a blade to the grass and cut the grass?
That's how the gods think of you.
And if you know look all this up that I'm saying by the way.
So once I'm not saying abuse them or whatever but I'm saying disregard them on the subject matter but you have to regard them on the food, clothing and shelter.
If you see somebody that needs something help them out.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So.
You said that well you've stated this many times that it's all a secret and it will be a secret.
Yes.
But later.
Much later.
Yeah.
And concerning now I haven't done been able to do much searching on the Parthians but Seleucid Parthian Empire.
Seleucid, yes.
But Daniel was taken captive there and you stated that he was a a good example of how to pray how to interact with the Elohim.
Right.
Now, he was called a mad guy.
To a certain degree, yeah.
To a certain degree.
Yeah.
He was not in other words just like today well well I shouldn't say because it's very mixed there is no there is no just separation Let me just say this.
A hundred years ago this is more clear and more to the point.
A hundred years ago you were not considered educated or a hundred and fifty years ago you were not considered educated unless you knew the scriptures.
Period.
It doesn't matter what country you were in where in the world.
If you didn't know the ancient rites it doesn't matter who you were where you were you were not considered educated.
If you were went to the best universities in the world in any country and you didn't know the ancient rites you were not considered educated.
If you were a farmer that never went to school and knew the ancient rites you were considered educated.
That was the benchmark of how knowledgeable someone was.
Do you see what I mean?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
So when you when you look at someone like Daniel who was privileged to be in the king's court but it wasn't all that it was cracked up to be either.
Right?
Because when Yeah.
So but on the other hand he had access.
Right?
It's about access.
And also you know, believe it or not Okay.
All the people Yeah.
He had access to to physical the best of the best stuff.
You know.
Like for example I'll just well, I don't know how to say it.
Okay.
Let's say I know someone who had been to some a very, very, very wealthy person's home.
And once they get to when you go now I'm not just you know, you visit for a few days because you're it's also business regarding what business they do.
Let's say I'm not going to mention the business like petrochemical or something like that.
But they start showing you all their prized possessions and they taped out like a map a brass tube and they show you this map it's a map that's 500 years old and you look at it and it has days and dates on it and all kinds of directional and charts.
And that would have been worth in today's money several million back then.
The reason why was it not only was a map of how to grow the over the world's oceans but it was also a map that gave you when to go when the wind currents would be on your back so it would cut your trip in half or cut it by two thirds.
That was worth a lot because if you can cross the Atlantic in a week instead of two and a half weeks you have to carry less food and you get your you see what I mean?
Yeah.
So but if you just go out into the world right now they don't have if you tell them about this they've never even heard of it.
Yeah, but they did that back then.
Yes, they have.
During Solomon's time, etc.
the Phoenicians I mean they traveled the oceans to well, the Americans.
There were secrets also that they had that are not made public.
Right?
So when you read the book of Daniel and he was highly learned in many things you're like, well could you learn all the things?
No, because those things have never been made public.
Yeah.
See?
But also you should go back to the first part when you suggested about how to pray he was very diligent at it.
He did it very often.
And when you read for example in Scriptures is knock and the door will be opened it doesn't say that really.
It's not written that way.
It's written in an aorist tense.
Aorist is where it means you constantly be knocking.
You know?
It's like Yeah, you don't give up.
You keep pushing.
Yeah, it's a tense that we don't acknowledge.
It's a in grammatical tense called the aorist.
And the aorist means it's constantly going on like breathing or living or Yeah.
Or thinking.
Or thinking about.
Well, for most people that would be completely far.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
And, you know in that Well, wasn't there a time where they said that it was pray without speaking?
Sure.
Yes, that's Yeah, that would be the aorist.
But what It's much easier to make a metaphor an analogy now.
If you're in front of a computer all day how many tabs and windows can you have open at the same time?
Especially if you have a really large several screens.
So, when you get up in the morning first thing you think about the gods and you're in a state of prayer like, you know communicating with them what you would like to do according to their will of course.
Because if you ask things against their will they're not going to help you, right?
Well, of course.
Yeah, so Or they'll give you what you wanted and it won't be good.
Well, then even if you well, yeah, that's another whole other thing show me a prophet that had a good life even Solomon, right?
Right.
So, if you don't want to be it is a state where it's not yeah they'll use you and spit you out but we don't understand why at this point.
I'm talking even the most high.
But well, we know why but we don't know exactly why they do it that way consistently.
Very rarely does anyone other than Job Eob and a few others do they have a peaceful ending or a peaceful life.
but the thing is when you when you start acknowledging when your day starts for example the gods and how you want to walk with them or them to walk with you or guide you when you when you first start thinking with the next thing you do don't change that thought keep it running in the background or the foreground.
You see what I mean?
Always there.
It's always there, yeah.
It's not there's the technical aspect that I discussed which is, you know you should be in a clean state if you want to know what that is.
You know, washed and no meat no dead animal around and you they know what you well, the most high knows what you need to know what you want they they you know how I said what do you give to someone what do you give what do you give to someone who already has everything?
Yeah.
That's all you if they have so the most high already has everything so the only thing that he doesn't have is your attention.
You see?
So that's what I mean it's a technical aspect.
I always I was always amazed by the the fact how they use the analogy of father.
Right.
And the reason they use those terms is because it's understood in the society that we're in.
You notice that that's not used in the book of Enoch?
It's always the most high or the most Right.
Right.
Yeah.
Because the society the development and the discussion of the book of Enoch was already from an insider group.
Right.
When you start going on a more social group you bring up father, son, mother.
Oh.
Interesting.
Yeah, I see.
You see?
That's why they call the son of God well he's not really the son of God because God doesn't need to have how's the God going to have a son?
You know?
I mean, what does that mean?
Well
in a sense
that we discussed
but he is the son of God
to show authority
and I've given the example
if you have a corporation
that you've ran
for 30 years
and 10 years
into the corporation
you have a child
when that boy
or girl
becomes
especially I would say
as a boy
becomes a man at 20
when he walks into
the boardroom
even though you
started that company
and you have guys
that have been with you
for 30 years
even though your son
is only 20
your son
at 20
has more authority
than they do
in terms of inheritance.
You don't have to.
Right.
Because of the progeny and the primus familius and all that pedifamilius the first you see coming forward and so what the son means is to come in full authority of another not just an agent See, what makes an agent an agent is an agent does not bring himself he just represents what his pledge is to represent you know?
So you have
they have agents
angels work
as agents
but the agents
don't have
the true authority
outside of their
purpose of being
a representative agent
Now, when you say
someone is a son
they not only
are representative
agent
but they also
have the authority
within themselves
like when an angel
like if you
study scripture
several places
it says
and Yahweh
sent my own angel
not just an angel
he has his own angel
that he sends
he sends angels
and then he has
his own angel
his angel is like
a body double
like you ever see
like years ago
Saddam Hussein
had a body double
or the president
would have a body double
or the king would have
a body double
So, the Most High
has a body double
a few of them
that are
just like him
in other words
if you
are in their presence
you will be vaporized
if you look at them
you will die
just like the Most High
but they are not
the Most High
they can only
act within
the authority
that they've been
given as an agent
but when you
give the other
person
another person
or another being
full authority
and they can
act on that
full authority
as themselves
that is
like a son
you see
that's what
the Christ
is
in other words
comes from
that family
it's just like
when you see
let's say
you're the monarchy
you have people
coming and
representing
the king
all over the world
but here comes
the king's son
he's called a prince
you know
you see
so as long as
there's no conflict
that prince
his royalty
and he is the
highest form
that can be bestowed
when he's at a
you know
wherever presence
he gets
you know
and he speaks for
and
yes
and he speaks for
and for himself
you see
because that's
who it is
yeah
because it's
it's actually
the creator
doing it all
sure
but in full authority
just as good
all the way through
through
see where you read
in Exodus
and in
Genesis
all the presence
is when the most high comes
that's not the most high
that's his angel
coming
his angel
versus
an angel
there's a difference
like
when Moses
was speaking to the angel
that gave off fire
but didn't burn the bush
notice I didn't say
the burning bush
okay
that was not
his angel
that was an angel
but when
it says Yahweh
descended upon the mountain
and the mountain shook
and smoke came out
that was
Yahweh's angel
his angel
doing that
there's a difference
you see
his body double
let's say
his spiritual body double
it's very hard to discern
but it's there
you can see it
yes
at one point
he tells Moses
I am sending you my angel
uh oh
wow
not just any angel
but you know
the body double
when I mean body double
I mean spiritual presence
full
you know
but that
when he says my angel
that angel that he sends
that is just like him
does not act upon
on his own
sense
he only acts on what
he does in agency
where the Christ is different
the Christ
acts
on what the Father does
and on his own
so
anyway
yeah
it's very simple
all these things
are very very simple
and uh
again
not good for the slaves
to know
this is the
as I mentioned earlier
Yah I mean
it changes everything
you can be a terrible slave
you can't be a good slave
if you know things
and then
you know
the crab
the buckets
and the crab
what is it
the crab and the bucket
all these people
that are out on
you know
you see in the world
and on the internet
if they don't like
what you're saying
see if they got caught
into some ideology
or
whatever
thought
and
they hear what you're saying
they
somehow
inherently know
it's true
but they don't like it
they fight you on it
right
and they bring up
all this crap
to back up
their stuff
so
what happens again
is it's best to keep
discussions simple
uh
keep them narrow
and not too deep
right
on these matters
because they're so simple
what makes them complicated
is the
quantity
of possibilities
and things
but the quality
of the discussion
the quality
of the information
is very
very simple
you know
there's hierarchies
there's physical
there's non-physical
then you have to
understand authority
you have to
understand law
and that's it
that's pretty much
knowledge of the universe
mhm
and it's all
it's all in scripture
and a lot of ancient writs
yes
but not ancient writs
that are
you know
like you see
like Gnosticism
that would be like
the 9-11 commission
or the Warren commission
right
which is a bullshit
uh thing
even though people
take it seriously
you know because
back in those days
for example
Gnosticism
the first century
was flooded
with uh
events that no one
can explain
so they had to
make up stuff
uh to explain it
to the masses
and at the same time
prosper from it
what people don't
understand
the Gnostics
were like Hollywood
is today
they put out
a lot of stuff
for what
why does Hollywood
do what it does
for
for money
and power
fame
you know
and
um
so
yeah
someone mentioned
in chat
about
food
clothing
and shelter
and uh
do you want to
maybe talk about
the human body
a little bit
or
yeah
yeah I can do that
um
yeah I had
uh
before you start
um
I just wanted to
mention that
uh
when
when you first
started your
conversations
about clothing
and the mixed
fibers
and all that
I took the liberty
uh some months
later
in going through
and uh
to my
complete
profoundness
of this
um
just very little
was of
mixed
oh good
and I just
I was just
what are the
odds
you know
well it depends
on what kind
of work
you do
uh
you know
if you had to
also
on how
uh
you know
I mean
um
it
it's
yeah
it depends on how
elaborate of a wardrobe
it depends on if
you're a fashion
slave
if you're not a
fashion slave
you probably
have mixed
yeah
the ones that I did
have
you know
I tossed them
down
and uh
but yeah
that was
just
stocks are the most
difficult
and for women
they would be
pretty much
all around
difficult
uh
even jeans
these days
are five percent
lycra
now they put in
you know
stuff in there
so
weird stuff
yeah
and that's
for a reason
uh
but uh
nonetheless
uh
there's nothing
wrong with
making your own
clothes
if you want
to invest
in it
uh
like anything
you have to
buy the tools
yeah
there's lots of seamstress
out there
that love to work
yeah
and uh
mercenaries
uh
is that the proper term
for cotton
and everything
yeah
I really started
looking into that
and oh my goodness
uh
boy what a fascinating
subject
yeah
mercenaries
and the weaving
yeah
okay
so
I think
I think I emailed you
a couple days
after it happened
um
but it looks great
and um
uh
the vacuum
has been
restored
on a uh
person
who
um
is non ambulatory
and uh
due to
uh
pneumonia
issues
breathing
problems
and uh
that's been
done
with
eating
longitude
latitudinally
um
that has been
corrected
uh
in the last
year and a half
hello
yep
let's go here
sorry about that
that's fine
that's the piper
coming around again
yeah
sorry about that
but um
and uh
there's a child
uh
who uh
um
they're going on
their um
so I want to go back
real quick
Valerie
if it's alright
the person who
was not ambulatory
and all that
I think
the process
if I recall
will keep it as anonymous
as possible
was basically
uh
applying
compression
to the entire
limbs on the body
was that
was that it
if I remember
yes
and I
I get
I should have
explained that
I just
that's fine
I think I'm just
assuming that
everyone has
listened to
everything that you
have stated on that
so
that's my mistake
yeah
oh that's fine
I apologize
so basically
uh
manipulating the vacuum
by understanding the
let's say
for lack of a better
word
basic physics
you compress
uh
something that's
soft
and increases the
pressure
so the
so that it adjusts
to if it needs a vacuum
to start to create more vacuum
and then when you
release the pressure
you have extra vacuum
because it had
adjusted to that
you see
so you're
pulling
yeah
it's
anybody can play around
with
the weights were
applied to
his arms and legs
and um
with padding
let's say
yes
and um
that went
very smoothly
I did that
for a few days
um
and
no problems
since
uh
I
I think
that the
um
I don't want to
use the word
diet
sorry
intake food
um
this person
has to have
um
everything chewed
for him
which would be
pureed food
um
uh
because of
digestion issues
and um
elimination
has improved
uh
almost
100 percent
um
because of that
and um
that's been
going very well
very well
that's amazing
yeah
uh
it is amazing
um
there are people
that have
visited him
that
are
uh
medical technicians
that
are amazed
at that
wow
yeah
and didn't
they were
didn't know what to say
they
they never know what to say
they can just repeat
what they've been
yeah
they can just only repeat
what's in their training
like the
like the circus bear
yeah
they didn't know what to say
and
yeah
you know
the circus bear looks really smart
to the audience
but if you put him in
with the other bears
in the forest
he's a real dummy
yeah
you know
right
you ever see the circus animals
like oh look how
look at this animal
you put that animal
in it's natural state
all the other animals are like
what's wrong with him
what an idiot
yeah
so
and um
uh
I have used the
um
restored the vacuum
on myself
well
my spouse did it for me
and I've done it for him
um
and
uh
I've actually done it on
it's been done on a child
um
a child now
is going into his
fourth year
and um
he's been eating
latitudinally
um
seasonally
yes
and um
he's doing very well
yes
you'd be like mid
we were talking about
mid hemisphere
not near the equator
and you're not in a cold place
you're not in a hot place
you're kind of across
the middle latitude
like middle
middle united
US
middle Europe
or middle China
so you still have a lot of variety
if you go across latitude
right
where you are
you can
you can go
I suggest people get
uh
yes I'll stay at a globe
and uh
find out where you're on the globe
and just spin the globe
clockwise or counterclockwise
and everywhere your finger lands
along that
line
uh
look up different recipes
from those countries
and that's how you get your variety
yeah
um
he had
the little one
had taken a
um
uh
transatlantic flight
that was in
uh
oh
year and a half ago
and was
uh
the only time that
this person
had been ill
was after that flight
right
and um
the parents asked if
I would take care of him
I said sure
and um
he had a fever of about
a hundred and three
so I got that down
uh
put the vacuum
restored the vacuum
through
um
weights on his little
legs and arms
and um
it just took
maybe a day
and he was fine
because I
I
discerned that it was
probably
um
possibly the
airplane flight itself
for sure
possible
uh
and what
and the eating
uh
it could have been a
pathogen that
the
the child acquired
that it replicated
yes
yeah
by the way these pathogens
that they tell you
that's why there's so much
into injecting
vaccines and things
into people
because they know for sure
they'll get it into your
system that way
uh
which is not
you know by the way
there's never been a study
uh
people say are you for
vaccines or against them
I was like neither
it's the dumbest thing
I've ever
heard you know
when you hear about
pathology
and
uh
all of these things about
um
what is the
the other field regarding
the disease
uh
it's so ridiculous
they don't even know
how the body works
how could you trust them
on therapies
and
and uh
remedies and things
they don't know anything
uh
again why would you tell
slaves you know
I mean they're just
you know like a chair
do you care if a chair
gets vaccinated or not
sure
shoot it up
big deal
but my point here
is very
simple
is um
the
the person's
susceptibility
to reproduce the
pathogen
is
when they get the
pathogen
you see
that's why how many times
have you heard
uh
various plagues
and
diseases that have gone
through society
and certain people didn't
come down with it
and
uh
it's not that they were
immune to it
their body did not
reproduce the pathogen
it's very simple
and
by the way
you've heard me say
there is no such thing
as an immune system
right
yeah
that's a fiction
medical fiction
you have
circulatory
nervous
and you have
eliminative
and nutritive
and you know
skin, lungs
and stomach
are all
nutritive
right
so
you have
the essence of
understanding
these things
when someone
for example
has a high temperature
what's going on
you know
in
near the equator
a fever
is a cold fever
uh
north and south
of the equator
uh
as you go further away
from the equator
the fever is always
a hot fever
and that's another
discussion
I never brought this up
and I probably won't
um
uh
for either ever
or a long time
because it
requires discussing
you know
doing sonics
on just how
you know
how the body works
how biological organisms
work
but
nonetheless
uh
what happens
with a fever
is the temperature
goes up
and uh
that's
that is the symptom
uh
of losing vacuum
so you already
started losing
your vacuum
before the fever
came on
you see what I mean
yeah
and I'm just going to
throw that as a hint
because then it gets
I have to get into
a discussion
on what a fever is
and why
you have hot fevers
in most places
and cold fevers
near the equator
and certain
venomous bites
create a cold fever
uh
make a
long story
short here
uh
for sure
and I'll just
stop on this
is that
most of the things
that people consider
other than replication
of a pathogen
um
to be an illness
or a state
of
bad health
is
because the vacuum
has been lost
you see
it's not that
restoring the vacuum
makes the fever
go away
it's that
when the vacuum
is restored
there is no reason
for a fever
there's no symptom
for it anymore
you see
um
it's just like
for example
the common cold
in western civilization
when winter
comes on
it has nothing to do
with any pathogens
it has to do with
their diet
yeah
because
they should have
started changing
their diet
weeks before the cold
come on
and once the cold
came on
uh
they're still eating
the same
food
that they
you know
that makes their body
uh
adjusted to a warmer climate
so
you see
all these things
the colds
fevers
the certain illnesses
are symptoms
way down the line
from the vacuum
being lost
uh
and restoring
the vacuum
makes these things
uh
mitigate
but
you know
here's the thing
when you try to
restore the vacuum
you're not really
restoring the vacuum
you're creating
a condition
for the body
to restore the vacuum
and sometimes
if the body
is too far gone
or too weak
um
no matter what you do
it will not
uh
go
back on
it's like
priming a pump
or
you know
when you
have to prime
put a little bit
of suction
so it can start working
if the pump
is damaged
you can prime it
all you want
it'll run a little bit
and it'll go back
it'll lose suction
and it won't work
so
uh
but that doesn't mean
you have to be in a
position to say
well
we've done everything
we can
it won't work
you still keep it going
because
the body's so resilient
and
another thing I want to say
is the modern medicine
and actually
modern medicine
I mean
if you go back
even a few thousand years
is a testament
to the robustness
of the human body
because
they don't even know
what they're doing
even today
at all
they cannot
simplify
the most foundation
basic principles
of anything biological
and all they do
is abuse
the majority of what they do
the biological
whether it's a vet
or a regular doctor
and people
still survive it
and it shows you
how resilient
and how
robust
the human body is
yeah
so
once you understand
the subtleties
and have a good foundation
on what's going on
in any biological organism
whether it's a plant
a bug
a small animal
a large animal
or a human
it
because we know
the living creatures
are very robust
and very resilient
the slightest push
gets it going
just like a stick shift
that won't start
you give it a little push
and as soon as the gear
turns the
crankshaft
at least 120 degrees
it fires up
so
yeah
this is all
because
of
the adversary
this is the
quote unquote
satanic society
on this planet
it has been for a long time
and
it's very simple to understand
when I say satanic
it's just the opposite
if something is simple
they say it's complex
if something is complex
they say it's simple
if something is black
they call it white
something is bad
they call it good
if it's good
they call it bad
it's just
the opposite
of
the
opposition
adversarial
yeah
okay
so
in terms of the body
when you say
restoring the vacuum
it's basically just
putting the squeeze
on things, right?
and pressure I would pretty much say yeah yeah yeah okay cool alright so yeah and from your experiences from what you've heard on Greek speak I'd say you're pretty much on your own just like anyone yeah whether it's a family member a friend or a passer-by the chances of anyone you know it's a very interesting thing right?
yeah you can't really talk to anyone about it they're not interested really or they just look at you like really?
what are you talking about?
right
I agree
pretty much impossible
to speak to anyone about it
that sounds like a
general electric
yeah
that's a general electric
turbine
you know the
Rolls-Royce turbines
they have a much
lower
they have like
a double hum
that was
a general electric
turbine
had that high
Rolls-Royce
on the end there
yeah
that's on the tail
that's what they call
the dopper
I don't know about
the Rolls-Royce
engines
they have like
a dual hum
on the front
but
anyway
are you all
listening to airplanes
or
yeah
I once did a
I had a discussion
with some people
on an airplane
a jet
that once you get it
going
the more
the faster you want to go
the less fuel you need
and it's silent
and they said
no we can't use that
design because the jet
has to make noise
oh I see
it's just like
when I do
certain car
modifications
they tell the
people
the higher ups
they go
no the car
has to have
pollution
you know
when you make
the pollution
go away
you know
they tell you
no it has to have
pollution
so
yeah
or it's not working
correctly
right
yeah
and people
ask them
you know
recently
are you guys
familiar
there was a
publicity
it was a
Rockefeller
or some
banking guy
said that
you need
sick people
it's good for
business
do you guys
remember that
it was an article
a couple of weeks
or maybe
a few months
ago
no
it was a
bank
advice me
yeah
talking about
funding
medical research
like we have
you have to
remember you
need sick
people
otherwise
it's bad
for business
that means
their glass is
overflowing
that means
that all of
what they're
doing is
to make you
sick
and the
glass is
full to the
top
and it
overflows
you see
yeah
if you go
to an
emergency
room or
hospital
they're
completely
ridiculous
what they do
there
unless you're
walking in with
your guts
hanging out
or you have
a gunshot
wound
even then
they treat
you like the
critical
they treat
immediately
but 99.99%
of the stuff
that people
go in the
emergency
room
if it
was done
the way
we've
discussed
it
would be
just fine
you know
actually if people
just knew about it
from
let's just go back
to what we said
earlier
you can't discuss
this with
people
so when I say
humanity is
unrehabilitatable
you can't fix
them
it's not
something that
you have to
consider
whether it's
believable or
not
it's something
that you
can directly
observe
that people
don't want
it
they can't
but you know
on the other
hand
the only
slack I cut
people or
humanity
the only
slack I
give them
is the
cosmic
censorship
in other
words it's
beyond
but if
people were
are the
way they
are in
their own
volition
oh no
they need to
drop all the
nukes right
now
yeah
they're very
evil
shitty
creatures
just like
Lord of the
Rings
where the bad
guy lives on
this planet
just nuke the
whole thing
but because
I know for
sure
that they
are subject
to cosmic
censorship
and just
getting rid
of them
you know
like you
would
clean out
a house
of roaches
or vermin
isn't going
to help
it doesn't
mean anything
because they're
not doing it
on their own
they don't
really know
and they
can't
you see
that's the
only slack
that I cut
humanity
but if you
were in a
let's say
flying through
the universe
and you said
these people
are not
subject to
cosmic
censorship
and they are
this way
oh that planet
needs to go
you need to
scrape it
you see
because that's
pure evil
you see what I
mean
but because
they're not
the majority
of the people
are evil
and downright
bad
but the
minority
that is not
downright evil
and bad
that is subject
to cosmic
censorship
they still
act just like
the evil ones
right
but how can you
discern if
someone is
downright evil
and
manifesting an
evil spirit
versus being
cosmically
censored
you can't
that's why you have
to cut humanity
slack
you know the
interesting part
is when you
read about
the
a lot of the
dictators that
would do
like
they would go
and destroy
large segments
of their
population
these were not
they didn't just do it
because they were
brutal and crazy
they did it
because they saw
the people
as being
unrehabilitatable
and it had to be done
to at least
leave something
good just like
the way you
you know you
pull out weeds
to have a good
lawn
what they didn't
understand
is the cosmic
censorship
and because
there's cosmic
censorship
and you can't tell
who's who's who
you have to leave
the whole bunch
alone
and you have to
let the gods
do it
you see what I mean?
I see
but in other words
what I'm saying is
there's some bad
shit coming on
this world
and
even when it
starts to come
when it comes
the people are not
going to view it
as being bad
because it's going
to be part of the
setup
but you know
yeah
the spouse and I
have talked about
that
how good
it's going to be
and then how
terrible and
horrible it's
going to be
the worst it's
ever been in
since the beginning
in human history
and
it's hard
it's hard to
fathom
how bad
I mean
how much worse
can it get
worldwide
all at once
right
but remember
just like the
flood
it comes in a
wave
you know
I know
And that's in scripture, that's in scripture as well.
Well, it's in scripture by example.
Here and there, yeah.
By example by the Christ, because the Christ symbolizes the end times, by the way.
And this is another discussion.
You know, I have a couple of clipboards with discussions I was going to do on the radio at AFR and with Seth and with Sam and all this stuff, and I just put a big X through all this stuff.
And a lot of it was, like, I'm not going to discuss this stuff in public.
And actually, I have to get paid for it, because I have to sit down and to do this right, I'm going to have to do references and really buckle down and do a professional presentation.
But one of the topics is what the Christ symbolizes here on earth.
Because he didn't have to really do what he did and come to earth and do what he did, but he did because it's symbolic of a certain time period.
See, because if you lived, and this is all I'm going to say about it, if you lived in the first century, just like today, I mentioned I did a survey a while back asking people, do you think we're in the end times?
And 99 out of 100 said yes, or 90 out of 100 people said yes, we're in the end times, but no one can explain how and why in any detail.
If you ask those questions back in the first century, are we in the end times, 99 out of 100 people say yes, we are.
But they couldn't give any detail.
So, just like you might have heard me say before, any time in history, if you preach doom and gloom, people will listen because they like that.
You know, it sounds about right.
But is it right?
And the answer is no.
Just like it wasn't right for the first century, and it's not right the way they're doing it now.
You know how they give dates next year when we have five years left?
They can't tell you why and how in detail.
And the details of all of this stuff is in the life of the Christ.
He keeps talking about Terran building, destroying things and building things up.
This is also brought up in Jeremiah.
It's very important.
Well, I'm going to take something here for a moment.
I'll be right back.
Give me about one minute.
Okay?
Okay.
You guys talk amongst yourselves.
Alrighty.
You know, it seems like a big giant time loop.
Sometimes it does, like a circle or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's very interesting.
You know, speaking, he brought up Revelation earlier.
Well, I guess that's a secret.
But it seems like it's past, present, and future type of a book.
And if it was his first book, I guess that makes sense.
Right.
But that is a difficult book to comprehend.
And I think he's correct that maybe no one does.
Just the observation alone in my daily walk.
I just heard that Revelation something in your daily walk.
Well, it gives you the instructions in the first verse or two, in Replica of Revelation, how to comprehend that.
And they're simple.
And they do, when you read Scripture, it means what it says, and it says what it means.
It's for the servants, not for believers, right?
If it was the believers, it would say that.
And belief has to do with having information before something manifests.
That's all belief is.
There's no other.
That's why all the world religions, the small and the major in my words, are garbage.
Because they ask you, what do you believe in?
And it's garbage.
Ask any religious person.
Doesn't matter what it is.
That was like 30,000 different religions in the world.
Seven billion potential religions, right?
Because everyone makes shit up all the time.
And it's all garbage because they base it on belief.
And you can ask them belief of what?
And they can't answer.
And what they do answer is Mickey Mouse.
Without a doubt.
And so it has nothing to do with belief, because belief is information of the future.
So if you believe in something and it doesn't happen, guess what?
That was not a good belief.
But if you believe in something and it does manifest, guess what?
That was a good belief.
You see?
So it's very temporal belief.
It has nothing to do with what...
But then again, the last thing you want to do is have the idiots on this planet give them incompatible...
You see, people are a project...
Or a project.
Yeah, I could call it a project.
Or the product of thousands of years of malevolent spirits guiding them.
And they do so willingly and unwillingly, unknown.
But they still don't question it.
So you could say unwilling.
Not unwilling, but just unknown.
And the truth with people is incompatible at this point.
Because it's incompatible.
Number one.
Number two, they're devoid of the ability, because of cosmic censorship, and the cultural and social pressures that they have to learn the truth.
Right?
Okay.
And those very, very few that the truth can be compatible with them, and they have transcended the social, cultural, familial pressure, and can deal with the truth, it doesn't mean you can still deal with the book of Revelation, because the instructions in Revelation are, it's for the servants.
Yes.
So, does the servant sit around on the couch all day?
Or does he do things?
A servant is a service function.
A doer.
Yes.
He's a doer.
Right.
Exactly.
So, just that one thing for the servants.
Now, to find a servant, you could write an essay on what a servant is and what a servant isn't.
And now, you start to really narrow it down to see who can comprehend the book of Revelation.
And there's nothing better than hiding a secret in plain sight.
And the primer is held within.
The code...
In other words, years ago, if anyone knows about the American military, the Marines, they get all the hand-me-downs from the Navy and the Army.
So, they develop technologies, weapons, communication devices for the Army and the Navy.
And if it's too complicated or it's not popular, they just...
old stuff, they hand it down to the Marines.
So, they developed years ago an Army communication signal where it would scramble the signal and also send the...
and unscramble and then scramble the signal in real time.
So, whoever got it didn't know which was scrambled and which wasn't.
And they had a code that would also change in real time.
So, when it all got together, they'd have to piece it together very quick, chop, chop, chop, to get the signal.
You see what I mean?
Because the Army before, it was too complicated for them, but it was almost impossible to crack.
Because sometimes it sent the clear signal and the enemy, let's say, would get it and think that it was coded and they would try to mix it up again, but it was the real thing.
And then the next second it would be coded and they wouldn't know which way it was up, right?
Right.
So, it was a great system.
It used fuzzy logic and all that.
And the Army was like, oh, we're not used to it, man.
It's either all coded or all non-coded.
So, they said, okay, let's give this system to the Marines.
Because, you know, it's a left-handed gun and the Marines were like, this is great.
This is great.
This is the best thing.
We know for sure that when we send something across this, no one will figure it out.
Because they can't tell if we're coding it or not.
You see what I mean?
So, here's the point on this.
You can read scripture all you want, but if you don't wrap your mind around the book of Revelation, you're never going to see what's going on.
That's a fact.
That's why no one can explain the book of Revelation publicly.
You get it?
Because Revelation is clear sometimes and other times it's in code.
Right?
In other words, most people think when they read something that they think they understand, that's clear.
And then something that's not understood, they think it's code.
I'm telling you, it could be reverse.
Some of the things that you think are clear is really the code.
It's scrambled.
And things that seem coded are clear.
And it switches back and forth.
But how do you discern that?
By example.
Remember?
Remember the scripture says, you know, I'm going to repeat myself in the book of Isaiah, and I'm going to give you examples.
Right?
Right.
Yeah.
If Revelation is the...
And I should have never gone...
I'm the only person I think that's ever gone on in history saying that the book of Revelation is the first book of the Bible.
Now, what does that mean?
It's the blueprint.
And Genesis is when you start putting the shovel to the ground.
Okay.
So, Revelation is past, present, and future.
Altogether.
Yes.
It's really, all of it is the future.
But it's in the time outside of what we consider any event that we know.
Other events that we don't know.
Because the writing of the book itself, where that information compiled, was an event unto itself.
You see?
So, then when you go through the scripture, you're going to figure out there is not only a numeric order to the books, right?
But you're also going to see that there is a concentration of, you know, when most...
You know, you have most of scripture with Moses, and then most of scripture around the time of King David, and then little bits here and there, and then a little bit of what they call the New Testament, right?
Or a lot of it, allegedly.
Right?
And now we have nothing for 2,000 years.
Almost.
1,900 years.
Nothing.
Right?
Do you see the patterns?
You know, there's nothing written for the first 2,000 some odd years.
Actually, it depends on which man you're talking about.
Right.
The first man or Adam.
But either way, once you start to look at these patterns, the actual symbology, in other words, when and how scripture was inspired for man to record it, is part of the code.
And that's all I'm going to say about that.
But you have to live it.
And here's the thing, I think everybody needs to do what they do, but we're so closed right now that even if you did nothing, that's why very often I tell them, do nothing.
Just wait it out.
Food, clothing, and shelter.
Yeah.
You know, let's talk slave talk.
Pay your bills, brush your teeth, go to sleep, work, repeat the cycle.
Doesn't matter.
And because here, in the end time, there are going to be people that are going to have a calling to do certain things.
You know, knowledge-based, not physical, because you'll be squashed like a bug.
And that's evident.
We're not talking about lying to the people like all the ministers and preachers and rabbis and imams are doing.
We're talking about, you know, real calling.
Now, how do you know if you have a real calling?
Because if you, your life is to do nothing, just support yourself and your family and just brush your teeth, watch TV, sleep, wash, you know, defecate, whatever you, the most basic biological stuff, and you are led in a way to do extraordinary things.
That is not you doing it.
You're one of those that has the calling, or being called, chosen and called.
You see what I mean?
Forget about, you know, there's no school of the prophets or let's go groom these people to go out in the world and tell people the truth.
That's a bunch of shit, if you ask me.
That's all platonic garbage that you see, you know, the adversary doing that, putting it in your mind.
But if you lead a life where you are knowledge-based,
and you know you have integrity and you know the truth,
and your goal in life is to do nothing other than exist as lawfully as possible and study,
and you find yourself being endowed with support,
and whether it's financial, you know, physical support,
you know, where not just, you know, people coming to help with your personal stuff,
but to move a certain thing on without a message, without asking,
that is the gods doing that.
And this is the time period for that.
So, that's why I always suggest, do nothing.
And if you find yourself in extraordinary positions, that's the gods doing it.
It's the gods doing it regardless.
Like, if you see wealthy people, I've been in the presence of some of the wealthiest people around, on the planet, and they're idiots.
I'm telling you.
They're very savvy in certain aspects, and you can see that they were there because the gods put them there.
Right?
But what I would suggest is that if your goal in life is to do nothing, and you're put in extraordinary places, then you might be one of those that are not only called but chosen.
So.
Yeah.
Well, this is an interesting...
What does this all mean?
You do it for your personal satisfaction, your personal, private, spiritual growth, which means absolutely nothing when you compare it to what you're going to have later anyway.
Because right now, in order for you to learn and perceive, you're either going to have a direct download, you know, from the other side, or you're going to have to study, or hear it from someone else, and then study.
Right?
So, all that stuff is still minimal.
And also, no matter how much you try to learn or whatever right now, you know how much of it has been censored out?
I'm not talking about cosmic censorship now.
How much of the truth has been hidden, from a, let's say, academic, for lack of a better term, point of view?
You know, like, how many times have you heard, the burning of the Library of Alexandria?
They keep saying that.
The burning of the Library of Alexandria.
But they never talk about the Library of Alexandria, because it wasn't burned.
It was burned.
The building was burned.
And anything that was made a copy of was burned.
You know what I mean?
There are many copies.
Remember years ago, going to the library, and there was more than one copy of a book?
Well, you leave the copies, and a certain amount of copies, and whatever, and you burn the thing, and you tell people it's done.
But it's not.
All that stuff still exists.
The majority of it.
Yeah.
But you don't have access to it.
I don't have access to it.
Bruce doesn't have access to it.
Yeah.
So, but later on, you won't need that to get knowledge.
I mean, after the Resurrection.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
You'll be able to do direct download if you inquire.
So right now, again, so that's why I keep saying, why bother?
The real juicy stuff right now, all you're going to get right now in this life, or for anyone, doesn't matter who it is, unless you have internal access to this stuff on the physical realm, is a direct download from the gods.
Right?
Where, you know, that's where people ask people, where do ideas come from?
I don't know.
I was just doing this, and I got the idea.
But remember, they have to do something.
No one's ever invented anything sitting around all day.
They're working on stuff, and an accident happens, right?
That's the new invention.
Or they're working on something that's a failure.
Someone else is like, this can be a great thing if we used it like this.
Like, you know, the Post-its, remember?
Sure.
Mm-hmm.
Designed of super glue, and it didn't stick, you know, see, it didn't stick to anything.
And the secretary says, this stuff is great.
Can you give me more of them?
And if you look at the...
I just happened to glance at a little bit of study on Trevor, and he was mentioning how the study of the ether came about by an accident of a guy stepping on a pipe and watching over a lake and how it changed.
Well, that was more on the weather.
The ether was before that.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, Wilhelm Reich was biological forces.
Oh, that's neat.
Yes.
Yeah, well, they were building at his HQ up in Maine and the construction site, some pipes went into a puddle, and he would notice a shimmer in the atmosphere every time he did it.
Yeah.
Well, right now, that's been evolved.
Weather work has been evolved.
Like, imagine what telephones and TVs looked like back in the 50s.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
And what telephones and TVs are like now.
Right?
Wow.
Now, if you go on the Internet, all these weather devices, cloudbusters and Trevor's stuff, that's 30-, 40-year-old TVs and phones, cell phones or whatever.
Right now, what exists is like a modern TV.
We've evolved it to the point where it's unrecognizable as such.
Like everything else.
Yeah.
So, and I was one of the last people to work with Trevor before he passed.
The last time I spoke to Trevor, his wife said, well, he's in a hospice right now, and that was it, you know.
Wow.
So, that was years ago.
But I remember we were sending, I have a box of his personal notes and things that he sent me, and I sent, I would build certain experimental things and send them to him back and forth in the mail, and he, well, the last time, one of the few last times we spoke was, I don't understand how it works, but it does work, he said.
So, I knew I was on the right track.
So, that's what I mean about, right now it's, it's not on the internet.
It's evolved to the point, all I do, basically, regarding weather stuff is tell people the principle.
Take a piece of metal and wrap it in non-metallic material, put a mirror on the back.
Yeah.
You know, for starters.
That's, and even the water guns now are evolved to the point where they're over a hundred times more efficient than what Wilhelm Reich was doing.
Right now we can do anywhere on the planet.
Not just locally.
From one location.
So.
I don't understand.
And that's, truth in it, yeah.
Yeah.
We can do weather, it doesn't matter where you are.
Because it's the ether, right?
Right.
Princeton, it's everywhere.
You can do weather on the moon.
So.
And by the way, if anyone wants to discuss that, if you have a pretty good telescope and you're at a high altitude, just pick a crater on the moon.
You don't have to name them.
You could look up, you know, whatever you like.
And start observing it.
Right?
You film it or whatever, right?
You can even have a four-inch telescope.
I have an eight-inch Dobsonian, which is pretty good, with a two-inch thickness fastener, so it's very stable.
But, if you study any of the craters night after night, well, actually the moon changes every day, but if you study, if you start learning the features on the craters, and sometimes you look at the feature, let's say the rim of a crater, and you can't get it in physics, or you don't see it, but minutes later you do, guess why?
Because that's a cloud over the crater.
Asteric cloud.
Like, imagine, so let me give you another example.
If you were on the moon with a telescope looking in the direction of space, you would insist on things, no matter how high.
The tallest buildings wouldn't really show up.
You would have to take a photograph of it, and then put it on a big screen, and start magnifying and looking at it very carefully.
And it would be a blur.
Manhattan, you wouldn't see any of the streets, right?
Because of what's called reflectivity.
Mm-hmm.
Have you ever been on an airplane and looked down at, like, a big parking lot, all the cars look the same?
How can they all look the same when there are, like, silver cars, blue cars, red cars, white cars?
Well, when you get to a certain distance and the sunlight is so intense, they all have the same reflectivity, and you can't tell what color anything is anymore.
Mm-hmm.
So now let's put this in reverse.
If we're on Earth looking at the moon, you really can't see what's going on until you really study it, and then you're going to see there is tremendous activity there.
I mean, it looks like Tokyo, if you really want to get into it, or New York City looks primitive.
Anyway, if you want to get more information, there's a guy that has integrity.
He doesn't...
He's pretty censored, but he does...
It's called Bruce Stiesow.
And there's another guy called Alien Hunter, I think, and he puts up just photos that NASA had from the lunar orbiter in the 60s before they started transferring everything digitally.
Okay.
And you could look at them, and you see, like, streets.
You ever see, like, go to Google Maps, put in Manhattan, streets treat you from the top.
Satellite view, you see a grid pattern, right?
New buildings, you know?
So...
So, I mean, the moon is a very active place.
It has an atmosphere and all that.
So, what does this have to do with the heat?
That's a really loud cicada.
That is.
So, my point here is when I talk about the ether, it's as common as cities and other things are that we consider.
You know, applesauce, chocolate pudding, biscuits, poppy seed muffins, anything you see, an elephant, a house, a bird or a plane, anything you see and can acknowledge, the ether is in all of that.
It's everywhere, right?
So, the commonality that you see here on earth, you can somewhat...
I'm not going to put my foot down and say the moon is inhabited and all that, but you will see man-made structures or made structures on the moon that just look like any...
whatever.
You know?
But what's interesting is if the earth was no longer inhabited after a few dozen years, it would...
looking down at a city, the overgrowth would start taking over, right?
Or if you lived near a desert, the streets would be full of...
about a foot full of sand.
You wouldn't see the asphalt anymore.
You see?
Even now, if everybody left in Manhattan, within about 30 or 40 years, you wouldn't see the streets anymore.
It would be full of sand and dirt and dust.
You know?
So, if you imagine what you're looking at when you're looking at other planets and you start to see the level of development on the moon, it really hits you across the head like something...
you know.
But anyway.
Yeah.
You know how you say you've been lied to and you know things told you?
Do you really want to know more?
Because, you know how I say, who are you going to tell it to?
And like Sam used to always say, it doesn't matter.
But after a point, it does, because you'll realize you're on your own.
So that brought up the thing on the moon, because yes, you can do weather on the moon.
But don't do it when it's like a full moon, because that's like doing stuff on high noon and you're competing with the sun.
So, that's a whole other discussion.
I think weather work and...
you know, we discussed the body and dreams.
I think going into...
developing these subjects publicly is for the next society, not for this one.
Still very interesting.
It is.
Yeah.
Especially if you could decrease suffering.
I don't like using...
You know, we like to in common use to help someone, but who cares?
No one...
You know, people like to say that because it makes them feel good to help someone.
But the reality is if you really are on a higher level, operating on a higher level, at this point in human existence, you do it to decrease their suffering.
You get it?
Yeah.
Because you really can't help anyone.
I can see that.
It's to decrease suffering.
Because even the healthiest, most affluent person is still experiencing some level of suffering if they are learning the truth.
Sure.
And it's interesting to not ponder, and just to bring this up again, the level of people that has been adopted by the human race, across the board, any religion, any country, any race or whatever, should not be pondered much because once you understand how much it is cosmic censorship and how much of it is their inherent evil, we will not know until later.
Only the gods know that.
Right?
Because the gods do have earmarked certain people for destruction, even though they won't be resurrected.
The gods, you know, it does consider certain races, family lines, nationalities to be downright evil.
But we don't...
I mean, other than what scripture, you know, tells us explicitly, we don't know.
And that should be kept in mind.
Because if there's this wiping out large swaths of their population, that's the error that they had.
Because they were trying to do the job of the gods.
The gods will start wiping out very large swaths of humanity for that reason.
I don't think any human is capable of doing it for that reason.
We just don't know who's censored and who's not.
You know what I mean?
So...
I can tell you that the majority of the people on the planet are just downright no good and evil.
And what I'm saying, I'm saying from a biblical point of view, not from what they think.
You know?
Yeah.
They have no idea.
Because if you boil it down, also, they're just property.
Most people on the planet, except for a few thousand people, are viewed as property.
Like a chair, or a shoe, or a sock, or a lawn that needs to be mowed.
So, don't buy into the bullshit.
That's how they're viewed, by the leadership.
I'm not talking about the politicians, either.
Yeah.
And I don't think scripture exhausts one's inability or rubs the reader in a way that they have to find out who is who.
That's why very often you'll see a very general, you know, when it says, the king of the north, why scripture couldn't give you his exact name and physical description?
Of course it could.
The reason why it just says the leader of the north is because it's a secret.
And it's meant to be that way.
Yeah.
Yet there's hundreds of thousands of YouTubes just on that.
And none of it's true.
It's stupid.
None of it's true.
Oh, you mean, oh, the people attempting...
Yeah, people attempting that.
Oh, yeah.
Explaining this, explaining that, the total confusion.
The people that know don't go on YouTube.
Right.
True, I'll tell you that for sure.
No, yes.
Uh-huh, scripture, yeah.
Yeah.
But, you know, people watch those things as in going to temples, church, etc.
And they think they know.
And they're positive.
That's the answer.
Well, here's the other aspect of it.
You know, I remember I said that if you pass through the planet and you pointed at the earth and said, this is the planet that's inhabited by the sons and daughters of the adversary, Satan, that would be very accurate.
Right?
Meaning, sons and daughters doesn't mean that's your spiritual father.
Spiritual, yeah.
Yeah.
Because when you say your father, you have the biological one and then you have the spiritual one.
And that's why in a lot of religious sense they call priests father because that's where you get your law and your right and wrong and your spiritual father, right?
The spiritual father of humanity is the adversary, the Satan.
So, that's why the most deplorable thing you still have people out there saying you're branding someone as a Satanist.
They're not.
They're all Satanists on this planet.
So if they're all Satanists, who are you going to point a finger to, you see?
If everything is all black, well, you know, point to the black.
If everything is all hot, point to the hot.
You can't.
You need a contrast.
And the contrast is not public.
It's all, it's pretty much all, it's like a monopoly.
There's a satanic monopoly on this planet.
Adversarial, right?
But, keeping that in mind, right, if one were to encounter that being known as the chief adversary, do you know what he would be saying to you?
Everything that comes out of his mouth would be scripture, against you.
It's not like the way Hollywood, you know, remember?
Yeah, yeah.
The power of Christ compels you, like the exorcist.
That's all a bunch of crap.
And by the way, when these Catholics, you know, engage in these demonic exorcisms, those are demons that follow them around, specifically, anyway.
Those are minor demons.
That's not Satan, by the way, the chief adversary.
Those are minor, you know.
But anyway, the point here is this, there is a monopoly on this insanity.
That's why, again, you know, how much of it is censorship, and how much of them are inherent in this, dedicated.
Because, let me just clarify one point about inherent.
You know, the bloodline, the familiar thing.
Going back a long time, there are people on this planet who have dedicated themselves to evil.
And you wouldn't know if your grandparents, or great, great, great, great, great, you know, parents were part of that group.
You know what I mean?
That's why it's good to renounce ancestry, doing the opposite of what the Asians do, which is worship them.
You know?
Like, for example, I renounce anyone that came before me in my private space to the gods.
I'm like, I don't want anything to do with the people that came before me, if I can spiritually, because I don't know anything about them.
Yeah.
And at this point, I don't want to know anything about them, and don't attach what I want to do, what will I want to perform here, with their stuff.
So, what I'm saying is that there are people that have dedicated themselves to dark forces, that still, their progeny, in other words, their generation still exists.
The people that still exist don't know that, but the gods do.
The gods see that, you see.
That's what I mean by the inherent evil that exists in the world.
So, but the interesting thing is, um, uh, well, I don't know, there's a lot, actually, I don't know what to say first here, but there's a lot of interesting aspects to it, and like you said earlier, on the YouTubes and all this stuff, none of this stuff is out in the public, in accuracy.
There are those that have tried, look what, in the mid-1800s, they tried real hard, they got the rupture, the rapture, when it didn't come, you know, the end of the world didn't come, you know, they got people who sell their stuff, and all that, so it created the rapture, or rupture, or whatever.
And then, uh, in the mid-50s in America, you had the Armstrongism, uh, the evangelists, you know, uh, all that, a bunch of crock of stuff, and then you had the Ernest L.
Martin's crock of crap again.
They all, they all did a little bit of work that brought stuff to the surface, but as a whole, you need to discount them and put them aside when you understand this was all a secret.
Yeah.
And also, you can go back even hundreds of years, forget about the Catholic Church and all that other stuff, but all these guys I mentioned in the 20th century, they did it for the money also, and to make, they, like, um, the evangelists and all the other guys that came after them, they have some books that have some notable things in them.
What you'll see is that they still use the J-E-S-U-S, and they use the G-O-D, fervently, and they use the Christian term, okay, and I've confronted some of them, and I've said this many times, and the reason why they do that is because they want to make a living doing that.
That's how much faith they have.
In other words, they, I've had some of them, I say this again, they say, well, Greek, if we tell people that you can't keep time with the Pope's work schedule, no one's going to want to buy our books or listen to us.
So that's how much faith they have.
And they, and they know that.
Oh, yeah.
They know.
Yeah, I've run into people that were around me, Armstrong, since the 50s and 60s, worked for them, and Ernest L.
Martin and all those guys, and I brought up the points about the Pope's work schedule and using the names, and they're like, oh, yeah, no, no, we can't do that because that'll divide us.
Oh, boy.
And we won't buy our books.
And, you know, we get $4,000 a month from this and that.
I'm like, oh, man, you guys are a bunch of, you know, they talk about good Christians and real Christians, and they're like, oh, by the way, that's, if you see the J-E-S-U-S and the Christian come out of anything, it's, you're going to be, now you're sifting for corn and poop.
That's a pile, a big pile of poop.
All the Ernest Martin stuff and the, and the, the stuff that came out of the Worldwide Church of God and other stuff, that's a huge pile of poop.
You need to go through there and find some corn if you want to.
It's all poop.
And these people are, I'll pass.
I'll pass.
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't mean you, you know, if you put a clothespin on your nose, you can go through it.
Fortunately, there are a lot of other people that have gone through it that you can pull out the good stuff.
Sure.
You know.
But all of these people are always looking to support themselves based on the status quo, which was Christianity and Asclepius, you know, the J-E-S-U-S character, and all the versions that they have, and they focus on the writings of Paul.
How many, you know, you don't even have the New Testament.
I've even said many times to people, go online, do a cursory observe, search, how many verses have been added and taken away from the New Testament?
There's plenty of websites on that now.
There weren't, there wasn't nothing on there ten years ago.
Yeah.
Now there is.
And they, and that way they tell you this verse was added and they'll give you the reasons how and why.
So...
Yeah.
So even if you have a K-J-V New Testament, that's poop.
You're going to have to go in there and look at the corn.
Find the corn.
I'm telling you, it's really that bad.
You don't have the New Testament.
You don't have anything like that.
You have versions of it that are so far removed from the contextual information that if you said it does not exist in an integral form that's very accurate to say that.
It has no integrity.
But you're going to have to, for example, Sabrinthi's saying that the New Testament is poop and you shouldn't read it.
No, I'm saying it is poop, but you should read it.
You're going to have to go through there and really pick out, you're going to have to do your research, find out, you know, what the Catholic Church put in, what the, uh, uh, what the academics put in, what they took out.
But I'll tell you this for sure.
This is for sure.
The New Testament is poop.
And I don't say guarantee, but I will guarantee you and assure you, I usually say assure because only the gods can guarantee, but let's say as close to a guarantee as possible.
If you don't have a full comprehension of Mosaic Law, you will be wrapped around the axle and you will never understand the integrity of the New Testament.
And you will not be able to see the mistakes in the New Testament.
There are huge mistakes that are contrary to, uh, so if I were to tell you the New Testament and the testimony of the Christ does not exist in an integral form, that is absolutely accurate.
Is there a body of work known as the New Testament that needs to be gone through and researched?
Absolutely.
Yes.
For sure.
It needs to be looked at.
And that was beyond graduate level.
Yeah.
And it's getting a little late for that, right?
Oh, yeah.
It's getting late, but it will be done because it's promised that it will be, it will be, uh, exposed to the world and then, but it will be very late, won't be now, won't be for another decade or so.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, you know, take Paul for instance.
Um, you know, people that, yeah, there are people who have built, oh, how many denominations just on a few things that he had to say.
Yeah, all of them.
Yeah.
Or it wasn't even true.
I mean, he's a woman hater, uh, women, women can't do this, women can't do that.
Um, et cetera.
But it's all out of context.
Yeah, he, he didn't, actually.
He doesn't hate women.
No, no, you, you also told the whole thing of, of, of Wilbur's writings as prospect anyway.
Yeah.
You know, because he's not an apostle.
So, you might be of a different, because he was, he never met the Christ.
Yeah, and who was he speaking to also?
Yeah, there's a lot of problems with it, but, here's the thing, if you, and also if you understand, uh, um, the writings of Paul, I've gone through them, and I said, ooh, this is beyond graduate level also.
This is here, this is the stumbling block that Isaiah spoke about to many.
Yeah.
if you, like for example, if you go to, uh, third, fourth graders, uh, and give them a university theoretical calculus book, what are they going to get out of it?
Nothing.
They're going to recognize in the equation the numbers, because they know from one, if you know zero to nine you can make all the numbers, right?
That's all, and outside of that, there may be an equals sign and a parenthesis, they know nothing.
So, what they, what the powers that be did for thousands of, of millennia, at least, uh, is they put the writings of Paul, where they knew you wouldn't understand it, because before that they would only put it in a foreign language, like Latin.
Right?
So, now they said, no, let's keep confounding them, let's give them the language they understand, we'll put Paul in front of them, which they will totally screw them up.
And that's perfect.
That's exactly what, what you, if you're flying by the planet, uh, and said, these are, you know, these are the adversaries' children here, you, you want to confuse a bunch of idiots, give them the writings of Paul.
Because Paul, uh, just to make a long story short, he was an ex-parishion, he was in the high political in the priesthood, right?
And he was well-studied, he had the best education money can buy, that's brought up, because not only did he have the best education money can buy, he had the best political status money can buy, right?
Because, he says, I had bought my citizenship, right?
So he had the best stuff that money can buy.
Yeah.
But ultimately, even today, if you have the best education money can buy, is that a real education, or is it still part of the bullshit?
Part of it.
But what people don't understand is that, uh, back then, in the Judean culture, even though he was not a Judean, it was the Benjamite, Benjamite, yeah.
Yeah, uh, he, uh, he still had to be prolific in the law, he still had to know the law.
You see?
So he knew that, uh, but the political sense, and also his mission, was very, very disturbing, because he went to people that didn't know the law.
Right.
So he had to tell them that don't, basically, this is the message of Paul in a nutshell.
All that pagan shit that you're told, you die, you go to heaven, or hell, or past lives, and future lives, is all bullshit.
Um,
you, you,
you could rest assure
that the truth has been
exposed,
because the Christ came,
he died,
and was resurrected,
so now we know exactly
what is meant by the
resurrection,
because we've had
physical proof of it,
and, uh,
if you don't know
what I'm talking about,
which you probably don't,
because you know nothing
other than that pagan
bullshit,
you're going to have to
eventually study the law.
But when you study the law, you have to keep in mind that you're going to die anyway, and what happens after you die is what the Christ showed us.
And that is all the writing of Paul in a nutshell.
Yeah.
And also, basically, by the way, uh, the law, you know why the law brings death?
You know, he says that?
If you're in a pagan culture, and you insist on biblical law, what are they going to do to you?
They'll kill you.
Right.
Yeah.
Yep.
And that's reading out of it.
And also, when he spoke to the pagans or the non-Judeans about the law, they didn't like it, because they didn't know Mosaic law, they knew the Paradishim, what's called the Halakha law, which was the law that, uh, next to the law that prevented you from breaking the law, right?
Like, you know what Halakha is?
It's a hedge.
So, let's say the Mosaic law says don't eat pork.
Well, the Halakha would be, well then, let's not, let's prohibit pigs from being in the country, because if there are no pigs in the country, then people can't break the law, you know, transgress by eating pork.
Yeah.
But they, see, because that makes it very hard.
So, for example, if the law, the Mosaic law says be in by sundown, the Halakha says you have to be in two hours by sundown.
Right?
And so what happens is they force the people and enforce the two hours before sundown, but those that know the law, they don't do it.
They just come in at sundown, but see, so that's why I said you force the law on the people, it's like a heavy burden, but to you, you don't rest a finger.
He's not talking about the Mosaic, he's talking about the laws that they put the people Put on the people to control them.
To control them, to prevent them from breaking the law, from transgressing the law, by making other laws that surround the law, so if you at least follow those, there's no way you're going to fall into transgression.
So, you know, a very simple one is the pork example.
You know, don't eat pork.
You know, you might want to have pigs on the farm because they serve a purpose as scavengers and for the soup, compost, and all that.
But, you know, if there's starvation, if there's hunger, you might slaughter and eat it for its meat.
But, you know, I'd rather eat grass.
So if they decide no pigs in the country, then even if there's starvation, they still can't, you know, transgress that, you see.
So, it's much harder to do the, it's harder on the people to do the halakha, which is the hedge.
I'm sure.
But Christ knew that.
That's why he says ask for a hedge of protection around you, meaning like if you know what the law of the gods is, then develop in your mind systems that go beyond that so that you don't approach the borderline.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
You know, there's a lot of, but basically I broke down Paul in a nutshell, which will never be understood if you call yourself Christian, by the way.
And if you're Christian, you will never comprehend the Bible, I'll tell you that for sure, because what happens there is that you you will be censored.
If you're censored enough to be limited and not renounce those religions, whether it's Islam, Judaism, or Christianity, because Judaism, by the way, is Babylonian, you know.
Sure, sure.
It's not a religion as much as it is a tradition that's become a religion.
So, I don't know, what I do, well, I mean, in other words, the reason why I say I don't know is like, what angle do you take on describing and explaining what people are engaging in with their religion, their education, and their beliefs?
I mean, there's so many angles.
It's just, yeah, it's overwhelming.
It's overwhelming, it's screwed up.
Yeah.
But the thing that isn't overwhelming and screwed up is that when the gods make it right, it's going to be right, where man can't do it right now.
And the very simple thing is the, is, um, this is still the least, from a legal point of view, the least of the earth and its inhabitants is to the adversary.
Right?
So, when that lease runs up and it's time for his eviction or his containment, then that time, so these are things that are beyond human power and beyond, again, to bring it up again for the third time, this is the mistake that these dictators made through the ages, thinking that if they eliminate a group of the population or a certain group of people, they're going to fix things.
That doesn't work, right, from a human perspective.
Only the gods can do that properly.
Yeah.
To say those things shouldn't be done is foolish from a, from a cosmic, divine censorship.
Why?
Not because I believe so or my liking or liking, because the gods say so.
Um, speaking of the adversary, when did he get his lease?
When was he given his lease?
That's...
Sometime around, sometime around, um, well, that's an interesting thing because there's options.
It would have either been in the sixth day or the eighth day, so it would have been 6,000 years ago or 8,000 years ago.
It's not that clear, but I would say, I would presume 8,000 years ago.
Yeah.
But not with a different intention.
It's kind of like you get a lease to a place to live in and now you're going to run a, and then later on, you, not only do you live there, but you run a business out of it.
Right?
It's like someone gets an apartment just to live and then they run a home business out of it and it changes.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Because right now, it's, uh, you know, it's to the point where, you know, actually, go ahead.
You were going to say something?
No.
He had a responsibility, um, um, I think that was from Ezekiel of...
Right.
Certain things, precious things.
Yeah.
And he was pulled from that position from a cosmic level.
He was pulled from that to do this.
But also, keep in mind the time already ended.
You know, I've mentioned before, you're in the credits right now, so one thing about the lease is it could have ended already.
Mm-hmm.
You know, and you have the grace period now to get out.
So, just from, from an informationalist point of view, I would suggest that his lease already ended roughly 20 years ago.
And this is just the grace period.
I would, I would suggest from a legal point of view, cosmic legal, legality, that it ended.
Yeah.
Because, you know, even when your lease ends, they give you, it's like, you know, when you're late on the rent, what do they give you?
Five, ten days some places, seven days, three days, depends.
Yeah, so the grace period to, yeah, I think it already ended 20 years ago.
These things are, you know, things that need to be, inquiry needs to be done on and, uh, they need to be rationalized.
It can't be, well, the worst thing anybody can say is, well, this guy said this, and I like him, so I'm going to go with that.
Or the worst thing is, I want to know what your take on this, what do you mean, my take?
What is this, like Hollywood, take one, take two?
What do you mean, my take?
Yeah.
You know, or what your opinion is, you know, who cares?
Those things are, in the future, will be dealt with in great severity regarding matters of importance.
Mm-hmm.
In a negative way or any severity.
That's sort of the adversary stuff.
Again, if, if the state of mankind has been this way for thousands of years, so, you know, if you look at, give you an example, the state that has been preserved, this, this fucked up state, to use the medical term there, Mm-hmm.
uh, for thousands of years of mankind, now, the, the contrast here is, if you look, go to look at a stone inscription that's five or six thousand years old, no matter how deep they carved it, it's going to look pretty freakin' worn out.
Mm-hmm.
From weathering and whatever.
Unless it's buried deep underground under heavy protection.
But I'm telling you that the, the, uh, the, the screwed up stuff that mankind has been involved in is just as sharp as the day that it was chiseled into, you know, into him.
Yeah.
Over time.
It has not worn away.
It's gotten worse, actually.
But how do you notice?
You know, if you're brought up in a certain culture, what you consider is right is right.
It doesn't mean that it's right.
It's just that because you were raised believing it's right.
Yeah.
Tradition.
And culture.
Yeah.
Tradition and culture.
So, again, when I say why bother and do nothing, it's because of that, tradition and culture.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, I think, well, you can look at your life and think, not your life, but, wow, what a waste, you know?
I didn't know all of that.
No one told me that.
Well, it's a waste because you're tired.
Yeah.
Because, you know, you get sick, you're subject to injury, you're subject to aging.
That's why it seems like a waste.
If you came into this world, grew up, lived a physical, in physical perfection, and then you were taken out, I don't think you would say it was a waste because the purpose would be more clear.
But because there's so much suffering in the meantime where you're subject to a vulnerability, you might say it's a waste because, in other words, it's, oh, yeah, I've worked all these years and I got nothing.
Right?
What a waste of time.
I mean, you could put what a waste of time if you tagged that on the end of many phrases, thousands or millions of things to say about it.
Yeah, but you would prefer that you had known more truth when you were younger.
That might have helped you out a little bit.
But it wasn't meant to be, I guess.
Right, because then you would have the potential to explode.
You may not live as long as you did.
Okay, I see.
Yeah, and also you would be upsetting the wagon too much because, remember, this is the adversary's children, the planet.
Wow.
On a grand scale.
So, again, why bother and do nothing other than your basic, basic stuff?
You know, you know, you sit down on the toilet, wipe your butt.
You know, if you're training, you know, young children, you know, wipe your butt.
And if it's a, you know, a male, wipe your butt.
But a female always, you know, you've got to wipe from front to back.
You know, there's still important things, you know, for children.
Proper instruction.
And all this other stuff.
And that's it.
That's all.
Just wipe from front to back for your girl.
And boy, just wipe it.
Don't get any on your finger.
I mean, you get nasty, but this is a nasty business and it's a stinky business being here on this planet.
Yeah.
And that's it.
Pretty much, you know, eat, sleep, keep the law if you can.
Because, remember, the worst thing for the powers, the people and the spiritual leaders of this world is for anyone to discuss that the law has not been done away with and the laws of the gods still exist.
The gods, you know.
And the Most High still exist.
That is their chief enemy ideology, let's say.
That is the worst thing that could ever take hold in this modern society or even older societies is that the law of the Most High is still valid.
That is the chief enemy from a spiritual and physical and social and cultural sense.
Yeah.
Right?
You know, but he does say in scripture he doesn't change.
No, he doesn't.
That's why the ridiculousness of religion...
Yeah.
And by the way, you know how the Christians say the law has been done away with.
You know, when people tell you that and they actually believe it, just walk away.
You can't...
That's a...
You can't deal...
In other words, that's somebody that's just like, you know, alright, whatever.
You know, just stand there and hold this.
You can't do anything.
There's nothing there with someone like that.
Right.
But if someone doubts that, well then, of course, obviously, they have to take out the big eraser that's for erasing everything, you know what I mean?
And a clean slate.
You can't mix the two.
No.
The other hand, the other thing about that is, you know, on one hand, you know, what's that goddess with the many hands?
Right?
The Shiva or whatever?
One hand is Christian, the other one is Islam, the other one is Hinduism, the other one...
They all...
All of these religions, at one point, adhere to something that they say is done away with.
Even in the most conservative sense.
You know that?
Yeah, they seem to have some similar connections.
They all have...
they all do.
Yeah.
It's a...
It's very bizarre in that sense.
Yeah.
That's why I'm telling you, there's not much...
Yeah, there's not much to do.
That's why, when I joke around often about getting off this planet on a spaceship and leaving, it doesn't matter.
Just get away from here.
You ever see in the movies when the bomb's gonna blow and it's like, well, let's go.
It's like, where are we going?
It doesn't matter.
The bomb's...
That's where I stay, you know, because this is not...
And it's a beautiful planet, obviously.
You know, if you have a telescope, you can...
We don't know what's underneath the clouds of Uranus or Jupiter, whatever.
It might be beautiful there, too.
You know.
But all I could see is that the Earth is the most beautiful that we could see.
And it's shameful.
And the people are shameless.
Yeah.
They can't even contrast.
That's why I'm saying, it's...
Only the gods can fix it and only the gods could have fixed it.
Just like someone posted in chat earlier, talk more about the natives, how they lost their territory because their gods support.
Yeah, well, the battle had to happen with the gods first.
You know.
So you start it all.
It's very simple.
Knowing...
Having the notion is more important than the details because the details can be fun.
You can make a movie or make a comic that kills three hours.
I did a lot of that with Sam.
He'd bring up a question and we'd beat it, you know, for three hours.
And so what?
It doesn't...
I mean, it might help someone, but no, no big deal.
Like, for example, telling someone for something very simple, or saying very simple that the Native Americans lost their support from their gods, that's why they lost their land.
Talk about that.
Yes, that's right.
Why talk about that?
Now you got the idea.
Just like telling someone the law was never done away with.
That's it.
You get it or not.
It's up to you to go now and study what the law is.
You see?
Just a very simple notion.
Like, every biblical character is still a secret and not known publicly.
Well, you don't need to go in and spell it out.
Just, okay, now that you know that, now you have a foundation to work on.
You see?
But the problem there, again, that's why I say why bother and do nothing, is let's say, go back to the Native Americans lost the support of their gods thus losing the territory.
Okay?
Go to the library and look that up.
What are you going to get?
Nothing.
Not much.
And on the internet, eeeh, maybe a little bit.
So how are you going to research that?
You're going to give, you're going to give up time with your family and whatever you're doing, even sleeping, to go research that?
What?
Go ahead.
Go travel.
Go talk to the elders.
When you go, we can't talk about that.
Yeah, they're not going to say anything.
No, they know.
Yeah, so why bother?
Oh sure, yeah.
So what, you know, the point here is where do you want to dedicate your time?
You know, what can the Greeks talk about?
What can we talk about?
Anything and everything.
And even if you don't know a subject, let's go look at it together.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
But the problem is we have no access to it.
Very little.
And, and, couple that with the people around you, either people you know or don't know, don't have your best interest in mind.
They say they do.
Right?
Because they want to co-exist, whether it's family, friends, or whatever.
They say they do, but ultimately they don't.
Because, you know why they don't?
Not because they don't want to have your best interest in mind.
They don't know how to do, how to, how to do that.
What the right thing is to do.
Yeah.
They don't have the tools.
Right.
Like, what's that?
Yeah.
They don't have the tools.
Yep.
Like, you know, love is bullshit.
Fresco talks about that.
I've never listened to that.
I saw the YouTube ones, love is bullshit.
I was like, great.
I don't need, I didn't go listen to it, but I, I got to know exactly what that means.
Because they don't know what that means.
You know, no one knows how to love.
No, you know, very few people know what it means.
Yeah.
So, they're always just so good.
Why bother?
Do nothing.
You're at a time right now where, if your lot in life is to just take care of the most basic stuff, and that's it, and basically do nothing outside of that, and why bother?
And, you find yourself in extraordinary positions, and extraordinary knowledge, you are not only called, but you are chosen.
And that is really interesting.
Yeah.
That's just me.
So, yep.
And that's, I think, a pretty good motto.
Why bother and do nothing.
That's been your motto for a while.
It has.
Yeah.
I used to say that because I've told her to the public for a year or two.
Or, I think, I've started this with Duke.
Yeah, don't get involved in any of these organizations.
That's why I kept bringing up Gustave Le Bon later.
You know, after a while, you know, I was like, I don't think people are getting this, so let me bring up Gustave Le Bon.
At least they have something to lean on.
If they want to get a little bit more of what's going on, you know.
And, you know, even though, you know, if I keep saying, forget about these groups, you know, if you want to destroy something, organize it.
It's not because organizing something destroys it.
It's actually quite the opposite.
But on this planet, in this society, in this culture, yes.
Why?
Go read Gustave Le Bon.
But even if you read Le Bon in his work, he says there are good things that come out of it, but he doesn't understand them because there must be divine inspiration.
There are forces that are beyond what we comprehend.
You know, he states that, you know, that do that, so.
So, there are many things to lean on.
Jack Fresco I brought up recently, I was asked to look at some city planning stuff, and I looked at it, and I said, let me go look on the YouTube and see what's on city planning.
And Jack Fresco comes up, and I found out that his whole notion was stupid because he doesn't know about the gods, but his perspective of looking at stuff and how fucked up culture is, is correct.
You see, so I brought him in the fold as much as possible to what I was listening.
But he doesn't know about the bears, but it's best that he didn't because if he did, he might have adopted why bother and do nothing and we wouldn't have found out about him.
Yeah, very true.
Very true.
So, either way, it's fine, but again, like we mentioned earlier, like you were mentioning about discussing how when things are going to get much worse, they're going to appear to be better and how do you fathom the change and well, the only way to do that is to ask that the gods give you discernment, right?
Just like with dreams, like imagine, do you know how many people are being tortured, literally, when I mean tortured, I mean mentally tortured by dreams, right?
Yeah.
They go to the psych, they get medical help, psychological help, none of it helps because they can't discern it, what's really going on and that's the whole thing, it's called diagnosis.
They're terrible, you know, the diagnosis that the professionals do, you know, they say we have professionals diagnosed, it's almost the same as anyone can do on the street.
Someone at a bus stop, what's wrong with me?
And they'll tell you.
They're not very good at that.
So, if you, let me just use the P word, which is pray for discernment, right?
Would be the first step.
Sure.
Because telling someone about what to do doesn't help them when the situation changes a little bit.
So, but if you show discernment or give them the tools, right, then if the situation changes, like I always use the food and the law as a metaphor, you know, like if you read the Koran, it has one verse, which doesn't really have much to do about food.
It says, do not eat the flesh of a swine or an animal that has died, meaning of unknown causes.
Well, that means, well, if someone reads the Koran, they'll say, well, I guess we can eat a camel then.
You know, these people have no discernment, right?
They do eat camel, you know, they do eat all kinds of stuff.
But the Scripture gives you discernment and example.
It says, four legs, it has to chew the cud and clove and hoof.
And it says, a pig has a clove and hoof, but he doesn't chew the cud, right?
No good.
And a rabbit chews the cud, but he has a paw.
So, not only does it give you how to discern, but it also gives an example.
Right.
So, right.
So, in this case, pray for the discernment, and guess what?
The example, how are you going to get the example?
You're going to start singing it around you.
Friends, family, news, walk out in the street.
You get it?
Yeah.
It won't just be black ink on white paper or pixels on the rectangle anymore.
You're going to, what's going to make it difficult as the times have come is, as you gain discernment, it's not going to, it's going to be in living color.
You know, it's going to be, It'll be live.
It'll be live, yeah.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
So, yep.
I mean, I don't know.
There's this, there's so much that can be done, and I'll say that the, what they call the web, the internet, is a great tool for that, and no matter what tools exist, ultimately, who's the end user?
Surface dwelling earth inhabitant that's inherently evil or cosmically censored, so you're looking for the .0001%, you're looking for a few thousand people out of 7 billion, right?
So, why bother?
You can't find them.
They have to be brought cosmically.
You get it?
So, if that helps anyone that is learning the truth, don't even bother with the people around you, and I don't mean around you, I mean like around like anywhere on the planet.
They have to ultimately be brought to you.
You guys have to be brought cosmically.
In other words, the odds for the lotto or the lottery are in the billions, it's the same thing.
In this case, it would be the millions, because one in a million is roughly 7,000 people, and that's roughly the number of people on the planet.
And it's provable, it's, you know, by just learning it.
So, if you understand what's being said on these phonics, guess what?
You're on your own.
You're not And, you know, is it possible that people don't want to be around you because of this?
Yeah, if you open your mouth, you can.
Yeah.
Yeah, and there are some people that care before you open your mouth.
I've noticed that, yeah.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
And also, part of discernment is when you run into people, they won't be able to really pigeonhole you.
You know?
So they don't talk to you.
No, they don't talk.
Some people will be afraid.
Some people will be strangely attracted to you, but don't know why.
Or they do know why, and it will be super superficial.
But they know there's more beyond that.
Did I ever give you the story about I had two cars that I needed suspension work done on, right?
And we're talking about like, you know, steering and suspension, very specific stuff, not just regular mechanical work.
I didn't want to do it myself, so I took it to the suspension shop.
There's a specialist, you know, they not only do suspension, they do other stuff, but, you know, like struts and alignments and chassis work, you know?
So, I go in there and the guy says, well, it's like 700 bucks, but I'm going to do it for 300.
I'm like, wow, thank you.
I asked him, you know, what would give me a better price.
He says, well, I'll bring you another car, and I want to do the same thing.
Okay, yeah, well, we'll do that one for 200.
They kept going down and down and down, and I was like, he's charging me like half or a third.
And then, like, I brought him another car and I said, hey, I really appreciate you guys have the best reputation in town and you're giving me like a killer deal.
I said to him, do you know what kind of work I do?
And he says, well, you're a preacher, aren't you?
Ah.
And I never mentioned anything.
Oh, wow.
The only conversations I've ever had was about the car.
Yeah.
Never about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know the cars are in a trust, so, you know, you look it up, it's just a trust.
There's no name on it on the registrations.
Yeah.
So, it's a trust.
It's not, right?
So, I'm like, well, what made you think that?
And he says, I don't know, I just thought that, you know.
I said, holy shit.
So, this guy sees me as a preacher.
Another guy, I was, uh, you're going to another supplier and if there was, did you know what I do?
He says, yeah, you're a professor, aren't you?
So, what makes you think that?
He says, I don't know, I just, you know.
Right?
So, anyway.
So, I've had, in other words, as I keep going on, uh, uh, I run into circles.
It's, you know, like a service industry or whatever and just basic stuff and everyone thinks I'm doing something else.
An engineer, uh, one guy thought, you know, I worked for an intelligence agency, another guy thought I was a preacher, another guy thought I was a doctor, right?
Yeah.
Another guy thought I was an artist and, you know, and we're not talking about Greek speak now, we're just talking about service industry.
Hi, you know, fill this out, I need this done, see you, bye, I'll see you later.
Right?
What made you sound?
Yeah, I was like, whoa, that's really odd.
Uh-huh.
You know?
The one, the funniest one I had to bring up first was the guy that thought I was a preacher, you know?
Yeah.
I mean, you guys have heard me, you know, there's nothing preachy about what I'm saying.
Right.
So, and I, again, when I ask some questions, you guys say, I don't know, man, I really don't know, I just thought that.
So, in other words, what are they, through their eyes, how do they see you?
And, here you go, when things get thick, if you know the truth, um, the spiritual influence that most people have, because it's external input, right?
They're going to be really turned off.
Yeah.
You know, that's why 13 was an unlucky number, right?
Because when you had 12, the 12 and the 1, if they were approaching a town from a distance, how many people are coming to town?
13, right?
You had the 12 and the 1.
So, every time these 13 people rolled around places like Judea and whatever, the whole hell broke loose.
It was bad luck when this group of 13 showed up.
Anyway.
Yeah.
How many times have you read in what they call the Old Testament the gods are coming to town and how many people were happy about that?
Never.
Right.
Yeah.
what's going on now?
Total bullshit.
Right?
For thousands of years.
All of them.
Yeah.
It's all crap.
So, why bother?
Sure.
Sorry, now I'm back inside.
I was outside.
I didn't have planes and cicadas, but if there's any...
Sorry about that.
No.
No, that's all right.
It's not your fault.
If there's not anything else, we'll just...
We've been on for quite a few hours, I think.
Two and a half plus.
Okay.
But there's so much to do, but, you know, you have to realize it's been my motto, yes, why bother?
Again, it takes a lot of work to do it right.
Sam puts my feet to the fire.
He says, you never do what you guys say you're doing.
You were going to do this and that.
You know, kind of like a baby, you know?
Where's the podcast?
Where's this?
I said, you know what?
I have desires and I do want to do this kind of stuff and I like sharing and I like developing, but I'm not stupid.
You know, the response is so minimal and I'm not going to work for free because it is a lot of work in a professional way.
Sure.
Right?
And, again, if I'm going to work and I'm going to walk my walk and talk my talk, do nothing.
And if you find yourself being put in a position where you have to, you're going to get the help and all that.
That's not on your own and you're not falling for some adversarial trap of, you know, what human, what I call, what's called human frailty or what they call ego, which is not accurate, but...
Yeah.
Yeah, and it's not like, you know, it's the first century A.D. where at least you'll do something that'll help, you know, what, I don't know, 20, 30, 40 generations of people.
No, actually, less than that.
20 generations.
You're right at the point right now.
So, so I don't see anything in emails or chat, so I'm just going to say, do you want to call it, Bruce?
Sure.
It was a good conversation.
It really was.
Appreciate it.
Yes.
Thank you for coming on.
Yeah, thank you all.
Thank you.
And I'm glad you found out that this stuff works and keeps working.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, good to keep working on it.
Cool.
All right, so...
Appreciate it.
Yeah, appreciate you coming on.
It's always best to have a conversation instead of a monologue very often.
I think, Bruce, I think it's been, we'll try to keep these things going on what they call Tuesday, which is not every week, by the way, on the folks' work schedule.
Right.
But, you know, we're coming up on the sixth moon in about a week or so.
Mm-hmm.
Less, you know.
But I've once gotten a suggestion regarding sonic events.
You know, try to give a couple hours notice on a topic to talk about, and if there is no one coming on or no topic, there's no reason to come on here and do stuff other than a loose conversation.
So...
Okay, so you would like topics suggested in chat.
Oh, yeah, otherwise I'm not going to I'm not going to stop digging into my clipboards and notes and start developing new stuff because no one's really other than yourself and a few others doing stuff, you know, like, you know, whether it's the human body or the gods or technology or timekeeping, there's not much there's not much being developed.
I mean, I don't it's like a government job.
You ever see the government employees on the street when they working, they have nine guys standing around, one guy digging, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
Not going to this is not I have humans in too low regard to go out beyond, but when I give out enough information where someone like yourself and others says, well, this stuff works and it's great I don't know.
Believe it or not, even with that, it's best to keep it simple, but you still got your hands full, right?
You know, I mean, there's so much that can be done.
Here, I'll give you one more thing before we go regarding timekeeping.
You know, most people still can't get the basics and most people do it on team to care, but here that's focused on that.
If you really want to do well, not really want to do if you one way that you could start studying time if anyone there might be someone nut job out there who's as crazy as I am.
When solar, it has two clocks.
You know, like the cheap analog clocks or you can even use a digital, but an analog clock is fine.
You can get them really cheap these days.
They're fairly accurate within two or three minutes per month, so they're for all intents and purposes for this, it's fine.
So you have the clock on the wall and then you have another clock that you have access to and every day that there's solar noon, you adjust that to 12 o'clock exactly.
So sometimes, you know, in the summer, obviously, it's going to be going back and in the winter it's going to be going forward, right?
So, you know, let's say it's 12.55 on the regular clock and it's solar noon on the clock that you always adjust, you put that exactly at noon.
Right?
Why do we do that?
Why do you want to do a time study?
And then you start seeing how the drift starts to happen through the seasons, but that's not even why you do that.
Why...
Should I answer that or just let it...
Actually, let me just say that this is not a put-down, but from what I've seen in various chats or emails, I don't think the audience has the aptitude to answer this, but I'm going to answer.
Okay.
Why do you do that?
Why do you adjust one and do the other?
Because then you learn...
This part I'm not going to answer because it takes too long.
The reason why you adjust the clocks like that and you see how much they're off is not to see how much the clocks are off, but to determine how long nighttime is.
And I'm going to leave it at that.
And then right away I might hit you like I know what he just said.
I know what nighttime is in terms of hours.
I know what that means, but I don't know what he means by the two clocks and all that.
Have you two put it together what I mean by that?
Have you got it?
It's a name for the Equinox.
No, it has nothing to do with the Equinox.
Oh, OK.
I thought for sure it would have went there.
It has to do with how long the nighttime really is.
Hmm.
OK.
And why?
Because...
OK, so I'm going to...
Do you see how...
Yeah.
I'm so discouraged about talking about new stuff because in background I understand.
you have to give so much discussion in background.
Bringing up a topic is like, you know, pulling a plug on a bathtub.
It's all this water and then it's gone.
You look at it and you're like, oh, this water's going to take forever to drain and you turn around and it's gone.
It's like, how did that happen, right?
So it's not good to do that.
You know, I think that's...
I should learn.
But, in other words, we can do ten four-hour sonic events on time and just barely start scratching the surface.
Right?
We can do ten four-hour sonic events just on eating and food and barely be scratching the surface.
In other words, I had a discussion with someone about a year ago that wanted me to do an interview and we ended up spending three hours on the cell phone with a manager or someone and he says, man, Greek, you know, you're bursting at the seams.
He's like, you've got so much, you're just exploding.
I'm like, yeah, I know, it sucks.
Right?
So, just to finish this sonic event off, do you see that I think it's better to, you know, have a topic of discussion else that allows me to gauge and see if it develops into anything.
If there, let's say there's nothing I'm not, just want to do a sonic.
Like, we don't have someone like yourself calling in or some pretty good, and I think people got a way of, you know, pretty good stuff in chat of an answer.
Like, if you bring up, this is not to be disparaging, actually, I want to encourage more if possible.
Can you please discuss how the Indian lost their support of their gods and lost their territory?
That is the answer in the question.
No, I'm not going to discuss more of that because it doesn't help anyone.
Right?
It's not going to help the Indians.
And you're all going to lose the land.
So, think those things through on how they are really, are they really useful.
You know?
How useful is it?
And I think, think about it for a moment.
You know, there's subjects we like, and then there's subjects that we like that are not useful, and there's subjects that we like that are useful.
So, how useful is it?
Now, again, it might sound a little personal.
Like, for example, other people, if you bring up, I'm not going to mention any names.
I'm usually nice because I mention a name.
But you guys might know who it is if I've spoken to a lot before.
You might know a certain subject, but you don't have a personal interest in it.
And even though I might, but I let it go.
Right?
Regarding time, there are very few people that, mostly anyone who understands or comprehends Greek speak knows the notion of time now.
But very few people have an interest in it.
Right?
So, if I'm around someone who doesn't have an interest in a subject, let's say the human body, I won't discuss it.
Or if someone doesn't have an interest in time, I won't discuss it.
Right?
Just be aware that it's much better that way.
So if I, if there's no topic or anything and I come on and start talking about this, like, hell if I know who's interested, why am I talking, why am I speaking?
You know?
Sure.
So, there's a tremendous amount, you know, after a while, you, it's like yin and yang.
When you get so much stuff going on, you want to do nothing.
You kind of explode or implode or you know, the thing, the circuit overload and you're just like, I'll just let it, you know, when a circuit breaker goes, you just let it cool down.
You don't hit it right away, you know, because the reason why it broke the circuit is because it overheated.
It's a very simple mechanical thing.
Right?
So, in a sense that the interest, I think the discussion or the sonics should be based on the interest that's inputted from the chat or email.
I mean, otherwise, I'd come on and say, Bruce, we're going to talk about time and do four hours of real heavy technical methodology of lawful timekeeping for my satisfaction.
I don't need to do that.
I'm already, I already know it.
I'm already satisfied.
Why do I, you know, need to come on a sonic and do it?
Say how smart I am or something?
No reason.
So, the only reason to do these sonics is, again, having someone like, have you noticed about some testimonians having another being discuss their experiences with the stuff or, you know, whatever.
But, I appreciate what you do, Bruce, but there's no reason to do a sonic unless there's input, impetus of some kind.
Correct.
Because, you don't need to come out and discuss what I've discovered.
That's personal.
Like I said, the, the, the knowledge is its own reward.
You know?
Just like the, the, was it Fresco?
I said, well, you're so smart.
How come you don't have any money?
He said, well, you have a lot of money.
How come you're not smart?
Right?
So, which one would you rather have, depending, right?
Kind of thing.
Mm-hmm.
Either way, if there's no interest, if I don't see an interest, by the way, it's just a, this is the first time I've been so bold about it, in chat or emails, there's no sonic.
So, just coming on and discussing what I'm interested in is not correct.
It's not right, I think.
Publicly.
Do it privately amongst the group.
Again, if you have an interest, let's say, in miniature trains or astronomy or whatever, you just, even privately, you call your aunt and uncle or brothers, they don't care.
You want to find, personally, someone who is interested also, again, privately or public.
It doesn't matter.
There needs to be an interest.
So, and it should be useful.
But, again, just to recap, when there are people that want to bring up in chat or emails topics that the question answers, they've already all encompassed.
You know, they just want more detail, but it's not something that's very useful.
Um, that shows a lot.
That shows that they actually got it because, like, in their suggestion of something to speak about, they gave the whole thing from start to finish, from soup to nuts.
So, that means they really got it, you know, which is great.
You know, I've had many emails, could you please continue talking about how dreams are external input and caused by gods or demons or spirits?
And I'm like, no, because you got it.
There's no more, there's nothing else to talk about, right?
Yeah.
But, if you structure the request like that, it means you do understand that.
And now, it's not a matter of discussing that, it's discussing specific aspects of it.
You know, from a technical point of view, do you want more dreams?
Do you want less dreams?
You know?
Do you, are, you know, do you see what I mean?
Right.
Mm-hmm.
So, it has to be, and how helpful is it?
So, anyway.
Yeah.
So, again, thanks.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming very, very much.
Yep.
And, thank you both.
we'll see you next week.
Thanks, Bruce.
Thank you.
You have a good night now.
You too.
Thank you, Bruce.
Yes, you're welcome.
And thank you.