We're popping in right now and we're on Okay, great.
All right, so we're on with Sam and Bruce, right?
Yeah And I'm making coffee and doing laundry and all this other stuff as this happens to be a conversation that we're streaming for the I Wouldn't say benefit or could be benefit or demise of others, right?
Right depending on how they view Whatever is being here or heard by them That's funny.
Can you see sound that sounds like an acid trip, right?
right The the aspect of Sam asked, you know want to ask that question again this Sam What are we gonna?
What do you want to talk about?
Right?
Do you remember that?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah Yeah.
Well, how about things that people don't notice in their everyday lives whether everyday commutes or their everyday Travels or their everyday whatever they do You know what?
I mean, whatever.
I mean, whatever right?
Mm-hmm.
So but the thing is doesn't that sound kind of paradox or goal to say?
Let's talk about things.
You don't notice Yeah, I could seem that way but Obviously an outsider can comment on what he sees other people not noticing.
I'm guessing that well, that's what we're gonna do Mm-hmm like I wanted to just bring up like I was gonna I was started to for a moment is There's a YouTube channel called seven second riddles.
It's not very good I actually don't endorse it or even recommend it but it has an idea of I show this to someone earlier To break through your mental models like it'll show you what what's wrong here and it'll show you six columns and six rows of the letter V and they'll and and it looks like all V's but there's a W in there So you have to find the W, right?
But it's very difficult to find and the way you look at that is when you have a string of V's, you know You have the two legs in a gap the W would be missing the gap right in the center It would look like TVs touching let's say so instead of looking for the W Why don't you deduce it and look for where the gap is missing you see the pattern?
Because most people if you showed them four columns and six columns and six rows of V's find what's wrong here They're like the pad it looks because their mental model is just a little they're not really looking at the picture They're looking at the letter V repeated and they said oh, there's so many V's here.
They're all V's, but they're not you see Yes So I would suggest that What I called mental modeling is what's used To go back to what I said earlier for people not to notice what they in in their daily lives You know, what?
Do you not notice in your daily lives?
It sounds kind of a riddle to ask that in the first place Because how can you discuss something you don't notice right, right?
so
There's when I when I have discussions with people that I have been
Speaking to in the past which I try to avoid by the way
I always constantly looking for new leaves to turn, you know new pages to turn new people
Not in a sense of burning bridges or anything, but discarding the
Separating the wheat from the chaff and discarding the useless
you know and
But not like, you know because in Stalin said there are useful idiots, too, so
but
When as you keep moving through people, there's seven billion people to move through, right?
So even if you move through seven thousand a minute, you don't have enough days Is is you're gonna start to realize that?
Even with mental modeling or without mental modeling
They're all the same essentially meaning based on what culture like Jack fresco talks about you pull them out
Of right with small idiosyncrasies and small differences and likes
You know, so and then you have to see how forgiving are you
You know, like he give an example personal example when I was doing with Shelly in the Greek somebody and I would agree some people
Commented that was some of the best Sonics out there.
But if you ask me my personal opinion, I think it's completely idiotic Because you know, you know speaking to Chuck is you know talking to the straw man and the Wizard of Oz, right?
If you know what I mean, I'm looking for brain, but he's not but he would be considered
I'm this is not pejorative to him
But in other words the subject matter that we were discussing when you have someone like anyone that just is not on Chuck
But you're so mentally modeled that you cannot examine what's going on
Unless two or three people around you already it's become fashionable to do so you see
You know if you once it's like the in crowd, this is like the trending or the in discussion to have
right and and
That's part of the culture.
That's part of the mental modeling So when people start to hear things that are really obvious that no one notices Well, it can't be so because no one else has noticed, right?
so Okay, let's go back to what I wanted to say what people are not noticing.
I'll give an example I just wanted to chat.
I did a speed read up a few lines and people are apparently discussing interlinears.
Why?
Let's say you read the interlinear.
So what?
So what there's plenty of people that have spent their entire lives there are schools dedicated to Translating the Bible, but guess what?
Can they tell you what the Bible and Scripture is about?
Okay, so nope.
Can they tell you prophecy?
Nope.
Can they tell you what timekeeping is?
Nope Can they tell you the application of the law and the metaphors and the analogies?
Nope.
I Would prefer that no one read the scriptures analytically and even out of the piss-poor Kim King James For example identified all of the mistakes.
I once have suggested more than once.
How about 49 people or a hundred people grab eat two people each or one person each grab a book of The Bible and sift through it in an interlinear and make an appendix or an index of all the mistranslated words and submit it as an Outline like, you know, here's the book of Genesis.
Here's a 102 occurrences where you have fatal mistakes in the King James Right and the and then explain what the purpose of what do you got out of Genesis?
No one is still doing that, right?
And this is not I've seen this in other places, too.
I
Wouldn't I would say that
Looking for an interlinear to find what where it's mean is more noble
Than making up stuff like everybody else does on the Internet
Well, this really means that and this is this and this is that outside of any rationale or logic you see
Which is just piss-poor
But can you tell anyone what the message is in Scripture and the answer is no
It's not being done
Outside of those asinine religious sense or outside of a fine point being discussed which spins off into error anyway
So what the hell is going on here?
What what's so difficult about?
Discussing a communication from a parallel society of high dynamics known as the gods.
What's so difficult about that?
It's not being done by the way, right?
Well, it's not being done in chat.
I mean, which is an indication of nothing No, no, yeah, no, but where is it being done on the Internet without including in having met a extreme let's say extremist views extremist meaning Fringe views that are wrought with error.
I Can't say that I can localize such a discussion.
I can't I can't either Well, and you know, there's no do make and yeah, but they do make there's there's a Christianity right away thrown in in order to keep the popularity and a monetary income coming in.
So it's a lost cause there Yeah, or astrotheology or Judaism or messianic or?
Like the stuff what's a Vlodovsky and Jordan Maxwell picked up on that astrotheology in the metaphor of synchronism
Bonacci does that and yeah nothing
So, you know what that tells me the grapes are sour to these people
Right, yeah that yeah, yeah to those people which it was just no consequence
I do feel like to this kind of rhetoric does devolve into sort of
monotone repetitive grumbling at some point because if there was such a lack of that type of discussion and
It was something of issue then we would just provide it because it's never been introduced
We don't well, let's but hold on who's we I mean, I know who we is.
Well, maybe Greece, you know Yeah, but provided how?
And to who and when and how and Methodically speaking.
Yeah, but those things can be structured.
Okay, and they can be structured kind of easily Yes.
Yes.
Okay, they can write So we're not we're not lamenting the lack of the conversation because we can create the conversation instantaneously Well, they're methodically one can rationalize with ease that it can be done, right?
Oh, yeah You just do a podcast you write a book you just go out and tell people or you you know promote it or Right, that's the methodological Well either actually it is, you know spending spending Three hours a day for less than a month.
You'll be surprised what you can do on the Yeah You have to grovel a bit, you know on the publicity and you have to start, you know Groveling into channels, you know, I mean come in in a very benign way let them know what you're offering and hopefully they want to Promote what you're doing as well indirectly or directly, you know all this other stuff, right?
That's not correct.
Yeah All right.
So if you want to explore that methodology You know anyone is free to do it because the stuff that I bring up is so obvious that to say that Greek says This or this is the Greek stuff is ridiculous, you know to say that time keeping is the way the Greek does time is ridiculous to state that The views on the human body is the way the Greek says is ridiculous.
It's freaking obvious Right, and I show yes, and it has to be promoted that way that it's obvious Obvious.
Yeah, I really would like to be left out of it unless it was Viewed as a business venture or a decision where I would benefit from it from investing time in it, right?
Right, but Sam on the other hand you could say well It's not happening organically You know what I mean Organically, I mean just put it out there and watch it grow on its own, right?
So what is your what is your idea about?
About this, I mean you said well we could go, you know, it might devolve into simple grow grow, you know, whatever I mean, how obvious Always okay fine Yeah, it does and it has been for quite a long time on a social cultural level as well How how does one show the obviousness of things?
when The people don't see it at the moment and I'm being kind, you know, of course because they're censored and they're morons But let's say they weren't let's put the censorship and the idiocy aside How do they how do you present something?
That's just blatantly obvious to them, right?
Well, I think there's a sense in which you ask Yes, it would be too.
I don't know You know as always what kind of audiences that you have in mind, I mean don't we're not we're not thinking about it Yeah, but we're not thinking about Catering to a general mass of people that are disinterested, right?
So even with corporations or with the entertainment industry they Have an endeavor that is geared towards identifying an audience whether it's through focus groups or it's through some kind of online research So I don't think that anybody is exempt from that.
You have to first identify the audience and then go after it.
Okay Let me let me just throw a little insight.
Have you ever been around people in film production and Producership like B movies or even on People that worked on like sound and editing for major movies.
I have
Mm-hmm, and when you bring up that point
Regarding what you know what people whatever, you know what they always say the people are stupid
Always and you hear it so much
But you're like, oh this is bullshit because there really is no creativity here
In a sense because they've already presumed
It's kind of like the thing is, you know
I heard of someone in the street recently discuss a political thing and she said something like what do they think?
The American people are stupid.
I said no, they don't think the American people are stupid.
They know the American people are stupid so I've seen this so much Even in that video audio that I sent about dr.
Day He said the people are so dumb.
They're never gonna realize anything.
You've heard me discuss the money system for example In great detail and all that and even like, you know, any host is like, okay Right, so Good I mean Anybody anybody can lampoon the foolishness of the masses?
But once again, we're not talking about that.
We're talking about An effort that is geared towards Constructing contours around a particular group of people and locking in on that.
So if there is no Scattered No, it's it's a mist it's a it's a mist it's it's a it's an ethereal group It's not a group like an Ecclesia or a body of people.
There's no body to it
I didn't say that what I said was we have to sculpt the contours around this
If the ephemeral, you know existence of people that could disperse at any moment
so if you don't want to do the grunt work of doing that and you want to shove that onto somebody else who's not showing
Up to accommodate that fine
But if you can't succeed with that then you have to do it yourself and you don't want to do it yourself
No, I'd rather just show up and the mic is ready and you pick it up and you speak
But that's not going to materialize under the current conditions
So you can either a doubt, you know adapt to the circumstance or you could just continue in your current vein
But when you take right, I mean, sorry
No, it's not even it's not even there is no current vein
we just have these sonics that we put on and and just
To put out a little bit of information here and there and and whatever and tell people how moronic they are and that's about it.
I Mean, you know, I mean A little more but that's fine.
Then that is the current vein, but here's an interesting There's something called a litmus test or testing the waters or whatever Yeah, are you familiar with that concept right an introductory aspect?
You know if you plan on running a marathon and you can't even run a warm-up Around the block once I think the second part of your endeavor is worthless Did you get it?
Yeah Yeah Yeah in a sense I mean you can if you show up to run the marathon Which is 35 40 kilometers and you can't even run a quarter of a kilometer to warm up Don't even think of trying the other thing, right?
And I'm not saying this is not a let me just focus a little bit more what I'm trying to say here That's not because I'm not doing it.
It's because so much stuff has been put out Let's say on the human body on Scripture this or the other as is there any interest on evolving it and Evolving a meeting unraveling it more.
No, they're very little I get, you know the similar, you know You're judging that based on what you see on the Internet not even based on real-world interactions.
I don't know how far away It is based on real-world interactions I've traveled I wouldn't been everywhere, but I've traveled around past decade and discuss things with people and the moment What you did a decade ago doesn't count oh Really?
Okay.
We're talking about what are you saying?
The same stuff?
I'm saying the same stuff same stuff wherever I go I bring up and people know me as one that To go to and ask some questions about this or the other and and it's like oh, yeah.
Okay, whatever No, there's no There's several points.
I think prophetically it's not time yet, and I'm not the one or whatever.
I think it'll happen Simultaneously I just think that maybe a lot of this stuff is a precursor to the simultaneous Evolution of it, you know unraveling or opening of it We might just be a little too early for the party, you know what?
I mean, and that's fine, too
Yeah, but if that really was fine
Then we would suffice with the current state of things and yet obviously the Greek doesn't because here we are
So there's no point in talking about that
You know sure there's always a point about it because there are fine points that can be brought up with different people
You know viewing on the subject matter
Yeah, but then we'd be addressing the fine points now.
I wouldn't be addressing, you know Well, I'm makes we well, we might be addressing the fine points in the next 30 seconds.
You don't know Sure, you know is this that we always have to go through these hoops, which is fine I'm not averse to it.
But I I personally am waiting for development in in the sort of Protest or the criticism or the belly-aching because what are we actually complaining about?
We should be measuring What we're seeing based on the efforts that we're making Right not based on what some random massive people are doing that are under the control of spiritual beings Anyway, that has really nothing to do.
I'll speak for myself.
It has nothing to do with me, right?
I just want I want to measure my progress based on my efforts.
So if the if the if the If the apex of our efforts is to come on this stream and Whine about the state of the world Then I don't think I don't think it's the apex or I don't think it's about whining I think it's really just giving an update but which is the same, right?
You know if it's like when you're in the desert, it's sunny every day if you turn on the weather almost
360 days of the year guess what they're gonna say on the weather
It's sunny
So that does that does that mean because it's sunny 360 days out of the year that you don't do the weather
But anyway, go ahead
There's an element of redundancy there and you can address that instead of being I don't mean you but we can address that instead
Of being monotone about it, right?
So if there are fine points, let's address the fine points if there are if there's a Grand here this is this is the fine point.
The fine point is very simple
You'll remember me saying this and I don't say it as often as I should I want and you'll see why I said why I
should
This is not about any subject or this or that or whatever it's about
Anything that mankind is involved in that's cognitive based knowledge based rational based or you know, quote-unquote science
which means knowledge and
Communication anything that you involve yourself in any field or trade if you look at Thomas manual
I think there's 30 different 30,000 or 23,000 different categories in industry, right?
And beyond that right?
Anything anyone wants to get involved in any field is still completely wide open Let me just say that.
Yeah again if you want to talk about the gods
You can go out and muster all the information everything that's been written about it doesn't even cover one-tenth of one percent of what can
Be done with that information
If you want to study human biology not even one-tenth of one percent is covered on that
In other words a layman right now
What it was is this is what I champion if I were to say some words that would champion Greek speak would be this
Anything you want to learn about or get involved in on a rational cognitive knowledge or scientific basis or spiritual basis?
Any field is completely wide open
Don't ever feel that
Any more than one-tenth of one percent has ever been accomplished in any field it doesn't matter if it's physics
Anything's spirituality meaning knowledge of the gods in your own self the human body biology energy
Mathematics anything airplanes not even one-tenth of one percent of that topic has been dealt with
Are you with me on this what I'm trying to say?
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's not but you're saying it's on from saturation Open to anyone who's interest.
Mm-hmm No, no It's not just open to anybody who's interested as if we can just pick out any random person and expect them to function at that No, no.
No, I'm talking about.
This is the mindset that I'm giving
Yeah, but the mindset notwithstanding
It's open to those who have the background and the technical proficiency to even grasp that field in the first place first
It would be the inspiration
Well, you know, you know like an airplane designer
There was one guy a French guy and he they asked him a while back
What made you want to become an airplane designers is that four years old?
I took interest Well, what the hell did he know at four years old?
It was inspiration.
You see?
Yeah, but a four-year-old has the buffer of the next 20 years to amass that Sensibility, there's no point in looking at a 25 year old who's already cemented his not just the mentality But also his skill set and his idiosyncrasies and say you can go study aeronautics.
No, you can't of course you can No, you don't because you don't have a buffer as far as time as far as resources and as sure it is No, you don't.
Well, okay.
Hold on If you go look at let's take the human body, which is very simple If you can go and study anything and everything about the medical Industry and all the science of the human body.
That's not even one-tenth of 1% of what the human body is even about not even
Anything that you might study regarding the human body in medical science, let's say
Doesn't even address the biological vacuum
All you need to do is pick up the bylot the concept of the biological volume which vacuum which is completely ignored and pick up
On that and in three days you will be a thousand times more advanced than the most advanced medical technician
Because he's not even looking there.
It's the same thing as as as you know, if we're all in a room and We say we're gonna walk to China The person who gets up from the sofa and walks five feet towards the west or the east where is closer to China Is he not measurably you're still a long way there, but you're so much closer.
Yeah, but you're 300 percent.
Nobody Mm-hmm.
No, but nobody measures progress relative to something as minor as that kind of effort What progress?
as far as the progress of you Moving forward with your own personal endeavor if there's three people and they take, you know One guy moves a few steps closer to China and he's close.
He's closer to check Yeah but he's closer to China relative to those other three guys who have done nothing and He himself in the grand scheme of things will have done nothing like there's no Missed it.
Now.
Hold on a second.
It's not Yeah, but it's not measurable relative to himself and I've done this when I was out in Texas For example, you could walk into a medical conference and when they're finished They're doing question and answer and then if there anyone wants to bring up any upcoming whatever you just don't know What about the vacuum in the body and you give a couple of examples?
That makes everything everything that they've done seems so asinine
That they've that they are ignoring that and now you are the expert in that field
They're gonna be they've got 40 years medical practical experience
But they're looking at you now as the expert because they had never considered it
And you keep building upon that
So after you research it for two weeks you report back because remember you're still the world expert on it, right?
So It's it's the same with the magnetic fields Once you find out how a magnetic field works You could go to all the physicists in the world doesn't matter how much experience they have and you show prove to them how?
It really works, even though you've discovered it yesterday
They're gonna look at you as the expert on that new concept
Yeah, but you're once again presupposing that this person even knew what
Magneticism was in the first place you go on on the street and you ask the average person what the net is
Is what I'm talking about find that no, of course, we're not taught even physicists can define it
They can't nobody even on there even according to even according to standard
Money, whatever education they they can't do it.
Mm-hmm.
Now if you can and you could prove it That makes you a world expert now.
We're not talking now, you know that we're leaving out like
about five or six critical points and one of them or two of them might be that you're not going to be recognized an
Expert because you don't have the credentials
Also, they're gonna they're gonna the second thing is the the the culture is going to say
well, this guy can't be an expert based on his
race
based on his culture based on his
That's those going on by the way and based on his education based on how many years he's been doing it
You see you're gonna have an answer a seemingly unsurmountable amount of resistance
Against you but it doesn't negate that you're the only one that knows about it or are progressing in a new direction
You know
Progressing by what by what measure and by let's go back to the same thing that we started on this
Conversation if this is the apex of our conversations or whatever.
Yeah, it sounds pretty it sounds pretty piss-pathetic Just to do these little streams, but instead of let's say doing the stream Let's say that you just want to talk about the human we can do let's say a stream on the the biological vacuum in the body Right.
Well, or we can write do a website on it.
And then once we do the website on it
Write a little thing about it
I'll do a blog on it do a podcast on it send emails to people in places that might be interested you see
Sowing seeds and then seeing how and then take a break and if that doesn't work try another
Thing on the biological like him or airplane flight, it's very simple, you know, I never saw a
Bird with a propeller on its nose or a jet under its wing of you
No, so yeah, so how do they fly
Yeah, what way changing their environment?
The bird doesn't fly bird changes its environment gives the illusion that it's flying You see that like for example cork doesn't float on water.
That's an illusion It's because it doesn't displace it's because of its density that it ends up rising to the top You see So if you had say if the cork had more density than water it wouldn't float It has nothing to do with what you call a whole cork floats.
No, it doesn't cork is floated Relative to water if you blow bubbles very fine micro bubbles under the water.
What will happen to that cork Bruce?
You might move around no sink Really would fire you oh yeah, because the bubbles if you took a given volume of the water and Measure the density of the water with the bubbles.
It would be less than the cork wouldn't it?
Depending on how many bubbles that's how you sink a large ship.
You don't need I shouldn't sit
Well, anyway, I'll say you just have a submarine with a drone
With compressed air and go underneath the ship and you you form
Cavitating bubbles
Underneath the battleship
you don't have to do the whole battleship you just do the
The engine compartment side which is heavier and then they all the ballast will run towards it anyway
And you just dip the back
But what happens even the largest battleship or aircraft carrier if you dip if you dip the bat one side of the ship underwater
What do you think will happen?
She's going down Yeah, she's going down it doesn't take much you could do the math it requires about 160 cubic feet of compressed air Which is the size of a small tool shed a small tool sheds up really 500 cubic feet.
I Mean the size of a large, you know house refrigerator could do it right And what does that cost a couple thousand bucks take down a billion dollar aircraft carrier?
And no one wouldn't even know what happened, right?
So, I mean Yeah, you want to get into weapons design, but like Jack Fresco said don't cast your pearls to swine.
Here's one for your Sam even Weapons design is completely wide open You know, occasionally I'll run into websites on the current weapons and I laugh I'm like are these people like eight-year-olds in 80 80 year old or 75 year old man general suits.
Are these people stupid or what?
This is their weaponry.
This is ridiculous But anyway, are you guys familiar by the way, it's just a little trivia here Are you familiar with the aircraft carrier that was sunk by a Vietnamese sponge fishermen that was never really reported You could look it up.
Yes.
I remember you mentioned me not It's very embarrassing to the Americans.
Are you familiar with that Sam?
Yeah, you know, you know an aircraft carriers is like a very expensive piece of
You know, it's putting all of your liability in one basket
Well, you know even back then it was considered the most expensive thing you could have floating around and a bunch of sponge divers
Well, how much resources do sponge divers have of your you know, they're like the poorest, you know
In the fishermen culture, the sponge divers are like the way at the bottom
They're not even fishermen are like Kings compared to these guys if you know what I mean, right?
Great.
So anyway
Any field is wide open
Everything is completely wide open
That's the point of Greek speak, I mean how many times you ever listen to any
Sonic event that I've done and I do only one subject never
And some people say what's your problem need to focus on one thing
I'll say well, it sounds like a personal problem that you might have with what you're hearing
so
The concept I mean, it's all very well to elaborate
You know somewhat anally on narrow scientific fields at 99% can't follow
But what I don't see is any comprehensive effort to condense that into a presentable product or a format or a package you avoid that
Right despite that also being open to you, right?
So the only actually in many cases I do have I do have pretty elaborate writings and bodies of work Some people say you have any wheat or white papers or treatise Someone said you have a treatise on your end and I was gonna send it to him and I was like now I'm just gonna send him one page just one page.
See what happens And and then it was like I got well, you guys see the rest I'm like, well damn I said that that one page should have floored unit didn't so I'm like, yeah You know, you just want to read words, you know Or do you do you get what's being said here, right?
Also when they engage they don't engage enough.
No, they don't engage in a pertinent way But in other words, how are you determining what's perfect?
Oh, it's very I mean because the what I did send I had a couple of Things that would have made anyone jump out of their seat and say that's not really so is it Yeah, but he might have done that on his own away from the conversation.
Yeah, but it wasn't it wasn't done at all ever So I don't send stuff out Back Yeah, I didn't I didn't send any Either either you Bruce or personally Sam you anything either?
No Because it's just you know, I haven't seen any direct interest I need to see more and more and more and more on this because here's the ultimate thing Is power knowledge in the knower is knowledge power to the knower the doer, you know What are you going to do with that?
Right?
But What this conversation is like Sam what you're bringing up perhaps might be what you're gonna do with it is just keep it in the informational realm and Just structure it so it can be you know It's some kind of distributorship, right?
Yeah, I mean the extent to which people I don't know act on what they know is also based
Upon how strongly they're hemmed in by their circumstances
So, I mean if you give if I have a million dollars what I'm gonna do with the information is very different than if I'm
Dead broke and I'm only hearing the information then I can perhaps only contemplate on it
So once again, we come back to what is the target audience and how are you, you know looking to?
Empower people to work with this information as far as targeting certain groups or starting circuit certain individuals
And it doesn't seem like you've identified those people at all
You're talking about because they're everywhere who have no resources whatsoever to do
They're the people are all over I've been around billionaires who are complete morons and I've been around homeless people who are geniuses
That's the gamut, you know
I've seen street sweepers that would make better heart surgeons and I've met heart surgeons that would make good street sweepers
So when you say target, yes, it sounds like something you you know
It sounds weaponized again, and you know when you bring up the million if you want to make a million dollars doing this start off
with five million
Anyway, it's a joke get it
Yeah, yeah, but it's not about you're gonna lose four million doing it.
Yeah, so anyway
Here's the other thing, okay
Do you ever tell you about the two brothers selling watermelon they needed something to do and they had some money to invest and
they were selling watermelons and they they rented a truck and they went down to the
market and they bought the watermelons for five cents apiece wholesale and
They filled up the whole truck and they showed up and they sold each watermelon for five cents and they sold all the watermelon
The end of the day they counted the money and they said well, we didn't make any money
And he says well, I know what we need a bigger truck
anyway
They bought it for five cents up, but okay you see
So what does that sound like you like this?
They missed the point, right?
All right Let's go back to a little bit of Criticism of either people in chat or emails or people that we run into or whatever You're gonna notice let's just the simple criticism Jack fresco stuff the about you know, you're part of your culture Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, you know that the shrunken heads analogy.
Okay, are you upset?
They have five shrunken heads?
Yes, I am.
My brother has 20
right
so what happens here is
Also, you have mental modeling
right
The reason why people I found
Ninety nine point nine nine nine percent of the people which except for one or two or three maybe the past 15 years
Want to say they want to study scripture is because they were raised as young children told them told through society that it's something important
That's the only reason why they want to do it because they know it's important but they have no cognitive or rational reason
Why to study it?
Yeah, you're talking about a group Which is pretty much everyone.
I've spoken to thousands of people in 15 years only two or three have risen above that So then work with the two or three Okay, so so in other words what's going on here, I mean Where's the group?
Where's the Greek study group with these two or three people?
I don't see that either So no, I don't even know where they are now The last time I spoke to one of them might have been three years ago and the other two maybe five or ten Okay, so so there and actually I would include I'm still Waiting to see that there are some potentials You know, you never say they don't exist.
You just don't know of them
Right and also people that are working on it now that I'd say in chat or yourself or they're out there might be at that
point
What are you I don't see you doing anything to empower people to go down this road
Besides putting out information that you hope that they can assimilate on their own
like when you can show me the group of people that you've put together as an effort and it failed because they dropped the ball then
We can say that people are not ready
But if you're not putting the contours around any sort of endeavor to crystallize what you're doing in the form of some kind of outworking
this is just
Complete what I
Can't even find the word.
Well, the thing is they failed.
You don't want to just fail you want to do failures?
You want to do in heuristics?
You want to run through do as many failures as possible.
So, you know how not to do it, right?
but the the interesting thing about this is That if you have let's say the methodology or the example that you gave one group that failed that with this the second group that you assemble or try to procure Through whatever Program is forming a group.
How much different is this system going to be?
You see like certain research groups when they're turned science to told to do some not much anymore
When they have to do stuff
They try to they deliberately create failure systems to measure the failures to know how things fail to know
That if they think that they're on something good if they start seeing the signs of failure
They don't have to go down all the way so they want to go through as many failures and study as possible
But when you're putting a group together or forming a group, hopefully, it's not a Gustav Le Bon type group
How much different is is the failed group going to be from the successful group?
How much different can it be or are you going to be doing the same failure thing over and over and over?
That's called insanity, right?
How can You don't have to answer this but think about how would one group fail where another one wouldn't what would be the system?
That's employed if the information is the same I don't I can't see how the information can be changed because the information is not that specific Information is very general in a direction that no one is looking at It's kind of like having ten doors.
Everyone's looking at that six or let's say three doors and you're saying hey
There's seven more doors that never been opened
You know just crack the door a little bit and look in you're gonna see a lot more of that than if it were closed
the whole time I
Can't see how forming groups and organizations and efforts and having them fail is going to be different the second time
well, the
The potential climate is different the second time.
I'm assuming that you could be speaking to different individuals second time Oh, that's a good point.
Yeah, the gods might just choose to favor you the second time.
What do you mean?
No, no No The thing is also you're further down the road when the climate is different when you said that the climate the weather is different meaning You're further down the road in time.
Yeah I'll tell you right now that there's a different attitude from let's say discussing this seven eight years ago this same stuff same exact stuff Seven eight years ago.
There is less of a Gustav LeBond attitude now
Like seven eight years ago people would say oh this guy
He's the guy blah blah now people are not focusing on that mother trying to focus more on the content
I noticed as the group loosely put
You see that's the only difference I've seen which is positive
So, okay, but the thing is what are it whether the point of
Speaking tonight is what people are not noticing and I'll bring up something like again
I went into chat I put on that we're on doing a
Sonic right now and there was just a couple of last entries about all
interlinears
So what?
So what you can so what are what are people not noticing?
Let's say it's a tool, you know If you want to build a house and you're just focusing on a good saw and a good hammer and getting a really good You know, whatever.
I don't know what else do you you know used to build a house level and measuring tape?
Ultimately, those are just tools that based on your skill and level of performance is going to build the final craftsmanship.
I've seen You can go to like a Stone Age Woodworking shop and they build fine furniture or you can go to a computer controlled Woodworking shop all the latest stuff in their furniture is crap.
You see what I mean?
Yeah the tools, you know a poor mechanic blames his tools a good mechanic can pretty much work on a car with kitchen utensils and Again, I saw the thing about interlinks.
I would rather see this is just everybody close your ears.
I'm not saying this But I'll just say it anyway What you've discovered in in the message rather than?
What you're discovering in the tools which By the way, interlinears and versions and all that are completely outside of the scriptures.
Those those are just tools There are metaphors of reaching for the information So The level of discussion in the chat concerning any subject is never going to rise above the mundane So I don't know here nor there.
No, of course, but but the other thing is you also see this In various information systems, whether it's the rectangle whether it's stuff that's been written prior whether you go down to the university to the theological department or the archaeological department by the way is also Very much involved in a lot of this stuff, right?
But when you say various groups, you're talking about
something in terms of
Conforming to a certain culture or a certain climate
Culturally, you're not talking about the reality on the ground where anything could be the case
There could be people doing all kinds of research right now into something more substantial than what you're talking about
But perhaps you don't know of them where they're only doing it on an individual level, right?
Right, you're all the absolutely.
The only one is ridiculous.
But to say let's say you're the only one on the Internet.
Yeah, that's obvious Or whatever.
Yeah
but you know
It's but here's the other thing the the mental modeling, you know people think like well if you're you've got if you've got a great idea
regarding computer hardware
most people will tell you go to
Hewlett-Packard Apple one of these big computer manufacturers, right and that seems to be stands to be correct because they're naive
But if you try to do it on your own
You you don't have the resources to do it.
You see Okay, so now there is there an in-between ground yeah, of course, it's still wide open There's a huge in-between ground Look with regards to that if somebody really wanted to get off the ground with their product or whatever They'd look for some middleman investor Right, they'd look for somebody to throw them some money and only then can you know that person who's giving them the money?
Claim that look I gave him this money.
He didn't do anything with it Once it so we come back to the when I see the Greek getting behind somebody or some endeavor to say look I'm gonna put some time and effort into this instead of just throwing seeds to the masses and half the swine is just gonna trample on it Until you during that.
I don't see you moving forward in this regard at all Hmm, you're coming back.
I don't think the point.
I don't think my point was ever to move forward At all on this as on a what people call as a career or an endeavor to be the highlight of one's existence Then what are we talking about here?
Other than I don't know.
This must make it a short sonic and hang up The point is what I found interesting is just looking at things that you don't notice and why you don't notice them What is it?
Is it censorship?
Is it mental modeling?
Oh We're not going to talk about specific things that people don't I thought you're gonna bring up specific things that people don't know They're there.
Of course, there's specific things.
You can this is a Western culture It's very easy to pick once you pick up once you under start studying the culture itself It becomes very obvious.
What to you what is not obvious to others?
Right a very simple thing is timekeeping people don't seem to mind that they have Days of observance different days of the week every year They they don't mind.
Oh, I think yeah, I mean they know they think it's how to reckon it, right?
They don't know how to reckon it, right?
So it doesn't take much to to Go beyond that but then the noticing is not the crux of the issue the it's the knowledge of how to implement it But here's the thing.
They they only notice it once the point is brought up a point doesn't ever made it Really okay.
I know because I noticed this the discrepancy in those things when I was like 11 12, but it's like well What am I gonna do with this?
Oh nothing.
Okay
Well, then let's go play video games tons of people notice tons of things
But it has no practical significance because it's not given that outlet
That's a different thing and we can talk that down to cosmic censorship or whatever
but if it's chalked down to that then there's nothing to address because that's coming from a
From a unilateral place position of force by the gods
So there's nothing there to address anyway, right exactly hence to the point that I've been saying for the past few months is why bother
It's the same thing like if a day if you have a father a very strong patriarchal matriarchal figure in the family and
You know all the children in the house by five o'clock and they shut the door and you can't go out
If you if one of the children gets a call from a friends has come out to play at six o'clock.
There's like I can't Yeah You're using the model, you know of a 1950s 60s society in today's situation.
You get a call from a friend No, I can't come on.
Okay, let's get on Skype.
We'll do some stuff on the computer I got a project you get out your tools from whatever I want and why and why is but you still but you're still doing it Informationally spiritually new no physical other than the actual device itself.
There's it's all mental, you know other than the pixels Changing oh, I just said no like I just said I you can walk me through a process Why if we have a science project, okay, I'll get out stuff.
You're gonna tell me what to do I'm gonna do it.
I report back to you the Feedback it becomes a game So Here's an example right now.
This is not that easy to find but if someone is diligent, they'll find it There are patents on solar panels that are 30 to 40 percent efficient.
The best panels now are 10% not even 5% really Some might say they have some for 20% but you can't buy them So three times more the efficiency or four times actually some of the panels are more than 50% efficient, right?
This information is not difficult to get it.
So over a hundred years old now why you know Why isn't any interest being done in that direction?
Let's say to do that.
That's something very practical and simple you see Yeah But that could very well be done by people who just don't have the wherewithal to see it through what's the name of the dude?
With the Nikola Tesla recreations, he's doing what he's doing, but he's also hemmed in by just being you know Down and out and health-wise in his old age, and he's not gonna get it off the ground On dollar.
Yeah Kind of a madman also Surprised house.
I'm surprised how civil and how composed he is on his public interviews He's a madman but in a good way.
I mean obviously because he's not working on stuff.
That is Irrelevant he's working on very relevant things But okay, but he's not he's not mad in and of himself He's if anything he's been driven mad and secondly, he's old and you take a 23 year old dollar.
It's not the same thing So once again, but he was doing a 23.
He was still doing that.
Yeah Okay.
Yeah, he was doing at a 20.
Yeah, he was he was doing it at 8 years old at 15 years old 12 years old actually, I think it's 16 years old.
He that the one of the big laboratories hired him right, so anyway Yeah, the point is that is there a methodology that?
That can be You know standardized and put on a platform and promote it is that what you're saying because You know and it's not about scripture, you know, it is well, you know The only have I maybe I haven't said this enough in public, you know, the most people think I just talk about scripture Do you know why it's not I just don't talk about scripture.
There are many other things to talk about but why because it's information that comes from the most powerful beings in That we can conceive of and because it comes from the most powerful beings we can conceive of it's the most powerful information So it's a matter methodology using a basic rational hierarchy, right?
So like if you're going to set up a mining operation and you know, you could pull on gold just as easy as you could pull on iron well That's a no-brainer.
You should pull the gold you see If it's the same effort.
Yes, so that that's my point.
Yeah, so but the thing is it's not about just about scripture It's about anything and every every subject really And what I found out is the people's I wouldn't say they resist I think they're apathetic And stubborn as a general whole and then like going back to address the point that you said, what group do you target?
Well, I think the groups have to be formed, but then you're gonna have the pitfalls of Gustave Le Bon, right?
so it has to be a leaderless a leaderless Personality lists.
I don't think that you've made I don't think you've made the kind of comprehensive effort That is necessary to establish whether or not a group even a group of two or three people or four people is viable I don't think that you've run those tests.
I don't think that you've gone out into the field to find those people.
Oh sure
I think you can make claims as the efforts that you made a decade ago, which count for very little at this point
I don't think that you've done anything within the past year that would be tantamount to anything significant
No, I wouldn't say the past year at all
But I would say that I could tell you from from a failure from a heuristic point of view from a failure and success point
The you would probably
Put your personal stuff out, but simply you're you're single in your 20s would be the best
Profile human for this type of information why because if you're married or coupled it's going to most likely break up
The relationship unless both and the chances of both
Living if any lifestyle changes were to come because of better ways of living through information
The couple will not survive it
right, so the people between let's say
18 and
26 are the most viable for this kind because they tend to be most flexible and almost every aspect of their lives
All right.
Yeah So, right And I've noticed that yeah Yeah so if you can hem down that kind of a profile and sort of measure in a roundabout way the statistical probability of Who has a greater success rate versus somebody else and that is the part a part of some kind of an effort that can lead?
Somewhere and yet I don't see Aspect yeah, so the success rate being high another, you know, there's several other Ones, you know, I can go I can go down a long and short list.
It's up to you, but you know, I've Yeah, but but what you're not doing is assimilating that into a sort of comprehensive report and then acting on it It's not it's not taking on it.
No, of course not That's up to you guys to act on it Oh us guys, but we're not but we're not the ones who are being vocal about it If the Greek was being vocal about the state of things, I think it's on a random Sonic here and there or a weekly one recently here and that's about it Oh, so the best we can do now is go off our whims Instead of putting together something that's comprehensive.
No, you could put it anyone could put anything together But it's it's all that most of the stuff that I've discussed is excessively cognitively any Yeah, we're not talking about anyone.
These are your streams So what I'm saying is that if the best that you can do is go off the whim To get off and do a stream and complain about things.
I Think that that's an indictment on the Greek because you're the one taking the comments.
No, the comments are that Comments are made when comments can be made if it's if it's not comment our then let's not comment I don't think it's common our I think it's making things happen our Okay, so let's so let's make it happen.
I don't know.
I'm outside right now near the garden.
Just had some chicory coffee I'm gonna go back inside.
Is there any reaction?
What do we have the chat?
I could open the emails I don't know who's listening or what's listening.
But Bruce anything you want to add or take away Well, you know I sat and listen Sam.
I really respect your ideas on this But we we've got These streams going out to people at different walks of life different areas different time zones Yes, I Can I expect nothing from people on chat by the way and that has nothing that's neither here nor there But Greek has a right personal circle.
He has his own professional connections.
He gets emails I don't know.
I don't know if the quality of the communication in the emails differ significantly from the chat, but I've garnered that yeah, they do They're better if nothing.
Yeah, right So there there's a lot of things that are not on the table as part of this discussion That you know, I know of privately he knows of privately so if there's no effort being made to move It's not for lack of there being no pathway to walk down That's what I'm saying.
So the alternative to that is is this which is you know redundant?
To sit here and you know go on we can we can have a good conversation here on these streams But I'm just talking about this aspect of continuously lampooning the state of society and people's unwillingness to act Which is neither here nor there because that'll change in two or three years.
Anyway, so right this should just be put aside and
Yeah, but by the way, then, you know, what's in the short
what's going to change in the next few years is the level of tension is going to increase and
and when some of the cosmic censorship is
Let go so people are more open
So it won't really even though they can see more
It's not going to benefit them because the tension will be higher you see
Sure, but anyway
Because otherwise, how are they going to be deceived later on?
So if everything's hunky-dory all the way through so right now we still have the luxury look quote-unquote to
Well, either openly or semi-openly discuss these things, but I assure you in the next few years
There's going to be a lot more tension in the air from various
Things are going to see people are going to be more urgent about other things
And how do we get things out you see and at the same time the censorship will be lifted
more and more
Yeah, that's fine.
And by that time you should be ready to reposition yourself based on the things that you've learned.
So There's an appropriateness that goes even with that now if you haven't reached that level, that's your problem.
I have no problems not you
But whoever it may concern it's their problem
Mm-hmm, so
Once again, it's not it to me
It's never about the masses or what humanity has in a holistic sense wants to do
it's about people that are interested and you cannot tell me that there are not people that are genuinely interested and
willing to pursue this
route of inquiry
the question is can we establish who they are and put together some kind of a
However, small collective of people to to to pursue something and yeah, I'm pretty sure that can be done
But I don't see it being done by the Greek which is fine
but you know, it does put a dent somewhat into the the legitimacy of these
Complaints as I call them because you could be doing more we could well, okay
But remember this is knowledge basis information base.
There isn't a there isn't a product being sold, you know where people do e-commerce Right, even even if it's a writ, there's nothing being sold like as a product You know how people sell DVDs and books or you from informational also, I mean, it's informational based.
We're not Doing confer physical conferences or trying to build, you know, how people do funding drives or go fund me to get something done Mm-hmm, right.
There is no physical thing.
It's not like the sponge Divers who said let's go sink an aircraft carrier or something like that.
It was there is no
Man a physical manifestation of this
just because there isn't any manufacturing or economic component doesn't mean that that the only reason that there isn't is because we
The endeavor is not at that stage yet where that is pertinent
But even if only at an informational level this was something that was given priority
We would see what we would see a more comprehensive Greek website
We would perhaps see some kind of a collection of Greek speak writings somewhere
We would see something that is more useful than random streams that are really hard to find unless you're part of chat
So even on the informational level, this is not being hammered in in a way that suggests any urgency anyway
So the whatever level of analysis that we apply to this effort this criticism to go all around
Yeah, okay, that's fine.
So I'll accept that but doesn't it doesn't It doesn't change the matter It doesn't matter meaning in other words that doesn't inspire me or anyone else to say, okay.
Well, maybe we should do something
You know, here's the interesting thing
There is an example
Okay years ago, you know what a tone arm on a turntable it holds the cartridge which is the stylus
You know that you swing over and drop on the vinyl record
And the audio file said oh, it's really important that if you use it, you know
Something between the base of the cartridge and the tone arm it changes if you bond it slightly
So it's not just bolted in you use some kind of bonding agent.
It sounds better You get better bass a little more dynamic.
So this music sounds a little clearer.
We found that this this Stuff that they use the real like decoupage glue.
It's like white wood glue, but it it's not even for wood It's like just tissue paper anything beyond tissue paper.
It doesn't hold very well Well, we put a little layer of that underneath a tone arm and a cartridge and bonded it and it kind of stuck pretty good And you could break it off and clean it off.
You could rub it, you know comes off, right?
and we bought a gallon of that for eight bucks and
We put it in quarter or tenth ounce bottles
Which so bet that that gallon made a thousand bottles and we sold the little tiny 10,000 10th of an ounce bottles for $10 each
So eight dollars were worth of the stuff and forty dollars worth of packaging yielded about
$2,000 and we called it tweak and
And none of the people were all the wiser all the better to say hey
This is just that really cheap ass decoupage glue.
They thought it was some high-end formula Do you see?
But you see but if we told them go to the store and get some decoupage glue And that's enough to do a hundred turntables even a small amount for two dollars Do you think they would listen?
No, they wouldn't buy it.
It's that's ridiculous For that coupons glue on a high-end turntable.
That's stupid But if you repackage it to something you Bruce you understand what I'm saying, right?
Oh, yeah Mm-hmm.
Yeah So there's your marketing in other words, that's why nothing's gonna check because I'm not gonna go down that route I'm telling people I'm telling people this stuff is this decoupage glue and they're like No, that can't be good.
That can't be true.
I Can just see that happening to yeah.
Yeah, it's company called cheating the 80s
We also did you know, if you look at highly polished metal under a microscope, it looks like the Grand Canyon
You know, we're mountains and valleys a very good, you know, so when you put interconnects together
We found that if you put slightly conductive mineral oil it increases the contact of the two
Pieces of metal by 20 or 30 percent and again that sounded better
so we did we went up a tenth of an ounce bottles and got unscented mineral oil a
Gallon of it was like four bucks and we said we sold the tenth of an ounce for ten dollars also
do the math that so, you know ten less than ten dollars of mineral oil and
$50 worth of containers made another two or three thousand called it tweak connect, you know
This is it back in the 80s, but if we told people
Wrote a little article and said hey just try this inexpensive mineral oil with a swab on your
Interconnects will sound better.
Nah.
Nah, that's not gonna work.
Nah, I Was just picturing my my friend from back in them days who was a real audio nut He was a sound engineer high-end Audio systems for the time you think back then it was a quad I and I'm just picturing him shaking his head in Disbelief and and what he would be uttering.
So yes, I can relate to this totally Yeah, let's go back to what Sam was saying about each Sam You said you noticed that there was discrepancies in Events and and days of observances as well as you were you you were young You said around 11 or so you noticed that the you know, that was evident, right?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Well, that's because you know, and you said you went and did video It just went about your life like nothing like it wasn't a big deal because if you made a big deal of it It wouldn't be a it would be a non event also, right?
but but it does apply like The middle of the month when the moon is dark metals do not coalesce in crystal form or plating So it when you know, the metal plating industry is very large like doorknobs kitchen faucets bathroom faucets You know all that chrome that you see and Fancy brass that's a plating.
All right, and there is a large industry that does that and their reject rate
Meaning where the blemishes are high and and it doesn't pass
Standard is highest around the dark moon
This is documented by the way
But they
But they persist on running their operations
During just as if it's any other day on the dark moon and they put up with the blemishes and the defects and
They just you know, we do them
So there's some total of that.
So it's so some total of that is that it's not a non event for them Is it right if you can't apply it?
Yeah, but see but here hold on But if they look at the regular calendar one month, it might be the 13th the next month It'll be the 20th so they can't use the popes work schedule.
They have to find a moon Schedule, you know or visibly do it, right?
That's what once you suggest that that's now you might as well.
It would be no different Then going to the appointment to the CEO I'm speaking firsthand now of that company and instead of walking in, you know in Casual Western attire or business attire you walk in with a bone in your nose and face paint with your hair up You know with a with, you know chicken wings and chicken blood on you.
It's that's the reaction you're gonna get From them the minute you say that not once but twice but three times in industry once you bring this up Like you're some kind of voodoo doctor You see what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Oh And another thing of my favorite thing is oh, we're gonna run this by our site University scientists and they'll tell us Right, I had what somebody wants to tell me Oh Greek your water stuff doesn't work because I couldn't find anything I talked to some people at university and they never heard of it So it can't work Okay, so there is your your what does it go?
Who are these people in industry?
They're humans, right and they're part of that culture.
So it's not the people.
It's the culture that you're going against you see and And in order to and you might be going against it because you've pulled yourself out and when you pull yourself out when you come Back in you can't relate to them the way they're used to the only thing you could do is inform them So let me go back When you you know the plating shops, I don't know.
Are you familiar with how they work?
They have three shifts They're basically going 24-7 Right, because the reason they have the three shifts and they go 24-7 is because the labor is not that expensive It's economically feasible to do so because it's Mostly mechanized, you know, you put into these tubs of liquid the liquid doesn't care the conveyor belt doesn't care You just need someone to man the operation right Bruce.
It's a mess like two people three people can produce a 10,000 Metal plating Yeah, okay.
There you go.
It's just bath bathtub square.
It's just bats of liquid and conveyors and inspectors.
Yeah, okay Yeah, so they have these things running 24-7 You see so when you approach them and you give them this kind of information They look at you and say well This has been going on this way for so long and look at everything we've invested in you How can you be the only one that's noticing that knows this can't be true?
You see they don't look at it so It's not only the people in industry It's the you know, and he and Jack Fresco does a thing about this also I'll bring him up again when like when you he brings up a few examples like this Thin wire can hold 5,000 tons.
Most people say nah, no way, but if you speak to an engineer Engineer will say oh really?
What's the tensile strength of that and he'll go and test it, right?
Or if you show them a little point and say this is 50,000 lumens But the average present not in a million years that will light engineer won't say that it says how do you power that?
What is it made of right?
But I'm telling you one step beyond that is that when you do go to the engineers They still don't want to hear it.
So there's another this is in other words
If you you have to be plausible to get through to people
Yeah, but what you I mean, you're making it look as if you're taking this you're trying to take the situation apply to a broader
Exposition on the state of society what I hear you doing is grieving about your impotency
To penetrate industry with your endeavors or to reach through to industry folks
I mean, that's you know, it's it's regrettable.
But ultimately that was a small factor of things Yes, it is but it's not it's not regrettable because it's many many many people like I said I know a handful of inventors and their inventions are genuine.
They're very unique and they can't penetrate either No one could penetrate the state it because they they don't want to you have to understand the times and you have to understand what?
It takes to go through that
Like the Wright brothers never read all the peer-reviewed scientific papers that said heavier than air flight was not possible
They never read those peer reviews
Yeah, and that's why they develop, you know what they did and it wasn't just the Wright brothers
There were other people that were doing and they were viewed as kooks or you know on the fringe
You know, for example the US the Wright brothers did several demonstrations from the military and and the military denied it
And it wasn't until the Wright brothers went to the World's Fair in Paris and they were greeted
You know with great fanfare and publicity then the military says, okay.
We'll look consider it So it's not a matter of penetrating industry or whatever, it's a matter of public opinion if you if I gave you the idea of why you didn't penetrate industry is because What they do is is let's we're gonna call a university and see if they could substantiate this.
I'd never don't bother You see Or look at us.
We've been we have 50 million invested in in several plants and we've had people from all over the world Consultants none of them ever said any of this So it can't be true So maybe then what it is to go to the media and have the New York Times write an article about it Then you think the plating people will come back and say well, it will consider your dark moon theory now Yeah, yeah, sir.
I hear what you're saying
But the end all be all of this diatribe is that ultimately people are stupid right which is a circulant
They're stupid about many things they're moronic meaning they're stuck in an immature mental rat irrational state
You're right all the same right which is caught no, it's not the same
It's very like idiocy is different than more being a moron and being stupid and being ignorant
Those are different levels
There is a mental cognitive handicap that prevents people from moving forward.
Essentially.
It's all this It's it's a deficient.
In other words, it's a deficiency that you don't want around if you're gonna have progress and efficiency You can't have that.
Yeah, right So I'm just struggling to see the viability of this type of polemic if it if we're not going to break new ground This ground has been broken since Ocelli in the Greek days So at some point it has it has to be left behind and other things explored.
Oh
There's tons of stuff to explore
There's stuff in industry that I'm considering right now that I have I am not discussing and have not discussed
That's quite interesting and because of my experience
I ponder it and
What I'm probably going to do is have a more diversified or different approach than before
But then the standard approach right the standard approach is approach those
Excuse me already in the industry or do it yourself
But neither one is really viable because you know when you try to do anything yourself
You are the the let's say the boss the worker the mop the janitor the accountant
It's it's a 30 hour a day job, right?
If you've ever been on a business venture where you have you're dealing in an industry you have to portray or you have to
Satisfy all the needs of the operation which are many and that's not what I want to do
And I don't want to go approach the industry
There's another way in between and I'll discuss that maybe if we're still speaking publicly or whatever in the next few weeks or months
Okay, there's still being
And it's quite interesting and I did bring something up in the last sonic that the for example
I would suggest that someone does a highly marketed website
that invites even viable or semi viable ideas for people to publish and
Also is sent to the Patent Office and the International Patent Office on a regular basis even if they ignore it
Even if you don't get a response
What that'll do is it'll throw a major
Patent industry because basically the patent industry is to restrict is create restrictions, right?
Basically, you know if Michelin tire comes up with a new tire and they patent it
Well, the other tire companies can't use it unless they license it from Michelin so restricts the industry
right and the reason for this is because I was doing some research and
There's a guy in the 80s on a spoof
He did it he looked kind of technical a document called a digital loudspeaker
And he showed how it would work and a friend of his or he was a writer at a magazine
They published it and even today when people want to get a patent on a digital loudspeaker.
The Patent Office will cite that publication
Public notice and they will not issue a patent
So the there will never be a patent issued to digital loudspeakers or very slim
they will be because this guy wrote a
comprehensive
fictional or a science fiction article on how
Digital loudspeaker would work in the 80s and the and the Patent Office is still citing it today
So if anyone has any broad or narrow ideas about a gizmo a device or a methodology
You can have a website where they just do a comprehensive if they can't we'll find someone who could write it up
Descriptively and just put it up there and send it to the past so that in the future if one of these big companies like
Apple or whatever wants to patent this they can't because it's already been made public
People don't understand how patents work.
They think you have to have a patent
No
If it's publicized the Patent Office will research it and if they do find it
They will not issue the patent not because it has previously patented but previously
publicized you see
so that would be a great thing to throw a
monkey wrench into industry or whatever that entire
gamut called patent patenting or patent
Patent licensing and all I think that whole thing needs to go away.
You know what I mean?
How you get what you're saying, but I mean a lot that's an idea in itself right there that that should be implemented Yeah, but this is you can't just pull out ideas and say that this would be interesting or this would be interesting I mean there has no it's not interesting.
It's more than interesting.
It's it's more.
It's almost like a public domain protection Because if someone if there's if someone if an idea is put out there and someone can't capture it Hey, let me give you another example.
It's in pharmaceuticals How many times do you you know have you here?
Well the reason why they they offer this drug is because they're patentable, right?
All right, that's why they do that, but but if something is not patentable
There's no benefit to them you see
To do it to get involved in it
so if you have all these
Semi-synthetic compounds
Anyone in biology that understands that have applications for let's say medicinal purposes even on a far shot start publishing them
So the big pharmaceutical companies can't do it
Do you see what I mean just throw a monkey wrench?
Yeah, did I cut it out for a second you might have yeah?
Okay, it's not a night.
Just an idea.
What if it should be done?
in other words to to balance out the Wanton wanton Capitalism which is useless, right?
Yeah, but what I was saying, I don't know if I cut out is that that that still feels like a zero-sum effort I mean look at a lot of what you're talking about to me Sounds like it has the veneer of careerism attached to it where a person goes out In carves a space for himself within an industry works with a bunch of people There's a research funding manufacturing distribution element and to me.
I'm like for what though like comparatively That is an interesting when you position it next to scripture and say that you're gonna pursue that which is to me a higher Order of things like what are we gonna?
Go do all this industry stuff for for what it's not gonna be here But it's not even if you want to you want to talk about industry scripture is an industry What's the most highly printed book in the world?
Statistically, that's no I don't know from I know but from a mentally ma mental model.
What's the only mental model?
I know but hold on.
It's not scripture
But it's the only book that you'll see published that goes from Genesis to Revelation or Genesis to the Psalms
So it is you know, they're modeling it after that
You see and by the way
you know, the King James was considered copywritten and restricted in many academic uses back in the day and
Obviously, it's a version but when you bring up the entire subject
Just like I've said and I think it's very rational to say so when people say well
I want to just read the interlinear or the Hebrew and the Greek.
I'm like, well, yes, that's that's good to extract the the Key point so you could communicate what it's about But if you're going to have a discussion with pretty much anyone in the Western world You must know the King James because that's the level on how they're going to discuss it.
Also, you know, although Only when I say that you won't even be able to have you won't even most likely Succeed in having a rational discussion in the King James because what they're going to be do is giving you the core doctrine That's it's created Now you can have a good discussion that depends on your level of communication Once again, that's each person's business and that can be done.
I've done it to a certain extent and It's yielded, you know results that are satisfactory for me.
I didn't do it out of altruism
But that's between you and yourself like a lot of the things that you talk about should be addressed at the level of the individual
Where it's it's about your effort and it's about your willingness to pursue a certain thing
But instead you and you address it at the level of the group, which is completely useless because the groups won't don't get anywhere
Well, then I'd have to do one-on-one like a psychotherapist.
I
mean at the level of
Analysis that we're at all the only thing that matters is the individual
Individuals who are willing to participate in this endeavor as a matter of almost personal gain
I do this for personal gain not necessarily in the economic dimension, but certainly in the cognitive dimension anything knowledge
Knowledge is its own reward, by the way
Yes
Wisdom has its own reward because you can you how many fools I would say
Do you know that are worth tens or hundreds of millions and they're just fools and if I?
In in someone would you want their money?
Well the answer to most people would say yes, but would you know in order to get their money?
You have to be a fool like them.
I'd quickly say no Yeah, so what I yeah, so you go back to tool.
Yeah, so you go.
Well, yeah Now if you want to say that but that's being but that's being done anyway behind, you know at the scenes I don't discuss I don't take all that Okay.
Okay.
So then there are people that I'm in communication with that do call for consent.
Yeah and counts counseling on various things Yeah, no, I what then if you know that there is a realm in which some kind of progress is being made Why are you getting on these?
Diatribes.
Oh, why should I don't know?
Maybe maybe it's it's time not to not to not do it at all.
Yeah Well or not no diatribe Pull up a subject and let's discuss it or not.
We could just you could just send the stream right here.
That's fine Of course, there's things that could be discussed but I Just don't know what you're doing Why are we not discussing the things?
Why are we talking about this stuff?
This other stuff.
Well, let's just let's just well, let's just focus on one thing.
What's interesting is that right now?
What what?
Just change the subject segue This is obvious but the Comprehension of prophecy is is of dire importance, right?
if anyone is going to be a student of scripture they Need to prioritize understanding Prophecy, which is multifaceted.
You have to understand how to keep time.
You have to understand what is
Coming in the future based on what has happened in the past and what how it will be different
and also you have to understand how to discern the lack of
detail of this current society and what I mean detail in this current society in the biblical narrative is that you don't see like
computers actually being mentioned and automobiles and
Rocket ships and right all this stuff.
So you need to understand the narrative
The this the very partly nature of the narrative, you know, in other words, there's no detail regarding our society
so you can't use the details or
Or lack of them that are in the narrative to pinpoint where you are
So you have to understand timekeeping and when and how events will repeat and that is really a dire
Need in the comprehension of scripture, believe it or not.
So your knowledge, you know history would also have to be pretty good then, too Yes, and but the history that pertains to scripture correct now now how often have you been in a situation?
Where let's use the term again Like we've been discussing a group of people that you found completely irrelevant or stupid If you were to go explain that group to another Group or a colleague, would you give a lot of detail?
No, you just say there's a bunch of idiots that like to go and do this and that's it That's how the scriptural narrative is when it comes to this society.
The gods are not impressed by anything technological that we're doing
obviously
They're not impressed by
much
Really, there may be a few individuals were you know, we're impressive to the gods and that's it
It for us to you know mention
So, how do you how do you know what's coming and how it's going to come because if people did comprehend the scripture
On these worldwide events, don't you think some would cry foul when they were happening?
but I'm telling you they're gonna be happening in front of everyone and no one's gonna be noticing and I don't mean no one because it does say some people do So, how do you put that together in today's language and comprehensible in today's mindset?
That would be a project to do all right In itself, but you know when people start discussing I need an interlinear for what?
Through osmosis.
You just put it on your head and you sleep with it at night and you'll understand it doesn't work that way
Yeah, let's go back to another way to look at it
If you were if if all you had was the King James Version
That's it and you read it with comprehension more than once or twice you would get about 90% of it
it would be extremely frustrating because after the first or second reading you would start to notice anomalies because the
What the words that are being used are not supported by following doctrine in the text.
So you'd say that word cannot be here, right?
Like for example, he says my name is the Lord.
I am your God
Well, you there's only so many times you could read that and say well Lord is not a name
there's something else missing here and you mark that as
spurious or a detail that is erroneous you see and then you're finally going to keep going and
Notice things that just don't make any rational sense, but you're going to get the story
You're going to get the timeline even though the books are out of order and you're going to get the law
Because if you don't understand the law
You're not going to understand the principles that are given in other places, right?
Mm-hmm So that's strictly with the King James no interlinear you can do that By the way, you can do that with the requisite level of urgency and focus, which is very rarefied Very rarely, but we're not talking about it.
It is possible Yeah, and you're also saying that in retrospect after having done your own research over the period of a decade plus So once again, that's out of most people's purview to even say it's possible it's it's still impractical Sure.
Sure it is.
But because ultimately Let me give you an example that might be helpful just sticking with the King James and I ran into someone Stayed over here for a few days during the Passover about a decade ago.
It was an older head.
He was twice my age and We were talking about scripture and a couple of people brought out some different versions and I and he looked at me and he says Yeah, you know after a while of reading the King James you end up finding out where all the mistakes are It's no big deal, right?
He's that's what he told me.
I said, yeah, exactly
He supplied that to me, you know, and I was thinking the same thing
You see it was in other words
We had a parallel thought on the document because what was arising during there were other people here
There were arguments or debate on which version was better
And I just we just looked at each other and basically said if you find out where the mistakes are, it's no big deal
You know on a general doctrinal point of view, but you're gonna miss there are specifics that you will miss by the way
You know, like the word forgive is not in there, you know
And things like that, you know, and the word sin will not really be defined
Until you go to the you know
The one that give is not there, but the word pardon sort of is
The word pardon is yeah, but it's not yeah, so in other words
What there is a benefit to going into the languages of preservation of what we have or can call the languages of preservation?
To the best that we can access still today.
You will glean more but they will not change the story that much
You see in some cases if you look at it
From a narrow and deep perspective some things are changed very deeply
You know like your perspective on the Christ because there's nowhere that you pick up in the King James that his name was
Yeshua or Joshua if you use the J you see you don't pick that up
But once you find out it was Yeshua and the sixth book of the Bible's Yeshua if you insist on using letter J
It can't be Jesus.
There's something really amiss there.
It has to be Joshua You see so there's some legal ease something a legal loophole.
That's being down there And I think I've explained it on a sonic the reason they use Jesus instead of Joshua's later on if you put their feet to the fire.
They'll say well we never talked about
The one in the Bible anyway, this is a whole other invention on top of it
So it's like giving them room for denial
But anyway
No anyway
Amen, I'm just I want to move along ever more increasing lines of efficiency when it comes to these kinds of discussion
I'm so past getting
Forget about the discussion the thing is you've got any updates or any improvements on food clothing and shelter the rest of it doesn't matter
Well look if here's the thing if you understand scripture.
What are you gonna?
Do you can tell your children and grandchildren like it matters?
I'm going to stockpile that knowledge until such a time that the times change and I can position myself more efficiently to use it of Course exactly and and you'll be dodged.
Hopefully dodging the cacophony of the Antichrist, right?
and his group Yeah, hopefully Yeah And again bringing that point up if it's so obvious You know half the idiots on the internet are talking about this guy Already know the term Antichrist as a world leader Right so how you know It's gonna be a secret who he is even even when he's Performing his duty as such no one will know that it's him.
I mean now say no one.
I mean you know the general group So think about the import yeah, well yeah, which is irrelevant Mm-hmm It's irrelevant qualitatively, but quantitatively it is very relevant because it's the mass Majority who cares you love this group stuff, okay?
So go do something man go go put together up Do you like I get so you you do it?
I'll show up if I do if it's Sonic if it has to be written.
It's or whatever is I charge like $2 a word so Maybe five And that's pretty much it.
I'm not gonna work for free I'll go paint someone's kitchen to make a hundred bucks.
What the hell you know I'm not gonna sit there and write stuff for free No, the writing is the easy part That can be done by Gruntz Yeah, yeah, it's no, but the import of everything is do you know where you are in navigation if you navigating?
Scripture and I give many examples if there were plenty of evangelists in World War two in Europe that were crying
This is the apocalypse, and it was very convincing when those what bombers were they using b-29s and C
Was a tens Bruce were they using World War two that those twin-engine planes that were hard to shoot down
You know you bring a rudder off landed
See nines or something whatever they in that area.
Yeah Yeah, they were dry they were blowing the shit out of everything the evangelists on the ground were Saints the apocalypse and the people were saying Yes, it is very convincing But they didn't know how to navigate scripture They didn't know where they were in time if you know how to navigate where you are and how you are you know?
You got to know you had to have a clock and the clock is you got to watch what they call Israel The land and the attitude of the people Have we you know I've been doing by the way.
This is a so what am I doing?
You know what is the Greek doing?
I'll tell you what I'm doing recently past year.
I've Been doing some very gradual Meaning gradual in one week.
I'll do a lot Maybe a month will go by and then I'll do a lot for three weeks.
You know it's it's very spurious
I mean the sporadic on the
specifics on the rebuilding of the temple
Right I think we've discussed that at one point
I was you and I Sam and I was
Ready to fall out and I was like I need to talk about some other time because I've been really looking into and there's a
lot of details that have come up with
That is something that is quite interesting that would be a very interesting
Because of recent events also to write a short paper on
And give the details and the scripture because it's not what you think yes
there will be a temple, but it's not going to be the way people envision it and
Also putting in detail the other the temples that are mentioned in there you see like Ezekiel's temple
You know is not going to be in Jerusalem.
You know so It's gonna be north of it, but Let me just give a little bit a highlight out right now when the The final temple is built.
It's going to be completed way at the end Where it where it's ready to be?
dedicated
It's it's very very very end because it's not around for a long time before the Antichrist steps in into it
You know it's like brand-new almost
You see what I mean mm-hmm, but there's so much political
Mayhem that surrounds the concept of the temple that needs to be forgotten and
Pushed aside, and it needs to be more practical
before
You know it actually happens
And it's not going to be on the Mount of Olives like certain groups
State because unless they scrape the Mount of Olives down to bedrock
Because you're not it because what is the Mount of Olives predominantly
Known for it's a cemetery.
You know cemetery, and you can't bill It would be you can't put it on top of a cemetery unless you scraped it down to bedrock You waited a moon or two, right?
So anyway
There's some very you know very specific points that need to be
Addressed that are in Scripture that no one is talking about
So and
Some of the points you see what happens is the scripture will give you like a B's in C
D won't be there, but you can write about D because of a B and C you see it's like a it's like a triangulation
They'll give you the coordinates and you then start naming the location
We've already discussed that the Antichrist is not going to have an open
Assyrian identity and various things like that there's other things that could be discussed about him
He will be a Syrian, but not openly right, I think you said Jewish.
Yeah, he was gonna show today Yes, yeah, did you do?
Yeah, yeah So as in as in lineage right right Because if you read in Scripture like in the New Testament is the festival of the Jews It doesn't say that's the festival the Judeans and the Judeans had adapted Babylonian timekeeping They still used the Levitical days, but they did him on Babylonian times That's why the Christ when he was invited to go to the feast of booths.
I think in Mark He says this is not my time.
This is your time It's an evil time and a lot of Christians or whatever cite that as the holiday being bad No is he specifically discussing when it was being done?
Anyway
That's that's a very obvious point
But you know with mental modeling people don't see it because they've approached it with a model that they've been shown prior to seeing the information
But here's another if you're going to consider from here on out the tension worldwide tension is going to keep increasing
All the way to the end
But it's going to get increased to the point also the cosmic censorship will be lifted so you will you can't complain later
that you didn't know and also that you fall for this promise of
What's going to be done by the you know world geopolitical and religious and scientific community on humanity?
Because you know as time goes on you notice that there's a blur between the legal Scientific and political community you notice that there's everything the lines are blurred.
They all overlap The religious is the site well scientific legal and political overlap You know like the politicians will write a law that you have to have vaccines right and if and then the attorneys back it up Right so they have science.
You know BS bad science politics and Attorneys you know just you know the goddess religion.
They all work together So all this is going to be worked together So that's why I say food clothing shelter just chill the fuck out.
It's not a family hour.
It's a medical term, but So if you're in don't play this sonic event for your in-laws right Bruce Yeah Anyway Yeah, all right.
Let me see if there's Anything going on here no emails, and I think no one in chat, right?
Someone's in chat why bother how about the Mets are you supposed to spell dem?
DEM Mets how about dem Mets like turdy turd and turd Mets Dem Mets yeah, damn DEM It's funny again with accents you know if you have a New York accent.
You know like hey, how you doing turdy turd and turd How about the Mets no matter how smart you are you sound stupid you ever notice that people that have a heavy accent like that It doesn't matter what how smart you are you said you sound stupid Yeah, well you can use that as a form of misdirection.
You just sound stupid doesn't mean you are that's right Anyway so great anything else on your chest no not at all I'm just chillin, bro.
I
Have to I have to take this whole this kind of thing with a measure of light heartedness because it's like
It's almost like listening to somebody vent
on some therapy stuff
Depends on what end they're venting from sometimes if they vent from the other end
It's not you don't want to listen to that right whoever smelt it dealt it right remember that when you're a child
Bruce you brought it's an American thing.
Yeah Because you can vent various ways Yeah, I don't think it's quite reached that level of Flatulence what yeah or turpitude or whatever yeah, it's fine.
It's fine for now But um Yeah, I mean it would be fun to address things with a higher degree of I don't know specialization or certain certain things but um We'll take things as they come I guess I Do think that in general and I think I've said it enough that We can do a bit better than the reoccurring harangues against society and things like that.
It's not against it's just a matter of But just the general the general vibe of you can't go against them and well I Think it's quite.
I think it's quite scriptural actually Okay, I mean I'm sure that one can bend anything to towards one's bias You know I'm happy to be I'm happy to be a part of streams, but it's a forward bias It's a phone you know anything about electronic design at Bruce You might this might jive with you when you forward bias something.
Yeah, I can take right.
Yeah, it's a good thing It is yeah, you're forward biasing look it up.
Yeah Things are generally measured by the extent to which they are they are productive and useful And I don't think anybody feels empowered by being a part of something that leans towards the factuous so This could be this could be done better, and we can do it better, but It depends on you know the extent to which people want to apply themselves.
Well.
There's many ways of doing it you know there's like for example the Hitchhikers guide to the galaxy is a jestful even though.
It's stupid is a jestful way to Objectify things you know what about writing something well if someone were to visit this planet.
What would they see?
You know Keep it simple make it a children's book or planet earth for dummies You remember those yellow and black books Yeah, I have one of those or you could just make a book of Greek speak No, no, no, I think I think I think bowing out.
I think bowing out of that is
Just speak how about just speak why Greek speak Greek speak is kind of like a pet thing
You know for sonic events in the past
So or speak you know any whatever suits your fancy the point is that things could materialize in a more substantive way
And there there are valid avenues to take that down
You have the the Winston Churchill book like that's a format if you wanted to do it you could do it
You know I'm familiar.
I also have one on various quotes from Einstein the
Memoirs of another and see I have it somewhere here
several several people in industry science politics have memoirs, and it's just a compilation of letters and
Quote unquote smart things that were said that were worth memorializing you know
Various formats and doing that with con you know Sun Tzu is a good one
You know Sun Tzu is only like a few hundred words, but it's it's a it's a small pocket
Version you know several women maybe less than a hundred pages most of its commentary
so you can you can
compile any bit of information
With some commentary or not
If you're here's the other thing if you're going to avoid any commentary.
You know what you do right t-shirts
anyway
So right
You have bite-sized
Presentations at BYTE or however either way that's fine, but
Yeah, I think it has to if it's anything's going to be done
It's going to have to be from an objective point of view as one would say visiting planet Earth
And you'd have to go break it down
You know temporarily conditionally qualitatively you know temporarily would be you know spring summer
Fall winter these are the you know you know building up growing and breaking down events on this you know political whatever personal
Happen this way.
You know it's just be real objective.
I keep history out of it unless you have to show an analogy That's why history is bullshit.
It's too neat
Anyone who's has any practical experience on this planet knows that nothing is as smooth and as neat as history is shown
That's your first sign that it's bullshit
right so
It's too tidy
Even people's concept of the scripture is too tidy
You know like I think on the last sonic event I brought up
I heard several people during the week and different aspects of life say why does God you know they don't know
But this is what they said why does God allow all this misery in the world, and I'm like duh
It's very clear in scripture.
They have no problem killing
85,000 Assyrians in their sleep
Did it say may they rest in peace after they did that no
Right so I mean come on the people's miscon you know how do you give a miscon
Misconception of the gods is by just leaving all information about them out
It's not that they have a misconception
They have no information you see
So start from scratch on that
Mm-hmm
I'm sure you've heard that before
Say how can God allow all this because it's not that they're misconceived that they have no concept no information when someone asks that no
information at all
How can you so it's like asking?
Why do people get hit by cars?
You know it's it's like well Get inside of one get busy or whatever or have a mechanical failure and see how easy it is to do that When the time is right, so I mean you know they have no concept they have no concept not a miss So the thing is again.
There's no constant.
There's no information out there, but yet it seems like you have practical industry
practical culture practical
Science practical whatever right it's practical is it it seems practical
Yeah, I think food clothing shelter and that encompasses knowledge of the human body which is also the mind
Which
Is completely intangible
between that that transitions segues into the realm of you know other realms, let's say the gods and
Is would be paramount because everyone has one you're presuming that anyone and everyone
That you're approaching let's say like you said earlier marketing this information to as a human body, right?
So that would be what they all have in common, so you have to cover that really first Or within you know primary so I Mean again.
I've had several healings this past week Pretty deep cut and like okay Put the squeeze on it paper towel electrical tape and next day.
It looks like a paper cut and if it would have been a standard Westerner in America they would have ran to the hospital So it works well with burns as well You ever lean up against something hot, and you don't know what's hot and you're like wait a second.
Oh, I'm being burned
right
And you pull yourself away
That's very common by the way with people that have motorcycles larger motorcycles where the exhaust pipes are exposed
You'll see burns on the inside of their legs from the between the ankle and then the calf if you've ever seen that before
Usually usually women that ride on the back
You know of the older motorcycles now they tend to tuck exhaust pipes
So they're out of the way Bruce.
Are you familiar with what I'm saying?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, people in shorts get on a motorcycle You know a 10 15 20 30 year old motorcycle exhaust pipes coming out the side.
Yeah, oh, yeah They're not you know.
Yeah, you don't know you're burned until you smell something or you're like why why am I so uncomfortable?
Oh, you're being burned idiot Right it's not like you're approaching a hot stove, and you know it's hot and when you touch it You immediately retract knowing that it was going to burn you before it actually does that's the less severe.
Let's say
but what I'm saying also the the
Extreme compression on the body for also works with burns
I've had discussions in the future about how burns can be treated even to some real esoteric stuff
Which we've discounted ever heard of someone called the burn doctor when someone is burned the you call them up and give them some
Information and they do some kind of radionics thing on you no matter where you are in the world
The burner the burn heals faster
I shouldn't have even said this because I don't endorse that
But I just want to throw it out there that stuff like that exists
Mmm.
Yeah, yeah
So and they have a lot of testimonials they even have people in fire departments
They pull someone out of a building and they have their ID
they just want like the day you were born in your name and
Then they do a radionics thing and you heal faster
And there's testimonies that people have and I did but there's people also that I've told to use it
This is a while back decade or so or less and they said I'm not sure but we know
There's other ways because what a burn actually is here's a here's a hint
Have you heard me discuss energy how electricity heat and light are interchangeable
You could take light make electricity heat make a little light or they're all three interchangeably ever heard of someone
Getting burned by light, you know sunburn right you ever heard of getting burned by electricity or getting burned by heat
They're all interchangeable.
So essentially what a burn is is Light heat and electricity which are interchangeable.
It's like saying steam water and ice.
It's the same thing, right?
When you get a burn what it is It's something compromising the insulation of the body because you're electrical the skin is Imagine in a very rudimentary sense.
This is not really accurate, but just to meant to model a thought Imagine your body is the wire and or a conductor and the skin is the insulation That's pretty easy to imagine that analogy and Can you imagine a wire where the insulation gets burned pretty easy analogy?
Right anyone who's has a curling iron or a toaster or electric stove, right?
You've seen that done before right soldering iron, especially So how do you and but now that we know that the heat is actually electricity or light or heat?
Not and or or either form So then what do you know about insulators and what do you know about heat light and electricity and put those together?
And how do you take that knowledge understanding that there's a vacuum in the body biological vacuum to make burns heal rapidly?
Regardless of what type of burn it is Pretty interesting.
I haven't gone public on this at all yet And I'm not really experimenting with it on it.
Like I should like walk up to and physically burn myself, right?
To and then try to you know, I'm not into that.
You know how they have Psychotherapists before they get their certification They psychoanalyze each other and write reports before and they have to produce the report as being a viable Report and analysis in order to get certified you familiar with that practice you've heard of it.
Mm-hmm.
No Okay, you know a psychotherapist or a psychiatrist has to produce a certain amount of certifiable or reports on his colleagues They do it to each other to show a model analysis, you know to their peers to get awarded a certificate Like part of their internship, right?
Now do surgeons start doing surgery on each other?
And to see how well they did the surgery on each other in order to get certified as a board-certified surgeon No, they don't do that.
Do they?
What's the difference one is spiritual one is physical?
People are very squeamish You see when it comes to doing physical experimentation Unless it's of course to a subgroup Cultural subgroup right like prisoners are usually experimented on right?
You see how it works it doesn't seem right to you that the Psychotherapists have to do that amongst themselves, but the surgeons don't are not allowed to cut on themselves.
It doesn't seem right to me So you're going to be experimenting on a subgroup anyway You see is does that mean that there is a double standard there?
Yes, clearly there is but on the other hand, it's a quite a serious thing to
start just
Cutting you know someone open that doesn't need to be cut open just to show that you are capable right anyway
These are things that need to be considered
That's why I bring up like you said earlier marketing this to people they were presuming that anyone and everyone enter
Acting with this information has a human body.
That's useful So that is paramount so then I think understanding basic dietary principles and basic healing mechanisms or First aid mechanisms would be one of the things at the top of the list But you have to be careful how you position such information in a general body of work because if someone just sees it In a serial way they'll say I'm not interested in that anyway, which is funny, right?
I've by the way, you know, it'll turn them off to the rest of it.
So it has to be categorized in an equal footing I've you wouldn't believe how many against I know you don't like this Sam, but I'll say it Anyway, how many people I've discussed basic?
Dietary principles or healing modalities and they say well or you simple the fact that you don't absorb, right?
It's not possible anatomically and they'll say well, I don't know anything.
That's funny.
I'm not a doctor I don't know anything about the human body Right, but you have one, right?
Okay You see.
Oh, I have I have a couple of cars, but I don't know anything about them That's okay, right that's fine that means it's a ritual, you know when most people when they get in a car It's a ritual to them They know that if they do this and do that it's going to get them to where they want to go outside of that They don't know anything about it most people View their own physical body as a ritual.
They know that if they don't sleep they they the next day is ruined So they sleep, you know, so they sleep and they do this and they do that, but they don't know anything about it See and they don't want to know because there's been a selective group of entitled people called doctors that they Right.
Does that sound right to you?
That doesn't sound right to me
And by the way, if you've I don't know if you've ever had the experience of doing this is rhetorical
I'm not expecting an answer, but if you ever approach a medical technician aka doctor of any type
Especially an internal medicine type and you and you go over the anatomy
They will agree through the anatomy that nothing goes through any of those walls
Let's say the you know through the lumina of the intestine nothing or the lungs nothing ever penetrates through there
And then once you say then well, how does how does the food get absorbed?
Then if they you've just agreed that nothing goes through there
Well, they they all medially immediately abandon all reason and they look and it says it must be absorbed and they walk away
Just like that's something you would hear from a four-year-old
You see you see so they they don't want to see it now and the other answer whatever
an intelligent
What they call that when a child has a little tantrum connect tantrum, yes
They have a little mini tantrum the the most rational
Answer I've seen to that once they've come to the conclusion themselves
There's no selling here, there's just presentation or I'm just telling not selling this to anyone when the most rational answer
I've had I heard more than once which is the most rational is passing the buck
Like they're not responsible for how screwed up the medical systems what they say is oh, yeah
I see that now, but they don't acknowledge that I said who's they well, you know the hot the people that teach me
And the people that supervise me and the people that are over the the industry
They don't acknowledge it so that means oh, so that's okay because you just passed it over to them like oh
I just work here right?
I was just following orders
That's the most rational that I've heard
That's about typical for just about every place you go
Yeah, no from the medical people
And I know well, I shouldn't I'll just say I know there's been
Maybe a small handful that have abandoned practice because of being subject to this information
You know found another vocation
Which those would be at the top of the list
You know in terms of the what you would call a moral compass.
You know what I mean And I've also run into some attorneys that have abandoned that profession because they were found out what the bar Association was about and what the courts were really doing And the attorneys do the same thing they say well, that's what they do.
That's what they tell us to do You know pass the buck, you know So it's still wide open.
It's everything is completely wide open Sure is And you've got a decade and a half maximum At this point, you know decade and out less than that You always keep shifting these dates.
No, it's the same.
It's like three or three to five years No, not at all the last year.
I said 15 years now I say 14 years, but still a decade and a half you were rounded off a debt a little bit more than a decade 20 25 around 20 around 20 25 you'll you'll be in the throes of a Middle East Union and in the throes of an upswing Global upswing and don't believe anything.
I Mean that that keeps stating it's not going to be a propagandized upswing.
It's going to be an actual one You will actually see manifestations in Every aspect of you know, what what can be conceived or perceived?
You know supporting that upswing It's going to be real no one's gonna cry foul On the aspect of it not being real.
There will be some crying foul about
You know from a prophetic point of view, you know what I mean crying foul that this is
going going lead to abominations
So
In other words you could show something as being right and it's not right at all like I give the example of patriotism
You know, if you didn't have patriotism, would you have a military that no you wouldn't
You wouldn't have a military as such you would have
Every the government would
Promote that all of its quote-unquote citizens were well armed and well trained
So you wouldn't need a military?
So anyway, hmm All right, anything else anything else you see Bruce any messages or anything or we'll just call it Not really.
No, we got a 1517 people on there Listening, okay Yes, Sam's laughing.
Yeah, they don't expect much And you won't be disappointed No, I've never disappointed saying well, there's stupid stuff, you know, or or there's nothing there and just showing that I'm disappointed at it No, because I never expected anything You know Well expectation and hope is slightly different.
Yeah.
No, I don't have any Will hope is that's too broad of a term to apply to you know Something is as reactionary as a comment or a question No Yeah, the how can you have any hope when you've been elected to?
Subsist and exist in a world that is Leased out to the adversary and his lease is expiring.
Of course is coming to an end but you know, how can anyone find any hope in a world that is You know, basically you share you're sharing a bed with the adversary protection Yeah Yeah, yeah more like sharing a building but he could he's on floor 78 you can be on floor 20 Yeah, there you go.
But still You know, there's no hope in that condition Yeah Within within that condition nothing.
There's hope outside of it.
Yep, and that's all knowledge-based and and any hope or any Advantage advantage you have even within it is still knowledge-based So, there you go Mmm, it's all knowledge-based You know when people act Without any knowledge It's either they consider it a stroke of luck or good fortune or they said that was just a stupid thing to do But it turned out okay, or it doesn't turn out.
Okay.
It was just a stupid thing to do.
Anyway, you see so What do you think Bruce anything?
I got nothing on this and great.
Nobody nobody's chatting or anything Anything closing for you Sam Um, no, I feel like I've said what I need to say Perhaps next time we can be a bit more topical Well, the topic is was a slightly paradoxical to discussing while discussing Discussing things that not circular at all things that you don't normally notice we didn't even get to that.
Yes, we did I opened it with an example was that not to bring up the chat again But people when I went into chat to write down that we're gonna do a sonic There was about two or three comments about an interlinear.
I'm like, why bother?
You could read every interlinear all day and I can you explain what script can you get the message?
The answer is no Yeah, this is just repackaged stuff that you said before ain't nothing.
Yeah Well, you know the Sun's gonna rise tomorrow like it did today and yesterday.
There's nothing new there But I don't ask anything of the Sun.
So I don't invest my time in the Sun the Sun does what it does
I invest my time in these streams
Not true, you know, believe it or not solar flares are are instigate able from Earth, you know, but anyway, that's another discussion
Yeah, yeah, so again, it's it's very simple
You know what it boils down to is communication is there any communication
Meaning if from then in here and and now and then in the future and I would say no there's no communication
That's that's the standard precept of rational and caught, you know
beings is is to being able to communicate properly and I'm telling you there is no communication and
Communications and things that what are them?
What are memorialized events?
What are what are scripture?
What are textbooks?
What are his real history?
What is anything?
It's communication You know art is a communication, you know Clothing fashion is a communication, right?
Speaking of the Sun and things that can be known objectively What's this idea about the Sun goes through periods of what they call coronal mass ejections?
Which yes some kind of a discharge that can heat up the earth's surface and set fire to things Well that there you know, there's an 11-year cycle of high and low that they've been recording for a long time since 1860 something 1840 right the the coronal mass ejection if you study that term very Very carefully.
It's not the actual Sun itself.
It's the corona of the Sun In other words, it's the immediate surrounding boundary layer of the Sun that the ejection happens, right?
What happens on the Sun is expansions and contractions and things, you know on the surface, right?
So what they've missed out and this is more on I've had discussions with quote-unquote people on this that are this is their job to study.
This is there's a misunderstanding of The in other words is a difference between the Sun It's activity what the Sun is actually doing itself.
It's visible Versus what is at the corona that affects us you see what I mean?
So that is that is the crux of the understanding So the Sun goes through a minimum which it's at right now now The last what sparked this science or this field on the Sun was in the 1800s.
I think 60s or 70s It was a mass coronal ejection.
They call her solar event.
That was so electrically powerful.
It fried all the telegraphs Yeah, and the telegraphs were the you know, that's like frying all the Internet, you know all communications now it would fry, you know But also you have to comprehend that it was very they were the were very different now than then But still susceptible to it.
This is a particularly high
With this past week is pretty high for the cosmic radiation
Yeah, but you know
But you understand that if you're if you went out into space past the Earth's atmosphere, you wouldn't see the Sun is not there's nothing
There it's basically induction through the atmosphere that makes the Sun the Sun to us
So, all right, I do understand that it plays a big role in prophecy as well, you know in terms of what it does
And it's going to be anomalous.
The scientists will not know it's doing what you read about in prophecy That's why it's in prophecy because if it was not anomalous, it wouldn't be in prophecy.
Does that help?
Yeah, that's fine.
But I'm I'm trying to understand also as far as
the cycles apart from the 11-year cycles, which I've
Seen there's also this idea of a 10,000 year cycles as far as violent outbursts that if you map backwards you get
something with them, they can only measure that by the
Geo plate geo a job a geology by going down layers and I'm telling you when they go down through layers of earth
It's not as accurate as what they believe
We don't know.
Yeah, the only time I could substantiate
Anything that they say is going back to the mid 1800s
when they start when you start going beyond a hundred and something years when I
Older stuff to me is isn't it has to be re-examined and why they're telling us 10,000
You see what I mean can't be trusted and that which is the antithesis of what their purpose is because the purpose of these guys
Is people could go about whatever interest they have in life and when they want to know about the Sun they go to a trusted
Source these scientists and I'm telling you they can't be trusted.
So Everyone's on their own.
That's why I'm saying again.
That's wide open Mm-hmm.
I don't think that particular aspect is a mainstream thing.
That's more of an alternative stream of conversation Not that that's necessarily any more legitimate.
But yeah, I'm just throwing that out there.
What's the relationship between cosmic rays and cloud cover?
They have some kind of a relationship do they not where when one picks up the other decreases and vice versa space weather and There's a boundary layer.
It's kind of like saying, you know, you have a motel or a hotel with one room next to the other What's the relationship?
Well, you know if somebody knocks on the wall on one side, they're gonna hear it on the other
Even though the one knocking is in the other room
Of course, there's a really they can't even define cosmic rays and all that activity, but there is weather in space and
We're in it
Think of it as the the nature of the oceans and a ship
How it's affected by the what the ocean or the sea is doing and that's what we're the planet is in that condition
Or a relative state, you know what was going on and what they call space which is not really empty space
Is affecting the boundary layer known as the atmosphere, you know, which is cloud cover and all that
Mm-hmm
Okay, so anomalies
It's all anomalies.
It's it's been gradually the thing about prophecy.
It's progressive and It takes you know, some prophecies take a long time to build up, you know with these end time scenarios I start seeing the pre what he called a precursor to them now So they seem more gradual.
It's the frog in the in the pot to slowly Yeah And then clouds are misunderstood also, there's no information on what clouds are on the internet by the way What they really are there's no moisture there's no water there's might be some moisture but there's no water in the clouds, you know Because if there was they wouldn't float they'd be pulled down to the ground Now fog is is water.
That's why it guess what when you see fog, you don't see it up in the sky You see it where it descends down into the valleys.
It's actually pulled down by gravity Pushed down by gravity So when you talk about if you want to bring up clouds, I think I have discussed what clouds are in the past so And it's not there's nothing written.
You want it?
Here's the thing.
We can just write a thing about what clouds are
And put that out that that's a thousand times more than what's out there right now and provable as well
You know people the they have this grotesque
View that clouds bring rain
I
Mean bring the rain they do bring rain the conditions for rain, but they don't bring any water
you know a square kilometer with a
Centimeter of rain is a million tons of water.
There's you times on there's a million tons of water in that cloud there's no water in the cloud and They say well the humidity then accumulates around dust particles Well, if that would happen you'd have transfer of energy.
So that means when it rains the humidity should go down
Right
Because it turns into water
But the humidity actually rises
Incrementally as as the it gets to the rain event and when it's raining the humidity goes up even more
So anyway, I've discussed what what's going it's it's if that's why I have if
I've said this a while back
Maybe not as frequent as I should have or could have if you were completely awake and aware of what's going on
You would be you would be considered a total madman in comparison to anyone
So
Hmm.
Yeah, I bet you've heard the the Greek speak on you know, right before it rains if you know, it's surely going to rain go
stand underneath
Something and watch the whole process
From the clouds rolling into the rain starting and all that watch the bottom of the cloud
Watch how the rain is actually formed if you have some good polarized lenses or glass
You can see it more evidently what's going on how the rain is created
It's it's quite, you know, you know as I go a Greek I've done it.
I don't know I said well, okay watch for this watch for like a small short list of stuff Then they come back to yep.
Everything was exactly like you said You have to kind of help people out, you know like people with weather So when you go out and see a clear blue sky, do you see the 14 shades of blue?
And they're like no, I just see it's blue Right, most people can see the three or four shades immediately All right Once you point them out, right?
And these are not we're not talking about like super subtle Things where you know, you pick up the violin and start playing with no lessons.
I'm talking about this is technically accessible to anyone You see what I mean?
Right.
I mean, yeah so No, I get it.
I Think my roommates just came back Yeah, I might have to check out because I can't make noise when they're around hello Yeah, no, we're here.
Oh I just think I'm just clanking it around here.
Yeah I think I'll call it a day because people just came back.
All right, call it a day.
Call it a night.
Whatever.
Thanks Maybe we'll do it again Yeah, be prepared for you.
No, you know, you've been around long enough, you know, I'm gonna rant and rave for 20 minutes
So anyway 20 minutes 20 minutes is fine when it gets to 50 is when I'm like, oh shit, yeah
Yeah, that's like someone wants this guy was an author an English major and all that I said
I'll just go read he was interested in reading the Bible
Would you recommend so start with the book of Jeremiah gets back to me says this guy's a real whiner
I read the whole chapter is whining like I you don't get it.
Never mind Anyway, you get it But No, no, no, no, no, no because there's not a one-to-one ratio of conflation between these things as if you're saying something profound You're saying shit Everything that you're saying is you understood and grasped and it's fairly but my who Well, certainly by me.
I don't know.
I'm gonna send you a multiple-choice question and answer test I'm gonna Skype with you I'm gonna write one up and then I'm gonna share the the the results with the rest of the class Well, let's see how much you actually get but I doubt you'll actually send it because you say you'll do stuff and you never do It anyway, so that's fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, not no regarding this kind of stuff.
No, I'm not working for free Mm-hmm.
I mean, I'm not that smart, but I'm not that stupid Right.
Sure Whatever it takes to preserve the integrity of the Greek online There is no such thing It's like walking through the sewer or landfill.
It's like oh, yeah, I don't leave any more.
Don't leave any more poops here Well, who's gonna notice the place is full of poop?
Anyway, okay.
Cool.
Well, thanks Sam.
Well, maybe we'll do it again.
Yep Okay All right Yeah, so the main point I guess for my rant and all that coming on is Whatever you're coming across anything any information Be rest assured that it's quiet.
It's it's completely open
Any field that you get into is wide open and if you don't see it, it's
partly because of whatever mental model you bought into or allowed yourself to
solidify around you regarding that thought right so
Yeah, like if you want again eventually interest in the human body you say oh, well
There's not much more research to be done on that
Look at all these universities and all these medical centers and all these government agencies and I'm telling you they don't know jack shit
Comparatively to the effort and the resources that they have they should be ashamed of themselves shameful shameful
completely any field aeronautics aerospace medicine
acoustics electricity shameful
shameful
You know the that what's that CERN that big thing they have wherever it is in Europe now
If they took all the copper they used in that or whatever.
They could have built enough Joseph Newman machines to run Half of Europe, you know for free right usually yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah shameful
They are all across the board automobiles any field, you know, you know, so and there's no one by the way again
There's no one on the internet talking about anything useful
And it might see even if you think it seems like it in the beginning, you know, you go to some alternative
Speakers where they start bringing up the importance of bringing down your blood pressure
I'm like, oh boy, you know how many times you heard that right or the immune system?
Yeah, you know, it's like there's nothing I think I put in chat the the the Internet is hosted by either morons idiots or assholes Take your pick.
So you're pretty much
It's the same thing as the
As what the culture can provide, you know, in other words, I would stress that one
Learns to relate to what has been set in culture before what is provided within that culture
you see like in other words if you're living in the Western world and
You're using the English language and you go on the Internet
Whether it's alternative or mainstream or commercial or corporate or where it's all this I'm telling you
It doesn't matter because they're all coming from the same cultural perspective
Which is who's going to get the most shrunken heads you see?
Yeah, how many times have you gone on to the alternative radio Bruce?
it doesn't matter what the subject matter is whether it's Fox News or Any the most fringe alternative when Christmas comes around?
What do they all say?
Merry Christmas?
Yeah, when when there's Yeah, when there's the Pope's work schedule when there's a when the when the agency's put out You know the medical scares about these outbreaks whether it's Fox News, you know, it's a swine flu whether it's the Fox News or the most fringe alternative radio what they're all concerned about the same bullshit, right?
Yeah, why because commercial in between so that they can garnish their money income and sure For money, it's a little hole.
Remember the hole in the walls.
Oh Depends on what's wrong Restaurants.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yeah Downtown New York, they had the glory hole politicians could go right there Genitalia through in the meat district.
But anyway, yeah, what right?
Talking like small business or a tiny little building in between mom-and-pop shop Yeah, yeah, and that's what you got on the internet right now.
It's just a bunch of little hole-in-the-wall.
Oh, yeah, that's come on Yeah, there's nothing.
Yep, and they're all the same Regardless if it's the big corporate mainstream Internet or the smallest Mom-and-pop hole in the wall.
They're all interested in shrunken heads.
Yep, because they're that's their culture.
They they yeah, so that's a real Like Sam was saying earlier, you know, he senses an urgency maybe, you know, why don't you do something?
We got to do something I don't see anything going on.
I think that's hardly a and that's the thing I was trying to I was trying to wrap my head around but you have Yeah, I have 160 some hours Which might be too much.
I think a little overdone overdone.
Okay, how much of its repeat?
Okay fine
But half of it, yeah, and it's done in fantasy it's articulated different
Sure, it's like looking at a natural might not capture the attention as well as the next one, you know
It's it's subject to the person their understanding
what first
Attracted me was the history
Straight up so, you know where things come from, you know, right and
Then I started putting two and two together and his whole leash, you know
Yeah.
Oh Yeah, it's from that point on it's it's been you know, I got to find I you know I'll I'll go on little tangents looking up different things in history, but I it's it's all different than what I was given every bit of it Mm-hmm.
Well, how can you know anything about a thing if you don't know where it came from?
What how long it's been around The understand first thing about understanding anything is the history of the thing That's why one of the most important things I go out and say is that anything and everything people are interacting with right now?
It's hard to find that anything goes back more than a hundred years Yeah, it's like they've negated everything Prior to that and I'm telling you that around that time more than a hundred year years ago Anything that could have been known was known They talked about it it was continuous, yep, it was Better.
Yeah The next city was talking about it Yeah, you know anything that was the growth of our generations.
None of us passed on none of us talked about Let's go have a beer grab a brat or you know, whatever, you know Mm-hmm This new song this new TV program this new radio show In total distractions to take your mind off.
Well, is it between each other?
But it's not so much of a distraction as it's food clothing and shelter You're you're here because of the gods number one number two You're here because of the gods and number three you're here because of the gods and why are you here because of the gods?
Because a certain amount of people have to come through a certain amount of time So why are you gonna fuss and muss about all the stuff that's going on?
Just have a good time Like I said lately I've been trying to Entertain the concept of watching TV again because I noticed I'll turn it on and sit in front of it And I'll see how stupid it is and I'll say to myself This is this is how you know, it has a technical effect on the brain on the cerebellum and other parts, right?
too and the medulla to Affect you through the freaky flicker rates and things like that.
Relax like you said with the new and improved stuff.
It's you know, you got Four or five times as much Easily.
Yeah, and I'll sit back and I thought for just a second when you said technical.
I thought you're gonna go to the
you know what the
adversary uses as a tool because you know clearly there's
The distractions alone are just you know, look at all its tamed
multiples of generations
the different technologies, you know
What he's using as a tool or the purpose one of the purposes seemingly it's it's indirectly
Scriptural is to show how inadequate mankind is is you know, and it's all voluntary by the way
No one's putting a gun to anyone's head right spiritually to do anything now people
Spiritually if you got enough people to do something they will put guns on other people to do it also, right?
Sure, but he's not doing it, you know later on I had a conversation with someone recently
he was an English teacher and he
we just sat outside for an hour in the shade talking and
He was a quote-unquote Christian or you know was a proponent of it and I'm so I'm not for it or against it
I just find it to be you know, not a good thing
If I could be easily against it if you look at how much harm it's done
But at the same time if you see what the purpose of it is as a dummy load
That's you know, then you can't be for it or against it but I was having a conversation
With an English teacher who supposedly is an English teacher.
So, you know, he's he's a wordsmith.
You're alleging, you know, and They didn't have comprehension of you know what the words mean not only even in the English together when you string it together or The importance of reading it all in context versus verse out of verse You know how the crit, you know how they use just verses to build a piece Versus together to create a new doctrine.
That's not really there right and he thanked me.
He was like, well, you know This is interesting.
I never thought of reading the whole thing in context and this is someone who's was an English teacher who Grades people on writing essays that they have an introduction body and conclusion and context supported, right?
Oh, this is their job.
You think about it how how?
Ridiculous Anyway, yeah Yeah, that's why I keep saying to the people you're screwed because the ones that you're going to for knowledge and training are screwed Or miss, you know, don't know anything or they seem like they know but they don't Qualitatively Quantitatively, they have a lot to say but the quality is very low So essentially again back to the adversary and us being here.
It's just a matter of taking time So let's go have a beer or Brad or you know, or watch TV or whatever, you know Ultimately scripture tells you the rich man and the poor man both die naked.
You can't take it with you
I never saw never saw Brink's armored truck follow anyone behind
Not a one, right
Or whatever
Yeah, they don't pour the money in the coffin
And again, like I think on the last sonic event the reward that will be gotten later by everyone by the way
even the malfeasant ones
Will be greater greater to the point where not only will it compensate whether you know or didn't know what was going on
But it'll overly compensate you see so it is in the end.
It'll be worth it, but not this end Because if you want to go even further, this is not the end that's coming.
It's the beginning You know is when a when a child is born when it exits the mother Is that the end or is it the beginning?
We never see it as the end We it's the end of the pregnancy, but we see it as the beginning, right?
Mm-hmm.
No, no when a baby is born people don't run around saying it was the end.
It's the end.
It's the end Well, it is the end right the end of the pregnancy, but you don't focus on that you focus It's the beginning you have a new baby with a new right?
It's the beginning right you see Congratulations you see mm-hmm.
So what's coming is really the beginning anyway?
And the thing is I don't want to you know
There's so much optimism and I deliberately hold myself back because I don't want to sound preachy
Right, but those who you see if you have all the background
I'll say it and then it doesn't sound preachy because now you understand you see it
But if you don't understand the message in Scripture and not aware of what's going on here, then you sound preachy
You're not going to do the the homework that's necessary to understand why it's going to be so wonderful
You're just going to go for it and fall for the yeah
If you want to feel good stuff, there's plenty of stuff to make you feel good.
Oh, yeah Yeah, and stay stupid or ignorant or whatever So stupid is as being negligent and Negligence basically ignorant.
It means you just don't have it.
You know, it's an empty bucket, you know, yeah, so stupid would be pouring a
gallon into a one-quart bucket
Ignorant would be you don't know, you know, what size bucket to get which is I think the latter is better, you know
Yeah, and wasting so either way
Yeah, but I think Sam most Sam knows and private we say there's nothing out there at all and he's
Followed looked at various things and yes there there is if you're interested in
Finding edible corn in poop the yield you can do that
But we what if it comes to the point where you just want fresh corn right now, what do you right?
And let's just not even use the poop analogy just use you don't want can a corn out of a can Right, you know, you know Do you want fresh corn?
Where are you gonna go?
I'm telling you there's nowhere to go And it's it's sad and you know It's qualitative not quantitative because I haven't gone through every page on the Internet.
I don't need to Yeah Yeah Yeah, and the thing is like just to address the thing with Sam I'm not gonna create an endeavor You know like for example, Bruce you you you work, right?
You you know to get credits and support yourself and do those other stuff in order to do what Sam was talking about It's it's actually quite an endeavor.
It's basically is a lot of work.
Yeah, I'm not going to The idea on the website about the one where you want it where anybody could come on and place their thoughts about a gadget or whatever You know That's not an easy task Well, you know Domain right the page you still got to get it visible to The masses we need moderators, right then you're gonna have the the corporate assassins.
They don't want to take it down Oh, yeah, because it's a good mother Because you know, there's gonna be an interest that does not like to see that Right and a coming for you.
Oh
There well, yeah, cuz it's gonna mess up there, you know
I'd say you hit them in there what they consider to be a pocketbook, which is just digital now good starting place
Yeah, I mean
Yeah, I mean I could spend the rest of the next three days just coming up with various semi
Synthetic and semi organic and organic compounds the nail that you know
So the pharmaceutical people can't do anything for patent anything for the next 10 years.
What do you think that's worth?
That's worth taking you out quickly, isn't it?
So that's that's a given.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm You know once you put that kind of but it needs to be done It needs to be done.
Why should it has to you know, you almost have to be a hundred percent anonymous to it Mm-hmm And very clever you have to know you're networking and a lot of good stuff and Sure.
I mean there's there's tons of stuff to do But I think that Like Sam was saying to build something up well You know when you're gonna start a business or an endeavor you think about how long do you have to do it for?
It's not like being a roadie, you know when you're it's easy when you're a roadie
Let's say you're gonna go on tour with a band, you know, you've got five
Nights and you've got ten shows or whatever and you give it your all, you know
You work 20 hours a day sure because you know, you're you and that's it, you know, or you might work, you know
It's not practical to work more than 20 hours a day
You need three four hours sleep like in the military even infantrymen, but I would say that
You know, it's finite
And and that's how it has to be viewed in a sense because this is finite
This is and and also you have to understand that most of the stuff is not for this society
So they got that working against you, right?
Yeah, right.
It's not you know, so It's for the next society.
So, you know, and then of course, are you casting pearls to swine?
Yes, you are
Yeah, so, you know, so the best thing is just chill
It's it's um, have you ever met anyone, you know is rhetorical that has a bona fide treasure map and
Actually, you say too much
but let me just say this sure a
bona fide treasured map and but it happens to be that the treasure map is old enough that that where the treasure is now happens
to be State Park land because you know since the 18 late
1800s 1930s and in the 70s started turning a lot of this public lands into state parks
So you can't quite you can't quite show up with backhoes and start digging can you no you can't
All right.
So what do you do with that?
Well, you know, the gold is there And but you know, you can't quite You still can do it.
You still all you got to do is get enough people insiders, you know You know just get hired by the Parks Department and pay off some people you get it done, of course Without letting the CIA and other people know because they'll come and steal it from you Once it's validated that it's there Right.
So what do you do with that?
I mean, don't you feel kind of wealthy knowing that it's there even though you haven't you can't really quite spend it Yet, but you know, it's there you got it.
You don't have the concerns that other people do Well, what if I only had was a fiddler on the roof?
What if I was a rich man?
You know that song if I was a rich man, right?
No, you don't you don't sing that song But you don't have it you see so that's another perspective.
Mm-hmm
Sometimes it's just better off to leave it be
Yeah, leave it be but it doesn't mean you don't have to say it and ultimately before we go
I I know for sure
validatable and confirmed
Through firsthand and through digital, you know emails and messages
the Greek speak has helped quite a few people with health and food and other things practical knowledge and
Yeah, I've gotten enough
That you know
Some people said, you know, you've heard in artistic circles if I can just help one person that would be it worth doing right, right?
So I know it's helped quite a few And that in itself is quite a reward oh Yeah.
Oh, yeah but either way, it's it's The stuff that people have in their minds is insurmountable if a bunch of sponge divers can take down an aircraft carrier Right, I mean Doesn't that tell you that anything is possible?
You know mark Yeah, so I mean One oh, yeah, and of course, you know that was never publicized, you know, oh god, no No, that's a David and Goliath.
I mean, it's more than it's more humiliating than David It's actually far more Yeah Anyway, yeah Yeah, so Maybe we'll do we'll just it's it's coming on site.
What's middle of summer almost?
Yeah.
Yeah, well summer and Sure you're on Yeah, well the fall pay attention to this time.
Well, of course always pay attention, but
This year spring middle of summer and then fall
Winter, of course, there's a lot of international movement and then you have one in other words
Let's just put it this way the seasonal effects of spring building up summer growth fall breaking down period winter transitional
Is going to be even more important now as time
goes on
Especially when you if you start to understand prophecy or the narrow the biblical narrative you're going to see the majority of these things
or the turn of events
Dynamically happening in the spring and in the fall
right, so
That's why when you look at even scripture historically
You have more events happening in the first second third month and then in the seven eighth ninth months, right?
If you you can just do a biblical a search on the computer Put in first month, you know, what do you get second month?
What do you get third month and then skip go to the seventh month eighth month ninth month.
You'll see so much activity Mm-hmm, right again And that's where I got it from.
By the way, this spring is planting building summer and tear down fall.
So
so you'll see
I
Noticed those events and like well, yeah, and this spring was kind of quite of a bang, you know when spring ended you notice
So change of events that will pull geopolitical and in your own lives, you know, I tell people if you're gonna start a business
Get all your stuff together, you know
If you're gonna make your decisions get all your stuff together by summer
So you have it all organized by fall you winter you design everything and you and you ready to go into business when?
Opening in the spring spring your campaign starts in the spring.
You can't just you're gonna open a business You just don't you know, it takes time.
So you You know by get the decision made by summer You know, whatever you're gonna invest in the business have it ready by fall right the harvest winter you get at the space Get your signs made get all your employees in order get the the space built up by the end of winter So when springtime comes you have your grand opening you see how it works.
It's a matter That's what I mean by the seasonal thing.
It's not as you know, you don't get everything done within the season it you know, but you use the seasons to create the rhythm that gets you to the The purpose that you want, you know, if you want to break close a business Let it run through summer and you should close it down and liquidate when in the fall, right?
If you want to it's springtime you say oh where you should go out of business You know what?
Hang on to summer and then just liquidate it in the fall because that's more in accord with the natural cycle of things And you'll probably get more for it then You know So hmm very simple.
It makes sense.
Yes.
Yeah Yeah, it's it's simple and you know I think well, maybe what Sam was trying to say is give them even more about it when you write a paper You just don't say well spring is planting summer build-up fall is breaking down and winter is transitional.
That's not much of a paper
That's only 30 words
you might want to give examples and historical and references and
Engineering of it, you know
So, yeah from that point of view Sam is correct, I've never really gone into depth on that, you know on many things
there's no reason to I
Don't see any reason to or when there's a in terms of private consulting and industry if I asked to a master work on a project
Very often I see the organization that I might be dealing with and I'm like, oh
There's so much these people need but I better leave my nose out of it and just address what they want me to address
You know what?
I mean, right?
Because no good deed goes unpunished.
You know what I mean?
So great Mm-hmm Yeah, okay.
Well, you're not gonna really sit back and try to Fix all the other things.
Oh, no.
No.
Oh, no, and you know when they want to send you something during Christmas You're like well I'll read I'll take it only if it's a Tribute as tribute and when they say oh, yeah.
Sure.
Well great now It has now you transmuted it from a Christmas gift to tribute right, and if you don't know what tribute is look up what it means, it's Yeah So I'll take it as true as a random tribute, but not as a Christmas gift.
Okay.
It's tribute then I'm like, all right, cool.
I'll take it right you see this you can transmute things that way, right?
All right, because you know in the corporate culture they do that around this holidays they want oh, yes, they do that's how yeah I can't receive it unless it's fabulous, wasn't it?
Well skeptic is the god of health it's an Egyptian Greek hybrid
The Greeks had other gods as well
And the Egyptians had other gods and they came together and formed a split the occult of a sclepolis
escapolis, which is the the cult of
Of
Health it's the god of good health and well-being
Right Christian the the JES US character the bust with the nimbus and all that what you see is usually
that image
That's why the Christians say God bless you right right there is there's no God bless you or
Anything like that in Scripture at all.
That's from that, you know, like when you sneeze Didn't the Christmas bonus came out of that too, wasn't it?
hmm That Christmas is a is a mesh.
Yeah, it could be it could be as well Yeah, but Christmas is a really strange thing because it's a strange.
It's an invention that the Romans finalized later on Based on the calendrical system, but it's a mishmash of you know, the the dark days of Babylonian magic Yeah, I high black magic mixed with Mithras mixed with Yeah, who's the one that the The women were wearing black crying for ball Tamu's Okay It's mixture of all kinds of it's a hybrid.
It's a synchronistic hybrid worship of ball of the grove the tree worship Yeah, it's it's really it's just like when you go in the sewer You know what floats by Yeah shapes and size and things you can meet people through leftovers down the drain, you know that You know what?
I mean?
It's not just poop.
Yeah, it's urine feces and other waste in general all put together and formed into The high holidays of the Western culture and you know, Eastern don't the Easterns are not scot-free That's why very often.
I say the a lot of these East White people that go to Buddhism and Hinduism.
They're just reek of Jewish Christian rejects You know what I mean, they don't know anything How can they know anything if the high gurus the Dalai Lama doesn't even know anything?
Provable by the way, he's an idiot.
How do I prove that very simply is by Reading all the stuff that he all of his quotes and stuff that he's written and put out none of it has anything to do with the Basis or the scripture that his religion is based on none of it.
He's a complete completely devoid
So if the very highest
Almost sainted leaders of these people know nothing about their own writs
What is the possibility of the lower adherence knowing anything notice I said adherence
because there are those that want to go into Buddhism and you know in the beginning they're naive enough to go along with everyone and
They're like wait a second
There's something here that doesn't ring right or this says that you know
The censorship is lifted and they go and study
Some of the scripture and they're like wait a second
These people are doing the opposite of what it says in scripture or they're devoid of rice in it
This is with every religion, this is doesn't matter what it is even Scientology, which is a total mind
You know what?
psychology And manipulation And black magic on the inner circles those people too They'll say if you you know ask people what it's about.
It's not at the core of what they teach So any any group?
You know and the ones that leave it ain't pretty
You know
Yeah, but this is early Christianity was was like that
It was started with Simon Agus and the Gnostics that that got heavy investors
Because they saw it even moved in one name when they quote-unquote discovered America
Oh
The Jesuits followed the one they just well, you know under the what discovery is a legal term
When you bring something to trial
It's used as as evidence to why you're prosecuting something
So the process you can call it the prosecution of the Northern Americas here
Yeah, which one was done by the Explorers to claim it under you know, the the Vatican
Let's say not directly, but the adherents, you know
the kings and queens and Dominions that were
Because the Europe was run by the Emperor and the Vatican together in parallel
You had the Emperor's and the last Emperor was 1790 something Edward in Holland
And he also had yeah
Yeah, people don't they talk about the Popes, but they don't talk about the Emperor's so
Yeah, but they ran it together, you know, it's kind of it's like in Congress you have the Senate and the in the
Whatever the House of Representatives or whatever, you know, you have the two houses
You had the two houses running Europe the Emperor and the Pope.
Yeah
So yeah, it's yeah, it's not as neat as people you ask most people, you know anything even the pretty even
University professors I recently spoke to someone who's college major and
History and had never studied for four years history world history and American history and just general history and he had never
Heard the Parthian Empire being mentioned
So, I mean go figure
Mm-hmm
That's why I think the last time we did a sonic I try to bring up the example of reading the MIT nuclear physics curriculum
actually
If you read through it great
It's kind of ridiculous
Yeah, it's basically just a bunch of hokey-pokey stuff that's why
Yeah, there's no progress in the world
And why should there be?
All right, anything else or we'll just wrap it up.
We can we we certainly can wrap it up We we certainly threw away some time on that.
Well
Very well done
Okay, well contrary I think what Sam was bringing up I think these these are semi-productive if
I would if other you know from feedback that I get from others and I would say so myself
Simply because what's being said here is not being said anywhere else
No, so then it's not just not just saying it and and it's not just saying it because not being said anywhere else
It's just saying it because it needs to be said right so
It's a provable point most of the stuff.
Oh Yeah, yeah Yeah Okay, okay Bruce, well, thanks up and we'll do you have yourself a good night sir.
Yep.
Okay.
Bye