Yeah, true.
And there was Solomon.
Solomon obviously wrote a whole lot of stuff that is gone.
And, you know, he's interesting because he had a world empire also, kind of like Nebuchadnezzar, that you can't really find any record of it as if it wasn't there.
So you would even imagine that other cultures would have written about him because he was a pretty well known figure.
Other stuff, sparse albeit, found his house of David, or, you know, that's been found.
And which one?
You know what I mean?
Because it was quite unusual for the Israelites to be known through their king.
They were always known as a people.
Solomon would have been an exception because he was a world king.
He's the only world king that they had.
Yeah, right, right.
So the question here is, I think there are things that have been found with his name on them, indirectly.
And they're just questioning his name, you know, meaning in another language, right?
So, because, you know, how Shlomo, Shalom, Shalom, right?
Because it's not Solomon and you wouldn't find it.
It wouldn't be something to be Shlomon, right?
It would look great, like Shalom.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
I think also there's some records of Josephus scouring libraries and sort of complaining that he couldn't find this stuff on, you know, Judah's history or Israel's history beyond a certain point.
Well, Josephus, let me just interject real short about Josephus.
No stain on him, but he was a turncoat.
You know what I mean by a turncoat, right?
So now he couldn't go – once he got the posture that he is known for today, there was a lot of people in the community that he came from that turned, you know, away from him, right?
So he forfeited access to much.
So basically when he did achieve the position that he is known for, he basically had to perform everything that he did with what was in between his ears and in his heart.
That might be a little extreme, but that's why I said he's a turncoat.
And this is all from what I can glean from it, but Josephus to me, not only because he's common – and I like to look at things that are not common – but because he's so common, I think it's been diluted and even more investigation into that could be done.
Another thing, I mean, you know how Greek philosophy is common?
Well, how many people are saying that they actually translated it from ancient Greek to English properly?
Nobody.
They take it for granted that they know what it says.
Well, what a novel idea.
I'm telling you they didn't translate it properly.
Not completely, but a good amount of it, you know, when you read Greek philosophy.
So, I mean, hey, doesn't that sound like scripture?
Yeah.
Yeah, kind of, yeah.
So what do you got?
You know, you got this bad – that's why I keep saying Greek philosophy was so good.
How well has it served your society?
It's shit.
Because maybe you didn't quite get it.
You just told your – so a lot of people say this is, you know, this person's this, this person knows scripture.
No, no, no.
There's a big difference between knowing scripture and having the appearance of knowing scripture.
You know, speaking with people in the alternative media and others, they're like, oh, I don't know what to say.
I don't know how to do blah, blah, blah about a certain subject or a host or a guest or whatever.
And I'm like, listen, you don't have to really know what you're saying.
It's just a one-hour show.
No one cares anyway.
You're going to do something else.
You're not here to be didactic in any way.
You just have to – I'm breaking up.
Okay.
I just tell them you just have to – how about now?
I got a good copy on your Greek.
Okay.
I suggest to people that do public work and they're not serious about – you know, they're just doing what they call a show.
I'm like you just have to sound like you know what you're talking about, and the people are happy with that.
Because the moment you start – if you know about something, the truth of the matter, and you start to structurally develop it and impart it publicly, you're going to lose most of the audience, not everyone.
So you have the majority of what people interact with thinking is a knowledge base in any field is the appearance of that.
Yes, but it sucks to be the masses I guess.
I never like to think in those terms, but there's clearly a mass population of people that are in that category.
You can't really do anything about it.
Well, the information base that someone goes into is custom-tailored to accommodate that mindset anyway.
I mean, in other words, as the times change, the academia changes also.
See what I mean?
Very simple.
Just pick up an eighth grade final exam from 120 years ago, 1890.
Yeah, eighth grade.
There's probably no one in any of the professorship in universities that would pass that test today.
Well, what's changed?
The people dumber?
Well, yeah, as they're getting dumber, the entitlement around them accommodates them, and then they become dumber also, or more removed.
And that's fine, because if you read about the summation or the termination of man's society or man's rule on earth, it's not a pretty picture, is it?
Well, to sort of conclude on this Babylonian thing…
Now, Bruce, Sam is breaking up for me.
Sam, you got it.
I think it's intermittent.
I can't really control it.
Am I still breaking up?
No, it's intermittent.
It's fine.
It's better.
Let me know if it comes back.
What else on Nebuchadnezzar are the Babylonian stuff?
Well, no, we can wrap it up.
I was just going to say that it's kind of important to pay attention to the short things, because even if you look at – especially for me in the Old Testament, though not exclusively in the book of Job, because most people overlook it, and I kind of think it's like the book of Revelation for the Old Testament, because other than the first few chapters and the last chapter…
But you can pick up on little things showing that they had a knowledge…
lost me still?
I got you.
They had a knowledge base.
All right, so you bring up the significance of the book of Job and…
Yeah, like there's a little spot in Job 38 where it mentions that the waters are hid as a stone in the face of the deepest frozen in Job 38.
Right, so if you take that literally, it's kind of clear that he was acquainted with the Arctic regions and the fact that there are certain places where the entire ocean is frozen.
Right.
You can pick up on those types of little things.
Or it could be a confluence, it could be a freshwater body that'll do that more readily than a saltwater body, right?
Yeah.
But I think he's talking about the ocean, though, because the face of the deep, the deep is usually the abyss which is connected to the oceans.
Sure, and you know the ocean in scripture is typically the Mediterranean, right?
Yes, typically.
Or the Caspian or the Black Sea, you know, or surrounding bodies.
It could be south of the, you know, the Sea of Reeds to the Red Sea.
You know, just fan out, just, you know, just do a radius around that entire area of a thousand plus miles.
You have a body of water in each cardinal almost, east, west, south, north, right, don't you, pretty much?
If you've ever been to a large lake, it looks pretty small on a map, but it looks like the sea.
You ever been to the Great Lakes or a lake, you know, a lake that's, you know, looks like a round, you know, circular format, not something in a valley.
We have something called Lake Havasu near here.
It's pretty big, but you can tell it's just a, you know, a valley that's been filled up.
But if you look at various seas on the maps that you see there, they, if you're standing on the shore, you don't think it's disproportionate to how you perceive it on the map.
It just looks as vast as any ocean, you know, especially when it's freshwater.
It's even more impressive.
All right.
That about does it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Now, your In-N-Out, I think, is your device, by the way, because it's almost doing it at 50 cycle or 60 cycle.
I can see the Skype as your avatar.
Yeah, it's your audio.
I can tell you it's something to do with connection to your audio, whether it's the card or your device.
You're probably using the speakers and the microphone built in.
But if you want to do a reboot or if it's a laptop, make sure you're getting a lot of air under it, right, because when they heat up, they break down, you know, the connection.
Resistance goes up.
It changes the value of the circuit, right?
Well, let's see.
When you heat up, resistance goes up, right?
Yeah.
So if you have a circuit with capacitors and coils and other things and you change the resistive value.
Yep, that's right.
It depends, yeah, what the circuit is.
And an audio circuit, I know for sure, I'll tell you, if you heat that puppy up, I know that card has got at least half a dozen resistors on it.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I might just call it a day for me because I'm starting to get a little bit tired.
Yeah, and the connection thing is not going to improve, don't mind.
Next time I might just call from a different device.
Oh, a pay phone, remember those?
Anyway.
No, actually, you're fine.
Yeah, right now it's fine.
I think it's his audio device gating.
Yeah, yeah.
It's gating the background, and it doesn't know when to release, and it's gating out his voice.
But what else did you want to, if you were to continue, anything else you just want to …
Well, I did put together a thing on Old Testament history in general that I kind of wanted to run.
I was going to do it like in a private conversation just to run by to see whether it looks good.
We can do it here if you want, if you're up for it.
Well, it depends.
That's one hell of a brush stroke.
But go ahead, yeah.
Old Testament history, I mean, what else can we go through other than the narrative of the Old Testament, which is basically lineages and certain events, and most of the events is going to be in the latter part anyway.
Well, there are things that we can read out of the text.
Obviously, we all know the stuff itself.
We're not going to look at them.
Let me give you an example just for the listenership.
If you talk up to the Flood and even after the Flood, you've covered almost 2,000 years with just not much to talk about, right, unless you want to get into the lineages.
And then after that, you can go another 1,000 years, and then it gets really busy, right?
You see what I mean?
Because there's 4,000 years in the Old Testament.
Would you say that's appropriate?
Yeah, that's about it.
Okay.
That could be done as quickly or as lengthily as one wants to, but it's very poignant and dynamic in the beginning, and it gets near before the end of it, three-quarters of the way down, it gets really, really busy.
And then towards the end of it, it just seems to just shut down.
Okay, there's the proverbial hit the fan.
I believe so.
Yeah, he just lost juice, and he knew it was happening.
Yeah, you can just see him going, oh.
You want to take a break, do some music, or you want to just call it?
Yeah, we'll do some music.
Sure, and that'll give us a little pause.
Yeah, I'll go into the office and check out the chat and whatever, and we'll see if he comes back.
Okay, thanks.
Okay, sounds good.
I know you're a smart boy.
Old Testament.
We're streaming again, right, Bruce?
Yep, you're up.
Oh, sorry.
Cool.
Yeah, you're up.
Okay, so the Old Testament was canonized by Ezra in the 5th century B.C. to a large extent, when he had the Judeans in front of him who had just come out of the Babylonian captivity.
Many of them didn't know Hebrew anymore, presumably, and he would have had to give them a sense of what the earlier stuff meant, because they wouldn't have known it very well.
Right, but before you continue, I just want to interject.
You not only did that logistic compilation, but there was an aesthetic also that changed.
The script changed, right?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Not to reopen the discussion of where scripture comes from, because we know it comes from the gods, but these things do have physical outworkings.
So accordingly, I've heard that Ezra wrote some of those books for himself.
For example, Malachi, obviously Ezra, and Nehemiah, because they're one book.
I've also heard that he wrote Chronicles, though, which was one long book, which would make sense, because why would they write Chronicles in the time of the kings, when the stuff was happening when they already had the kings?
It would have come later as a compilation effort.
Right.
They would have had a team of scribes, and it would have been contemporary, and it wouldn't have been called a Chronicle.
It would have been just called the condition of the country at the time.
Mm-hmm.
I've also said in the past, in private conversations, I think it's kind of clear that there's an editorial hand and changes to the text and stuff, like with the Psalms, obviously, we read in Psalm 72, this concludes the prayers of David, son of Jesse.
Well, how can it say that?
And then there's 78 more Psalms.
So that doesn't make sense.
And even in the Septuagint, there's Psalm 151.
Look, a prayer is one thing, and a Psalm is another.
A song is not a prayer, and a prayer is not a song.
It doesn't have to be.
But go ahead.
But there are more prayers after Psalm 78.
Sure.
But isn't there, aren't there, how many authors are of the Psalms?
I think four, five?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, and we presume that when we don't have a specific detail on an author, we presume it's David, right?
I think there are Davidic Psalms after 78.
Okay, that's all I have to say.
Yeah.
But some people actually are walking around thinking that all the Psalms are David, so I just want to throw that in there.
And they're not.
Yeah, so at the end of that stuff, David legitimizes the texts, but you can sort of see these things quite clearly.
So from what I'm seeing, there's sort of seven distinct periods of time that the Old Testament talks about as being different from one another prior to the 5th century B.C. And post-flood, you have the patriarchal period from Noah to Joseph.
That's like 600 years.
The Egyptian period, Joseph to Moses, is like 200 years.
The Judge's period is like 400 years.
David and Solomon is like 80.
Then the divided kingdom until Jeremiah is about 400.
And then the Babylonian captivity is like 70, up until Jerusalem is destroyed.
And then you have the post-exilic period from Cyrus to Ezra.
Cyrus' decree to Ezra.
Right, and then you have the Hasmonean period and the Maccabees.
Yeah, after that.
So looking at the 600-year period of Abraham, this is kind of interesting.
You don't really have to study that much to see what kind of civilizations existed at that time.
But I've never heard anybody really bring it up, whether it's a scholar or obviously the Christian pastors don't know much.
But after the dispersion of the races at the Tower of Babel, the remaining people in the Middle East had very small and limited populations to develop their city-state societies.
For example, during Abraham's time, when you had these four nations or these four kings that came together to conquer the cities of the plains in Jordan in the War of the Kings, Abraham on his own was able to fight four of them with just 318 people and subdue them.
So these so-called nations were only small families of people.
They weren't these nations of millions.
They were just a few hundred people that comprised an entire nation.
Right.
It's kind of like if you go into places in Chicago or years ago northern Manhattan, the neighborhoods were divided and they had their leaders.
In other words, there's so much centralization that's been going on for the past 2,000 years that this mindset is not really known to most.
I think it also says later in the text that the men of the city of Sodom, when they went after Lot to get the angels, all of them went to Lot's house.
That shows that there couldn't have been more than 200 or 300 people in the entire city of Sodom.
Or it could have been all the ones with that interest, I should say.
No, it says all of them, all the men.
But they were all degenerate.
And even if you look further, like two generations later when you had Jacob and his sons, two of them, Simeon and Levi, they were kind of violent and they went and killed all the men of the city of Sheshem after having deceived them into circumcising themselves.
They killed everybody in the city.
So there couldn't have been a million people there or half a million or even 100,000.
That's a stretch.
When you look at a football stadium that's full, that's 20,000, sometimes 30.
That's a very containable whatever.
But when you see them disembarking or leaving the event, it seems like the entire city is moving.
And that's still a large, it's a small number relative to today what we say a city is.
So keep that in mind, like what Sam is saying, a few hundred people could have easily comprised of a city.
And even like Abraham, when it says that Abraham went into Egypt in Genesis 12, as soon as he arrived, Pharaoh knew that he was there.
So that couldn't have been a nation of a million people because if you walk into New York, nobody knows that you're there unless there's obviously security looking for you or whatever.
They do.
Maybe it depends on who you're rolling around with.
But he only had, he couldn't have had more than a few people with him, like 50 people, like servants and whatnot.
Well, we don't know.
And also they had people go in front of people very often.
The Egyptians did that often.
Like one of the ways the Egyptians increased their territory is they would have a small band march through a country and put up a banner and then walk away.
And through acquiescence, if no one took the banner down or fought them, they were like, oh, that's our territory too.
You know?
I see that happening today.
There's some crosswalks and it says no trespassing, a little yellow sign.
This is state property, no trespassing.
It's on the crosswalk.
I mean, you know, in a media and you're like, what do you mean?
You see?
And they're just using admiralty on that, you know.
You know, children do it all the time in the games.
You're it now.
You're it.
They touch you and you're it, right?
Get it?
But let's go back to the population aspect.
The dynamic of such things is not dependent on how many people are there.
It's that it happened to all the people that were there.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
That makes sense.
In other words, whether there were a few or many, if you killed everyone in the city, I ask this question often, if no one lives there, is it a city?
Well, you know, it's a ghost town or whatever, but I'm saying that's why a lot of times in Scripture when you'll see they interchange city and people in the translation, not often, but I've caught it enough.
You know, is a city a city if no one lives there?
Is a room a room if no one's in it, you know, kind of thing, you know?
Is a bedroom a bedroom if no one ever slept in it, you know?
I mean, well, then is the architect expected as such?
Okay, but, you know, functionally, no.
No, that makes sense.
It's the dynamic, I think, that's coming across here because you also have to remember there's an archetype behind this, and we find it in Isaiah and other places, and there's more detail in the book of Zechariah about how things unfold.
You're told what's going to happen before it happens, and there's your example of it.
You see?
I think we were having a conversation earlier about, you know, there's a sparse narrative, and when you see days being given, you know, like 24th day of the ninth month or something, can you wrap your head around that?
Most people don't, you know.
You can't go to the Gregorian calendar.
It doesn't work.
So when you're talking about everyone in the city and all this, what's the dynamic?
And archaeologically, that can be proven.
For example, if you have a non-industrial type of setting and you see there's a floor plan with 50 houses, on the minimum, two to three people per house, you can do the math and get the logistics of the population pretty quick, right?
Mm-hmm.
You know what I mean?
But, you know, you also have to know vertical.
You know, in New York, if they flattened out all of Manhattan and you look at the floor plan, it would be rather deceiving to use that estimation if you didn't know how tall the buildings were.
So we know that in ancient times they went up quite easily three to four stories.
Typically not.
Typically it was two stories.
Very typical.
The reason why is because you had to be space efficient.
Why?
Because you usually had a protection wall around you.
And the larger the area, the longer the protection wall.
And the longer the protection wall, the less robust it usually was for the same effort.
So if you had a vertical city, you can have a shorter protection wall on the perimeter and it could be built more robustly with the same resources, manpower, and material, right?
Mm-hmm.
So they were – so one thing that people – it's not like the Walt Disney or the Bible Museum and all the stuff where they show you these shantytowns and, you know, mud brick, single story.
That's not true at all.
You know, they went up vertically as much as possible.
So anyway, just wanted to throw that little detail in there.
How pertinent it is to how many people lived there needs to be considered.
Mm.
Because the city – So what?
One thing you'll find out, by the way, when you read scripture in ancient texts, the city was actually considered safe or not depending on what?
The robustness of what?
Not the military, but the robustness of the wall surrounding it.
Right?
Right.
Yeah.
Regarding the Abraham thing, I do think he was trying to sort of keep a low profile at that time because he was even afraid that they were going to take his wife from him.
So he told them to make up a – well, they didn't make up a story, but to say that they were siblings.
So the fact that they noticed when they entered, I think it does suggest that even the whole of Egypt probably was no more than a couple of 5,000 to 10,000 people.
I don't think they had a huge population at that time.
OK.
But then you can also look – Yeah, it's a guess.
I would suggest that it varied too greatly to speculate.
I think that's something that should be studied, but it should be studied properly.
In other words, you can't take what we are told about these things and rely on it as it being how it was back then.
I think one of the things I've always been saying years ago is it will come a time, which is right now, starting this spring, is where people are going to start to wipe away all the presumptions of fact and presumptions of history and reexamine it, and they're going to be in a surprise to find out what really went on.
And how things really were, and I think you're bringing up whether there was a high population, a large population, or a small population is relevant on many other factors.
And you're bringing up what can be literally surmised by, for example, how can Abraham take over this king with so few men and all that.
These things, yeah, seem plausible that there were few people.
From a plausible point of view, yeah, I would suggest that.
But I would say that a concentration of a high number of people in a small area was common also, so we have to consider that.
I mean, you can say Jerusalem is only a few city blocks, right?
It wouldn't even be considered – it would just be considered in modern-day parlance a neighborhood, far from a city or far from any jurisdiction that it merits when we use the term Jerusalem.
Yeah.
So think about it.
And also back in those ancient times it was conceivable that a million people, or at least close to that, would have passed through places like that for obviously – for cultural reasons, commerce, what they call religion, military, financial, all this other stuff, right?
Resources going through there.
Yeah.
There's even a point – I'm trying to look for it now.
I don't know if it was Lot or if it was Isaac.
But it said that one of them got so big that the Philistines were afraid of them, like they got so much wealth as far as the cattle and stuff.
I think it was Lot maybe.
I don't remember.
It's either Lot or it's Isaac.
I know it's one of them.
But they got so rich that the surrounding countries asked them to leave wherever they were at because they felt threatened by them.
So once again, Lot or Isaac could not have amassed a nation of millions of servants and cattle.
That would have once again signified smaller numbers.
They probably reached a population of a few thousand and the countries around them got threatened.
Right.
Well, are we given numbers of the beasts and possessions of Abraham?
Yeah, somewhere.
I think that's written.
There's some simple – yeah, thousands of camels and thousands of asses, right?
Thousands in the high hundreds to low thousands, you know, 4,000, 3,000, 2,000, right?
So logistics on that, how many cattle hands or ass hands or camel hands you need to manage that, right?
Because, you know, getting the animals is one thing.
Keeping them is another.
Right, Brian?
Oh, yeah.
Lots of maintenance.
Yeah.
So not just that they're there.
So what does it take to keep those animals?
I mean that in the husbandry sense.
You know, how many – you know, what is it on the ranch?
You need like one hand roughly per 40 cows or 60 cows or now I think it's up in the hundreds.
So, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Specifically it was Isaac.
Isaac got so rich that it threatened the Philistines and other people around him.
Somewhere in Genesis 26.
Now, you could threaten – like for example, you know, you could say in a story, for example, like a small town in Canada is threatening the United States of America because, you know, let's say that town is right on the border and they decide to put a parking lot that goes six inches into the United States.
I'm just giving a metaphor, right?
Oh, yeah.
So moving on from that sort of small numbers.
Remember, by the way, when you read about military stuff, it's in Admiralty.
And then the question is, well, what do we know about Admiralty?
Very little.
Well, yeah.
Well, it's – a lot of the parlance now is maritime Admiralty law.
You know, like a simple thing, you know, it's fine.
It's difficult to find these days.
When I was studying this before it became popular, what do you call a captain of a ship when he starts ruling on land?
You know, a ship pulls up, you know, parks, you know, they dock the ship.
Now the captain of the ship goes out.
He maintains his authority as the – over the crew.
So now the crew goes into the land and starts running stuff on land.
What is the captain now called when he's on the land?
He's no longer a captain.
What is his new title in Admiralty?
Now it is governor.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
So you see, there's just a – is it the same?
No, it's different, but you see how it – you know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
The status change.
Right.
So, Adam, what do you know about Admiralty?
Well, we just mentioned, you know, the medians here.
I was beginning to notice that little yellow sign, state property, no trespassing.
What are you talking about?
This is a median.
It's supposed to cross through here to get to the other side of the road, you know, chicken or not.
So, you know, what are these guys doing?
You know?
Well, I know what they're doing.
That's another conversation.
So moving on from the 600-year patriarch period, you get into the Egyptian period of 200 years where Joseph sort of heads things after becoming second in command.
And it would seem that you have sort of a growth in civilization as far as the numbers go.
Once Joseph becomes the number two, the conditions were so good in Egypt for the next two centuries that you get this population explosion where the children of Israel were fruitful and increased abundantly and the land was filled with them.
Personally, I'm guessing that the population explosion is global because the abundance was global.
It's not just Egypt that prospered.
It was seven years for the entire world and then seven years of famine for everybody also.
And we know that…
Just like today.
Just like today, you have periods of that.
Yeah, go ahead.
So we know that the Israelites began to rival the population of Egypt itself, meaning that they would have had to be roughly the same number.
And the Amalekites also must have had something close to the same number because they went to war with the Israelites and it doesn't say anything about a disparity in numbers in Exodus 17 when they're in the wilderness.
Usually…
But hold on.
We were given numbers of 600,000 fighting men leaving Egypt.
So if each fighting man had two relatives, you'd have to say there was 1.8 million people that left Egypt.
If they each had three relatives, it would be 2.4 million.
Same for the Amalekites though.
Whatever army they sent to fight, they'd have had families somewhere else too.
Right.
When you get numbers, it's not strictly that's the population.
That's just the fighting population.
Yeah.
I'm guessing that there was a period of great sort of activity, building activity around this period of time also where you would have had a lot of pyramids, canal systems, ancient temples and stuff that were created.
And I've read some stuff on that, that certain ancient monuments can be traced back to that period, which would make sense because they would have had the manpower for it.
But you can't build big temples with just 100 people in a city.
Depends.
It depends on how savvy they are and how well-versed they are in moving things.
Okay.
You could build that pyramid, that Great Giza Pyramid in less than 20 years with less than 1,000 people.
Probably be more like several hundred people in less than 20 years.
Well, if the gods are helping you, I guess you can do whatever.
Let me just interject something.
The gods are always involved.
They're either helping you or hindering you, right?
Yes.
I mean overtly.
Yeah.
Well, once you find out about it, how can that be overt anymore?
So the key is to block knowledge of the gods to the people, just like it is right now, today.
So then you go after that and you get into the judges period, which is about 400 years, I think.
And we know that the tribes, well, first of all, Egypt went under because of the 10 plagues.
And then following that, we know that there's this Hyksos tribe that came in and invaded.
I'm guessing that it's the Amalekites.
There's some good evidence that points to that.
They took over Egypt for 400 years, and the country went through a period of decline.
And then even if you read the biblical text, not until it's the time of Saul does the Bible even mention Egypt.
It didn't even get mentioned until it's time for Saul to go fight the Amalekites.
Well, there's a list of nations they had to contend with, and nowhere is there any mention of Egypt.
Right.
They were like almost, well, they fell flat on their face.
As a matter of fact, there's more evidence as time goes through from the history of other nations of that time period, Egyptians losing, I mean, just the Egyptian void, I call it, you know.
And I think if you read Samuel pretty well, it does show that the Amalekites were occupying the northern part of Egypt.
I think 1 Samuel 15, 7, and Saul smote the Amalekites from Havalah all the way to shore, which is before Egypt.
So like right at the border.
So if you're fighting them at the border, they would have been living in the country itself.
So, yeah, and even I think David also went to war with them at one point.
He said he extended his sovereignty to the Negev also at that point, which means your control, yeah.
Right.
So the whole thing about this is not anybody can, you know, say, well, this is my land now, or this is whatever.
You know, that's fine.
Anybody can do that anywhere, but can you keep it?
You see.
So and the way you keep a place is by disarming it, right?
Right.
As far as the David thing is kind of interesting, it says in Samuel 27, 1 Samuel 27, and David and his men went up and raided the Geshurites and the Gursites and the Amalekites.
For those nations were the inhabitants of the land of old as you go to shore and even as far as the land of Egypt.
And, yeah, that wasn't actually the verse I was looking for, because there's another verse that very explicitly.
Oh, here it is.
So it says that the Egyptians were servants of the Amalekites, which actually justifies the Amalekite exhaust theory.
It gives us a biblical basis in Samuel 30.
And they found a man in the field, an Egyptian, and took him to David.
And they gave him bread and wine and he ate and they let him eat because he was close to fainting.
And when he had eaten, his strength came back to him for he had not eaten for several days.
And David said to him, to whom do you belong and where are you from?
And he said, I'm a young man from Egypt, servant of an Amalekite.
And my master left me behind for I had been sick three days.
So that makes it explicit.
What is interesting, though, in connection to that, is that not just Egypt going through a dark age, but there seems to be evidence that the Israelites also sort of had a dark age.
Because if you think about it, they were in the wilderness for 40 years.
Their professional class or their artisan class that they would have developed in Egypt would have died off in that period.
And then you have a new generation coming along that for all practical purposes would have also been a desert people because they grew up in the desert.
And it seems as if they also lost the ability to...
Well, I don't think they would completely have nothing to do because, remember, there's surface materials that can always be used.
And at the time, it's different than, you know, the readily access of whatever you had, you know, that was all used up, like, you know, like easy, the deforestation of places, you know, that we don't see forests.
And now, so they were in the wilderness sustained from divine assistance.
But when you read through numbers and other places, you know, make references to them in the wilderness, they were pretty crafty with idols and other things like that.
I don't think it completely died off.
I don't think they were useless.
Yeah, the main die-off was the fighting men.
But there's also a mention in Samuel that it seems to suggest that the civilization had degenerated so low that there was no blacksmith found throughout the entire land of Israel.
First Samuel 13, 19.
And the Philistines made sure of that later as well by banning their ability to procure iron instruments.
Yes, that also.
And it seems as if that lasted until David, though.
So it was quite a bit.
It was quite extensive.
And then you get to Solomon and David, which is about 80 years.
And you have also the divided kingdom, which is 393.
And I'm kind of still looking into that, so I don't have much on it.
But you have worldwide prosperity and flourishing trade.
And you also have Israel serving as a bridge between Egypt and Mesopotamia.
We talked about that before.
And then Kings and Chronicles sort of lays that out.
But, yeah, I don't have too much about that right now.
It's quite a lot to look into.
You have the Babylonian captivity, which is 70 years.
And there are more than that.
Yeah, more than that.
But they assist the assistance to break free and go back.
I mean, it was timed also by the Medians and the Persians coming in and changing the status of Babylon as ruler.
Yes, and allowing them to go back.
And assisting them, right, and acknowledging the god.
Yes.
Which is still hidden, by the way, in their history.
Their history.
And then the post-exilic period, which covers the time from Cyrus' decree to the Old Testament, the close of the Old Testament.
Right.
And when you – let me just throw this in there.
They never recovered from that pre-exilic condition that led them in.
They never fully recovered from the Babylonian captivity.
And I would suggest that the modern, quote-unquote, Judeans are still suffering that time period of Babylonian captivity.
How do I know?
Well, I could say loosely, just have a conversation with a high-level rabbi, and every other thing that comes out of his mouth is Babylonian.
You know, in terms of why they do what they do.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
You've heard that?
Oh yeah, I've heard it to my ear.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So there's still, you know, from a Babylonian point of view, not much has changed for certain societies since that time period, right?
Mm-hmm.
Pretty much.
But you have a lot of new breeds, in terms of, you know, when you talk about deific and religion.
You have Islam, you have Christianity, you have all these things that have come out in the last 1,500 years or less, you know.
Mm-hmm.
Which are, you know, complete mockery of both the pagan gods and the Most High, by the way.
You know, so where does that leave us?
You know, if you want to take a swath, you know, I said earlier, a swath of time of over 2,500 years that not much can be said of, you know, up until after the flood, you know, to patriarchs.
I mean, you cover that pretty quickly.
You can pretty much cover the past 2,000 years when it comes to the gods.
Not much.
I mean, you can't take Christianity and Islam seriously, I mean, unless you've had a major head injury.
You know what I mean?
There's nothing going on for the past 2,000 years.
Nothing.
No, not in public.
Probably in people's private lives.
Yeah, there's a lot of magic, but it's subdued.
There's a lot of just rustling about, busy work, you know?
Mm-hmm.
When you think about it.
That's a big swath of time.
And guess what?
It mirrors the beginning, doesn't it?
Quite a bit.
First 2,000 years, doesn't it?
From that respect.
In the sense that not much is said about it, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
What's going on, you know?
But they were very technologically advanced.
There's one fork in the road before the flood you can take, you know?
And right now, you say mankind is very technologically advanced and all that, but yeah, is anything going on?
No.
Dumb shit.
So, and I'm talking now from the way that society, through their culture, tradition, religion, what have you, academia, interact with the gods, you know?
Right?
Mm-hmm.
Like, I'll bring this up again.
There's, you remember Star Trek, the Borg?
You know, they're all plugged in to the collective.
Mm-hmm.
Any Christian you start that's, you know, very adamant about their quote-unquote faith, you start bringing up how it's extremely anomalous when you compare it to what's in the scripture, Old or New Testament regardless.
What they do is they discredit the document.
Who wrote that anyway, is what you hear them say most of the time, right?
I'm talking about, you know, the common people now.
Mm-hmm.
Who cares?
I don't need that, right?
Mm-hmm.
And it's as if anywhere in the world you go, as if they're connected in some hive.
Now, just bear in mind I'm talking about there is something behind that because the Borg, they were all connected.
There was something behind it.
There was a central cube or whatever, right?
You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
And the same with the Muslims.
If you bring up something that's supposedly in the Koran, which the Koran is just, you can't find any coherent stories in there anyway.
But anyway, they'll tell you, oh, that can't be in the Koran because the Koran was written to be simple.
What you're saying is not simple, right?
So it can't be in there.
And then if you show them where it is, they'll say, oh, that's a wrong copy, you know.
So they all say that.
Yeah, they say that.
I'm like, whoa, man.
It's like I heard this across country five years ago, the same exact thing.
How can these guys be verbatim, whether they're Christian or Muslim or whatever, say the same exact thing?
So what I'm trying to say here, if I said there is a hive mentality or something that they're tapped into, you say, Greek, you know, that sounds kind of crazy.
But I've been proving this, that there is a spirit or some kind of Borg.
You know, I'm using the Star Trek analogy here.
Albeit, however good of analogy or poor analogy, I think it's accurate in terms of the way it works.
But using Star Trek as an analogy is poor because it's fiction.
But this is reality, what I'm speaking on right now.
And I think that there's a lot going on, like Sam said, albeit quiet or whatever.
There is a very strong demon.
I'll give you an example.
When I run into people from Asia, especially Koreans, and they say they're very Christian, I'm like, why?
You gave up the demons of your forefathers to accept the demons of the Westerners?
What's the difference?
You know?
So anyway, there's an interesting undercurrent, something very powerful, that shows its commonality.
And am I interested in finding out more about it?
No, not at all.
But if I get more direct information on that, I'm sure to report it.
You know what I mean?
Right, right.
So, yeah, there is something.
It should be part of that Sons of Al-Ahim, right?
No, I think it's a different set or a different thing.
Because the Sons of Al-Ahim have been spread.
They're still here, because it doesn't show that.
Nowhere does it say that they're still here, but nowhere does it say that they won't be completely.
You know what I mean?
Right.
And also some of the anomalous things that will be happening in the end is because of them, or results of their interaction.
I would suggest that sometimes it's okay when people say, I don't want to know.
I won't say I don't want to know, but it's not something I have an interest in investigating anymore, because it's so active and so current.
I think it will be like dealing with a 50,000-volt underground power line.
There's a difference between dealing with an overhead power line.
You can see it.
It's there.
When it's underground, you're digging, and you don't know it's there.
You call the Blue Stake people so they could put us, you know, ground.
I don't think I want to go digging looking for something like that.
But I see it existing.
And what I just said about any Christian will start discrediting the Bible using the same terms.
Who wrote that anyway?
I don't need that to believe.
It's happened so many times that if you use what's called the scientific method to say that there has to be something spiritually behind them, all using the same terminology, this is good science, because the good science would be if the experiment…
Sure.
Yeah.
In other words, if you use the scientific method, you could prove it using the scientific method that there has to be something behind it.
You see?
Right.
So, yeah, forget about odds.
That would be statisticians now.
I'm talking about straight-up scientific method, you know, where you have the experiments set up.
And I do this often.
Well, not anymore.
But years ago, I'd say, watch this guy right here.
You know, we're going to go talk to this guy.
He says he's a Christian.
He wants to talk to us.
And I'm going to press him.
And he's going to say, oh, who wrote that book anyway?
I don't care.
Watch.
And so I go, you know, I introduce him to this Christian guy, and he starts talking.
And I just press him a little bit.
And he gets upset.
And I say, okay, this guy's a little bit more robust than the others.
I'm going to press him a little bit more.
He's still not saying it, I'm thinking, you know.
I press him again.
And he says, well, who wrote that book anyway?
And the guy looks at me and says, how did you know he was going to say that?
And I say, I'm telling you, man, there's some evil shit going on here.
And the same with the Muslims.
I'll go to, you know, a market, an Islamic market, and I'll press the guys and say, watch, he's going to say what you're saying is not right because the Koran was written to be simple.
Watch.
Watch this.
And even with a little bit of a pressure, he'll say, oh, that can't be in there because the Koran was written to be simple.
I say, how did you know he was going to say that, Greek?
And I'm like, I'm telling you.
I've done it hundreds of times.
It's good science, right?
Anyway, that's why very often I take this approach and I'll be like, listen, folks, you know, I don't know why no one's really speaking about these things because they're not, you know, they're not occulted.
I mean, you can actually experience them for yourself, you know, or gain information, you know, when I start saying certain things and I find out it's so obvious and it's not being discussed, it kind of scares myself into abstaining from, you know, speaking publicly sometimes from that because the stuff is just so obvious and no attention is being drawn to it.
But in closing, the ability for certain religious groups, especially these two that I've been poking, I've noticed they have this Borg thing.
It's like a pre-scripted thing.
They say no matter where in the world they are, it doesn't matter.
I've done it with people in different parts of the world in different languages.
They say the same thing.
So maybe Roddenberry, whoever wrote the thing with the Borg, was onto something.
We're talking about some serious disclosure.
And that's why ultimately, if I just say these people are just downright evil, you know, the humans, you know, not because they want to be evil, because they're controlled by something that is and they don't know it.
Yeah, yeah.
You see.
Until this time period where things get mopped up or cleaned up and turned around.
So I don't urge everyone and anyone to do this.
That's why sometimes I tell people don't do what I would do.
So, you know, it's an interesting perception there.
And none of these things are being discussed.
I think the conversations that even Sam and I have, and I've noticed that through private messaging and comments, people take interest in what we're saying, not because it's explaining complicated things.
It's because we're explaining things that are really simple and just looking at them in various ways.
And we don't cover too many subjects, which is fine.
But, in other words, trying to show that the mindset to see things clearly is quite accessible to anyone.
You just have to understand what that mindset is.
And in order to have the proper mindset in most cases with anything, is you have to be able to filter out all the crap that you're using in your current mindset.
You know.
You know, concerning that, I've been thinking about that a little bit, because I look at people around me and the way that they seem unrehabilitatable, sort of.
I think you've given some kind of an analogy before about things being molded into cement.
You can't really break them by impacting upon them in any way.
You sort of have to blow them up with dynamite.
Well, you can't change them without them breaking.
Once it sets, it's too late.
You can still change it, but it's catastrophic.
So, practically speaking, you can't change it.
And there seems to be a sense in which the mindset isn't something that you can necessarily attain through the application of some kind of behavioral methodology or diligence or vigilance.
It almost seems as if that also has to be given to you, because I could not.
I know people whose lot in life or whose mental state I couldn't improve, even if I explained things on the level of a fifth grader to them.
Well, it's not a matter of improving them.
It's a matter of showing things that are better.
Yeah, but they'll do it functionally, but they won't do it with any sense of understanding.
Because if you have real understanding, I think that also generates a sense of curiosity to understand what correlates to what you're looking at, so that you don't have this sort of tunnel vision.
You can explain things to people and they'll get it, but the tunnel vision doesn't go away.
So, do they really get it?
Well, no.
So there's a spirit there.
I haven't examined it too much, but when you look at the parable of the farmer who sows the seeds, and then he sows some and then the demons come and has the birds and they pick it up.
What are you going to do about that?
Other than pray, of course, but you can't use rhetoric as a way to fight that.
If you put it in an eloquent way that they'll take it, they won't take it.
Well, that's why I use the cosmic censorship, meaning it's not earthly.
It's not tangible, as people would consider censorship to be.
Which, by the way, in Greek, the word for censorship is logokrisis, which literally means a word crisis.
So this idea of a cosmic crisis with words and understandings and ideas, because logos is really just a communication, a body of knowledge, there's a crisis with it, is a blanket thing.
And if they decide for you to be, they meaning the gods, for you to be censored, there is nothing you can do.
To the individual, you have to go to who's putting the censorship on.
Do you remember with Elisha with the servant in the dwelling where he says he prayed that the servant's eyes are opened?
He didn't try to open the servant's eyes.
He prayed that the gods would do it, you see?
So there's that aspect.
But in a general way where you're speaking like on a sonic event like this, if people acknowledge that there is a censorship and they are censored, that is far more advanced than denying it exists or not knowing that it exists at all.
You see what I mean?
That you're far ahead of the game.
Right.
Just by knowing that we're all censored.
You know, a child used to ask me, aren't you censored too?
I'm like, you're missing the whole point.
You know, that's like that fifth-grader, fifth-five-year-old schoolyard mentality.
Well, you know, didn't she get it too?
You know, it has nothing to do with the messenger.
You know, it has to do with the message as the, do you get that this exists?
You know, who it applies to will come later, and you'll see that later.
But if you don't even know about it, at initial exposure to it, what does it matter who is and who isn't?
You were just made aware of something you never were.
Just contemplate that, and then we'll go to the next level.
And then we can discuss the fine points in a way that is mature and substantive and rational versus, you know, the five-year-old, you know, well, you're it and I'm not, or I'm it and you're not, you see, kind of thing.
And that's the problem when you get to these core matters, because when you're censored by the gods, it's not trivial.
It's a core issue, I think, right?
Same thing that can't be changed, like a core issue.
It's like pulling the rebar out of concrete.
You know, it no longer can hit us.
It's pulling the structural element out.
It's a structural thing.
So, yeah, it's pretty wicked in some cases.
In most cases it's fairly benign.
You know what I mean?
It just basically turned people into cattle kind of thing.
So seemingly benign, because even when they're like cattle, they're harmless as long as you don't poke them.
But when you poke them, they can get violent or they can get aggressive.
Yeah, yeah, and they're very curious.
I've been startled by quite a few of them once.
I was around a campfire and I turned around and there were like four cows leaning right towards me, listening to the conversation.
And I was like sitting side by side with someone, so we were both facing one direction in the fire.
And I turn around and there's like four cow heads right there, I mean just about two feet away.
And they're all listening, and they're like looking right in the eye.
I'm like, whoa!
And they're very impressive, you know, physically as well, right?
And the biblical metaphors to animals, of course, you know the goat will be very agreeable but eat anything, even though it just finished saying this is bad.
You don't be like, why are you eating that?
You just said it was bad.
Well, I'm a goat, I can do anything.
The sheep is very peculiar and very specific.
In other words, if it eats something it's not supposed to, it actually does great harm to it.
And the dog will eat its vomit.
When something is bad, it gets rid of it but then goes right back to it.
And the pig is a violent eater.
So...
They'll eat just about anything.
And they do it with violence, yeah.
They're violent.
So the pigs are the worst than the dogs and goats and the sheep.
And that's why I always object to the people being called sheeple.
They're not sheeple, because if they were sheeple, they wouldn't be in the condition they're in.
They would mostly be dead, or they would set themselves apart.
They're mostly goats and dogs.
And the pigs are, if you're an authority figure, if you want to secure your authority in this type of society, you have to hire pigs.
They'll tear you to pieces immediately if they don't like it, right?
So...
That's the character.
But the cosmic censorship is an interesting thing, because that, I've mentioned for a long time now, that will be lifted to a certain degree for a certain amount of things to be acknowledged.
So later on, when things start to change, the people are aware of why they're changing and what's happening and what's coming.
Because if they weren't aware of it, the mop-up crew and the destruction of man's society will be deemed unlawful.
Because later on, people will say, We didn't know any of this.
Why did you rip us up and kill most of us the way you did?
And the gods are smart enough to know that the last thing they want to do after the resurrection is hear a bunch of sniveling humans complain.
So they're going to make people aware of enough that they can actually do the job lawfully.
You see?
So what do people need to know about the gods before the gods come down here and start hacking 90% of them into pieces?
Well, they have to know, first of all, they have to acknowledge the gods exist, right?
And they have to acknowledge some kind of hierarchy.
And they also have to acknowledge that the gods are the creative force behind everything.
Simple, right?
And also they have to acknowledge it enough that they're going to take something good, lawfulness, and use it to an extreme where it becomes something bad.
You know, like water is really good.
You need it, right?
They say if there's no water, there's no life.
But also water is, according to insurance companies, especially the cause for most property damage.
And also you can drown someone face down in a little bit of water.
You can literally drown someone in a bowl of water.
Not much.
It's just how you use it.
That's why I keep discussing what you will see in the future as an adaptation of biblical law in the harshest extreme.
You know, that's why I discussed the tattoo thing.
And even before the tattoos became prevalent, I was like, there's going to be, obviously, a prevalence of massive tattooing before it started taking place.
Before it happened.
Why?
Because I knew that biblical law would be used wrongfully, and one of the things in there forbids that type of stuff, right?
So obviously people will start engaging unknowingly into things that later on will be...
You know, if you look at, for example, the same-sex marriage and what they call homosexuality and all that other stuff, I've had people come to me and say, Greek, aren't you upset about this?
You know, you're an Old Testament kind of guy.
You know, the Bible forgives us.
I said, well, yeah, but, you know, just looking at the fact that it's open and it's acceptable and actually the unions are enforced by the legal system and the powers that be is not the issue.
The issue is you have to connect the events that have been going on in the past months or years to what's coming to see it in its proper perspective.
So in the future, what's coming is a very adverse, extremely draconian application of the law of forbidding same-sex unions at penalty of whatever.
So all of this going on right now is very simple.
They're all coming out and being catalogued.
You know what I mean?
They're being recorded.
So when the time comes for that draconian application of the law to its extreme, well, take just a couple of keystrokes away and they got 99% of them, right?
And you look at how much they're cataloguing, you know, the medical persuasion, legal, social.
Oh, everything, yeah.
Yeah, social media.
Oh, yeah.
So how many times have you heard me say, you're being set up by the gods?
See, if you get set up for failure by a human, you kind of feel, oh, man, I don't believe I let this happen.
But if you're getting set up by the gods, I mean, what are you going to say?
You should have seen it coming or you could have done better?
It's the gods that are doing it, man.
Relax, chill.
There's nothing you can do.
So I sit back and I watch this.
It is a very slow train wreck, you know, in super slow motion where it's like one frame every week versus 16 frames a second.
And it's so clear.
And anyway, I think I'm the only person around discussing the tattoos and the same-sex union this way.
I've researched it and, like, there's no discussion.
I'm wondering sometimes I have to doubt myself.
You know, I'm just like, wait, how can I be the only one saying this stuff?
Maybe I'm not correct about this.
It's not a matter of being correct.
It's a matter of are you adding up?
It's mathematical.
Are you as anyone else, are you doing the math on this?
And the answer to that is no.
So whatever, you know.
You know, the same applies for tattooing.
You get stopped in any way, shape, or form.
You're not going to remove it.
You're indexed by all the marks on yourself, cuts, whatever, all sorts of stuff.
Right, and also the electronic records of those applying them.
Right, right.
And also the, yeah.
So it's, yeah, it's quite interesting to see that happening.
In other words, let me just say it this way to everyone categorically, anything you want to discuss.
There's no reason to be upset about anything anymore, folks.
You get it?
Because you're being set up, you know.
Like I mentioned earlier, a couple of people I've known in the past say, well, you're an Old Testament kind of guy.
Aren't you upset about all this same-sex stuff?
I'm like, why?
You know, if you thought everything was open-ended, you might say, yeah, it goes against what I think is right.
But if you know what's coming, it fits perfectly.
You know, the same with the tattoos, you know.
Right, years ago when I was writing this, I noticed an increase.
Now I can't go in public and see anyone without one.
I'm not looking for them.
I'm looking for people without them, and it's a very difficult.
And recently I saw someone I thought was without one, and I looked down and they had one like on their foot.
So I can honestly come home and say I was out for three hours today at the shops and I didn't see anyone without a tattoo.
I'm not saying that no one was without a tattoo, but the people I interacted with, absolutely every one of them had some kind of marking.
It has nothing to do with what you, you know, this is not opinion.
This is just, you know, statistically looking at what's going on and what you knew was coming before it even happened and what it's going to end up as.
So what else is there?
I mean, you know, in terms of that respect is the cosmic censorship and what's coming and all this other stuff needs to be all looked at together.
Why?
Because look how censored you have to be to get a tattoo, let's say, in earnest.
And I'm not talking about a mark that you say, oh, I shouldn't have done that.
I'm talking about like everywhere, hands, feet, you know, all kinds of stuff, and also these same-sex people, you know.
Why are they falling into the paramour philosophy and the – well, there's a God.
It's an ancient religion actually because there were erudols, right, temple prostitutes.
Erudol, I think is the term.
Erudol.
It was an old term.
It's an English term used for altar.
It literally means altar servant.
They had to be bisexual and all this, you know, men with men or men with women and women with women or women with men.
Yeah, I just want to trace that historically back to the mystery schools, a lot of that sort of people serving at the altar of the gods had to be that.
I've seen that.
Asexual or bisexual, but not just – I forget the names.
Well, the term is an erudol, H-E-I-R-D-U-L-E, I think.
I don't like using those types of terms that, you know, I've researched because it doesn't carry over well to the audience at large.
I just use simple terms.
These temple slaves or temple servants, basically altar boys and girls, literally is what it means.
So, yeah, a revival of those things to some extent.
But, you know, what's a temple these days?
You know, right now there are none.
Are they or are they not?
It's a mindset, you know.
Well, you know, the television – well, the television has replaced the hearth.
You know, years ago people would sit around the fire and stare at it.
Now they stare at the screen.
So years ago people would go, what's the temple now, right?
And a temple in ancient times was a place where you had the aggregates of the judiciary, you know, the courts and the university and offerings to the god all in one place and the treasury all in one place.
So if you went to any city right now and you developed a campus where the university, the courts, the treasury, and the government were all in one place, that's a temple.
And it sort of has that archetype today because when you go to the downtown of any city, typically you will find the university in that area, you will find the courts in that area, and you find the rulership and treasury in that area typically.
It still exists in some form like that.
But anyway, I think what's important to discuss, which not much can be discussed about, is the censorship.
Because once you understand that, how can you be upset?
Obviously there are things and matters to take.
You know, people say take your law into your own hands.
How dare you do that?
Well, how else are you going to know when the law has properly been done?
When you have a minimum of 12 years of education in any Western country, a roundabout there, I think it's really eight that they require.
How many hours?
I didn't even say weeks or courses.
How many minutes even of law education do you get?
None, right?
That's your sign.
How many people are raised – or how many – you know, when you read about – you take classes.
I've spoken to economics professors that can't give you any details at all of where credit comes from or what it means to be in receivership, the condition of the government.
They can't discuss it.
They don't know.
And these are the people that are educating everyone else.
It's just like a priest.
Oh, by the way, when I mentioned the Borg mentality about how they always discredit their books, I finally sealed that statement when I had just about every priest, pastor, bishop, whatever, say that to me as well.
That's what really sealed it for me because they represent their congregation, do they not?
So every time I had a little pastor or minister tell me, it doesn't matter what the Bible says, who wrote that anyway, indirectly I said, well, how many people do you have in your congregation?
He says 150.
So right away that was just like to me speaking to 150 people just by speaking to him.
Yeah.
You feel me on that?
Okay.
So because I'm looking at him being apolitical, right, and not like, for example, when you could say the president speaks for everyone in America.
No, because it's a political system.
It's broken up.
But when I speak to a rabbi and his wife says, I don't want to know anything about that law stuff, because who know if Moses existed anyway, the rabbi's wife, right, says that to me.
And I'm wondering now, well, is she speaking for him also?
It's a good question, sure.
You see, and the chances are they're either, yes, she either is or they're in division.
There's no other possibility.
So this is the stuff I've come across to, and I started lumping it together, and I said to myself, Greek, how many more years are you going to spend going around interviewing people?
Stop.
This is it.
It's enough.
You know what I mean?
Just sit back until the times change, which is now.
Starting around this spring and the next midpoint of that period would put you three and a half years, it was around 2021, 2022, around there, the censorship will be lifted enough where people, very matter of factly, will start accepting enough about the gods that what comes after that will be considered lawful.
Well, because what comes after that is a lot more as well.
With the leadership on the earth, an agglomerate and conglomerate of people, whether directly or indirectly, meaning publicly or secretly, ruling the entire world is a pretty big deal.
Because here's the thing.
Very easy math here.
Is it correct?
Well, we won't know until it pans out.
The biblical Christ was born in the year 4000.
So instead of antichrist, which represents man, when would he be born?
The year 6000.
Simple.
The biblical Christ, he was a complete secret except to a few.
Now, you could say that the antichrist will also be a complete secret except to a few, or he will be the opposite.
He will be not a secret except to a few.
He'll be open.
But I would doubt that.
I would say his identity would also be a complete secret.
Because right now, if you went out and did a poll through the world, whether you knew about the Bible or not, and said, do you know that will you be happy with the antichrist ruling mankind, just like scripture say, how many show of hands will say yes?
Hardly anyone.
You see?
So it has to be a secret again.
So you see, there's mathematical rational.
When I say mathematical, it's just simple yes and no stuff to start filtering through what's coming, you know.
Will biblical law and strict adaptation of it be applied to the whole world?
Yes.
Will it be done properly?
No.
You see what I mean?
Yes or no stuff, right?
Then you start putting all this together, and you get the picture is very clear.
It's just like when you see, you ever see a very realistic artist rendering done with just charcoal or pencil?
I mean, it looks like a photo.
Yeah.
That's just a pencil.
It's just one color.
It's black and white.
You know, you just need black and white to make the picture, and that's one way to look at these harsh.
When you look at things that seem extreme and harsh, stop.
Most people through the history have created this gray area.
Well, that doesn't mean that, or, well, that happened already, or, well, it's not going to happen if we do this.
No, no, just what's the black and white aspect?
Start building this picture, and then you're like, oh, this looks so clear.
You see?
Right.
And the thing is, these things will happen.
Exactly how they will happen, we don't know exactly.
No, exactly, exactly.
But the interesting thing about prophecy, the way it's declared in Scripture, you ever notice that it's declared to be prophecy when?
After it occurs.
You notice?
Just after the moment, let's say, or shortly after.
So when these things that I discuss about the events that are coming, unless you really know as many specifics as you can glean, you won't see it coming at all as such.
You know, it's more surprising.
What's even more surprising is when these things start to take place and everyone just seems like it's normal, when you know it's coming and it comes, it's a total shock to you.
But it's not a shock because you were surprised, because no one else is.
You see, it's a shock because you're just astonished at how accurate prophecy is.
And very often one of the signs of a moron I always like to give is very simple, is where they say, well, how do you know?
Well, no one can know who wrote the Bible or that it's true or what truth is or anything like that.
That's a sign of a moron.
And I don't mean it's terminal because it could change, but at that moment the person who states those such things earnestly is an idiot or a moron.
Why?
Because Scripture actually defines itself and it proves, it self-states that the way you know that this is true is because you will get accurate information of what will happen, and when it happens you know it's true.
That's very simple.
So the way you prove these things is through prophecy.
And that's why I tell people, I assure you, if you're a Christian, you will not understand prophecy.
If you're a Muslim, you will not understand prophecy.
If you're Jewish, you will not understand prophecy.
That is an assurance, not a guarantee, meaning you could change.
But at this point you will not understand, comprehend it.
You might sound like you're comprehending it.
Big difference.
You see, it's the same thing with finances.
All these financial idiots you see on the Internet and other places, if you don't understand that the U.S. government is bankrupt and in receivership to the private bankers, you cannot make accurate financial predictions.
Now there are some that tout that they can, but they're not consistent, you see.
But once you understand the nature of the credit-based economy, that it's allotted for its people to operate because there's no money, you have to be given, like at a casino, chips, but you can't let them know that they have it.
Once you understand the dynamics behind that and all the deceit and all the unlawfulness, oh, now it's easy to make accurate financial predictions, see.
The same thing with medicine.
If you see someone, an old person with an oxygen tank walking around, you say, oh, you're going to die in six months to a year and a half from pneumonia.
Pretty easy.
Most of them will.
Why?
That's what happens when you put oxygen in the lungs directly, right?
It destroys the pleura.
Well, you know, the doctors don't know that.
I mean, well, eventually they will, you know.
You know, all these various things where, you know, someone gets a bad cut and they don't put pressure.
You know, oh, that's going to take you two weeks to heal.
It's going to leave a mark.
You know, I mean, what?
Because you know that body is under a vacuum.
If you don't understand the vacuum, biological vacuum, there's no way you're going to be able to make rapid healing and all this other stuff.
So there's just certain basic things that are what's called the crux of the matter, you know, where your perception and reality cross and you grab that point and you hold on to it and you use that as your reference.
But, again, just the simple mathematics that you see in Scripture can lead one, also with the simple instructions you see in Scripture can lead one to figuring out prophecy.
But also the Scripture in a way indirectly, I'll say this and I'll paraphrase, if you're a member of any religion, you're pretty censored.
If you profess with your own mouth to have allegiance to any religion, I'm not poaching and saying that if you do believe that you shouldn't do it.
I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying it's a very simple, I'd say more than a fact, the truth, that if you with your allegiance are a member, card-carrying member of one of these religions, you will not comprehend prophecy.
That's for sure.
It's interesting to see that.
They'll be given little pieces here and there.
And also what happens, another thing I like to say, is if you don't understand your condition or your place within the body of work that you're working on, when to slow down and when to speed up, and if you're constantly pushing, pushing, pushing, trying to do too much, you will be rewarded with error.
You want to prove that?
How many Internet sites you have with quote-unquote Christians or whatever talking about the end of the world?
And they give dates based on the Pope's calendar and all this.
You know what I'm talking about?
You see that all the time.
And they might have a little tidbit here that sounds right, but they keep pushing, pushing, pushing.
And what are they rewarded with?
Error.
You know, it's totally fine to say it's not time to discuss this right now.
And then there are certain things that you find out that there is no time.
Like, you know, the tattoo thing, I knew around 2003, 2004, I was sure of it in writing extensively about it and explaining it.
But up until 2000 and what they call 14 or 15, any time before that, you know, maybe even 16, I would say, no, I'm not going to discuss this publicly at all, ever, you know, at least up to this point.
And then I did that on the Freeman Second Hour, I think in 2016 or something.
Only then I was like, you know what, screw it, I'm going to do it now.
So I was holding on to that for over, what, let's see, 10 years, 13 years.
And if you knew me back in 2003 or 2004, you'd be like, oh, yeah, this guy's talking about, I don't see it.
I don't see everybody getting tattoos back then.
It's not my, you know, I'm just showing you how can this, how are you going to set up over, you know, six and a half billion people where a third of them are, you know, they just kill each other off for non-political reasons.
What's going to cause them to do that?
Well, you're going to have to find out things that are completely unacceptable, unacceptable in biblical law that is going to be applied.
Well, let's see what they are.
You see, very simple.
And what astounds me in a true astounding fashion is the accuracy of it.
I think that's what, you know, Sam and I, you know, even when he brings up like what's the population, you know, we're trying to find accuracy, aren't we, right?
What was the population?
I mean, what is population?
Well, we just start with the numbers first, right?
Well, what are the numbers?
Well, it's, you know, right?
Well, that's why, you know, we go around and, you know, the narrative is so whittled down.
I wouldn't say whittled down because maybe it was delivered that way, right, or should have been delivered the way.
Hopefully we're getting it the way that it was delivered.
It is such a minimal in terms of detail narrative, but yet it's so – it says so much with so little words, but then again there are complete aspects that are missing in detail.
Like if you go to prophecy, where's the iPhone in there?
Where is the man going to the moon or the airplane or the nuclear weapon, right?
And by the way, it's another thing.
You won't see any of that.
But a lot of people are mistaking, you know, the destruction of Babylon and Persia and other places in the end as nuclear.
That's wrong.
That's a wrong assumption, by the way, because you can drop as many nukes, dirty bombs, clean bombs, thermonuclear, atomic, any variety on any area.
It's pretty habitable almost, you know, a couple of weeks later, you know, a month or two later.
So it's not nuclear when you see these utter destructions.
So just keep that in the back of your head, because that's a typical Christian thing to say.
It's the nukes that are going to do it, you know.
Yeah, I think you're familiar with that, Sam, right?
Yeah.
You see a lot of writings about, you know, oh, it'll be destroyed because of nuclear.
You know, like no, no, that doesn't add up.
Yes, maybe if there's a new type of zero box or whatever, you know, device.
That's tech talk for a nuclear device called a zero box.
So, anyway, these things are big subjects, and they're easy to be distracted on when you're reading it from people that have been rewarded with error.
And so the first thing to determine is, are these people trying too hard?
And if they are, guess what?
They're probably being rewarded with error, erroneous information.
So, you know, hence the eating the corn out of you-know-what.
We had a question in chat.
And, by the way, that actually gives poop a bad name, because poop is not an error.
It's an actual determinant necessary biological function.
So, anyway, go ahead.
What's the question in chat?
Would you say the modern calendar is going to be done away with in the future?
Come on, man.
Yes, I would say so.
I wouldn't say done away with, but it's acknowledgement as the sole timepiece, yes.
Why did you say come on, man, Sam?
Because you've said that like a thousand times.
Oh, that's fine.
You have to realize that let's just – this is the hard part, because some things are just so big you could say, well, how can everybody miss it?
I assure you when I tell you this, and I've been saying it for a long time, the true nature of any biblical character, which is the Christ, the biblical Christ, is still a secret today.
The true nature, his purpose, what he looked like, what he did, what he said, all that is still a secret.
How could it be a secret?
There's religions formed around it.
There's Christmas cards.
There's movies.
How can it all be wrong?
I'm not making this up.
It is wrong, all of it.
But has it startled anyone?
Now, if you go out and start showing how it's all wrong and proving it, you know, based on what it's supposed to be based on, does it seem like it's going to shake anybody?
Nah.
That's why I keep saying this is unrehabilitatable.
No one can do anything.
That's why I'm saying if you see someone you know, or yourself, or you're in general just reading this really just screwed up stuff happening, don't take it personally.
I mean, in a way you can because the gods can exempt you from it.
But this is a planetary-wide setup, and you're being set up by the gods.
You think these people with all the ink and the same-sex marriages and the pork eaters and the banksters and the rabbis and all that know exactly what they're doing?
No.
They go by feeling.
Yeah, I mean, it's kind of hard to not take it personally.
I mean, you could get up one morning and say, I feel great, and then you run across the room and you stub your big toe on the kitchen chair, and you're like, oh, man, how are you feeling?
Oh, man, this is, you know, you're like, I thought you said you feel great a minute ago.
See how quick things change?
That's the normal way.
What I'm telling you, when this change comes, it's not going to be normal.
The people will still feel great even though they're being completely devastated.
That's an incredible stupor to put on them.
That's, you know, the Book of Daniel says the great falling away, and a lot of people are saying it's from the church and all that.
No, no, no, no, there is no falling away yet because they were never there to fall away from, you see.
You have to be somewhere at a point to fall away from it, right?
And what's being discussed in the Book of Daniel, that has not been achieved yet.
Again, you know, that's why I keep saying, if you subscribe to these religions, it doesn't matter which one, you will not comprehend prophecy at all.
It doesn't mean that some moron that's, you know, 80 years old that's been studying scripture for 50 years and says that his Christian doesn't have anything good at all.
Yeah, because that idiot was working for 50 years to find one nugget that you can validate.
Grab that if you recognize it.
You know, he spent his whole life on this one little myopic thing and he's incorrect about everything else.
Don't throw it away.
Take it and use it.
Because, you know, you're working on seeing the whole picture, you see.
So, I mean, artists get into this stuff.
I remember from even doing mural work in large stretchers and things.
I used to love going to one art supply place just for their stretchers.
They used really good wood and they did really good workmanship, you know, for the canvas and the frame and all that.
But I didn't like their brand of colors or paints or whatever.
I went to another place for that.
They had a much better price and better selection on certain colors and things, but their stretchers were lousy, right?
And then I went to another place.
I didn't like their stretchers or their paint, but they had really good brush selection, you see.
There's no one-stop shopping, right, when you're looking for the best outcome.
And there's no shopping here because I'm not selling anything.
But anyway, I had a private conversation recently about asking for donations.
And it's really for if you don't know what the potential of something is until you ask.
You know how many times you say, well, we didn't do anything because you didn't ask, right?
So if, for example, let's say the Greek asked for donations and, like, you know, six figures come in, well, right away it's like, okay, well, this is not cigarette and coffee money.
This is something you're being shown, resources are being put behind it,
where we need three or four people to start going through stuff
and producing a good body of work for the public at large, let's say,
or a larger audience, or, you know, putting whatever utility is available,
you know, websites, social media, art, books, even, you know,
physical brick-and-mortar type stuff, you know, and it's time to get going.
You see what I mean?
That's why you ask for donations and for that.
You never know.
Can you imagine, you know, we're doing this Greek speak, ask for donations, and in a month you get, you know, $100,000, right?
Well, it's come on, you know, and time to put it into, you know, the, what do you call it, all the stuff that you need to, you know, in other words, someone, something, some force is behind saying, look, you have all the wherewithal human resources, I mean not human as in human, but, you know, earthly resources to build on.
You have an edifice now to build, and you can put it out, right?
And that's, again, I want to just thank everyone who has contributed.
I'm good on my Old Testament stuff.
Just one more thing, then I think I'll call it a day.
The Leviathan, that's a whale, right?
Because people want to portray it like it's a sea serpent, and I'm not seeing that anywhere.
I'm seeing it like a big fish.
Yeah, Leviathan, let's see, Leviathan, Levianth, let's see how it would stand up.
You know, it could be even, yeah, the Lamed, Vanun.
When you look at that word, yeah, it's, but it's something prominent.
I would almost say that it's projecting.
It could be because the water that comes out of the breathing spout, or it had a horn.
Do you remember the old whales with the horn?
I think they still, don't they exist, Bruce, or anyone want to check on that?
Isn't there a whale that has this big horn on it, looks like a mast?
I see that in mythology.
I know on the top there would be a horn.
I'm not talking about a unicorn, or it could be the spout.
You see, whenever you see that Lamed, it means something that projects, you know, or shines, or a stick like the staff, or something that's projecting through the medium.
So if it's an astronomical body, it would mean light.
If it's water, it would be something that sticks out of the water.
If it's air, it would be moving the air in a narrow way, or something sticking out into the air.
There's a breed of fish called narwhal.
I can't think of any animal that behaves like that though.
Yeah, there's a narwhal, yeah.
It has a horn, doesn't it?
It's white or something?
Yeah.
How big are they, like, what, 10 meters or something, their biggest?
Medium-sized.
They're not huge.
Like three to four to five meters, I think.
Okay.
That's still a couple of tons.
Yeah.
Narwhal.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's where we get the Lamed.
So, you know, there was a 20-foot, you know, back in those days they had camels that were 20 feet tall, right?
I don't know about that.
Okay, yeah.
I shouldn't say it then.
Oh.
Yeah.
Where'd you get that?
Well, look at your archaeology.
And they're not as old.
They're telling you they're millions of years old.
They're not that old at all.
20 feet is two stories tall.
That's a lot of water, a lot of food.
A lot of food.
But I would say, when you say Leviathan, it would be, it's not a fish, right?
So it's a sea creature.
Well, yeah, it's a sea creature, but it's not this big serpent thing, like the Loch Ness Monster type thing.
No, a serpent would be a serpent.
Or a sea dragon type.
I think that scripture, sparse as it is, if it was a sea serpent, it wouldn't be difficult to render it as such in the language.
It's not a sea serpent, no.
A sea serpent would be gladly referenced in scripture if it was.
How many times, I mean, you know, the brazen, you know, serpents are everywhere, seemingly.
When they're there, you know it's a serpent, you know what I mean?
So I would suggest that a Leviathan is a sea creature with some prominent feature on it.
Identifiable as the horn, you know, the lower wall or the spout.
You know how a whale, when a whale is near surface, the breathing spout will shoot water up, you know, abruptly, you know?
We don't have any evidence that the fish that ate Jonah is a Leviathan or something like that.
No, no, I think there's a different term used for that.
It's just fish.
Yeah, it's just fish.
Dog, yeah.
Like a Liverpudlian accent for dog, yeah.
Dag.
Like daggone, right?
Now that's an interesting one, because...
Wait a minute, daggone, daggone, isn't that fish serpent?
Well, daggone was the name of...
No, I know, but if you look at the letters, isn't that then fish and serpent, like daggone?
Yeah, oh, and it's serpent, yeah.
Crawler, really?
Could be a lizard.
Do you know that the daggone god, have you ever done research on that, it was anthropomorphic?
Are you familiar with that?
Yeah, he's very famous.
I mean, he's the same one in the Greek, one that's Oannes or something.
Yeah, the river god.
Freshwater god, yeah.
But it's anthropomorphic, it's not a fish, like some people would say.
That's stupid.
Well, I know, but I just wanted to bring it up quickly and not dwell on it.
Stupid or not, I think filling in the details solidifies what we're talking about a little bit better.
No, but Jonah was interesting, because why would you send a prophet to a people that you didn't have any dealings with?
You send an army to people that you don't have dealings with, but you don't send a prophet, you know what I mean?
But you've said before that he, because when the Christ says that this 2,000 years is like Jonah and the fish, Three days, three nights.
But then the conclusion that you drew was that Jonah was dead in the fish.
But he's praying in the fish.
He is praying, but he's washed up and he looked dead when he came out, right?
But then he's not really dead.
No, he's not dead and resurrected, but there's a symbology there.
You know, the fish, you know, the sea is mankind.
You have animals within the sea, which are the animals that are given, you know, there are no pigs.
Are there pigs, sheep and dogs and goats in the sea?
No, you see, fish, you know, so, but there are, he's not in the sea, but he's in an animal of the sea.
So, but you know, one thing, by the way, that is always thrown aside, and I'd like to reread it again to get more of a perspective on it from, you know, just thinking about it, is in the end when he takes refuge under some vegetation, something that grows rapidly, and it's basically cast down or broken in front of him.
Do you remember that?
The very end of the Book of Jonah, that's always been overlooked as well.
As of any, in other words, it's been minimized on its significance.
It is a significant point that's also being made in the Book of Jonah, right?
That aspect I actually haven't looked at, but I will at some point.
Yeah, there are aspects to it that need to be examined.
I did at one point long ago, it hasn't really left enough of a, I didn't engage in an endeavor to really, you know, tie it into other things, but I think it deserves it because there's a profound dialogue going on or exchange going on there, you know, based on a desire, expectation, and then the expectation being fulfilled, but then it's destroyed, you see?
And it has to do with vegetation, you know.
I used to joke around that the jack-in-the-beanstalk is a metaphor that, you know, someone in dire straits and this thing grows up to the sky, even though it wasn't that big.
I'm just, you know, putting it out there.
It's interesting how you see things that, when expectations are, I guess, built up and then dwindled, you know.
I would suggest that any scriptural book, and that's what they are, you know, each titled book is a book in itself, requires further examination as we go into the future, and it sounds like cliche, well, of course it always requires further examination, but this time period coming now is unique.
Why?
Because some of the censorship is going to be lifted.
Take advantage of it.
Don't count on understanding scripture past the 2020s, when the world power changes and everyone is under the direction of this group of people.
Don't count on understanding it then.
By then you've already fallen for everything, you see?
So, in other words, let's just say it loosely, this seven-year period coming up is a pretty, it's a really good time to edify oneself.
If not, in many cases regarding some of the things that have been always difficult to comprehend, even from when the day they were delivered or given, that time period is now for these things to be understood.
So, it's like a once in a, what, 2500-year period coming right now.
We're in it.
So, we're just starting.
So, it could be really busy for some and, you know, really busy for some.
Yeah, I think I'm good for today.
Okay, good.
Anything else in chat before we go, Bruce?
Not really, no.
Okay, everybody probably fell out or it depends on what time zone they are.
It's really late.
Let's see what the screen looks like here.
We've got a bunch on there.
We're at 15.
Easily, easily.
Well, some interesting topics covered, no doubt.
No doubt.
Well, we're trying to keep it simple and not try to tie it into too much, but just talk about the cut and dried aspect of each topic that Sam brings up.
But I assure you that if you've listened to some of the Greek-speak stuff I've done, it's very easy, especially when I'm alone.
I can expand on how all these things connect into other things.
But why get into those connections if you don't understand what that thing is or have a grip on it, especially when we go back and suggest that anything you bring up from ancient times, most people's perception is just downright incorrect.
Why?
Because they've gotten it from television, basically, or Sunday school, or cartoons, or the worst one is probably school, university.
And the interesting thing, this is part of the censorship, by the way.
There's some people in academia, actually there's always been, but it's easier now with the Internet to witness it, that are very critical.
Well, they're not so critical, but they do explain how their colleagues are very critical about their work.
But they're okay with it.
They don't see that the whole institution is vile.
But they don't see that because if they did, they would leave it, and then they wouldn't have the resources to do the work that they're doing, you see.
Right?
So there are professors that say, yeah, my colleagues make fun of me or think I'm not doing the right thing, but they still stay there.
Because why?
The whole posture of the entire scenario is so they can use the resources of the university.
Whereas someone like myself, if I saw the university was coming up ahead a mile away, I would actually do a detour, so I would at least keep a mile away from it.
Because if I went up, if I saw it, it would make me physically sick.
You know what I mean?
So I'm way past the point of dealing with any of this crap with them.
I have to do it at a distance because I know what it's about and what it represents.
But it doesn't mean that it doesn't have the resources to get the job done.
That's why I call it grunt work.
Another example I give is I get a lot of people give me a lot of, you know, they ask, you know, what do you think of this technological stuff?
And they give me the link, and it's MIT developing something.
And you see who's developing it.
It's a bunch of 18- and 20-year-olds.
I mean, you've got to be joking.
I'm not saying that 18- and 20-year-olds can't develop anything.
But this is the stuff they're putting in front of people.
And no one gets it.
What they're putting in front of you is we have a school.
You have to be extremely censored to believe what they teach.
And it's very expensive.
And these people are very young and inexperienced and uneducated.
And they're giving you the latest technology.
Yeah, right.
Sure they are.
And you're not.
Ninety-nine percent of these articles that I get about technological stuff that's coming never are realized.
You can go back 30 years.
You know?
Oh, look at this great development from MIT.
Do you get it?
Nope.
And you're not.
It's obvious why not.
It's bullshit.
See?
Not all of it, but most of it, yeah.
So much of it that it's almost worth ignoring.
Do you remember the iPhone?
It's a desperation in a way.
You know, we have to put something out there.
We have to, you know, no matter what it is.
Well, yes.
No, it's not.
They're desperate to make sure that they accommodate the current mindset.
Right.
Because the current people are morons, so they have to accommodate that.
And a moron doesn't take a lot of convincing, especially when you're discussing stuff in their own mindset.
You're not taking them out of their realm.
You want to keep them in their realm.
Because taking them out of their realm.
Yeah.
And where do these people at MIT come from?
Alpha Centauri?
Mars?
Where do they come from?
Here.
It's the same crop.
You know, if you're in a potato farm and you leave a potato farm, what do you think you're going to leave with?
Potatoes.
Yeah.
You know?
But here is an example.
I think when Jobs was still alive in Apple, there was an article about the new phones that come out from Apple.
You won't have to charge them but once a month.
And I was like, yeah, that's great.
But I don't think it will come about.
And another year went by and they brought it up again.
And then what happened?
It got quashed.
And I said this is never going to come.
And at one point I said, oh, man, maybe it is.
And I said I can't because too many questions are raised.
People have too many devices other than phones and things that need recharging.
So then they would ask the question, why do I have to charge the iPhone once a month and these other things not?
What is really going on here?
And that would just turn the university system inside out from their bullshit electrons and protons and stuff that they teach everyone.
And voltage and current and Ohm's law and all that stuff, which only applies to a very limited aspect of reality.
So in a way my posture was they're never going to get this.
But I was doubtful because it kept coming up.
And then, of course, obviously you're not going to get it.
So one thing is when you do find out a certain mathematical reality, mathematical means, you know, I've got two eggs in the basket and I've got two in my hand and I put the two eggs in the basket.
Now how many eggs are in the basket?
Four, right?
Very simple.
It doesn't matter if it's eggs or birds or anything.
This is a mathematical reality, rational communication.
And I keep telling people you're never going to get this stuff.
And no matter how much they show to you that it's possible, you know, meaning the free energy, the batteries that charge once a month, and all this other stuff, because it just asks too many questions.
And then it snowballs and cascades into the rest of society, whatever else is going on.
It's only going to happen in regards to the gods, you know, that you have to have the majority of the people acknowledge the gods are real and the gods are the source of creation.
And the gods are where you get your law from.
And then, boom, now you're ready for decapitation, right?
That's why you ever see someone in a firing squad or, like, that furniture called an electric chair or a hangman, they read the conviction again right before the execution is done.
That's why it was written in Scripture, this will be preached, this healing message will be preached or this, you know, they call it the gospel will be preached to the whole world and then it will come back, right?
Well, if it ain't here, it ain't been preached.
Preaching just means to speak publicly, right?
So there's a lot of work to be done in the next seven years, tremendous amount.
And, by the way, you're not going to get it in alternative media or mainstream.
It's going to happen in a way that you won't be able to put your finger on it because it will come from all reaches, all parts of, you know, society.
You know, we'll see who they pick, the gods to start being the examples of the mindset change.
Interesting.
Yeah, and one way to do it is just ask for donations.
Like, no matter what you're doing, just ask for donations, right?
Yeah.
You ever heard you vote with your money, right?
Because you go to the mailbox, if you've been asking nothing there, well, guess what?
You ain't got no wherewithal from this society to do what you thought you wanted to do.
So shut up and sit down.
But let's say, you know, you invent, like, you know, some Barbie doll hair color thing, and you ask for donations, and you go to the mailbox, and there's a half a million bucks there.
Well, guess what?
The society is going to want to put their quote-unquote credit where their mouth is and back you up all the way for it.
You better do it now.
You're given everything that you need to do, the Barbie doll purple hair thing.
Right.
You see?
That's why you ask for wherewithal, and you shouldn't do it.
I mean, I shouldn't say it.
It should be done tastefully, and it should be done regularly just to see what kind of support.
How do you think these megachurches, you know, whatever they get, they invest in public works.
They're not interested in the money.
They're interested in the real estate value, by the way.
Yeah.
That's why, you know, they put it in public works projects, because when the thing goes down and the coffers are empty, they've got the real estate value to cash in on.
But how do they become megachurches?
They go around with a certain demographic and say whatever, and the people support it, right?
And they each have their own shtick or character or anything.
In a university, forget about it.
It's not tuition.
It's a donation.
The university doesn't need your tuition to operate.
It's a credit-based economy.
There was a lady that got tenure as a professor, and they got her to raise money, and she raised like two or three times more than they needed, and they went to her later.
She needed some funding and said, we don't have any money for that.
I said, well, wait a second.
What about all the money I raised?
And they told her, just shut up.
I told her that if you do some research, the contract that you signed to join that university is a financial instrument.
They issued a QSIP number, and that was deposited through the state through their mutual fund system, and your entire salary for the next 20 years was derived from your own job application.
Ouch.
Yeah, and she started looking around, and they told her to shut up and go away.
But she's still there.
But, yeah.
She didn't fully confirm what I told her, but she could not deny that it was, and she said, I can't deny it because when I started going around asking what you brought up, they got very upset.
They didn't even tell her that's ridiculous.
They just got very upset.
Like, don't go there.
See, so when you go to university, that tuition is a donation.
They don't need any of that to pay anyone anything.
So anyway, so what I mean is people are supporting it, right?
That's why I keep saying if you want to know if there's any change in society, just drive by the schools.
If they're still full, no, there's no change.
But if you drive by the university and the schools and they're totally empty, no one's in there, you're like, uh-oh, big change, right, or churches or anything you gather people with.
If you see it flush and full, you know, nah, same stuff.
Once it becomes vacated, okay, that's it.
You know, selling people, even selling one of the Freeman things, if you want to change this country, don't vote, not a one-person vote.
You know what will happen?
Anyone in every government, local, federal, state, are all going to pack up and leave, and anyone can walk in and just sit down and declare themselves whatever, authority, whatever, because why?
Because if the people that are in government notice that no one voted, they say, uh-oh, they found out what we're doing, we better get out of here because the next thing is they're going to come for us now.
As long as people are voting and arguing and protesting, they're like, right on, guys, you're securing our position.
And this is from a secular.
Keep up the good work.
Yeah, this is the secular.
We know the gods are.
So the reason why people are not realizing it's so simple that they shouldn't vote is because they're censored.
It's not meant for it to happen like that.
It's very simple.
I remember growing up there used to be strikes, milk strikes, bread strikes, transit strikes, right?
But where are the strikes now?
None.
Stupid.
I probably haven't heard of one in probably five years.
And boycotts.
Boycotts were big.
Boycott this product.
Remember that?
Don't buy it.
What happened to that right now?
Huh?
Yeah.
That's right, because you're being set up.
Little news once in a while, pissy about this or that, but, you know, it's in, it's gone, next day, you know.
There's another thing, you know, the military, you know, I'm tired of hearing about them.
Not that you shouldn't have one, you should definitely have one, but it's so poor right now.
Go down to an Air Force base, that neighborhood, the surrounding shops support the Air Force base, right?
And I run into these guys all the time, anywhere from the enlisted guy up to, you know, high-level colonels.
And I ask them, it doesn't matter who they are, I say, when was the last time the U.S. declared war?
You know, in a conversation, I don't go up to them and say that, they think you're a nutcase, right?
And they always say, all of them, 9-11.
Oh.
Stupid.
Yeah.
And these are the people that get behind, you know, 5,000 horsepower, 10,000 horsepower jet, you know, and, yeah.
Right.
Pretty serious, got some serious problems on this planet.
Wow.
It doesn't matter what field you go, it's all around, you know, everything.
It's kind of hard not to take it personally.
I tell people, don't take it personally, you're being set up by the gods.
And if you're going to be set up, well, you know, might as well be the gods because you've got no excuse.
You know, if somebody else sets you up for something, you want to go after them, right?
Or complain or whatever.
But if the gods set you up, who are you going to go after and who are you going to complain to?
So don't take it personally, just man up and take it.
Pretty thorough.
All right.
So I think we're more than three hours for sure, right?
I think we're into the four easily.
We're coming up on the four for sure.
Sorry about that.
Nah.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's okay.
Anything else in chat?
Anything else?
Anyone else?
Thank yous and things like that.
No, I'm good.
Pretty much that.
Okay.
Well, let's just wrap it up.
For a really good job and very enlightened again.
Okay.
Well, that's good then.
All right.
Well, thanks, everyone, for listening.
We'll catch you next time.
Thanks, Sam.
No problem.
Thank you, Sam.
Thanks, Bruce.
All right.
Be well.