Okay Anyway you guys are ready Yeah, all right, so we are streaming correct We got everybody here Okay Oh and Sam just hit the Sam you just went on to the radio stream.
There you go I Was monitoring sorry, sorry, this is a prime time You know, what's interesting if you guys ever have any real Training on for radio or television I Went through a rigorous training program in other words Even today TV stations are set up that once you get that the full training on it They're fairly standard.
You can go
to any television station in the world and
operate it right and
When you do training there's at least ten dry runs that you do in
different demands before you actually
They actually put you on a hot seat, you know what I mean
Yeah, I mean actually if people have a television watchers, especially if you remember growing up and you did
Sometimes a mistake like a commercial will come on in the middle or or whatever, you know, right?
So I call it impeccable performance All right, so Let's start off with whatever let's let's get right into it Sam.
What do you think?
I could hear your keyboards really loud and clear That's okay, sorry, I won't be inviting any of you guys to a five-star restaurant anytime soon, so We go to this week we go to the Denny's and the and the yeah, that's okay You know you get thrown out of a place if you go to a Put couture or hood cuisine.
No, they're really snobbish.
They they want everyone to perform it.
Anyway, go ahead Yeah, it's just anything that you're saying that from experience.
Oh Yeah, I've watched it.
Oh, yeah.
No, I mean you've got thrown out No, actually, I haven't and if I had been I'd be honestly I'd have to tell you if I was asked and now I've never Have it's quite the opposite Yeah Enough with the put-downs like most people I like how commoners always view sharp criticism as put-downs You know, is that interesting?
I think it's interesting how people who are smarter for the smarter than their own good always couch their put-downs in
I've noticed very often like when you when you start dealing with the public at large on any subject
They are very quick to rush
At any kind of statement, you know that they don't like order as a put-down or whatever
Put them down
We don't know what it's not
It's just the criticism and the interesting thing about it is it shows you that the the order there's a caste system
Even in America, they call it the middle class, you know, well, you know, you know what I mean by a caste system
You don't marry out of your
social rank or order
All these other little petty things that people think are done away with in certain societies and they're not they're quite still there
They're just not discussed and they're just as evident
Where if you go to somewhere like India where they have a caste system where it's openly spoke to spoken of and discriminated as
as such in places in Europe and
Especially the States they think they've done away with it.
It's it's alive and well It's very true, which also I want to do I want to do a little comment by the way I stepped on you there but About the new Skype system and I had a comment someone.
I just recently I use a laptop for Skype and all that and see So if something happens, you know, this is I have like a call it the you know, the worldly laptop or whatever if anything happens I have no problem, you know shedding it and getting another machine for it but you know in terms of viruses and all that other stuff, but I noticed that the subjectivity of the in other words.
There's a lot of negative reviews on the new Skype What it is from the intention.
You see I believe
Given opinion that the world is so full of idiots that no one has enough
Critical thinking or objectivity to notice that it's crap except for some of the users, of course
But that's on one end of the overall picture, but I think on another end from a more insidious picture
I think if you're gonna see it being deliberately
Judged as a poor functioning version
it's to remove you from the reality of using Skype as being obscure and and sort of
Confusing and not clear so you get more directed to other things that are more clear you see
So so if you're playing a video game, you'll see that they're making video games more realistic
The fake reality, let's say the virtual reality
But the things that you use in your regular reality because Skype is really like a telephone communication thing
They try to obscure that so now you're obscuring your perception of what is real and what is not
So now you go over to the video game and that seems easier to use and more functional than things that are more practical
So there's an obfuscation of rationale here
You see I mean the same with the smartphones
I always say it the smartphones are bait whether it's knowing or unknowing what it can be objectified as by examining the society
Is it's it has this all smartphones have a subjective nature within their programs whether it's Apple or Android or whatever
Subject you to the type of thinking of a nine to twelve year old girl Western girl
Western female, let's say that is
What's up, why do you say where do you
because okay, I'll give you an example because
women and the female of the
Sex are much softer than the males
in not necessarily in
The the the veracity of content that they get into but just generally in appearance the way they speak, right?
You can always tell if it's a man or a woman or a young man or a young woman or a young girl or a young
boy, you know typically I mean
Anyway, they're typically softer
But in the sense if you've ever been around women long enough when they interact on their own, especially in the Western world social
Ways, they're very subjective to themselves meant to be a little bit more objective on the way they interact
Okay, that's why you have most fashion and most things in the marketing or a society product
Manufactured targeted towards who men or women?
Because they know the subjectivity if they could get into the subjectivity they have loyalty in that direction
That's why and the reason where it's a nine or twelve year old girl is obvious not
Throughout history, but this current nine to twelve year old mentality
Which by the way is what most adults have I've recently had conversations with certain academics and I had needed to
Focus on the transcript of what they were saying and it was no different than it would a nine or ten or twelve year old
Would say I just had an adult voice
so what they're doing with all these devices is
They're making them very subjective within that realm of like this is you could say well Greek.
That's your opinion
I like it
But I've been trying to objectify this for a while and that's what I've deduced it to if anyone has any other suggestions on
The subjectivity or the imposing nature of these the way these things are set up
I'm open for suggestions, but right now I see it as being
Just the ludicrousness of it all right, but I mean, I guess there's a two-fold aspect of that kind of a claim on one hand
You would present the thesis or the thrust of what you're asserting and then you would point to some evidence
So in the case of the telephone or the smartphone
What exactly is it about it that you feel is equivalent to something that is so subjective that a nine-year-old would resonate with it?
A nine-year-old nine to twelve year old female or woman or young girl.
I don't like using the term girl, but yeah I mean why not why not a six-year-old or 15 year old or whatever like At that point there is a light financial aspect to things where a six-year-old.
There's not a lot of financial aspects to it Like you'll put a sale in front of a nine or twelve year old where you won't put in front of a six-year-old in terms of commercial marketing You're not gonna if you see like for example commercial marketing of products that are for six year olds.
It's never it's never towards the
Child it's always towards the person who's going to purchase for the child, but between 9 and 12 years old
They start targeting the market
At that point that's the early
You know aspect of them the because all of this is for
It's for monetization and all these idiots in the alternative media always thought bring up my not always
But they often bring up monetization and none of them just like a common moron would ever ask.
How is it monetized?
They just don't care, right?
So I mean, here's another aspect of why the Skype program is so eludes any rationale really or it's gone, you know retro great hit from being more rational to less rational is Because they what they're telling you secretly perhaps is that we have monetized the shit out of this so much We've created more credits than we could use in a million years.
So screw you guys Hmm.
I mean there's so many Aspects to this that can be viewed once you comprehend the mechanisms If you don't comprehend what monetization means and how what credit is and how it's garnered how it's used in this society You know the other dual money system and you have a dual law system here Also, and what happens it what happens to a venue when everyone vacates that venue does it still exist?
It does exist but really functionally it doesn't like in the Western world and most of the world people have vacated the lawful money venue Does it not exist?
No it and really it doesn't because you can't get lawful money, but can you operate within that venue?
Yes, can you operate let's say In an objective way with any venue, even though it's been vacated, you know I sometimes ask the question is a room a room if nobody's in it Well, technically, yes architecturally.
Yes But if no one's ever been in a room or knows about it anymore, does it exist?
No, it's no longer really functioning, right?
You're talking about imagination People's imagination that doesn't exist.
Well, it's very often like I'll give you an example working
Let's say if you look at the architectural field
very often you have architects doing surveys and assessments of structures and
Sometimes when someone goes out to the field to assess the structure
It reveals more aspects of the structure than the inhabitants knew of
Even though they're living there so I never used that, you know, I never went into the attic, right?
I Never think of the attic.
I never went up there, you know, and the architect since he's tasked with observing the function I mean the entire venue or the building objectively will survey the attic just as much as any other room You see and we'll bring up certain useful things.
Oh, you know things that were up there things that could be used you see I I've been in situations like that.
For example where there were servant quarters that were used as storage rooms
right and
the people that were living in Park Avenue duplex never considered was since they didn't have service it was a
Not they weren't a full live-in and imagine a five-bedroom
seven bathroom apartment on Park Avenue
And not being really inhabited it was used just to it was in the family and they had there were servants quarters there
You know three full rooms, you know for sleeping and the and the large kitchen the galley kitchen that was always used for food preparation
Very tight quarters and then you walk into the where the master or living their main living areas were and they're very opulent
All right, so the idea was to assess this the entire square footage of the place and bring it up to let's say
1990s standards
You know what?
I mean?
Because by the 1990s if you had a structure that was built in the 1920s and you didn't do anything to it till 1990s It became a little overbearing you only had like one outlet if that in every room, right?
You know re-electrification upgrading the plumbing and all that So, you know you're going through space and you're like wow, you know There's a almost a thousand square feet of serving quarter servants quarters and you're never being used There were storage, you know used for storage, you know But and there were wet walls and very functional.
They didn't have much of a view but there could have been used for Actually what happened?
They they they ended up making those into secret rooms with hidden walls and all that type of stuff, you know for
I
Was just gonna get to that, but I shouldn't just let's just say the type of artwork that should that everyone thinks is only in
Museums, let's just say that I wonder who has the Mona Lisa for real
Well, I think I've mentioned this before when you guys go to the museum
And you see all these things that they tout to be that from the Masters classics or not
They're all replicas all of them
You know, I told this to someone once and he had just returned from the Louvre
He's like, you know, I didn't want to say anything, but I understood, you know
I stood behind these ropes and and right there as a masterpiece, you know painting that's worth
You know tens of hundreds of millions in the world market
and all I had to do was go up with a razor blade or a spray paint and destroy it and I know that
Based on the way security and how obsessed they are about valuable things and keeping them away from the public
That was not the real thing, but it looked like the real thing
You know the Rembrandts the da Vinci's all that so that stuff is real anymore
They're putting out copies and the the
They're made they're being replicated.
I'll say it Most of the replicas for the past hundred years are being manufactured in what's known as the Czech Republic There's a couple of families that have been doing that kind of stuff for many generations.
They're the best at it and It's just not discussed.
So anyway, that's what I'm going to say about that So what we want to get on is Brewster, I think we're I'm showing to here I know Here I'm out.
I just let everyone know I'm outside About 10 meters from the house.
Let's say fully wired Wireless, so if there's anything in chat that pops up interesting Bruce Let us know if not other that you want to you have any kind of you want to go to some kind of agenda Sam You mentioned Yeah, we can go somewhere Maybe not Exactly what I mentioned we might get to that later depending.
Okay, because one of the
Good one of the things I wanted to do if we were going to get on that subject
I wanted to read the the private chat that you and I had an hour and a half ago about that
Just to let the people know the mindset of what we're talking about
But we'll do that later when it comes up or now it's up to you or not at all
Okay
Anyway, let's look at something that was mentioned before in chat, which is I thought was interesting
So at one point maybe two weeks ago or a week and a half ago
There was a drug shipment to the tune of around 400 million that was seized off the coast of Australia
that was coming from the US and
someone I'm familiar with gave some commentary to the indication that the captain of the seized ship would have probably been aware of it and
Would be culpable sort of in the underworld circles
The US government would buy it back from the Australians and that would lead to a bump in the Australian dollar in a few weeks
meaning that the Australian dollar would rise slightly because of the transaction to American money and
I
Will either that or lots of American notes would be pumped towards Australia to get the drugs back, right?
Now hold on before you continue if it if that if the Australians decide to keep it what's going to happen to the Australian dollar It's gonna go down initially, why Well spending no.
No, it has nothing to do with that because the relative exchange between the Australian dollar and the American dollar Stops, but the demand is there on the Australian side.
So their currency has to go down You see like if you've got something I want let's say and I keep making you offers and you keep saying no.
Well now I'm offering you more of the same More of what I have from of the same that you have which makes the stuff all of a sudden that I have less value Doesn't it?
You see how that works, but go ahead.
Just I didn't want it.
Oh, that was a partial statement I didn't want to give a full economics thing on that.
But good So the the Australians are going to be the the US are going to be asking for Australian dollars that they won't get No, the the the the old know the Australians are going to do nothing the Americans are going to make offers to the Australians with their dollars and the more the Australians say no the lower the The US dollar is worth Okay, and then the Australian dollar goes up.
That makes sense.
Correct, right?
That's how it works.
Okay, but but it's not a dollar It's a doll hair.
I Mean it's credit that you know, this is the thing everyone talks about the collapse of the dollar What does that mean?
No, all that means is that right now through culture tradition and just regular etiquette the companies that have first dibs on Transactions of bills of late in and you know big commercial transactions are all American based New York based companies That's all it means.
So when when they talk about going away from the dollar It just means they're not going to give preferential treatment to American based financial companies for the first initial Transaction because the first transaction is where you get the most monetization every time down that line.
It's it's watered down, right?
So that's all the American actually if they do that the currency here internally will raise but it's in Externally internationally, it'll be lower Because you have to you have to understand the concept of duplicity and everything right now, right?
You know, you know, there's two money systems.
There's two, you know, let's say that we talk about the gods You know when you when someone says God, I'm wondering are they talking about, you know, the God of this world and The King James or are they do they know the scriptures that are talking about the Most High?
You see there's a duality in every right even look.
It's basic words and someone says that's really nice now you're wondering For a moment in the context you have to re-evaluate the context in which is given Do they mean nice meaning foolish stupid senseless or they mean nice meaning pleasant and agreeable?
you see
So there's a duality
You have there in other words everything that's going on in the world right now
It's a blanket statement that holds fairly true is that it's on the irrational irrelevant fiat
What everyone is engaged inside or is it on the accurate objective real commute, you know communication of facts and figures side
And it's and when you're in it because
But not of it
You eventually, you know you you function in it, but then eventually, you know, you have to come out and say but you know
Listen guys, just stop for a moment.
I've been seeing your everybody's around me is engaged in bullshit for the past week Have you noticed what this really is what's going on?
You know just for a few minutes a week, you know, if you can do that You know, it's good for the good for the mind of the spirit, right?
It's like when you're at the beach all day in the water all day like hey guys Why don't we just take a half hour off because we're really soggy, you know So so the Latter aspect of this Drug process is that when the American government get their hands on the stuff again?
Then the DEA does what they they make it 40% bigger with some kind of lab cut so that they can yeah in other words, they have really high quality ingredients that they can insert in there that Perceptively doesn't change the quality that much.
It just makes it less effective less potent Mm-hmm But wouldn't they have already done that at some point in the supply chain So you know as if they would have gotten it pure It depends on where you are on the supply chain.
If you do it early on.
What does it do?
You know, you're trying to traffic a larger mass
Because you've done that
Well, they could have but I think usually it depends on where it was on the transaction
Okay, let me give you an example for example, let's say you have a drug that's one gram
You can hide it inside of the crease of a folded piece of paper
No one would ever see it
And if you drop that into one ton of just baby powder it turns that baby powder into a very powerful drug
You see that's very easy to traffic because you know, it's very easy to hide
But if you're going to move that one ton of baby powder with that drug in it
Then that's very easy to get caught you see
So what they want to do is they they want to get it in pure form the the key players
You know the ones that are behind it
Want to get it in its purest form as much as possible
Until it gets to the big money
Transaction first because you know when these drugs are being manufactured or these chemical substances
It doesn't cost much to it's all labor very labor and process intensive, right
Because they're extracts if you think about it, they're just extracts, right, you know when you go to the store and buy an extract
Especially all like the cocaine and the heroin which are extra plant extracts, right?
So if you've ever been around a place where extracts are produced, you know, they order let's say You know an entire bale of cloves to get a clove oil, you know a few milliliters of clove oil So if you're gonna manufacture the Opioid opiums and the cocaine all that other stuff you need crops fields and all that.
What does it take to work that right?
It's cheap labor.
It's very cheap.
Yeah.
Yeah, even and by any standard it's cheap and
Then it gets expensive or very time-consuming again not expensive
But time-consuming to get the extracts and once the extract is achieved whatever formula, you know, they want to do then that's what they move
But I'll tell you really since the beginning the even when the extract is created
They put at least 20 to 40 percent cut on it there the producer does
that's normal and
Then when it gets to the authorities of any countries, you know, if it goes to Turkey, it's the Turkish authorities
you know, the people are so
The the assertion of the free market which is the black market that's all it is when when any
Body politic.
I don't even like to use the word government government anymore or Authority whether it's a one that's suzerain, you know subject to another or whatever whenever they start regulating something and if they regulate something out of Existence, let's say in there in the open market that open market exerts itself through the black market you see Giving an example here.
I'm not this is not political but the Attorney General in the United States right now
They recently said that amidst, you know, all the
liberating of the legality of
Marijuana or pot and cannabis use and he says that he wants to impose the rule of law
And reverse all that but they know he never gives you a law because he can't he can't do that
Okay, all that if you know everyone's saying oh, he's done bad
But no one no one on the internet that I've looked at I spent about 10 minutes looking at it
The the issue no one says oh obviously this guy is dirty
The reason why he wants to crack down on the cannabis is because he has interest in the black market of it
See people don't understand that
so when you see an
official in any
Body politic pushing the banning of a substance that could be in the open market very simply
They don't have interest in your health or well-being at all.
It just shows that they are getting pressure to keep it In the black market because there's more money there So how many people are saying that the American Attorney General has interest in the black market?
That's why he's pushing you see no one I mean, it's like where are you?
Where is the anyway?
Do you see what I mean?
Yeah, it's so simple And it's it's good we're getting to the point now where I turn on most the media alternative and whatever it's all gibberish Yet the store the quote-unquote story, that's all it is gets through the mother goose stories that they tell everyone And they get through but there's no objectivity from its simplicity of what it is.
You know, what is the black market?
It is the open market reasserting itself after extreme regulation.
Is it not?
So What prohibition Right, and if you have an official that wants to change that in the austere Direction.
Well, obviously
He has interests in the black market, which is the reassertion at a much higher price, of course
You see
And it's like no
Just move anyone to sit back for a few minutes and say
You know how simple all this is
But what happens if the Australians decide to keep the drugs
Well, if they decide to keep it and the Americans then the Americans are going to be making offers to get it
Yeah
If they decide ultimately keep it then it's going to be a much slower change in them then at the money then it's all up
in the air
Then it's all up in the air.
You see depends on What I don't know enough about the parties in Australia But I would say it's it's they modeled it after the Americans how they would when they kept the substance Which is say how they were going to procure it Were they going to procure it domestically or send it back out?
Internationally again and that makes a difference again on their money, right?
Because now if they decide to keep it and then procure it internationally without now there
You can see the relationship between the Australian money and the other money again fluctuate you see
But if they decide to keep it for their domestic, well, then what will happen is the Americans are going to want to
Push the push the Australian value down as a sanction
Indirectly
All right
And that would include even if they destroy it because sometimes in Latin American countries the government would try to make some public relations
Pushed by burning marijuana and some big bonfire.
It doesn't really matter, but they'll try and show show off or whatever, right?
So if they destroy the troops, yeah Yeah, they don't do that.
Yeah
yeah, the
Here's the other thing about it whenever you discuss a topic like this you you have to
imagine that you're going to eliminate from your mind out of the audience 99.99% of the people on the planet when you discuss these
matters because
Most people think that these authorities are have their best interest and the legality and lawfulness or things are based on what they've been told
right
And and that's why you wipe away most of the people and also because they don't understand how the money system works
So that's what keeps all of this
You know what?
I'm talking about is basically on the level of card counting at blackjack table You know how casinos don't want a card counter because they say it's great, but it's not I mean you just understand how the hands work Right Right.
So what I'm discussing is the is the card counting and the you know
The statistical odds and high probabilities of what's going on based on how the money system is set up
you know the the the legal money system versus the lawful and
how these why these substances are the way they are and
Basically how dirty the people up top that run all the nations are they're all dirty
They wouldn't be there if they weren't that's just the nature
You know life on this earth right now
That's why when it always comes towards an election time for any country
I look and if I see crowds and multitudes and I said well
These are all morons all of them without exception every single one of them
Whether you like it or not, that's the objectivity of it.
It sounds might sound narcissistic and whatever, but that's you know tough Since you mentioned casinos What do you know about casinos because they have to be tied into the underworld pretty much as well Yeah, it's a show They tell you it's a show if you go there and win to see the house always wins, right?
That's the idea, but not always you could bust the house too.
There's the techniques on doing that But they won't pay you No, they don't pay you but you know what the IOU could be worth more than the actual payment if you go to their competitors But their competitors won't catch their check well, how do you know that?
Because what's it what's in it for them if they do that because that check is exactly that what is a check?
It's a financial instrument But they don't have the jurors.
It is it's not within their jurisdiction to do that
Not openly
Okay, we sure like to see it
You will get in other words if you get banned from one casino for that you're gonna gain fate tremendous favor from three others
But why won't they look at you, but it's a long
But on the other hand if you do if you bust them and don't do it in a in a way that it has the finesse
That would be required to be victorious.
Ultimately.
They could all ban you Just like the car just like the card counters at the blackjack table They when they find out your card counter, they you know, the security cam gets your mugshot You know They run it by the Attorney General who's in on all this stuff and they get all your personal details if you have stuff in The name in your name, right?
And then they pass it around to all the other casinos and they see if you're doing the same thing there
So there's two ways to the system, you know
You know, it's just like the legal system if you start saying well
I believe in the Constitution these guys and then they bring you into court
You start shouting a Constitution and try to defend yourself
They're gonna nail you in court
But if you go to court and you tell them what they're doing wrong, not what not defending yourself at all
Now the plaintiff that's a very different situation very different
Anyway
there's there's internal bets that are going on with these public defenders and
training of public defenders like for example ever heard of someone, you know, like rapes or
Murders someone and they arrest him in it, but then they let him out because of a legal technicality
Yeah, you heard that yeah, that's some someone on the inside playing game showing that the others look
you know if anybody finds out about this or show you how it works and we're gonna
you know show you that the court didn't do and the police didn't do and the attorney and the
Prosecutor didn't do all these things and they're like, what do you have to do?
Well, I have to let him go.
So let's just let him go just to show that that happens, right?
That's why you hear that something but when you go in unknowingly, they're not gonna tell you how to do it You have to know this already There's not there's other thing This is what in America has more prisoners than anyone in the world combined pretty close to or equals that right?
so the amount of prisoners are people in the what they call the justice system in The unit with the United States of America equals or exceeds or roughly are the same as all the other prisoners in the entire world combined Because why because if you ever listen to the inauguration speech of a the Bar Association president What's within the first 30 seconds of his speech?
What is he always say?
In order for a country to have a strong economy.
It has to have a strong legal system.
They always say that
Because they're charging you right stealing rocks from the moon
Running with a bucket of steam
Doesn't matter you see
So what I always say and this is the truth
There's no one sitting in prison or in any kind of probation or any kind of thing right now that at all in this country
That has been done legally or lawfully in the past 80 years not a one person and and you've got millions of them
That's another sign
To show you what's going on.
Yep, and there's and by the way Is there a silver bullet?
Nope, everything is different But is is the statement I just made true absolutely true without a doubt unequivocally true Is there are there any attorneys out there or judges that know the law?
No, they don't How do I know that because the moment they I should say know the law and use it The moment they know the law by definition and its entirety according to whatever case they have they are disbarred or off the off the bench So they have the they they're they have the appearance of law.
It's the same thing Are there any priests ministers pastors that know the Bible?
No, that's pretty clear right none of them do Because the minute they do then they they're no longer part.
They'll be exorcized from that organization You know, I mean, it's very soon.
Well, they'll just play dumb like Ernest O'Rourke Yeah Well that whole crew that entire crew Was always a young child sold if you if you look beyond what they hope procured You know what their wares were what they trafficked in All of them even the ones that survived today are very quote-unquote brainwashed by the American patriotism Like America's is great country.
The founding fathers were great.
Do you know what I mean?
They they don't know real history of the who they have a national allegiance to and part of that brainwashing is That if you do the right thing You will become Financially rewarded that's part of the brainwashing in America, right?
So what they started in there in their work?
They started noticing that if they did the right thing in its entirety, they'll be eating out of a garbage can and be dead broke So they had to hold on to the American value the perception of the subject matter that they were trafficking in Knowingly and I'm speaking this I shouldn't say I don't say it often.
I know people from the inside
that organization that have told me that
they did it because there was no way they were going to sell books and there was no way anyone would listen to them if
If they didn't use the quote-unquote Christian meme memes, even though they knew it was outwardly incorrect
So, right
It's just the attorney who stands up and gets publicity that says oh you have a Second Amendment right in this country
And he's and he always shows like, you know, he's for the rights of the people on this one thing, you know
But if you ask him about what does article 10 say about, you know
Jurisdiction and all this and what about things that have been repealed?
He doesn't know and doesn't want to go there at all Because if he does then they're gonna take his bar license away, right?
And then what he's gonna be used car salesman or a new car salesman
right
So
Unfortunately, you know, fortunately life is so short
But you won't have to relish and living in a society that doesn't appreciate the truth and honesty and all that stuff for so long
That you know, it's not like you're living three or four hundred years
You're sitting back and like shit, you know, I have to use the term Christian and Jesus and God
Otherwise, no one will listen to me.
Unfortunately, you're only gonna live to 70 or 80 and you could you know
Put up with it for that long, but most people think that that's the end of the world
that even with the short life that they have they need to hold back and say well, I
Have to say what they're used to even though it's actually an abomination just so I can you know get it through
On one hand, I think you said before that the cops the cops work for the Attorney General, right?
but But they're based out of the Treasury.
So which is it?
Okay the Well, exactly, which is it who runs the Federal Reserve the attorneys What Treasury?
What Treasury?
There's nothing in it.
They shouldn't call it a Treasury anymore Is it is is a Treasury a Treasury if there's no money in it?
That's a good another question.
Yeah, apparently it is But is it that the trade it's not that the Treasury doesn't exist Is that the ownership of the Treasury has been transferred to the to an outside institution, right?
But I
And the Constitution allows that it says it'd be bills
It was just I think it's article one or something our bills of credit and letters of credit are all federal
They're not by that's why the federal government went into a contract with the Federal Reserve with the 16th Amendment and not the states
so the actual fiat money system is
Lawful according to their Constitution which to me is a vile document
Why not because of the reading the entire contents, but because it was to establish justice
It's like saying let's just to us it would be no difference in saying to establish ballism or Satanism or whatever
But Satanism was already
Established through all the mainstream religions anyway, so yeah, so you got to look at these definite, you know, what's interesting still if you do
What does justice mean I'll show you how censored humanity still is on the inner on the
Internet you're gonna get it's all gonna be in positive light
there's might be a fraction of a tiny bit and I haven't done this in a while of someone maybe from a
sideband sort of way
Showing how the statue is, you know ancient whatever paganism or whatever, but no one is explaining that it is the revived goddess religion
That's how censored the you know humanity still is to that and how easy it is to grab their
Their allegiance into something that's just you know against them
It's astounding.
You know, there's still a you know, we should go over all the subjects one day That are just right in your face One day one day Yeah that that you you go on the rectangle, you know, the one, you know the warm rectangle that with the pixels on it, right?
And type it in any search anyway, you're not going to find anything about it still They can go through a list of a hundred items like that that are important Justice is one the biological vacuum in the body.
You know why your hands and fingers shrivel while they're in water right and prophecy timekeeping The list goes on and on and on and on a lot of the key points, you know, the the contrary direction of biological Heat and cold versus, you know heat and cold made from decomposition You know, they're opposite directions.
You know all these things.
It's amazing how there's no on the real serious stuff There's no discussion on the internet at all.
It's not even not even a website or a mention
Maybe it may be getting together and doing a website on all the things that
Missed all the obvious things that missed everyone that you can't find not one even to mention on the internet
Putting a site like that to go talk about being obscure to the morons
And in theory anything's possible
By the way, you guys have you know, what how many billions of pages and you happen to miss these salient points, huh?
Real real simple stuff It's planet Earth man By the way, I just wanted to also throw this in it's a dig on the alternative and mainstream is even worse When you look at a YouTube, you know where you have like, you know Completely Useless host and all they want to do is do they have content, you know That's what the thing is and they're looking for subs which are subscribers now, right?
I just this week learned this Over maybe half a dozen alternative and mainstream whatever sort of mainstream, you know I get a hundred thousand hits in a day kind of thing There the lingo is you know, there are the host, you know, and they want to give you good content, right?
So they're pretty useless
And they're looking for subs which are subscribers I was like subs is that but anyway, excuse the French term there
Anyway, and I look at the show in this and the guest which is even more clueless than the host or sounds like there's maybe
Less clueless I should say and then the icing on this entire
Shit pie is the comments from the people
Holy crap, so you've got a
Moron of a host idiot for a guest and just the rottenness crappy as possible
excuse for a human
Making comments and hundreds of them on
Them on it.
This is on either way.
It's looking on a moral level on an ethical level on a competency level
What the hell if you guys done
It was such a shock to notice that this week, you know on the quote-unquote YouTubes
Ridiculous shows with idiot hosts moron guests and the comments the audience
It just not even talk about poop with no corn in it
And there was one thing I had like 1,200 comments
I just scanned down real quick see if there's got to be almost like spinning the roulette wheel
I mean, I'm not gonna go through all 1,200 comments.
Let me just go through Randomly see all of it garbage This is what you guys are putting out on the internet as a representation of what you're doing on this planet Shameful Disgraceful You're on the ship, too So yeah, unfortunately, look I'll mop the deck all day.
Just don't invite me to your parties is what I'm saying
It's just garbage all of it and if anyone has anything that sounds relatively good
Send it to me now
There's some practical
aspects to it
Like how to brush your teeth tie your shoelaces like for example, I've always had an interest in looking up
Right, and I have an 8-inch very good mirror, you know
F12 speed f8 actually Dobsonian with really good eyepieces telescope and
I like looking around up in the sky and I know I'm not the only one looking and I will look on the internet to
See who else is finding interesting stuff and I have found a couple of people that have found some interesting stuff
But I just want to look at what I what is objective when you start looking at the rest of the stuff, too
it's just really garbage, but
from
From the practical sense how to drive a nail through wood
What can what are you?
What are you guys seeing up in the sky?
You know things like that.
Maybe how to bake a recipe of something but in terms of the academic social political religio Whatever YouTube's, you know all that stuff that the quote-unquote Absolute garbage from the host to the guest to the audience all throughout sad so sad Speaking of the credit system, I still don't understand.
How come no not not one Not a single third world country blows the whistle on the credit system if they're the ones getting raped the most Well The people that control the media and are controlling the credit system, they are not getting raped If the money system is so bad and the debt is so bad How come none of your politicians ever mention it in any capacity really?
They'll do some show trial your show hearing or whatever, but they know what's going on They're all broke.
See even when a third world see, okay, the problem with third world country is very simple They have a lot of babies and they don't It's very hard to get anything out of them.
So the birth certificate, you know, the initial banking financial instrument is not worth much So they have to get as many of those as possible because they have a very low value Right.
They have a lot of babies so it can't be worth much see initially.
It's worth a lot Initially when you go to a third world country and you put them under the you know, the credit system It's worth a lot because when you start getting the birth certificates Monetized you have very few initially, right?
So everybody gets all excited, you know, but they they they estimated that they have a low value by the demographic analysis, you see Thank you this Yeah, India.
I think they're either
Countries like India and China they're in your face
They're not like the Americans and the British which will lie
You know, they'll lie so bad that everyone gets used to it and then you know, it falls apart and then they complain
You see in India, they'll just tell you you're a piece of junk and we're gonna take cash away and just go about your you know
Doing what you're doing
You know
Where in England they lie to you in America of in America right now
It's all a lie if you tell if you there's no truth at all
If you because very simple they've been steeped in so many lies that if you give them the truth
It'll sound like a foreign language.
If you string together a thought that is truthful in America It won't be understood.
You might as well speak in Mandarin Because it won't you know, it's it will it will resonate in it such an unusual way that they won't be able to hear it It doesn't matter if it's in English or not or even American English You have to lie to them at this point because that's all they can resonate with.
That's all they can hear So that's too, you know, they're too far gone from that perspective But Things are moving along simply because it's a how do I call it biological necessity?
If you want to start a revolution or an uprising in America, very simple
Just cut off the sports games and hot dogs and junk food and you will have an uprising what you wouldn't believe
Because the people in America are just biologically dependent
all they do in America is manufacture enemies and
Manufacture terrorism and whatever that's all they manufacture
You know the rest of it is taken, you know, if they do any other manufacturing is just because it's already been in place
It's a it's a really sad
Society and not to compare the American society with the actual fixtures and geography that exists within it either
Because there's some beautiful features here, you know physical natural features, you know
But the society itself is just total crap
Mm-hmm.
Yeah Well, and here's the other thing if it was 30 or 50 years ago I wouldn't be here Clearly, I would but then with the reason why is because everything is being equalized right now.
That's not a cop-out.
It's I Constantly think about moving to another country or relocating and examining It's just the same crap is here because now it's everything is on a global level It just happened to be happens to be the worst here.
You see But there has to be an aspect of Censorship that's in place with the credit system as well because you can't have 150 third world countries and nobody blows the whistle.
Oh Yes, you can.
Let's see.
That's very easy to do I mean even like with like the Philippines like what's the point of the President coming out and being all antagonistic and dissing Obama, but he doesn't say anything about the credit system Right.
It's good cop bad cop.
It's a show
It's all just a show also what he doesn't know
He doesn't know a lot of people give too much credit to these people thinking that they know I assure you if you go to
the Bilderberg meeting
Even on one of their hottest secrecy greatest meetings and pulled these guys aside and asked them to explain the credit system to you
They won't be able to
No one there can
they'll be able to give you a little titbits of what they're aware of and how they're
What they're either in
Charge of investing their time and influence and influencing and in the you know, whatever industry they're in or
They'll know someone that knows something about how the overall system works, but they don't know
But I like I just said if you when these are geopolitical issues social issues financial issues
Go online and I dare you to find one commentator financial social anything.
That is not just total poop at this time
And they get in that you have to be able to see through the
The passion that they have there's a lot of people that come and scream their heads off and get pat
You know that just like yawning that's contagious, you know, you could put on
Any Pat an impassioned
What do you call it
Performance audio-visual whatever at any time and the audience will get ingrained into it
You know if the person is a is passionate about any subject
You know if you if you make yourself sit there and you know
Be influenced by it or allow yourself to be influenced by it
But look things are not this is not an urgent.
Oh, wow Greeks really opinionated tonight.
Well, it's not about that It's to say it was the same 20 years ago.
It's just that Sometimes when things don't change is When they is when they shock you the most, you know what I mean?
What a part of the censorship, by the way, if we go back to the very beginning in Genesis, you know the two trees I think we would discuss that several times loosely and Whatever and I've been threatened to get into more information about it or asked you or however One thing if you're going to walk away anything about those two trees in the in the early people that interacted with them is what?
Those trees are what?
I'm gonna answer it.
They are information based Yes, they're literal trees.
Yes.
They are symbolic of much Yes, they were on the prohibition list of one of them was yes, they were you know Okay, but what are they?
What are they?
How do they how do how do you interact with them through what their information based?
so No, well, yes, perhaps Speech might have been an aspect to it.
I wouldn't suggest that it was I would suggest there was a certain There's many ways to get an audible communication Let's just say right.
Yeah, we calls it a who?
Who told you that you were naked?
He calls it a who you can't who something that's not doesn't have a spirit So Well, it was the eventuality of the compilation of the information you get information and You know, someone says I saw and I heard it, but it didn't hit me till later What's going on?
Mm-hmm There's an eventuality to how we process things the same in the mind.
But what happened there was there was a Prohibition put on there.
So guess what started there?
cosmic censorship So it doesn't mean that you can't know and remember and acknowledge.
It just means that you're censored You know, it's it's a I like the I like the word in Greek for censorship.
You could look it up just put in a Translator Google or I think they offer translate I think or a dictionary put in censorship in English and see what the word is in Greek, it's logo crises Which literally means word crisis Indeed, and that's what's going on.
What's this thing?
Are you familiar with something called a wedding season a Rotting season or a wedding season wedding.
I could be pronouncing it wrong, but something seasons that sounds like wedding Well, like there's like four of them What's the source of that term?
I?
Think it's a past stream that you did, but I couldn't decipher though the audio Oh Rotting season could be that What is this?
Well, you have the the four seasons that are always in prominence, right?
Oh spring winter summer stuff, right?
and there's a fifth season that everyone experiences unbeknownst to As being called a season within itself because it's it comes you could come in any one of the others inserted and It's for example It's a rotting season.
It's where cuts don't heal that quickly
And even though the refrigerator is the same temperature all year round the milk seems to rot and spoil faster
right, like for example in north north
Western Europe it's in
The end of winter even though it's still cold out
People notice that or just before spring that things start to decay faster
So normally you'd keep let's say milk in the fridge for a week or two without
Souring but during the rotting season the milk will sour in three days
Even though it's it's still kept the same way
Where if you get a cut it doesn't heal for a week or two where before it would be three days
Right and you have strange things coming out like insects and larvae that you normally don't see and
You take them to scientists and they can't explain them there.
Well, then maybe it's this maybe it's that right I Can tell you in the American Southwest, it's it's in early fall.
I Could almost say there are two of them sometimes Oh, it's regular.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's regular.
Yeah an early fall, you know, it'd be the high You know in in the 40 degree centigrade hundred and ten Fahrenheit Fahrenheit and the milk doesn't spoil in the fridge for a week or two Come come that time Beginning fall late summer you buy milk three days later.
It's spoiled
It's cooling down now mind you outside
If you get a cut or something, it doesn't close up or heal as quickly more more likely for an animal or something to get an infection
Yeah, yeah, it's it's interesting I
You know, here's the thing, you know how give you another example of that
People are brought up in this very simple almost so simple that it's removed from reality
Especially what they call science, which is an absolute joke right now based because it's just so materialistic
You know the if you put they say if you have
Water that might have pathogens in it put chlorine in it, right?
Sodium hypochlorite right and that takes care of the pathogens and then you filter it out
Well, you know what they're not discussing is that yes, it kills a lot of the known pathogens
But those extreme conditions and that chlorine gives rise to a new
Pathogen that has not been classified or talked about by science because they can't explain it
See what happens is these morons in in science or academics or whatever?
They go for they get so haughty a haughty and proud with their accomplishments.
Then they hide The results of those accomplishments when they're shown to not be such You know what I mean is they'll they'll have pathogenic water everyone's crying for relief and I'll say oh put this Toxic this halite in your sodium hypochlorite in There and it'll kill the pathogens and they look at it.
Yay.
We killed all the pathogens You guys have been complaining about for 50 years And then you'll have some guy off in the corner who's got not you know Scientists or an engineer with not just one sharpened pencil on his pocket, but five and he'll say hey look guys Come here.
You know that water that we sterilize with sodium hypochlorite last week.
Look at all this other stuff growing in here What's that?
Oh, we don't know what that is.
Shut up and those pathogens are far more deadly than the other ones in a different way different veracity not always But they can be Does that make sense what I just said?
Yeah, but the fact that it's not identified.
How do we then?
Because it doesn't explain how an anti pathogenic
Chemical would lead rise to another level of pathogens that are not known never been cataloged never discussed
So we don't know what they do
No, you well here this is where you get into the real interesting research
We're now it's up to you to do high-level research
Just like for example when you look on there's certain people posted YouTube's with basic telescopes
Well, not I shouldn't say basic that are taking pictures of things on the moon that NASA has never shown that are clearly there
Anyone can see it if you follow instructions
or for example
How many times have you heard of?
Someone quote-unquote inventing or banging on something in their garage or living room that and then it's adapted into the market Maybe a decade or two decades later, but never in the beginning.
It's resisted, right?
You know, how many many computer companies and tech companies that were launched their?
footprint in industry started by someone banging around in a home shop many of them and How many of them were initially welcomed in almost none?
And because people have been so brainwashed when it comes to the quote-unquote scientific
Astrophysics by a lot biology know that they have completely surrendered
I should say mostly completely surrendered their power to research in that field to all the big institutions
You're not going to find too many people
I mean, I'm sure they do exist that have a microbiology set up in their garage to research these things.
Do they do you?
Because it's not trendy and if you do you'll actually be in trouble right because they understand how important it is to mess around with critters
You can mess around with little chips and software all you want and you know
Intermittent windshield wipers and this and that but once you start getting into the microbiology it scares the hell out of them
It's definitely frowned upon
Especially if you're granted a privilege of what they call a degree
Let's say you
You get a degree in psychiatry or psychology and all of a sudden you go into microbiology
Uh-uh, we gave you privileges in a degree to operate in psychiatry.
How dare you go and advance things in microbiology?
No, that's not your field No matter what you're doing if it's true or not, you see what I mean?
It's the same thing Like if you're let's say an electrical engineer and you end up being like a great artist the artist community say no He's just an electrical engineers artwork can't be good right What makes a great artist?
Anyway, I was having a discussion with someone
Recently about that and it's sort of like the Skype comment that I made earlier
What's interesting is when you look at a lot of modern art the reason why it's not pleasant
Yeah, the reason it's because they make it for their own community
Because they're you know, they no longer now that they've gotten so yeah, it is good
That's why I say you're was a Stanley Kubrick film full metal Jack.
You're about as ugly as a modern art masterpiece They're making it for their own community because now they you know, they've gotten away from what looks good.
So now they're into that perverted
They become desynthesized their aesthetics become desynthesized
It's like someone who likes sweets and they eat them off and eventually this is lost its sweetness
Now they need more sweet you see so what they're looking for is this perverse aesthetic to give them and what and it's only for their
Into it for the community of the critics
But they show it to the public and the public doesn't doesn't understand and of course most of the public
Morons are like well, I can't say what I understand it cuz then I'm you know, people don't think I'm stupid
So I have to say it looks interesting or I like it or something, you know
They don't understand that it's being done for the internal aspect of the critique of the critical
Community when they're so perverted at this point you see
It's the same with what's happening with computer stuff.
Eventually the geeks and the nerds that are designing this stuff They're designing it for themselves and then they force it upon you And if you don't have that geeky mindset, it punishes you for not having a geeky mindset you see Music music is the same.
Look at what the rappers have done There it gets more violent and more stupid.
Well, if you don't like it, then obviously it's not for you But but but it's prevent it but it ends up taking over the whole thing You know hip-hop music, you know, which is just been garbage for more than a decade now, I'd say 20 years Yeah 15 15.
Okay, let's split the decade Yeah, 10 years for sure 20 years.
It started 15 is pretty cool.
Pretty cool with me.
I Mean the art world and it suffers from a sort of white collapse of critical standards all around Unfortunately, what do you know?
It's interesting when you look at the Middle East that people want to talk shit about all they're crazy and they're violent
But in contrast to the Middle East the culture in the West
Is not really a serious business
Even though you know the average person thinks that it is they think that they're very heavily invested in music and arts and blah blah
Blah, but if it really was something that Westerners valued
They would have never relinquished that to the dictates of the elite classes and the corporations and the art societies
Whereas if you go or the perverts
Yes, the perverts because when you see perversion is in any field, you know, like a corruptor
Even a palate can be perverted or corrupt
I
Discuss the food also if you go to Midwest America
no matter how good the food looks it has no taste or flavor or it'll make you sick because they they're
corrupted and perverted from the Depression
Because they were they were so concerned about
Not running out of food again
They ended up taking all the fresh produce and making it putting it into storage and then eating it
So anyway, in other words storing the food took more precedent than the freshness of it
and then the you see so the same with the
With the art what when you have a wealthy person, let's say that wants to invest in art
Who does he go to before he buys it?
He goes to who a critic or in a set, right?
Or someone who's in the art field that critic, you know art historian.
That is also a critic and these people are Perverted yeah, I was saying about the Middle East if you go to the Middle East and you create the wrong kind of art there or Create some kind of a cultural projection that they don't agree with Obviously, they'll kill you.
It'll cost you your liberty or it'll cost you your life.
And the reason for that is because
on a certain level they understand that the purpose of art is to create a communication that acts as some kind of a mirror for
Individuals in society and a general repository of the human condition
That's why you can listen to 80s music and say all of this happened in the 80s
And this is an aesthetic of the 80s because it reflects that time and what people were thinking and believing
But um when you go to the Middle East and you try to create certain things like with Muhammad or whatever
The knee-jerk reaction is we don't agree with what you're saying about us when you do that.
So now we have to kill you That's what you're getting in the West and the West feed has a feedback loop to the East about that If I told you that most people and they don't really care about that, would you believe me?
I'm not asking you to but they don't We're in the east or in the West You know, I could tell you from first-hand experience from over meeting over a dozen Muslims you can insult their their religion their faith and they'll say yeah, you know, I It's important to believe in something and I know it's old stuff And the reason we still have it as people didn't have TV in those days.
So they had to have Something about Muhammad and I'm not I'm not saying they all say that but I would say maybe nine out of the ten or twelve or fifteen have said Same exact thing.
I'm sorry.
What's there?
What these are Western Easterners.
Yeah, these are well These are people you could say Western Easterners, but they're very well steeped in there came over here.
They speak English Exactly.
No, I mean you can't go to Yes Yes, you do you can but the political system the political system in Saudi Arabia Won't allow it.
There's a lot of people very upset not very upset, but they just accept it
Again, if you go to Saudi Arabia, let's do this experiment
I'll put it out to the world for anyone knows anyone Saudi Arabia start questioning don't insult immediately
But let's just say start pushing them to the point where it gets to the border that the borderline insult
They'll tell you well, we we have to have a religion
We have to have a faith because that's how people are and the reason we talk about it still it's because it's old and it
You know people didn't have TV back then.
That's why they invented that stuff.
And you know what?
They're pretty accurate
Well, my response is that would be in the event that that would happen and I feel like that's a very specialized case
You're saying the opposite
But if that does happen
It's only because that person at that moment in time when he's talking to you is not plugged into the hive mentality that would otherwise
Control him because as far as a collective you see people videos of people stoning other people that you know dressed inappropriately or
Burning people alive because they did this or that or this girl was seen walking down the street holding this guy's hand
so now the crowd has to
Ambush them or something, but you know what the same thing happens anywhere on that level
You know if you go in the backwoods of Kentucky
right
It's okay to be a drunk not just to be drunk, but to be a drunk to be a known
Alcoholic, it's okay
More than any other place let's say or there are many places you could find like that
Let's just give me I'm giving you an example on some there
But if you're a drunk and you start beating on your wife and kids for a long time
One of these days you're gonna go out to buy liquor, and you're never gonna come home.
You're never gonna make it home because the neighborhood and this surrounding community is gonna take care of it for yeah, and even if And the wife goes to share my husband's missing he'll say I'm sorry You know she'll be like yeah, I understand the community took care of it.
You know what I mean
You see so there are aspects like that deep little deep pockets
also
You ever heard the initiation and gangs are in order for gangs to maintain power
They just go out and do an act of abject cruelty just to remind everyone that they have the power to get away with it
I
Assure you the majority of the people that do get these stonings or or whatever that you do hear about are falsely accused
And it's a show of power a show of whatever whether it's influenced externally or internally why?
Why very simple because you if you bring that kind of attention to yourself you what have you just done You brought attention to it You know you ever heard like real up real power is unknown You know true power is unknown, so these are all theatre theatrical things there.
You know it's theater No, yeah, I'm not saying that they won't they don't go out You know if you go to let's say a quote-unquote Muslim country and say well this you know This is a gay guy or this guy.
Here's to drop the Quran on the floor, or she you know she's married And she kissed another guy Yeah, anywhere between three hours and 30 days.
You'll get a stoning or a beheading if you keep pushing it
You know I mean it depends on the location
depends on a lot of things
I've looked into that a while back when I decided that the there was no solution
Early in my studies when I found that
You know that history repeats itself stuff and all that
There's another level to it with prophecy and someone recently in chat mentioned well roots a repeat
I said yes, it is
But there are some new things that are going to be happening even scripture you ever remember some verses say I'm going to show you
a new thing now
You know forgot where it is and there you can look it up somewhere
Because I'm going to bring something completely new and this is in the Old Testament now
So I noticed that there is no solution in the stuff that the you know the satanic world
You know the regular human world the influence
In other words, there's no leader that you're going to elect.
That's going to make the country better There's no law that you're going to bring in or do away with it's going to make you better There's an inherent problem there, and it's a very deep spiritual problem And So you had to look at the the primacy of these of these things You look since you brought up the the Muslims.
Let's just say this very simply You know they have they have the paid the biblical patriarchs in high regard, right?
Whether they have them in accurate accuracy or not.
They do by lineage Biblically, they are descendants of Abraham through Hagar, right?
Yeah, okay period That's it Nobody's denying that yeah, so what you do is you follow that line down and into how it is today What were you know Here here, it's just this is a little scriptural now, right?
You have the most side that picks a certain people to get this message through
Okay
Through Abraham's descendants through his sister slash wife right which is an interesting concept
Okay, and
The message is
Given for lawful reasons because they have to tell you but it's also kept as a secret
To not too much attention so the people that it's given to are disliked by everyone
Because whenever you bring up the information the first thing that comes to people's minds is oh, that's that's
That's being held by those people that we don't like so because we don't like those people that message is no good
Do you see what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, so that's what's going on and it's been going on and it's very difficult to examine what I just said about They are descent of Ishmael right their descendants of Abraham also Why why isn't it examined from that point of view?
Why is it the Muslims and the Jews or Israelites have you seen that they don't understand or people don't understand the scope of?
What's going on here?
also
You know also how each nation has their God or jurisdiction of
The Most High set himself into a position as one of them in
in influence
Except for some exceptions like with Egypt and the Canaanites and then with Hezekiah later right with the battles how he protected them
right
so
Because this whole entire thing has to be played out on a sort of equal footing
You know this nation has this God this nation has this God Israel has this God right?
But it just so happens that the one you see think of that Israel has is the most high so so you can think of it this way When you have a father playing with a group of children a game, let's say a board game or a slip-and-slide Outdoor game merry-go-round.
I don't know hopscotch.
Whatever.
They call those the children things that they do You know Whatever.
He's not going to act in his full force and capacity You know when when they're at the jungle gym, let's say or whatever.
You know he's going to you know when they're playing Little League baseball He's going to act in the capacity that the children are he's not going to impose full force as an adult Otherwise he overcomes everything and nothing gets done right the game ends doesn't it?
Right so So there you have a situation of hierarchy here where when you're on this kiddie kiddie pool kiddie play park You don't come in like gangbusters you if you're going to play with the children you kind of do it loosely and you don't impose your entire being on them It's very simple.
I mean, I don't know why Well, I would say I don't know why these things aren't comprehended But I do know why very simply I talk about the censorship, and I talk about the you know who rules the planet It's in the air You know you don't explain that much.
What's in the air you know well think about it That's another important thing the nefesh the soul the breath is not only the inhaling exhaling But the entire metabolism is based on that right like you know if you if you if you let's say Pull if you ever go in an underground cave or whatever Let's say a gold mine.
That's very deep in the ground you need a co2 sensor and What happens is you?
Start slowing down you can actually suffocate you know the air quality is so low But you don't realize that you just you're you're thinking and your body slow down together You know what I mean so before you know it you'll take a step and pass out you didn't realize that God I think we're not getting enough air.
It's very gradual and It gets to a critical point You see, but if you keep the the body elevated and the mind goes down.
You know they're the you know There's a little contrast or vice versa If the mind goes up in the body goes on you see the Congress But when when you affect the the in soul in its entirety you know through the air Let's say through gases and other things chemically.
Let's say and you can slow down the mind in a formula
That's also slows down the body you relatively don't feel that you're being suffocated
Isn't that kind of like when you're walking in the desert and you
Pass out for lack of water, but you sort of don't see it coming
It just happens sort of unexpected expectedly if you don't
If you if you don't constantly acknowledge that you're thirsty, and you're you in other words
You get so thirsty that you get used to and forget that you're thirsty, and then you just pass out
Yeah, so
Connected to water isn't
Water is a main constituent in the brain
so
Yes, but in the terms of it is in the brain, and then you have this also this
Knowledge that water is
What was it mem mem means water as far as the memory?
It's connected to that so if you don't have a proper water intake or appropriate water intake does it affect your memory abilities Yeah, of course well, it's the processor it's just like for example the memory is not if you go to a picnic or Beach, and you see someone with a radio playing jazz It you think if you open it is a little jazz band in there.
There's memory.
There's music in there playing no
It's just receiving and transmitting
You see or receiving in this case so is the water important to receive that memory yes
Of course well, you know how they say the body's 70% water
That's fine, but if you take all the cells that you separate it out of a little water in the body
There are more than 70% water like 90% water
so the body is like
You know in general 70% water everyone agrees, but no it's more than 99% water
you can take bone out of a
Living creature and is there any water here most people say no, but if you actually
Compressed it you'll see it's about 10 or 20 percent water even the bone
Right and even you take all the water out of the body you have all this flesh
Well each cell in there contains water so that more than 70% so now the percentage ups
Very very high very very quickly
See and it's in a gel state I
Was explaining how the water takes on a gel state to one person and they you know watch someone
That's in their late 60s with various academic degrees and engineering field glaze over and tell you they don't understand it
They're not they didn't say you're wrong.
They just didn't understand it.
I'm like.
What do you know?
I'm speaking in like eighth grade science terms you see So this is the censorship.
Yeah, the thing is it's not the information is It's you know the vessel is the vessel going to accept it Are you if you try to put a five kilo load in a one kilo sack?
What happens?
You overflow the sack the rest is cannot be held or you can rupture the sack too, right?
Speaking of the air that was mentioned before there's this thin layer between the atmosphere and the terrorist fear.
What's that?
Well on the ground Yeah, there isn't a layer.
That's the vegetative layer where it predominates on the soil, but the vendors layers on the whole planet Yeah, the visually layers is big, but I'm talking about this this thin layer between the Atmosphere and the terrorist fear or the vegetative layer you mean on the ground level.
There's another one That's a high on the atmosphere before you get into the know that's the one I'm talking about the one that's higher Oh the one that's high up.
Well.
That's an interesting place.
You know you have various strata, right and
When you get to a certain point where the sunlight is created and
There's no longer darkness you see
When you go too far out everything gets dark
But when you start coming in you see the light again right when you're looking out right it turns the sky turns blue
That's like I call that that's where the that's the transmutation or the manufacturing layer
That's where nitrogen becomes oxygen and you know various
Materials are formed you know
Mmm.
Yeah, they call it the ionosphere You know like you know there is no such thing as an ozone layer what they're observing is the nitrogen imploding into oxygen Right and the energy that's released.
They're saying oh, that's not just regular oxygen compounds.
That's oh 304 which is ozone They're total idiots.
They don't that.
It's just the same with the the Sun they tell you that's you know Hydrogen becoming helium total morons.
Yeah, that's what their instruments read.
I mean
That's not what that's not what's happening at all
There's you know here's the other thing if you get into a comprehensive research on the Sun
I don't think you'll find it online, but you look around you'll see that
You know when they tell you the hydrogen is fusing into helium and all that
That's the cover story
You will find every element known and even some unknown elements that of course they don't discuss
I'm like those pathogens that are risen after the antipathogens are admitted
And there's there's all the elements are being produced out there
That's why very often
You've heard that all the elements are produced in the stars how many times you heard that scientific myth also
Oh, here's another thing with the schizophrenia with these academic idiots
They tell you that the precious metals on the earth form when the earth was formed
Which was stardust and all this crap, right?
And then you have another group in there that are acknowledging that there's bacteria and various forms of bacillus and things that create gold So which one is it was all the gold formed in outer space when the earth congealed all the gold elements, or is it?
also Bacteria that are forming gold because they're in within academia.
They acknowledge that there are gold is an organic byproduct, right?
So which one is it they never get together and say it's both so they're really schizophrenic, you know, imagine going to a schizophrenic person, let's say a dual personality and Discussing one aspect one of the personalities when he's in the state of the other personality.
How do you think that's gonna go?
Well, you think that's gonna go well Yeah, you also have this situation that I've read about in Norway and some other countries where you have these worms like things that Falling from the sky.
Yeah on occasion and they dissolve.
Yeah, is this from space?
Mm-hmm Hmm.
Yeah, it's all from space.
You know when you see your sprouts grow outside What did they say you need sunlight to make it grow?
Well without the sunlight while you could substitute it with you know grow lamps, let's say But you're even with a grow lamp you want to imitate the Sun So where does the Sun where does the sunlight come from from out there, doesn't it?
Yeah, there is an influence from out there that is assisting the manifestation, of course Believe it or not.
There's it's fortunately it's longitudinal and it goes through everything and you can't block it What the sunlight?
Mm-hmm Well, these academic morons are going underground and deep minds and they're trying to measure what nuance or what are they ones and What are those those neutrinos?
They go right through the earth.
They say particles, you know Anyway But the worms though, you can't just have worms falling from nothing.
Well, they're they look like worms What happens is they rain from the sky the scientists say that they were picked up by the wind from the ocean Yes on tornado or something.
Yeah, because that's plausible because they're you know near the water But when they hit the sidewalk or the roof or whatever in the in the sunlight comes out or the little time they dissolve into a liquid And they disappear So are they worms or are they just looking like worms?
They're looking like worms.
Okay.
Yeah here's an interesting thing there's a Couple of youtubes regarding chemistry.
I think I don't know which channel it is.
There's a couple of prolific ones meaning they they have Chemical basic chemical Explanate, you know explanations, right?
And they'll put a chemical in another chemical and this thing grows like lead crystals will grow out right now
If you look at the crystals growing it resembles a let's say a type of bush that grows out and in the highlands, you know
and if they do another chemical and
It produces a crystalline form that looks like a mesquite tree
They'll do another chemical reaction and it'll produce a crystal looks exactly like a blade of grass or a turf of grass growing
In other words, it's it's mimicking the plant world
Identical
Almost you can almost identify
What species of planted is just by looking at the crystalline forms in the chemical reaction to a specific plant?
And they're not making the connection That there is an archetype with these basic chemical reactions happening that resembles Something In nature, you know as a plant form or animal you animal forms, it's very difficult by the way They have something called a Pharaoh's serpent reaction.
Are you familiar with that?
Just put in a chemical Pharaoh serpent reaction, these are like old chemistry things.
I don't think they do them anymore but in schools there's a compound you put together and You light it and it's just like a little dab of this powder and it grows, you know A hundred or five hundred times its length.
It looks like a serpent coming out of the surface You know These are basic chemical reactions, but they they you know, that's maybe one where they lend a biological form to it It's the same one saying, you know, what are plants and trees?
They're just valves Just like you have a valve which regulates the flow of direction and and either turns or on a flow or turns off a flow Doesn't it?
With an archetype of geometry behind it you know imagine a Unity what's happening is there's a schizophrenic aspect to you all of the entitled classes and all your institutions right now You know, there's a lot of people talk about how the elites and whatever are controlling You know the schools and the media and this for their agenda Yeah, they do that.
But you're also what people are not picking up on
Is the schizophrenia one side of their own system will say it's this way and
the same system another side within it will say it's no it's this and
The duplicity just you know arises and it remains and it's just very casual
So not only are they moronic and censored they're schizophrenic which means a torn mind, you know
Duplicity and you'll find this in every field whether it's the legal system
Scientific the medical
Religious, of course
the religious tends to be the worst because they're put there I
Think I'll give an example years ago.
I used to go to these
What they call Bible studies both in the Judeo-christian
Realms I used to want to go see what they were telling the people in public
And this one was a messianic one, you know, which is Jews for Jesus type thing
I don't even like using that Jesus word
But and he was
The the guy leading the congregation
Was very passionate adamant about making the sermon about no matter what happens in your life
Everything that you do you have to call on God and Jesus to help you
All right, and he was adamant about this for about an hour
So as we were leaving I wanted to greet him because he kind of looked at me and it you know
I was a new person there.
Let's say and by the while people were exiting by the back door There was a sign that was about half a meter by half a meter and it said in case of an emergency call 9-1-1 Right, which is the emergency number, right?
And I said listen after how do you feel after that?
Yeah, I said to him, you know, basically I was interesting you were talking about no matter what happens you call on the the gods Basically, he says yes, you have to do that.
So how do you feel about this sign right here on?
On your building In your own space.
It says in case of emergency call 9-1-1.
How do you feel about that?
Isn't that contrary to what you've been saying for the past hour?
I mean you was staring at it from the stage and just say anything about that You see my point that's subtle but the hypocrisy and the duality and if you ask that moron Whoever it was a pastor or rabbi or whatever Outside of that show that he was putting on the sermon About something he would Do the 9-1-1 thing right away without a doubt.
Hmm.
I mean the duplicity and the duality is just You know, it's in your face Let's go back to the Paul and roll over the place but go to go to the politicians, right?
They all talk about making their country better again How many of them are bringing up the fact that their country is bankrupt and in receivership to the central banks?
How many none ever?
You could go look here.
I think it was Coolidge one of the president's Back around that time after the bankruptcy or before.
Oh I mean it there Yeah, it goes all the way back But not to get too far away from the other stuff you mentioned light so if light As far as the sunlight if light reproduces itself in a medium, why don't the rays just go on endlessly?
What rays?
They do The there's there's transverse, you know, I said what rays I mean, there's longitudinal and transverse aspects to it The sunlight is everywhere all the time But the sunlight that we discuss is not always all everywhere all the time because we're stuck in this transverse reality, right?
But I mean we were we were made to perceive it at this point Because if you were able to perceive and delve in the longitudinal guess where you're going to be You're gonna be in the realm of the gods, right?
No, but then we even so then we stick to the transverse aspect If you I don't know if you could call I mean obviously what comes out of the Sun is not the same thing that comes out of a flashlight But no what comes out of what you see what you perceive as the Sun only happens 150 miles up if that Outside of 150 or 200 miles up.
Do you don't perceive any Sun or stars or anything like that?
I'm not talking about perception.
The thing is there anyway It's just how it's a fact with you.
Yeah, it's effect is determined by your location in the universe but if I turn on a flashlight, that's that's a form of light and Those rays it seems to be visible at after a certain distance So why don't they just propagate endlessly since they're reproducing in the medium of air?
Because they're not keep reproducing because the initial source is a transverse source not a longitudinal source The flashlight is using a diode or a filament of a bulb or a flame or something That is all transverse from its from its inception.
But if you producing If you have a light form that has a longitudinal Production its energy can be measured in infinitum So by that There is in other words.
There is no there is a very minute if not Imperceptible longitudinal component within a battery-powered flashlight or a campfire Wait, our fire is fire a longitudinal source.
No transverse because it's chemical decomposition When you light a flashlight whether it's plugged into the wall or a battery.
Is that emitting what's called energy by chemical procreation and transmutation or by chemical decomposition The latter right the batteries run down everything gets hot right eventually the batteries stop cycling you have to change them, right?
That's all decomposition Do we have any example of something else that does longitudinal other than the Sun?
Mm-hmm your eyeball Is your eyeball degenerative or regenerative regenerative?
Constantly until even what happens is you have a preponderance of degenerative energy as you get older All right, but that is regenerate Regenerative energy is there till the moment you die?
That's why if you've ever been around people on their deathbed.
What's the first thing that goes is?
When they're you know, they're going to pass is their eyesight.
They can't see and they're hearing and Then their taste or not necessarily in that order But you know those things when you see that, you know, they they can't taste they can't see they can't hear Even though they're looking straight at you, right?
So when you say that there's a preponderance of degenerative energy is that Can that be tied to the idea of death as far as there's an entropic build-up?
Which eventually passes a threshold and then when it passes that threshold, that's when you die.
Oh like a natural causes so to speak Well, it's not that linear either.
There's an interesting thing if you understand a lot of the Taoist medicine the yin and yang concept You know, the yin is the life force It's a very subtle flowing field and the yang is another aspect of it which protects the yin Right.
Let's say for example Man is young and woman is yin Man protects woman woman is more subtle Softer more life-giving she bears the children you see so you have the yin and yang aspects So what happens is an interesting thing in Taoist medicine when people are let's say in hospice when they're dying.
They've losing all that yin and the last thing to go is the yang with which is the protective forceful aspect and I don't know how well this is documented But you can see this if you've been around it or have studied Taoist medicine is somewhat discussed loosely perhaps.
I hope it is What happens is when someone is before they die, you know, whatever, you know, the family is like, oh they're getting worse and worse But right before they die, whether it's an hour or two hours or a few minutes They sit up in bed and they seem totally fine.
They're speaking.
They're you know, full of energy.
They're emotional and That is the yang leaving the body and then right after that.
Boop.
They just drop dead and you know One of the symptoms of that that it all the yin has left and now the yang is leaving the body and they're going to die is Right before right what right before they sit up in bed and they seem everybody gets all this false.
Hope look they're fine Is they get this oil a very?
Very shiny sheen of oil on their skin it almost emerges immediately they almost look like they have a glossy tone on their skin and They sit up in bed and they're talking and they almost want to walk and they're greeting everyone totally lucid and then It's like a false.
Hope for the family and that's just the yang leaving the body and then once the yang leaves then they pass
so that's a Taoist
aspect of
I mean you're describing physical occurrences, but is he
the Taoist
underpinning
theory
No, no, it's a matter of fact
From a personal level I use it 90% of the time yin and yang yin is
expansive
smooth soft
Nurturing yang is contractive
hard
right
Like if you have too much yin food, you might have a yang manifestation
To balance it yin balances yang right black and white yin and yang
Hard and soft yin and yang hot and cold yin and yang
Now cold is very yin.
That's why when you're in the cold it makes you young to balance.
It's called balance, right?
Yeah If you study the Taoist medicine Now what happened at 30 years ago?
There was an influx of that in the Western culture Albeit an influx Some of it was accurate some of it was not now.
It's all gone now.
It's I would say the majority of what's been put out right now is was again hijacked by the new age movement They have no understanding of it The masters seem to have receded You know there was a there was an out an overt mastership interaction in the 50s to the 70s in the Western world and Eastern world.
I think it's all sort of in recession, but I shouldn't say completely There's some there's an aspect of the Taoist medicine in Asia Where they've actually set up clinics with modern technological devices where it never has done before but albeit a few you know They do some pretty amazing stuff.
I've seen there's a YouTube up on one where they a woman has an inoperable tumor and for these guys come in and They do some You know energy work on her.
It's very abrupt almost looks like a form of kung fu and
They have a sonogram on it to measure the tumor
You know its size and within three minutes the tumor reduces, and it's gone
We're right in front of the you know sonogram
All right, I think the videos about the ether and how it's real meaning you know the life force, right
But the Taoist principles
Even precede what's called Taoism
Right and they were actually used
Throughout the entire planet you know like Tai Chi
What Tai Chi Chuang we know the various?
You know how to manipulate the ether let's say or the life force every culture had an aspect of that But with the advent of you know the judeo-christian ethic and all that by What the 500 years ago was pretty much wiped out?
That's why you know China retained it from its xenophobia You know and I think you know with the advent of communism there.
They try to get rid of it also But somehow survived I Mean look here's something here's something really crazy Get a hollow metal tube, but configure it a certain way And you can change the weather right whether locally or long-range think about that all right, so What's the story about hikers in the 90s somewhere in Marlin County that saw a vision of some kind of a civil war or something?
After a power line blew or then they saw this like hole in the sky Yeah, that that things could happen.
You know here.
What's the primacy of that the gods, right?
Yeah, in a sense well, yeah, that's the primacy of everything so yeah exactly But I'm talking about the more you understand the gods well the science would be the material manifestation Explained you know how the material was manipulated.
Yeah
Now but I don't know what you call electricity or people call electricity has always been around just like the wheel has always been around
Sure all right, so those things affect
Reality when you when they're applied in extreme senses, you know
Yeah, I guess but but we can't actually break down why a blown power line would open up
Some kind of a portal or into some kind of a vision to some past event well
Can you explain you want to think about it?
Here's a term that might sound general?
But I assure you it's true with electricity could break down any element known.
You know you can break
Here's the here's the thing
This is one subject that is almost taboo to talk about because of the ignorance of it now
I mean even in academia the the whole field of atomic and nuclear physics physics you can meet
Every nuclear and atomic physicist in the world and only maybe about five or ten of them really know what's going on
Almost it almost sounds like the religious right you can meet every priest pastor and minister in the world and maybe five or ten know
the Bible right if that
What what you well people talk about nuclear or atomic those are electrical phenomenon
What in the field of dielectrics not induction, but dialect dielectricity?
not magnetic Tesla spoke about that You know with the advent of nuclear power.
He said that's nothing because he had reached the pinnacle of electrical research
or well at least you know within you know what what we know about and
He viewed the chemical source of that electrical discharge known as nuclear and atomic to be
Minuscule because they were focusing on the chemical side, and he's saying it's not chemical
You know actually if you actually understood electricity
You know he viewed nuclear reactions even in warfare to be he called it a consumptive infants breath
compared to capacitive discharge
Yeah
Speaking of which I just want to throw this in you know there's a company called nuclear demolition by the way
I think they're based out of Beverly Hills.
They're a functioning company.
They're actually a demolition company and They offer all phases of demolition services for the construction industry and they have this little little caption Even skyscrapers and tall buildings no matter how big they are we'll assess the safety issue we could bring it down cost-effective in just a few seconds We know What's that wink wink?
Right right that doesn't mean like you know what you're shown when you say nuclear
You know Hiroshima Nagasaki and the the atoll testings out in the Pacific no no
It's got to be deep underground or very at least you know the you know depending on how tall that you know the yield you
Know building in the yield it's got to be
That's why if you study nuclear devices you hear about all the testing done out and in the deserts here in America
They was mostly all underground
I'd say 90% of the nuclear devices that were blown in total
Were in the underground only 10% are atmospheric because they found out there was no use for them atmospherically
There's just a big flaw you're wasting all that energy
in the atmosphere
So there's very little knowledge of that field at all
That's why when you look at
The guys of what's called car bombs through the Middle East and through the world you know
If you look at eyewitness accounts, which are very rare as time goes by you know initially you have to get as much as possible
the people say
Typically, I'm just going to average out what people say when they see these car bombs and buildings blown up in the Middle East and all
over the world even in here in America
what the witnesses generally surmise say is
That they saw something that looked like an electrical event blue flashes and yellow flashes on the ground
and then this pink blue light that turned yellow surrounding the entire area emerged and
Then a fireball or then a very deep vibration in the building fell
Let me repeat that
When you read about these car bombs or these buildings being bombed or whatever where the Middle East or in America
Whatever the I the initial eyewitness accounts say it looks something
Electrical was shooting across the ground and then a pink and blue or yellow light came out of the ground just the light now
Right and the ground shook or then we saw the fireball
And everything came down now.
What was the last time you blew up CDX or c4 dynamite?
Underground or above the ground and you saw blue lightning flashes and then a light come out of the ground just pure light like a cloud of light and Then the explosion when when when does that ever happen with chemical high-speed chemical explosions?
Huh when never you know what I mean So and what I'm trying to say here is Not only is the public completely ignorant about atomics and what what how they're used They've actually up to like gen, you know level five or generation four or five or six and they're being used.
I would say consistently and no one knows what what they're you know, you you blow the face off of a building and You bring in an engineer.
They'll tell you it's a car bomb
Or truck bomb and you bring in any engineer
Even a new engineer or a seasoned engineer
From anywhere in the world and they will all tell you well that that took about
25,000 pounds of TNT to do that
right ten tons
Ten and a half tons of TNT now the the media tells you it was a car bomb now or a truck bomb
You know to have a truck that carries that much weight
Especially if it's like a milk truck or something they say or a Jeep.
Are you joking?
Do you know what?
Ten fifteen tons of material look like
huge
You see and they're getting away with that because people are ignorant
You know
The funny thing is when you they they do a building or something or a car bomb and you bring an engineer and they say
Oh, that was 40 tons of TNT
Or, you know 18 tons of CDX or whatever that did that and and they're telling you that it was a car bomb
How the hell are you gonna put that much?
It doesn't make any sense.
Does it what what is a car a whole baby quarter?
ton half ton maximum So there's no way it could have been conventional high-speed chemistry you see and this is being used consistently Throughout the world and no one knows it and the deal is a car bomb.
Yeah, whatever truck bomb Fertilizer, whatever.
That's what they say.
Everybody's like, yeah.
Yeah, you know why because even the nuclear physicists in the Universities don't know the properties of these devices or what the reactions are.
I think it sounds like Go to any Bible College or seminary and drill them on the Bible Do you think they know anything about it?
Or do they know a little bit about some, you know, the the seminary or the Bible College was under some religion They'll tell you a lot about the religion But they don't know much about the Bible at all.
I remember going to a
couple of Bible seminary curriculums and
There was no study on the Bible other than a little bit of the New Testament and one of
The courses was the book of John and it actually touted saying we're going to study and read the whole book of John
Wow
Then I saw another continuing education for pastors and ministers and all this
And they had all this study and you know, none of it was Bible reading was books about what other people wrote about their religion
None of it no Bible reading at all
You know as it as the whole thing or you'll see you'll I think Harvard has a course on
Genesis or chapters 17 through 25 or something like that or chapters 12 through whatever.
That's the whole course.
That's it Just a few chapters in Genesis in Harvard.
Do you get the picture?
Yeah It's a prank because if you went past the eighth grade we got you Now you're gonna have to pay for it.
Yeah, there's a lot going on that You'll behoove anyone