Acute generalism, right.
So hold on, I'm going to put in another so I can get this to fit if you guys need another power supply.
This headset, I'm about to go very mobile here.
Get it to work.
I'll try another one.
You guys still there?
We're good.
So, I wouldn't say, yeah, I wouldn't say that any of this stuff, you know the other thing with Fresco, you want to make the world a better place.
Big no-no, that's like a capital don't.
You can think it, but don't say it.
Right.
But at least he didn't suffer too badly from that.
It was, you know, so, but it was obvious that his idea would not be successful.
What a powerful event you put on last night there.
That was very tastefully done.
Oh, really?
Okay.
With Ocelli?
Yeah.
You did pack a lot of information in that little bit of time and it was amazing that you got that much in there.
Yeah, you packed a lot in there.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Did you hear it, Sam?
Some made it very well.
I'll listen later.
Yeah, the new motto is, why bother?
You know, Ocelli, I don't know.
At the end it says, what's your closing comment?
Why bother?
If you're hungry, turn this off and get something to eat, you know?
Right.
If you're tired, go to sleep.
If you need, you know, go get some socks.
The rest of it doesn't matter.
I mean, just pray for a quick and painless death.
I mean, once you're here, there's nothing else to really accomplish because you're going to die anyway.
Right.
So...
Yes, your cynicism is commendable.
Yes, and it's a planet full of, you know, reprehensible morons and that's it, you know?
And the rest of it, you can write it or read it anyhow you want.
You can make an action drama out of it, you know, like we're shipwrecked, right?
Or, you know, your spaceship has crashed and you can't get off.
Or you can make it a comedy, like Idiocracy, right?
Or you can make it like, what is it, Children of the City was that really dark city or something like that?
Dark European movies.
Right.
You could take that twist on it.
You could take Walt Disney's twist on it.
With, you know, Fantasia, whatever.
Or, you know, there's all these twists, but none of it matters.
None of it is going to make any impact.
You know what it really is?
It's who can and who will and who won't represent the intent of the gods.
Right?
So...
So how have you been keeping yourself there, Greek?
Oh, I'm just keeping to myself as usual.
Yeah, yeah.
Just doing okay.
Yeah.
Again, I mean, what can you do?
You're surrounded, right?
Right.
Well, it's like you brought up last night.
Who are you going to talk to?
You know, if you go back to the headhunters, you know.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Well, you can't talk with them.
You can talk at them.
Right.
That's about it.
And that could be challenging.
I mean, there's a lot of room for self-development with these kind of things.
You don't necessarily need to go looking for an audience or a compatriot in these endeavors.
Pursuing your own enlightenment is very edifying also.
Sure.
It's its own reward.
It always has been.
That's why you have secrets and secret groups and secret societies.
Right?
I mean, if something is so great, why don't you go tell everyone, right?
No.
When it gets really, really good, you stop telling people, you know.
It's like hidden treasure.
You find an old treasure map.
You're not going to go put the location on the public notice section of the newspaper.
True.
But the garbage, it doesn't matter.
The garbage everyone puts out on the street, right?
Right.
So, after a while, you start looking at what the desires and the actions don't match.
You know, people say what they want and what they would prefer, but their actions don't show that.
Their actions show that they want the worst crap, that they want stupidity.
They want, you know, through action.
Right?
Right.
Oh, well.
What with them?
Oh, yeah.
They're going to get it pretty good.
You'll see.
If you do.
I do remember the last time that I spoke with the topic.
The focus was less about scripture and more about examining certain sociological realities.
I think I put before the scenario to examine, and we talked about that a bit.
So, as much as scripture is always something to keep at the forefront of one's thoughts.
Lately, I found that contemplating certain social and political dimensions can also be interesting, and that requires some philosophical contention also.
I'm finding that you can't really just pull verses out of scriptures to easily explain everything.
Certain efforts that have been made by philosophers, whether it's Socrates or whether it's somebody more recent like Piaget, even if they have an incorrect meta-narrative that differs from scripture, there are still inroads to certain insights that are useful there.
Let me just throw something in for the listener also, whoever's listening.
Most ancient writs are there not to give you the rote, but to give you the exception to the rote, to show you the anomalies.
Anyone can study, whether philosophically or scientifically, which is really the same.
Philosophy is just metaphysics, the stuff that's difficult to measure, but yet can be contemplated.
Like emotion, like love, and anger, how can you measure that?
But if you look at, for example, the plants, it's very easy to determine that the dandelion plant is ruled by the planet Mars.
Pretty simple.
If you understand the cycles of Mars, you'll see that it matches the cycles of the dandelion plant precisely.
So all of these things that seem out of the norm are not.
The scripture and the ancient writs are there to show you what is out of the norm.
So when you look at political events and all that, those things are roughly set to the gods.
To them it's set, but to us it's not.
Like you were asking earlier, what about North and South Korea, so what about it?
If you don't know the history, then it's a mystery, right?
I think there's some wind blowing in the background.
Yeah, there is.
I'm going to move out of this breezeway.
I'm outside.
The other thing is, if you know history is bullshit because it looks too neatly packaged.
They say, well, this country invaded this one, this one won, and then this happened, and that's all bullshit.
Whenever you see that really neatly black and white stuff, there are no winners or losers in this realm, I should say.
We're all losers.
Oh yeah, if you're here, you're a loser.
I think I might have even said it on a sonic, in the future when others are born, either if you survive this or are resurrected, if there is any memory, there will be a gas that anyone had lived during this time, at anyone who had lived at this time, I should say.
That's very simple to rationalize.
Let me just put that in a little clearer perspective.
In the future, Satan will not be ruling man's society, and if you actually bring up that you had lived when Satan had ruled society, that would be the ghastly reaction.
You see?
Right?
That's in a nutshell, right?
Simple.
Except that he comes back later.
But anyway.
But not in the same capacity.
Well, he's given the same capacity, but the people do not become suzerain to him that way.
See, suzerain is just basically when you're controlled by someone else, but they give you enough that you think you're still free, right?
Like a colony that can pretty much do whatever they want, but they're still a colony.
Right.
Look, everyone is suzerain to the bankers right now.
Which are not even bankers.
So anyway.
Philosophy and politics.
Yeah, so I mean, I hear an echo.
Yeah, Bruce, do you hear that?
I hear myself coming right back to me as clear and as loud as I'm speaking.
I don't know.
It comes and goes.
Yeah.
So based in connection with what I was saying before, I feel like we kind of have two roads that we can take for the stream topic-wise in general.
We can stick to the mostly biblical slash political and miscellaneous questions about the natural world, as we usually do.
Or we can sort of go the route of analyzing some more thought experiments and philosophical musings.
I'll let the Greeks decide.
Okay.
Do both.
Because the gods don't view our natural world as being natural.
They view it as their art.
You know what I mean?
It's their creation.
Just like if you made a pot, you're a potter, or you're a carpenter and you made a chair.
You wouldn't view that as natural.
If you're a painter, you wouldn't view the painting as natural.
You know what I mean?
Do you get that sense of more than once removed from what's going on?
Yeah.
It makes sense.
They don't view it, yeah, what we call phenomena.
Like one thing I said with Ocelli last night, he was talking about science.
I was trying to say, well, art and science, they're very different.
Meaning, the scientist relies on his methodology to be repeatable, and the artist relies on his methodology to not be repeatable.
You know how many Mona Lisas are out there, right?
How many Rembrandts, right?
You see?
I mean, of course, there's a copy that you see in the museum, but essentially, when you show someone the Mona Lisa, it's not a repeatable.
And if it is repeatable, it is just a copy of a single event.
If a scientist says, well, this is one event, you know, it's a phenomenon, it can't be repeated, it's not considered scientific, right?
It's considered art.
Or pseudoscience.
And we're told in scripture, yeah, and we're told in scripture that all things repeat, right?
So scripture is scientific in that way.
But it's artistic in the sense that it's not exactly the same every time.
And here's the other thing, you know, there's many other ancient rites to discuss, if one wants to go down that path.
The reason I focus on scripture is because it's first class information.
It's got the most detail regarding science, time, history, right?
Yeah, the only reason I focus on it is because I haven't read the others yet.
And I don't know if I will, given that the scripture is quite vast.
Yeah, you won't be impressed, to put it that way.
You read the Koran, you're like, okay, I'm going from Syria to Syria, and there's nothing coherent here.
Of course, because it was written by a guy who self-professed, no, it wasn't written.
It was about a guy who self-professed, illiterate, uneducated, and his thoughts were written 150 years after he died.
So, of course, there's no, you know what I mean, nothing coherent there.
But you will find that the people that did write the Koran were very well-versed in the scripture.
So, you know, the biblical scripture, the Mosaic scriptures, and prophets.
And the only people that were well-versed back in those days, in an adamant fashion, were rabbis.
So, just put together what I said, now you know who wrote the Koran.
But, you know, the ones for hire, you know what I mean.
And they didn't survive.
Just like years ago, they said, go dig for this treasure, and we'll split it 50-50.
Once they dig it out, guess what happens to those guys.
Thank you for your service.
Thank you for your service, dead men don't talk.
Dead men don't need it.
I mean, this is, you know, but believe it or not, if you look at the descendants of the modern Islam, even in scripture there were people that were conned back then.
Think about it for a minute.
They've been conned from the beginning.
Think about it.
Do I need to cite that?
No.
Right?
Well, they've been conned by the gods.
Yeah, conned by the gods and other men.
Tricked.
There's treachery against them and all this.
And they go with it.
So.
And then, of course, when you talk about that part of the world, there is a very distinct part, you know, people call it the Middle East or Arabs and all that.
That's really limited.
Because the northern part of what we call the Middle East is very different from the southern part, which is like Saudi Arabia and all that.
And then the eastern part, which would be like Iran.
Right?
You know, like Iranians or Persians are not Arabic.
It's fighting words.
It's like calling an Austrian a German.
Or calling someone from Spain a Mexican.
They take offense to it.
Right?
It's funny.
Yeah, no, it's not.
This is the cult.
Like I was saying earlier, you put a Laotian, a Vietnamese, a Chinese, a Japanese and a Vietnamese in a room, guess who they're all going to be talking bad about?
Koreans.
All of them.
I'm not making this up.
Yeah, racism, bigotry, hate, all that stuff.
Yeah, it exists in the world, no matter how much they try to cover it up.
Well, let's go with some of the philosophical stuff.
I don't know how much we can do.
I think you'll probably make it so that it's both.
But I'll just focus on that because I think there's a lot to cover there.
So it's all very well to casually discuss how to perceive the condition of the world and our place in it.
But I found that most of the significant things have to be examined and addressed at the level of the details.
So you can't solely generalize or allegorize your way through an explanation or a solution.
Which is why I think some of our conversations see me bringing up certain questions over and over again in a rephrased manner.
And now I'm finally starting to create the thought experiment around them because it allows us to look at it a bit more meticulously.
But part of this sort of understanding or this mental exercise is to know that even though we know man society will crumble and placing stock in that is sort of worthless.
It doesn't mean that we shouldn't consider what the underlying axiomatic elements of human existence are.
Because I'm looking at that more and more and I'm like, oh, there are certain patterns in the spiritual that determine how things work on this side.
And that's been done, I think, for quite some time anyway by sociologists and psychologists and mythologists like Carl Jung and Eric Neumann and so on.
So for the sake of examining something like that, at times I find that one has to suspend the conclusion of the meta-narrative of humanity as explained in scripture.
So as to not be unnecessarily myopic.
Because sometimes I'll say stuff and you'll be like, oh, that doesn't matter because everybody's going to die anyway or something like that.
It's like we know that, OK, but we can keep that in the back of our heads.
But I think the thrust of this discourse is to gain an understanding of certain things like social being.
You're right, but let's backtrack.
You said axiomatic.
What axiom?
That's supposed to be things that are stationary or self-evident or maxim.
Most people don't know anything about anything.
What they profess to think they know about it is false.
So you have to establish the axiom first, which is in the paradox realm or the unknown realm.
In other words, the obvious is still unknown, so we don't really even need philosophy at this point.
How obvious is it that people don't know how the body works?
That's pretty obvious they don't know, once you do find out.
How obvious is it that they don't know history?
How obvious is it that they don't know what gravity is?
How obvious is it that they don't know what words mean?
So in order to establish an axiomatic principle, which means that these are things that are self-evident, what I see as being self-evident is stupidity.
Okay.
Sure.
But let me just say about that, you pointed to specific fields.
So yes, within those fields, there's a lot of ignorance that makes it hard to have a discussion.
What I'm talking about is the observable social reality.
So you can see how friendships work, you can see how families work, you can see how society works.
That's why I keep putting Jack Fresco stuff up.
Have you watched any of it?
Do you want me to give you an analogy or repeat it?
I did watch the video.
It's about headhunters.
It's a culture.
If you go to a headhunter and ask him, are you upset?
Does it bother you that you have five shrunken heads?
And he says, yes, as a matter of fact, it does.
My brother has 20.
Is there anything wrong with him?
No.
That's the culture you grew up in.
Does it bother you that you're doing a birthday cake?
No, it doesn't bother me.
Does it bother you that you're part of this religion?
Of course not.
What are you talking about?
Does it bother you?
No, that's fine.
I get that.
That's your culture.
Let's go back to the biblical stuff.
Does the scripture need to get into detail about why Joshua and others had to go in and kill all of the Canaanites or Philistines or whatever at any point?
Most people that don't know, they're like, oh, what a horrible God.
It can't be the same God as the New Testament.
Because, by the way, the New Testament is not full of love and all this stuff either.
I don't know where they get that.
Do you stand with me on that, or do you want to bring up a point that the New Testament is about love and friendly and all this stuff?
It's not.
At all.
But they think it's a different God.
Going back to the Israelites being commanded to destroy those cultures.
By the way, some of those cultures were not destroyed by the Israelites.
They were destroyed by the angelic beings.
If you read in Judges, they're female prophetesses, they're singing, look at all these evil people that the angels killed.
Didn't you see the angels killed them?
Remember those scriptures?
Anyway, to a modern, you're going to have to say, oh, the modern is going to see that and say, oh, that's terrible, it's a different God.
It's a God of wrath and bad God, kill all the society.
They don't know.
They don't know what was going on.
You see what I mean?
Now I understand that, and there's nothing objectionable.
Whether it's the flood or that, at any point, why do you take a car to the scrapyard to be compacted into a half a cubic meter brick of metal?
Because it's unrehabilitatable.
You can't fix it, you throw it away.
This was not a throwaway society, by the way.
If you can't fix it, in any society, it has to be discarded.
They were unfixable.
You see what I mean?
And it doesn't give the details directly, like, let's say I would, in a sonic, what those cultures were doing.
You see?
No, that's been talked about before.
That's all very fine.
It's understandable.
But back to the axiomatic element, I'm just talking about certain things being observable, and anybody can figure them out if you give them a little thought.
And they are there because they govern how society works, regardless of where you are on the planet.
Like a family relationship is still a family relationship, at a certain level, even if you, you know, abuse your children.
There are certain things that can be understood there.
That's there for strictly biological reasons.
If you read scripture, your real family is not your real family anyway.
Your spiritual family is not your biological, I should say.
No, I'm not talking about biological.
That's going to be, love, family, all that stuff is going to be redefined in the future, or defined in the future.
Okay, so let's progress with some of these thought experiments things.
I thought we'd start with something along the lines of looking at social being and hierarchies.
I think it's observable that one of the most fundamental questions for human beings is how to act in the world.
That is to say, how to be oriented morally, psychologically, culturally, and socially, all of which sort of links back to the idea that your law comes from your God.
But if we put...
That's part of the operating system.
You really don't have any choice from that.
Right.
But if we were to zone in a bit on the social phenomena at play here and what the implications are, we see that human beings fundamentally view the world through a narrative lens, not a scientific one which claims that all life is just physical matter, or a religious or cultural one, since those have to be bred into you by the environment.
The first-person viewpoint is a narrative one because human beings,
regardless of how atheistic some of them may say that they are,
are observably trying to gain an understanding of their place in the world
and how to craft the ideal society, how to act in relation to other people,
how to pursue goals and what the ideal way is to maintain ourselves across time,
as far as livelihood, health, family, that sort of thing.
So it's not just about each person surviving today and doing what they want, but you have to survive and live comfortably tomorrow, next week, next year and the next 50 years.
And your descendants have to do the same and everyone else in society as well.
Otherwise you don't have anything that's tenable in the long term.
Well, hold on, I'll stop you right there.
You can plan all you want, but if the gods decide to strike you down the moment you go out to pick up the paper and think everything is normal, that will happen, so you have to understand that aspect as well.
Yes, that is so.
Utter and complete rapid destruction can come upon a group, whether it's familial, community, national or worldwide in an instant, unbeknownst to them, with very short warning, direct warning.
In other words, they've been ignoring the long term warnings.
Yes, I should have prefaced by saying, if you put the gods aside just for a second, because we're looking at the social phenomenon, we're not looking at the metanarrative.
Hold on, let me go get a set of tweezers.
Mental, mental tweezing.
So I will preface everything I say from now on.
Mental tweezing, yes.
You know what I'm saying, it's like the old philosophical argument, the cafe setting, all the philosophers are in the corner wondering what the lady across the room is going to order, and I suggest we go ask her what she's going to order, and they all get upset because now they can't do their craft.
Yes, that is understood.
This is not on what you're saying, this is just where it's gone.
I think that philosophy is much better spent in the metaphysical realm, discussing the things that there are no measurements for at the moment, and how they could be discussed, they could be rationalized in a simple way where anyone can access the information.
I think we are going, I think we are trying to do that, or at least I'm trying to do that.
Of course it gets hard if we keep diverting into what the gods said, No, no, no, the gods didn't say, the gods do.
You know, I mean, yeah, it's what they do.
The thing is, you know, fortunately the gods do what they say, unlike men, so.
But go ahead.
So the question of how to, and I'm not saying that we're doing this, some of this stuff is just theoretical, the question of how to create a societal system that allows for the stuff that I just mentioned, like, for you to be able to iterate, so to speak, over a period of time, that's a question of social being.
And, you know, I'm not ignoring scripture completely, I'd like to see how that question is answered based on what scripture says.
So I'm going to come back to that, I just have to set up this stuff, and then we'll get back to the scripture.
No, no, go ahead.
But I'm guessing that if you want to be primary about it, then yes, you do have to look to the gods, because they run society.
By proxy.
Yes, I want to see what the Most High has to say about social being, because that's still something.
Maybe you'll get a chance to ask one of his angels later.
Sure.
I don't mean later tonight, but, you know, whatever.
So, to touch on the subject of...
By the way, let me just interject one more thing.
Of all the mischief, madness, and mayhem and evil you see in the world, later on it will be discovered that this was the most efficient way to accomplish the progression of the species, for lack of a better term.
So, in other words, we're probably amongst yourself or others, anyone having this type of conversation, or this subject matter, is going to want to strike through the reality of all the inefficiencies that we've been experiencing.
And I'm telling you, those inefficiencies are there for a reason, and I've discussed them before.
Which one of them is time?
How do you keep a society pretty much in a quiet enough state for them to hang around for 6,000 plus years, without being too knowledgeable, and also without being too unknowledgeable, where they make fatal mistakes all the time.
Basically, all they need to do is know how to rub two sticks together and make fire, know how to rub their genitalia together to make more babies.
Other than those two things, fire and making babies, that's basically the critical knowledge that a society needs to retain to maintain itself in a state of stupor for 6,000 years for curing.
You know what I mean?
Did that ruin their philosophy?
No, I'm just joking.
Rubbing genitalia and making fire.
I'll let you do that.
Think about it.
I've thought about this stuff before.
If you lose the ability to make fire, and lose the ability to rub your genitals, you have to start all over.
That's all, folks.
Right, because there's no fire.
Think about it.
No fire, forget it.
You won't even have agriculture without fire.
Why?
How are you going to do agriculture without fire?
I don't know.
Your implements.
You're going to cut wood with wood?
That doesn't work.
You need bronze, copper, metal.
Even the obsidian blades you get from volcanic glass to make knives and flint stones and all that stuff.
Guess how that was formed.
Anyway, go ahead.
Okay, so hierarchies.
We talked about that, I think, a bit before, but maybe this time I can finesse the topic a little bit more.
And this is kind of where I hope to get away from the allegories and more hands-on with observable reality.
So the last time we spoke, I offered up a sociological thought experiment about contrasting dominance hierarchies against competent structures and seeing which one is a bit more viable in the leadership model.
I postulated that most forms of power comes in two forms, the vertically imposed, the dominance hierarchy, which leverages the hard power of violence and money to enforce obedience, and then the laterally shared, which is sort of like a competence arrangement which strives for equilibrium among its members through voluntary agreements and meritocracy and can be iterated across time.
But I thought about things a little bit more and I admit that I might not fully understand the exact dynamics of the lateral stuff, and we talked about that as far as how things work in the world of the Elohim with the horizontal structures.
There might not be such a thing strictly, as I've said, because even in democracies, you eventually end up with a leader or whoever is the most charismatic or whatever.
So I'm just sort of entertaining that.
I'm going to interrupt you for a moment.
Put all the social-political subdivisions aside and consider how it would be done in what's called an anarchy.
Anarchy is castle doctrine.
Every man is the king of his castle.
Anarchy now has been, because of the modern Marxist and Engel movements of political templates, when you say anarchy, it's a bad thing.
Anarchy just means you don't have a king.
You don't have a president.
You don't have a centralized figure.
It's decentralized.
You see, for example, during the judges period in Scripture, that was an anarchy.
You didn't bother the judges.
You didn't look to the judges for what to do unless you were at war or you had a problem.
So how would an anarchy station all of those aspects of society?
See, that's something that the modern culture of headhunters can't contemplate.
It's too scary to give people the responsibility that they have to do the right thing.
If you don't do the right thing in anarchy, you will fall into chaos within a matter of days.
You know, like in anarchistic society, there's very little crime.
There's nothing to get away with.
What are you going to get away from yourself?
In every other type of society, it's what can I get away with?
And also to throw another thing in, is whenever you have a government that promotes people's involvement through secrecy, you're going to end up with a government that has nothing but secrecy working against you.
Like if you've ever studied history on King's Court, it's actually been dramatized in some film.
When a vote was going to be made, you told the people, you know, they would say this one and the people would shout or that one and the people would shout and the louder shout would be the vote.
Or they would say everyone on the left for this, everyone on the right for that and the crowd kind of intermixing and getting their positions so that you can see where the crowd is larger.
That was not done in secret.
That's not the type of voting that's being done now in secret.
So when they tell you you have a right to a secret, well then if the government gains its popularity through secrecy, well it's going to be operating in secret itself against you.
How many government secrets were there in scripture?
None.
How many government secrets in an anarchistic society?
Some of the benevolent monarchies, how many secrets do they have?
None.
You get it?
So right now we're looking at the big picture.
Hopefully this is not diverting you, right?
No.
So there's your axiom.
Or what axiom?
In other words, once you start changing a detail like that, the entire landscape becomes so different it's like the rainforest versus the North or South Pole.
Very radical difference in the landscape now.
So in other words, again let's go back, if you had the overt open society where everyone was responsible and there were no secrets, very different distribution of power and consideration of how power is going to be distributed versus one that is in secrecy with secret societies and intelligence agencies and secret this and secret that.
Very different distribution of power.
One is done through treachery, lies and deceit and the other one is done very slowly and carefully and overtly and benevolently.
Because you cannot, in an anarchism and benevolence within the society it won't last.
And when I say it won't last, I mean it won't last physically.
People will die and everything will be destroyed very quickly.
But the other one where you have secrets and deceit, secret societies, intelligence this and credit based economy, everything you have today, it can operate in the most maximum debauchery.
It can kick off and still keep going, you see.
There's no limit to how evil the society that is run like the societies you see on the planet today can be.
There's no limit to their evil.
Oh wait, now we're sounding like scripture again.
No, I was not trying to analyze the political system per se like democracy versus this or that.
Would you say that anarchy is lateral?
Yes, it has to be.
It has to be because you're not secretly casting a vote or empowering by limited decision for another to be a ruler.
Are you familiar with castle doctrine?
The owner, let's say, or the proprietor of a property.
Castle doctrine, a simple way to do it would be like the captain on a ship.
You know, he can marry people, he can have someone executed, right?
He's pretty much a sovereign within his range.
And he's only a sovereign not because he says so, it's because everyone around him says so.
You get it?
A king can claim he's a king all he wants.
He'll get his ass kicked in the next five minutes.
A king, socially, is if everyone around him acknowledges as such and is familiar with how royalty is treated.
Otherwise it doesn't matter.
Let's say you had King Edward go down to the headhunters.
They'd skin his ass just as fast as anybody else, wouldn't they?
It wouldn't matter.
A king could be skinned and his head shrunk just as fast.
They don't care.
Yes, it's interesting.
But, there is something to be said for the vertical hierarchy.
It does seem that this template of authority is the way of dealing with social being.
I mean, we see it in man society
at the level of the family
with the father at the top
directing his wife and children
generally or historically,
at the level of the corporate
with the CEO standing in contrast
to the fast food worker,
and at the level of the army
with the rigid chain of command
and so on, and even in broader
society with leaders at the top
and the masses at the bottom,
even though what you just outlined
is a bit different, obviously.
But we also see it in the animal kingdom from chimps to birds with one set of alpha males at the top and a decreasing progression of power from there.
So, there seems to be something about that hierarchy that is a primary aspect of humanity, social being, and it plays out when the top is there for a season.
Like the monkey or the ape or the dog or whatever that's up top is only when they're in their prime.
That's why, for example, they have term limits, right?
Yes.
So, they're only alpha animals when they're in their prime and then it's pretty obvious they either concede their position to another or they're taken out very quickly.
Yes, but to be replaced with the exact same structure.
Right, it doesn't have longevity though.
It doesn't have longevity with the individual, but the position is there.
The position is something that you can't un-graft, take out of the social order.
Right, and I mean, I think, like you see it in other configurations also, when you walk into a classroom, the chairs are set up to face the front.
You aren't expected to move them.
There's one teacher at the front of the class who faces the opposite direction so that everybody's looking at him.
There's no mutual expectations.
So, all things equal, no one goes into a classroom and starts moving chairs around because they want to face the window.
Those are things that are part of most people's procedural knowledge and they become a part of our expectations of society.
Yes, but that's industrial, institutional enterprise education, which is way down the line, hundreds of years if not a few decades down the line after you have the secret element put in.
Hospitals, prisons, and schools are all the same?
Yes.
So, there you go.
But we're talking about a social order that is separate of industrialization or not.
I mean, even if you're talking to yourself.
But it can't.
It can't.
The modern day, the way of the modern, everything is enterprise and industry now.
Masses.
No, but come on, if you're talking to a crowd, they're all going to face you if you're going to have a public meeting.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
I'm talking about the archetypical order.
I'm not talking about how So, you're just saying in a setting where one communicates to a group.
Yes.
There's a hierarchy that's established as far as where the focal point is and everybody that's under that that has to turn to that to listen because those are the mutual expectations.
Right.
And while they're listening, they're wondering when they're going to shut up so they could get up and tell everybody what they want anyway.
You know, be that as it may.
The order is still the order.
So, people don't act erratically or unpredictably because we share a map of cultural expectations that are built into our perception.
Unless you put enough fluoride and chlorine in the water, then they'll act predictably.
Even with that.
Anyway, so, what I want to know is this idea of the Elohim where vertical hierarchies are evidently being implemented in their social organization anyway.
You've expanded a bit on the existence of the horizontal structures but my response to that I think before was that we need to make a distinction where the vertical hierarchies end and the horizontal ones begin because the lowest grunt in the kingdom of the Elohim isn't looking at the most high as being laterally distant but rather vertically reachable.
This is maybe
If you look at how hierarchies function in practicality not in theory what you find is that at the top of the hierarchy is something that essentially no longer is a part of the hierarchy perhaps not literally but practically, yes.
You see this with renditions of the all-seeing eye on top of the pyramid.
At the top of the pyramid is something that is not ontologically part of the structure.
You also see it with monolithic governments and corporations where the grunts at the bottom for the most part they follow the rules but the higher up you go the more constraints and oversight lessens until you get to the top where the CEO doesn't pay any taxes embezzles all the funds pays himself huge bonuses sleeps with the secretaries and does insider trading.
So as a consequence of the dimensions doesn't that appear to be where the lateral aspect kicks in hypothetically?
Well, there's many things you brought up there like for example the all-seeing eye you've heard of the seven eyes it's a creature that he sends out I'm not looking for that I can't find it.
Or the eyes that he has
on the world
those are creatures
I sent them a month ago
I set them aside
they're easy to get
and that is a being in itself
that representation of the eye
on top of the pyramid
is a being within man's society
yeah, so of course
we'd be on top
and not paying any taxes
is totally fine
I'll give you a quick example
there's somebody
I don't and I don't intend
on paying taxes ever
because I'm not qualified
I'll tell you why
recently I saw some correspondence
with someone who has been doing
the Title 12 Section 411
demand for lawful money
and he was just wondering
if he was just going under the radar
or they were just leaving him alone
so he calls up the IRS
and he says
I'd like to schedule an audit
and they're like why
and I'm like well
I've been doing all my finances
and I need an additional endorsement
with Title 12 Section 411
demand for lawful money
the IRS says no
we're not going to audit you
no we're not
you get it
you know how people are threatened
with IRS audits all the time
oh my god they're going to use it
so what
if you're endorsing private credit
you're subject to it right
in other words
if you have blood all over the floor
contacting the IRS
and saying I want to be audited
by you guys
and they're like no
we don't want to audit you
do you see what I mean about taxes
where's your axiom there
I mean that's a psych thing
no it's not
and also by the way
this works in every country
I think I've discussed this before
reciprocity
all of your building codes
are reciprocated
by a worldwide governing body
so years ago each country
had its own building codes
now they've made it more
quote unquote universal
if you find a law
let's say you're in Scotland
or England or Spain
and you want to use an American law
well you could actually push
the issue of reciprocity
because an American passport
or an American license
or something like that
works well in Spain
anyway these things
they sound philosophical
I hope they're in line
with what we're talking about
no they're not
because we're talking about
the idea that you have
a vertical hierarchy
and at the top of the hierarchy
things start to become different
the closer you get to the top
because that's where all the power is
and people start to move along
different dimensions
so that's why the CEO
I was doing frequent talks
with Japanese engineers
in Malaysia and in Japan
I'm not going to mention
companies like Panasonic
Mitsubishi right
but what people don't understand
about the hierarchy there
I was realizing why some of the
real novel things we were bringing
to them were being refused
and we bypassed the engineers
and went to the CEO
but the CEO was totally afraid
of making any improvements
and we didn't understand that
because we always thought
well if you get to the CEO
that's the final word
executive decision
all you've got to do
is get that man to decide
and you've got it made
the company will do it
wrong
but people don't understand
in Japan
even though they have a CEO
the engineers have the power
of firing the CEO
if the engineers agree to it
that just renders them useless
and then why do you need
all these engineers
just to repeat myself
we thought bypassing them
going to the CEO would be better
he was even more closed
and more frightened of it
because we found out
well don't you think
that Steve Jobs could have
been fired again
I think he was
or he left the first time
he was fired
yeah but I think the key
word that you used there
was in Japan
you're talking about
a particular model
that existed a few decades ago
this is an exception
to the rule
generally
the model is what they
call 2008, 2009, 2010
I just gave it
it's still current
it may not be current now
but it's still
no I didn't say that
I said the companies
I won't mention
like Sony and Mitsubishi
Panasonic, Matsushita
there's a cultural element
in Japan
of certain formality
and rigidity
that we all know about
that makes things
almost claustrophobic socially
so we can't look at
the scale large enough
since when is taking
advantage of really stupid
people corrupt
look man
just using the dictionary
definition it's not a moral
judgment I don't care
but the point is
once you get to a certain
point people start to move
differently
so in the kingdom of the
Elohim
the God who's in charge
if I looked at the scale
it might not be like that
then I can see this sort of
what you're talking about
horizontal thing coming into
play
there's so many levels there
that it matches almost
the human society
would it sound believable
maybe it won't
that if I told you
if you met the God
that's in charge of grass
that you're completely
dumb to you
you wouldn't even notice
that there was any depth
or height or width
to the intelligence of this
creature it would be that
base
would you believe it
if I stated that almost
in a factual way
that the ones that are
more anthropomorphic in
nature from an intellectual
position are much much
more likely to recognize
a creature
like the God of the grass
because we're stuck in our
culture and our perception
that it has to have legs
and eyes and mouth
you could read about
biology in the 1930s
they went into some
caverns and they found
salamanders that had no
mouths and they were like
well how do they eat
well first they did all
these reports and no one
believed them right
that's the part I wanted
to bring up
when all these things
these creatures were
documented no one
believed them they had
to physically bring one
in for them to believe
that these things
existed because
can you imagine a creature
on this planet that
doesn't eat or has a mouth
right
no I mean you could
but if someone came
to you saying that this
is actual true in fact
that it exists you would
shake your head and say
no there has to be a
mistake somewhere
so that this is part of
the order right now
if you for people to
understand a lateral
kingdom of hierarchy
it's they're shaking
their head
no way
can't be
well well that's why
we're talking about it
you know I'm not asking
some scientist that
doesn't know shit
but okay so let's
look a little bit closer
at what lateral systems
are because I feel
like it is an oxymoron
almost to say lateral
hierarchy because
hierarchy seemed vertical
by design at least
intuitively
higher higher higher
means altar in Greece
a Greek word that means
altar or the central
part of a temple
hierarchy hierarchy
literally means
the altar of the
ancients or the
altar of the high
you know the
archos the head
yes like hero
hero means
hero means altar
that's why it's very
easy to use that word
altar in a metaphor
like you know if you
don't worship at their
altar they don't want
to speak to you right
academics
these are all religious
terms isn't that funny
anyway or
let's just say regarding
the gods
well first of all
hierarchies are of
course important because
they seem to exist at
the most fundamental
levels of perception
that is to say in the
realm of values
value systems manage
manage your perceptions
and your actions and
you can't look at
anything without a
hierarchy hold on
hold on value system
is based on two things
one is because you're
told it has value
or the other one is
because it's actual by
necessity
right if you have a
right
no two different things
like if you're told
something has value
which is I don't have to
give examples of that
you could look at this
society and look at how
worthless pretty much
everything is and they
think that certain things
have value
and yes it is used as
currency within their
society so if you're with
these morons yes
you're going to have to
operate as if it does
also
but then there's true
value like if you have
if you're starving
and you need bread
that bread has more
value than to a
baker
someone who has a
bakery
someone has a bakery
could say well this
bread here has got
finger
someone poked their
finger in all these
loaves let's just throw
them away
you know they don't
look good
very little value
right
and that's the
necessity side
and and like for
example gold and
silver was understood
to be the best
stuff from the land
and that did have
value wherever you
went
but now what they
consider to have
value has no value
even it's self
professed by the
authorities themselves
it's based on your
faith
you know they say
it's your full faith
and credit in the
economy meaning
they're telling you
it's whatever we
convince you of
because you know
people are incapable
of coming up with
rational decisions
on their own
that's why they have
to send them to
school
but anyway
no but I mean the
definition of value
doesn't change even
across those things
value is just simply
that which you
prioritize
the extent to which
you prioritize something
determines value
well hold on
prioritize on two
things
you have the
necessitative priority
which is my stomach
is growling and I
think I'm going to
die if I don't eat
in the next week
like I haven't eaten
in a week or two
already
that's why that bread
is very valuable to
me or the priority
could be well I'm
told that this green
paper has a lot of
value and actually
if you do that you're
going to be penalized
on the other side
right by the
taxation authorities
and all this other
stuff
sure sure
but I mean the
definition of priority
doesn't change even
across those two
things
but it does change
because one is taught
and one is
necessitative
if you're really
starving the bread
has a lot of value
but give you another
example on the other
side with the green
paper doesn't have any
value as a matter of
fact if there's a
small bank
any bank in the
world right now
if you go to a
small bank and make
a very large cash
deposit
and someone else
does the same
that bank will close
down because that
cash represents a
liability to them
where if it really
did have value like
gold or silver
if you went to a
bank a small bank
and people started
depositing a lot of
gold and silver in
that bank why would
it close down it's
actually the bank would
grow wouldn't it
you see
there's an article
I don't know if
someone wants to
find it
there's a bank in
Colorado
the story goes
thus this is in the
late 90s
you know all these
evangelists
so they collect all
this money from
people right
it turns out
this one guy
one of the evangelist's
son got into money
he was in accounting
and all that
he was also an
attorney and he
started going into
the basement of
these little churches
that are out through
Florida
northern Florida
which is really the
deep south right
and he noticed they
had all these plastic
tables open you know
like picnic temporary
tables with federal
reserve notes cash
money stacked up
piles high everywhere
you know and he was
like oh wow this
is great because I
know a guy in
Colorado who
has a bank he just
started and he could
probably use all this
cash so they got a
bunch of armored cars
and they went around
to half a dozen of
these churches that
they knew that they
were stockpiling all
this cash and they
shipped it up to
Colorado and these
are both young guys
and next week that
Colorado bank was
shut down by the
federal reserve and
the FDIC because it
had so much cash
deposited it
represented a
liability
I know it sounds
crazy right
to whom though
right to the I mean
if you printed this as
an article and to the
public they wouldn't
understand anything I
just said I mean they
would understand
everything I said but
they would not
comprehend why the
bank closed down
ultimately
it was a
liability to whom
the Fed
to the bank
of itself
the bank itself
yeah
that's why well
because yeah
the you know
think about it
how many canceled
checks on closed
accounts that you
are expected to
distribute can you
do before you're
shut down
cash money is a
canceled check on a
closed account it's
it's illegal as hell
just start searching
canceled checks on
closed accounts can
they be used in
commerce big fat
no
right
that's like going to
the pharmacist
thinking you got any
heroin for me
sure
right
what's wrong with the
coca-cola doesn't have
cocaine in it anymore
it's not can't be
any good
so
well the value
thing still remains
what it is in the
sense that you can't
look at anything
without a hierarchy
of value
because there's a
million things that
you could consider
at any one
given time or
place right the
reason why people
forget trivialities
like the color of
the walls and the
doctor's waiting room
is because who
cares some things
have no perceptible
emotional or
intellectual
significance so
in that sense I'm
trying to say that
hierarchies matter
because
hold on
system of value we
use
I'll interrupt again
the fast food
restaurants back in
the 70s and 80s
were having too
many crowds so
they figured if
they made like
pukishly putrid
ugly colors that
people would spend
less time in the
fast food restaurant
because they need
turnover and it
worked you remember
those days Bruce
when they went to
like hot pink
plastic chairs and
Kentucky fried chicken
and stuff
and some of the
chairs were rather
uncomfortable or they
turned the air
conditioning up in
the summer and it
was exquisite
and cold
and oh yeah
or the heat in the
summer and the air
conditioning in the
winter right
so that's what I
would do
just make it
uncomfortable
get your food down
and out
yeah
yeah but you keep
pulling up these
fringe things like
you know that
you know that if you
go into the waiting
room for your
doctor's appointment
or whatever
nobody cares about
trivialities like that
right
and if they do
it's
yeah the witch
doctors that I see
they got a mud floor
and a straw hut
raffia straw
hut
and they got the
you know
whatever
I'm just joking
I gave an analogy
recently
what would you do
if the doctor
the doctor will be
right with you
and here comes a guy
with a bone in his
nose and a face paint
what do you think
most people will do
they'll run right
what's the difference
you're trying to
tell me he's not a
doctor
see the value
sure
it's a culture
how many
how much value
does a shrunken
head have in this
culture
how much value
does a shrunken
head have in a
culture of
head hunters
think about that
the answer is not
obvious
it would have no
it would have
no value
in the head
hunters culture
because they got
plenty of them
it would have a lot
of value in this one
because it's rare
right
sure
the point is
just
like I'm just
trying to show
that vertical
hierarchies
are sort of
constant
in a way
that the lateral
thing
becomes a bit
of an anomaly
so like
on a different
level
applying
one's
energies
towards an
objective
for example
is one of the
most primary
mediums of
human age
you there
Bruce
or we just
lost
Sam
you there
you're speaking
and you
cut off
can you
hear me
yeah
it was
probably a
wire issue
now we
can't
10 seconds
ago we
stopped
oh
so what I was
saying is
that people
set goals
as one of
the most
fundamental
displays of
their agencies
I want
this
right
so I
moved from
point A
to point B
and generally
people are
assuming that
what they're
going to get
is better
than what
they have
whether that's
true or not
but in their
heads at least
that's how they
think
so any aim
towards a goal
is directed
upwards
but any aim
automatically
creates a
hierarchy
because if
people posit
an aim
like basketball
is great
or whatever
and I'm
going to
be good
at that
then everybody
who identifies
with that
goal
arrays themselves
in a
hierarchy
so
the
point is
you can't
eradicate
hierarchy
because that's
the result of
having values
in the first
place
so I don't
see
the same
type of
archetype
for lateral
goals
hierarchies
or lateral
systems
well hold on
within the
society
it usually
will not be
eradicated
the way you
eradicate
hierarchy is
by eradicating
that entire
society
yes which is
common
which is
Fresco talked
about it
for example
if you're
familiar with
the Venus
project he
was trying
to do
so how
do you
transition
he says
he can't
transition
this one has
to completely
collapse
it's going to be
very painful
for a while
I mean he
doesn't even
know scripture
he sees that
rationally
but I mean if
it does
collapse
what you're
left with
is
no hold on
and after the
collapse you
have to eradicate
the remaining
elements
because the
if you allow
the remaining
elements
to
proceed and
survive and
gain strength
they're just
going to rebuild
exactly what
they know
you get it
yes so
we're talking
about a
paradigm shift
into something
completely
different
that's why
very often
again I
know you
this is not
where you
wanted to
go
everything
that people
consider to
be normal
will be criminal
when the
gods rule the
planet
right
and you're
being shown
this right
now
there's oh
our privacy
is being invaded
well if you're
ruled by gods
you can have
any privacy
nope they
could read
you know what
you've written
and said
in private
they could
hear all that
they may not
be able to
read your mind
most of them
all right so
you're being shown
that right now
and a police state
oh the police state
well do you
think you're
going to have
something that
resembles a police
state of resurrected
angelic and
godlike beings are
ruling the planet
oh yeah
you're being shown
all these things
right now
AI
right oh yeah
this thing is
controlling oh
yeah do you
think you're
going to have
something like
AI when the
gods are ruling
not a machine
but actual
sentient beings
that act like AI
you know can do
trillions of
calculations per second
an infinite intelligence
and access to every
tide and everything
yeah
you're you
what you see
the complaints
and the concerns
of this current
society are
nothing but
a precursor or
a preview to
what's coming
when the god
the only difference
when the gods
were the planet
the only difference
is there it's
going to be
benevolent versus
malevolent
when you hear
lack of privacy
now it's
malevolent
intent
if you hear
you know police
state now it's
malevolent intent
on and on AI
now it's malevolent
intent but when
the gods are ruling
it's not going to
be malevolent
intent
so
just look around
you
let me just
interject another
thing this morning
I was out the
shops and
I was doing a
little bit of
talking and
one guy
this guy looked
at me and
he says so
all this stuff
one thing led
to another and
he's like well
it'll keep going
on I said no
it's not going
to keep going
on and I
got into a
lesson he got
roughly 14
years left
and he says
do you know
about the
biosphere
I said yeah
they built
this biosphere
and it was
closed off
from the earth
so do you
know why
they built
that back
in the
80s
and I was
like no
I thought it
was just an
experiment he
says no this
is because the
scientists were
saying we
only have 15
years left
until 1995
and we're
still here
basically
he's saying
so maybe
we don't
have 14
years left
I said but
yeah they
had no
what was
the reasoning
that they
gave we only
have 15
years left
in the 80s
because I
remember back
in the 70s
and 80s
on the
automobile
speedometers
they go in
miles per
hour
the 55
miles per
hour was
highlighted
in a
different
color
do you
remember that
Bruce
back in
those days
yes I
do
yeah
and the
reason why
they did
that with
the car
is because
of the
coming
to avert
the coming
ice age
because
they said
when you
drive at
55 you'll
be giving
off it's
the most
optimum
speed for
emissions
yeah
miles per
hour
which would
be like
80 or
75 kilometers
per hour
and they said
well the reason we
need to do that
is to avert
the coming
ice age
well what's
your reasoning
on that
opinion
you see
so all
of this
sounds valid
doesn't it
I mean
what's that
Bruce
the
ice
sheet
or something
like that
yeah you're
breaking up
real bad
something about
the ice
what about
sheets
yeah it
was the
breaking up
or the
shrinking
yeah
which is
stupid
yeah the
rising
let's say
if the
icebergs
melt the
oceans will
rise
I don't
know I
don't know
about that
because I
know that
water when
it's frozen
it expands
so did they
take account
for that
you know what
I mean
in other words
if you were to
melt
well in other words
if you melt
an iceberg
you're not going
to get the
volume of
water that
the iceberg
is it's going
to be less
right
anyone can
do this
experiment you
don't have to
be super
genius
I got a
chuckle out
of Sam
you saw that
right away
right Sam
that's so
funny
what's so
the obvious
that they don't
notice this
yeah they
don't they're
idiots
you know I
like to give
the analogy
with you know
back in the
late 1800s
early 1900s
the scientists
wrote peer
reviewed papers
on how
heavier than
air machine
flight is not
possible
but the Wright
brothers never
read any of those
peer reviewed
papers
you see
same with
electricity
if you want to
know how electricity
works you better
not read peer
reviewed papers
because if you do
you will never
find out how it
works
same with
magnetism
the same with
anything
you start
studying
whatever field
I was saying
on Ocelli
yesterday
all the fields
right now
law
legal
medicine
chemistry
physics
ancient writs
anything is
wide open to
anyone
because pretty much
everything that's out
there is BS
so
there you go
pretty raw
in other words
every day you have
an opportunity to
start
you know
new on the
real deal
versus the
bullshit
but there's so
much
what would you
say
if you were to
go the democratic
or consensus
route
that is the
resistance
not the actual
work needed to
expand the field
but what the
other people
in the society
think about what
you're doing to
expand the field
you see
that's why
this is a
completely criminal
society
it's much
safer to say
anyone you know
is a criminal
than to say that
maybe they are
and I'm telling you
they are
until they're proven
you can prove that
they're not
and it's going to be
very difficult
if you had to
defend them in the
court of the gods
you would lose
you know what I mean
this is how bad
it is right now
so
yes
well to
try to wrap up
on the lateral
hierarchy thing
because I did get some
insight into that
in the sense that
well maybe there isn't
enough of an example
in the current
society of that
to really
rationalize it
the way that I
want to
but
the idea of
the most high
god
imposing his
leadership
well his will
more or less
solely through
a vertical
dominance hierarchy
does feel a bit
unreasonable
which is why
I'm looking at the
lateral thing
because I would think
that the
I'm going to
stop you again
can the most high
god actually
impose his
will by
imposing that
he doesn't
impose
no
yes
in other words
there are
okay
spirits that
are working
against us
in a malevolent
nature
and if they
think that
he is
they are free
from his will
they're delusional
just like people
are
right
so
okay
put it this way
the
winner of the
war writes
history
what if the
winner of the
war wants to
actually write
history that
they lost
for sympathy
reasons
that's fine
right
okay what if the
most high god
says that
um
these guys are
rebelling against me
because he allows
it to
to suit a purpose
that cannot be
understood by them
or others at the
moment but he
sees it because he
has the wisdom
oh is that what you
were saying initially
then yeah
sure
that's fine
you see he has
that's why later on
you know people say
well you know
what about all the
you know what did
the baby that was
thrown in the
garbage can after
it was born what did
it do to deserve
what about all the
war what about
the poverty the
deceit i said well
you know later on
you'll find out this
was the most efficient
way to do this
efficient not
not uh
loving and
caring and
in the direct
attribute of what
you think loving and
caring is because
throwing a baby in
the garbage after
it's born is not
loving and caring
all the deceit and
war and hate and
hypocrisy and all
this is not loving
and caring and
caring the way you
think it is
but i'm not just
talking about the
physical world i'm
also talking about
how things work in
on the other side and
perhaps you know
maybe this is a
stretch but what
the ideal whatever
that means the
ideal way of running
things is i mean
would you say that
you know the
workings of the
physical let alone
the spiritual planes
of existence are
so you know
sufficiently complex
so that a
dominance hierarchy
i mean a
which is
would feel like an
insufficient means
of establishing
leadership priority
for something that
complex
yeah but when you
really are the
leader it's not a
priority to establish
it if you really are
the leader
you see in other
words if that
that leadership
position that you
have is empirical
versus ephemeral
which can change
you don't have to
establish it
well everything
needs enforcement
no one does
still has
also he doesn't
have to enforce
his position
no no he
doesn't
if you have a
bunch of rats in
a cage
whether they're
peaceful rats or
warring rats for
rabid rats as
long as they're in
that cage you
don't have to
enforce anything
else to control
them because they're
in a cage you
could pick up the
entire cage and
throw it in the
river or you
can know where
you put it and
let them out
yeah but you
put them in the
cage you enforce
the existence of
the cage in the
first place
yeah but it's based
on a high level of
efficiency once you
get them in the
cage you just set
it and forget it
you can walk away
all you need to do
is make sure they
get food and water
and the bottom
tray gets cleaned
out every so often
it's a high level of
efficiency that you
have to seek in
order to be in an
all-powerful position
it's all about
efficiency and
wisdom right
I worked with a
guy a long time
ago and he says
one of his sayings
was if you're not
efficient with
something God
takes it away from
you
we're not
talking about
typical western
moron doesn't
really know
if you ask him
to define the
gods he doesn't
know knowledge
but I think what
came through on that
is interesting
the combination of
efficiency
right
and don't think
when we speak of
the gods
it's very much
like you see
society
there are some
pretty dumb
gods by the
way
yeah yeah
sure
yeah
so
well we know
for sure
that one of
them is a
horrible military
tactician because
he knows he's going
to lose but he
still goes you
see
anyway
maybe he got
promised a really
sweet reward if he
loses I don't
know
yeah well we
don't know we
don't know a lot
because we lack
the maturity
again if you go to
a society
that's very
different from the
one you're in
you almost have to
introduce
one society to the
other and an
immature level
very childlike level
until they grow up
in the thought
you see
hmm
right
you know imagine
a society that
doesn't know
have electricity
you can't just
show them Las Vegas
lit up at night
I mean you could
but it doesn't make
any sense for
understanding
you'd have to
you know rub
you'd have to rub
a balloon or a
wool sweater
a little bit
you know keep
rubbing rubbing
rubbing and then
put it in your
piece of metal
you see a
spark jump
right you have
to show them
things that they
can relate to
first
no I get it
I mean
the only thing
I mean as a
as a concluding
note on the
lateral thing
you have
a being who
calls himself
the most high
he doesn't
call himself
the most
far away
or the most
hidden
anything
he establishes
a vertical
component right
from the beginning
yeah but hold on
we got that from
the prophets
right and the
prophets are men
right
and what kind
of a kingdom
do the men
realize
and acknowledge
and recognize
he doesn't call
himself
Elyon
well here's
the thing
everything that
we have from
the gods
has gotten
to us from
prophets
oh come on
if they're given
the word
it's not from
the prophet
sure it is
well no
it's given to
the prophet
they're communicating
to man
so they have to
communicate
within the terms
that man can
comprehend
I've gone
through this
before with why
the Christ is
considered the
son of God
alright if he's
the son who
is his mom's
you can't start
imposing
all this
minutia of
physical
man on
that
because then you're
going to start
drifting away
you're going to
have to force
reading into it
versus reading out
of it
the reason the
Christ is the
son of God
as I'm saying
in the common
western term
is because it's
of authority
no matter what
kind of an
organization you
form
and how long
you've been
forming that
organization
the moment you
have a
a son
when he reaches
age of maturity
he can take over
the
situation
even though the
people around him
were part of
the hierarchy
before he was
born
he just comes in
and bypasses
because he has
the first right
of inheritance
that's why he's
the son of God
in a human term
you see
but if you want
to push that
issue
well who is
his mom then
his dad
and then you're
trying to
now you're
walking out of
the communication
realm
and now you
want to form
not you
but form
in your image
make it in your
image
I used to give
more often
I haven't done
in a long time
the reason why
Moses
do you remember
why Moses
was buried
by angelic
beings
and his burial
location was
secret
do you remember
the reason why
actually no
I don't
really
yeah can anyone
Bruce can you find
that in scripture
there's a reason why
no
I know
that Satan
wanted it
well because if
they didn't
the people would
worship Moses
oh that I know
but
I mean there was
something even
under that
well there was
a battle over it
with Satan
Satan wanted to
expose it
because he wanted
us to look how
stupid these people
are to worship
another man
right
because he just
wants to make you
look bad
you know I mean
just think about
if you're against
someone you don't
have to directly
do anything
you just make them
look stupid
that's bad enough
right
no no well
you can suppose
that you know
but anyway there
was a battle
suppose not a
battle but
some kind of
adversarial
situation over
his body
right
in the
spiritual realm
right
and there was
a rebuke
that was the
final you know
part of the
dialogue that we
get right
all these
things you know
in other words
there's
you know a
little is good
more is not
necessarily better
you know
so you get
just enough to
flavor it
we get just
enough information
so that not
only is
the information
palatable but
it takes
taste good
but if you put
too much
flavoring now
it's no good
you see
hmm
that's funny
there's a
level of
maturity that
we lack
inherently
inherently means
from generation
to generation
you know
there are
certain things
whether you
regard evolution
or progress
of society
there's an
inherent level
of immaturity
in mankind
that not until
you go to the
next level
cosmically that
you know that
will not be
remedied
hmm
that's fine
we're just
trying to
that's why I
say
things
no that's
why I say
you can take
anyone from
any age
and bring
them to this
modern time
it'll only
take them a
few hours
or a few
days maximum
to adjust
it won't be
in any shock
at all
you know what
I mean
yeah I mean
that makes for a
good polemic
against mankind
in general
I don't know
if it's actually
true but
either way
well you could
well the thing
that would shock
them the most
would probably be
asphalt
how the hell
did you guys
put all this
black shit
everywhere on
the ground
you know what
I mean
that's not
you know
most people
would say oh
microwaves and
airplanes
no no no
they're going to
be totally
wigged out
by seeing all the
oil and gravel
and putrid
freaking asphalt
crap everywhere
you know
anyway
we can put the
lateral thing aside
but let's stay
with the
hierarchies for
a second
there does
seem to be
such a thing
you've mentioned
before as
archetypes of
existential reality
we see some of
this in the
writings of
you know
Joseph Campbell
with the
Hero's Journey
this concept that
underlays most
movies and comic
books and such
and you know
Carl Jung
talks about
some things
basically the
idea is that
mythology and
religious stories
however divergent
they are from
their source
material still
contain some
kind of a
blueprint for
how mankind
exists
right
but hold on
Joseph Campbell
was very
illiterate
in a broad
sense of
hold on
he was very
illiterate in a
broad sense of
comparative
he didn't know
anything about
scripture
what he thought
he knew out of
scripture was
out of Christianity
which is nothing
out of scripture
basically
out of context
you know
that's like
putting ketchup
on pasta
and calling it
tomato sauce
you know
he didn't know
he's pretty
illiterate
and also
the other thing
about Joseph Campbell
I got a lot of
beat bones
a lot of people
in the past two
decades have been
discussing Joseph
Campbell
looked at his
stuff and said
this guy's an
idiot
but anyway
go ahead
I'll lay off
Joseph Campbell
I didn't say
he wasn't an
idiot
no what I
was going to
say is
even tomato
sauce
or sorry
ketchup
you put ketchup
on pasta
it's still
discernible as
being related
to tomatoes
so it's not
fiction
right exactly
but it's this
preserved stuff that
they've actually
deprived people of
vegetables because
it got categorized
as a vegetable
in school lunches
in America
anyway
Ronald Reagan
categorized ketchup
as a food group
so they could
cut back on
giving children
vegetables
do you remember
that Bruce
you're old enough
to remember that
oh yeah
so I boycotted
ketchup for like
20 years
after that
I know I'm
bringing myself
in
well good ketchup
does
I find that the
quality of vinegar
that they put in
there is so low
like mustard
that you don't
taste the quality
of the
you know
the condiment
because of the
poor ingredients
but anyway
okay but anyway
you brought up
the Campbell idiot
but that's okay
he brought to the
forefront the
analogy of
mythology
in modern
you know
effects on modern
culture let's say
and mindset
I get that
but
right
would you sum them up
as that
yeah and I mean
the idea is that
within mythological
stories and religious
stories
there is some kind
of a
hidden something
or another
some kind of a
blueprint for
how things are
based on the
culture again
culture
I'll give you an
example like in
the American
culture I just saw
a movie and it
ended like oh
don't tell me the
ending I don't
want to know
well in the
Greek culture they
tell you the
ending from the
in the very
beginning in the
first act don't
they
I didn't do that
in some Hollywood
movies
some you know
some but
typically I'm
speaking of the
culture now
if you go to
any person
that's a spoiler
and that's what
screwed up a lot
of people that's
why I tell people
if you know you're
going to have a
conversation give the
important point first
then back it up
forget about all that
literary shit they
taught you in school
you have to have an
introduction the body
and a conclusion
give the conclusion
in the beginning
asshole
right
give them the
finding in the
beginning
so if you get
cut off at least
you get all the
crux of the matter
everything that you
oh he got cut off
I don't know he
was trying he was
going to get into
you know
you know like a
movie well you know
what happens if
you're watching a
two-hour movie the
power goes out
why don't they just
give you the
punchline in the
beginning of the
joke
isn't that how you
know when you read
about how mankind
is you know they
get the punchline in
the beginning
but anyway
yeah that's fine
that's more of a
criticism than a
matter of fact
progression or part
of the discussion
but you know
yeah
no that's fine
but we don't
you're saying
culture
okay
the headhunter
culture or the
headhunter culture
or the other one
which is the
headhunter culture
yeah they're all
headhunters
yeah I mean it's
you know the
story I gave about
the guys that went
down to the
Congo or was it
the Amazon
and they showed up
with a translator
to one of the
tribes and they
he lit a
cigarette lighter
and they all
were amazed
and they bowed
down to him
and he told the
translator I don't
tell them but
tomorrow we're going
to fly in the sea
plane into the river
that's really going
to impress them
and the next day
they do fly the
sea plane in
and all the tribes
come to the shore
and they just shook
their head
shrugged and
walked away
and the westerner
goes to the
translator
he says what did
they say why
aren't they
impressed
he says well
you know if a
man can make fire
come out of his
hand of course he
can fly it's no
big deal
right
so what impresses
one group is not
you see
see we're taught
in the western
culture that you
have this progress
right
look at the
airplanes you know
look at them now
you know wow
aren't you
impressed no
right
but they are
impressed
right
sure but what
we're talking about
is a little
different than that
in the sense that
if you
know but hold
it's not different
because the mythology
is the same
analogy
what mythology
what certain
mythological stories
will impress
upon whether it's
the individual
the community
or the culture
is very different
than another
mythological
aspect
but we're not
talking about being
impressed like reading
a book and thinking
that it's cool
like some people
read the bible
and they don't
think it's cool
they think it's
boring bullshit
that doesn't change
what the information
is if you can't
rationalize it you're
outside of the
you're in the
dumb masses category
so
well
in short
in short you know
the the biblical
text is done a
certain way
if you study it
long enough
to realize that
you're not
supposed to know
enough to upset the
plan
but you have to be
given enough that
later on you can't
say you never were
told
does that make
sense
that's the bible
in a nutshell
so the information
is something unto
itself
whether you
appreciate it or
your culture this or
that is not the
point it's something
on its own
so what i'm saying
is the mythological
stuff
it seems to have
been rationalized
by certain people
in a way that they
present it as
something unto
itself
whether whether
you like it or
you don't you
don't believe that
zeus did this
or you know
archimedes did
that like fuck you
this is what the
story says
can you rationalize
it
so for example
let's look at
something specifically
when you look at
certain
archetypal
representations of
experiential reality
that is
for example in
terms of leadership
um in
hierarchies
um you have
something called
the wise king
and the tyrant
right so the
wise king is
a hierarchy that
sustains itself
adds to its
population and
expands you see
this with like
somebody like king
arthur that's a
hierarchy
i'm going to
stop you again
because if you
have a wise king
there's always a
subgroup that
wishes the tyrant
would be in place
because then they
would prosper more
where the tyrant
right a quick
example is in
america if
you had a president
that didn't want
SWAT teams and
militarized police
that would upset
the people building
the the um
reinforced uh
what do they
call it
bulletproof stuff
and all the SWAT
gear all the
special tactical
gear and the
weaponry that
would upset them
wouldn't it
and they would
rather
right and
there's a
certain group of
people that
want a tyrant
let's say uh so
they can
prosper by
providing you
know weaponized
police and
you see what i
mean and tear
gas and all
that you see
so this is all
it can do
right
and
They are, but let's say when we bring up the Sons of Gods, I'll get off the topic,
the most memorable one that we see in the Book of Daniel is the Prince of Persia, right?
Memorable.
Not the only one mentioned.
Okay, well let's presume categorically that he is, would that be false?
Okay.
No, it wouldn't be false.
It would be as close as you can get.
What category would you put him in?
Prince of Persia.
Principality.
Principality that was put there.
The Sons of Gods got deposed.
We don't know what happened after that point.
Okay, alright, so if you want to say that they're discreet and different, then I'll just yield.
Okay, go ahead.
Well, the thrust of what I was saying was that generally you have these archetypes and they seem to work.
The reason why I bring it up is because we see it consistently, right?
But even if you look at like a fortune thousand company or government, corruption ends up being the norm, right?
But at the same time, we know that all this is happening under the auspices of a superpowered being called Yahweh.
And there is a difference, I will yield in this sense, there's a difference between something being partially corrupt and being totally corrupt.
So Yahweh has allowed his creation to become partially corrupt in a general sense.
And it seems because of that, it is unclear what the actual nature of things are because they're in this temporary condition.
So what is the actual nature of a scalable hierarchy that does not descend into tyranny?
I don't think we know that because all empires end up disappearing, all corporations eventually vanish, nations change, whatever.
So does what I wanted to know is that does the scripture indicate what that actually looks like beyond the sort of poetic blissful verses about the time after the Armageddon or whatever, like the lion eating grass?
Repeat the last 10 seconds.
Bruce, did you lose them also or is it just me?
No, I had a good copy all the way through.
All right.
Last 10 seconds, please.
Okay, what I was saying is that it's clear that Yahweh has allowed his creation to become partially corrupt in order to maybe push this plan forward in a general sense.
So the actual nature of what things could be is not clear.
Like what does a wise king hierarchy look like if it's just allowed to perpetrate indefinitely instead of eventually descending into tyranny and falling over because it's corrupt and people mess everything up?
Does the scripture actually show that?
Yes, but you've answered it yourself if you examine what you just asked.
How can it be allowed one way and not the other?
It's allowed all the way around.
It's predetermined.