Good evening folks, we are live with Rick and Sam.
Greetings to all of two, one quiet cricket and probably two other people.
The quiet cricket.
Yeah.
We don't do this for audience claps.
No, no.
They don't understand.
Did you hear the thing I did with Ocelli?
I was like, oh no, the Greek, he's talking about things I don't understand.
He's insulting my ignorance.
I might resemble those remarks.
Yeah, this is morons.
It's a planetary thing.
Anyway.
Yes.
By the way, this was not supposed to be streamed, but we've voted Sam on it.
So how about three people doing a vote?
One guy's for, one guy's against, and the third guy's like, I'm with you guys.
Anyway.
Anyway, as long as we can do something productive.
Well, not on this planet.
Well, you can for yourself.
I mean, I'll do the best I can for me.
Okay.
So the last time we spoke, my focus was on tackling some sociological and metaphysical themes.
And naturally, there was some pushback from the Greek, which is not surprising.
All right, hold on.
I'm going to stop you right there.
Metaphysical is a very, it's not accurate the way it's being used.
There's a lot of firm.
Okay.
There are many firm elements of thought and knowledge to be found in metaphysics.
Because metaphysics is a place where you cannot quantify.
You can only qualify.
Like, you know, you can have a substantial discussion on what love is lawfully.
No, not the emotional crap that the headhunters talk about, right?
But, and you could lay it out so it functions and it works well, and you have a healthy individual that approaches the concept of love well.
That is completely metaphysical because you can't quantify it.
You cannot quantify love itself.
You can only qualify it.
Metaphysics is based on qualification of, you know, whether it's ephemeral or empirical, meaning changing or unchanging.
That's the realm of metaphysics.
Now what's been done with it, metaphorically, is something else.
But I wouldn't mind just speaking on metaphysics for the next six months.
That's fine.
So go ahead.
There could be a sense in which I'm using the term a bit more loosely to just refer to things that undergird the physical existence.
So the immaterial things that you have to speak of, which are sort of structuring what you see physically.
But what I found striking during the last conversation, actually the conversation before the last one, because the last one was just me being a third wheel to a Greek rant.
But the one before that, what I found striking was this reoccurring pushback at the idea that there are archetypical templates for social being.
I can't imagine you objecting to the idea of axiomatic starting points for the physical reality in terms of things like geometric shapes or primary colors.
I think we've talked about that a bit before.
And it's also stuff that comes from, you know, Plato and Socrates as well.
Some stuff that they talk about.
But on the subject of sociological issues, apparently because mankind is encased within, you know, a fish tank existence as part of a science experiment of the gods, because of that we can't infer anything.
Well, fish tank process.
So because we're trapped in this existence, we can't infer anything definitive about the nature of the parameters that manage social being.
Seems to be, you know, what the Greek was indirectly saying before.
Because every time I bring something up, it's like, well, it can't be that because blah, blah, blah.
Or it can't be this because the scripture says something else, even though the scripture doesn't necessarily say what was being inferred.
What I mean by...
Well, hold on a second.
I want to just say something else on this matter.
If you're looking for a cut and dry 2 plus 2 equals 4 black and white aspect of it, you can only go to the metaphysical or the scriptural or the primacy to the gods.
That's where you get your definite, you know, answers from.
How everything gets set into motion, whether it's reactionary or result oriented, is where the discussion opens up and could be, you know, really large.
Just like before we started, Bruce was saying, wow, that Dr. Day lecture from 1969 really discussed things that weren't even in existence in society 20 years later that they were going to put in effect, right?
So it is a conspiracy, and it was from people on the inside looking out, not the outside looking in with theories.
So then we, you know, that's an example.
But no, you don't have to go...
I was not bringing theories.
I was bringing observable reality, and I kept stressing that.
Let's talk about what we can observe.
Now, if somebody wants to push back or to, you know, speak against a certain thing, then you have to bring your own thing.
But for somebody to just be like, no, it can't be that, because I can't read that out of scripture.
No, no, it's not just out of scripture.
It's the human element.
Like, you know, there was a study done, for example, of inbreeding or breeding in characteristics, and they said, well, a Chinese baby will obviously learn Chinese faster than a non-Chinese baby, right?
Because the Chinese baby is the product of, you know, many generations of just Chinese-speaking people.
Well, they did repeated tests in the 50s and 60s, and they found that whether you were a Chinese baby or not, they all learned Chinese at the same rate, you see.
So, in other words, how fast are we gobbling up to imitate and learn from what's put in front of us is the result that you're witnessing in society.
But I'm not talking about even that, because you can't tell me that just because people have been socialized a certain way that there is no template structure that governs social being.
Yeah, there is, but we don't know what it is, because we're kept on one foot always, like, you know, with the television show called The News, and nobody knows, and life isn't fair, and stuff like that.
Now you're just making excuses, because I've never brought any of those things up.
So I'm saying that we look at what's in front of us, and that we at least come to some conclusion.
And to say that something is inconclusive is also a conclusion, but we didn't reach that conclusion.
You're just trying to put that conclusion...
Oh, I lost him.
Is he there?
He's speaking.
I wouldn't be able to see him.
You should go to the group to see.
Oh, yeah.
Let's see.
Sam, speak up.
No, I got him off.
Obviously...
There he is.
Am I heard?
Yeah, you are now.
I was going to start fiddling to get you in again, but you're there.
Okay.
Okay, sorry, I'm streaming from a telephone.
What I was saying was that by archetype, I mean things that are common across all human experience.
Right.
So people tend to think that what we see with our senses or observe with our senses is the only real aspect of reality, and obviously that's not true.
What we see with our senses is only real within the time frame that we exist in.
What we don't see are the structures of reality, whether that's microscopic elements in the world or even the abstract structures of reality like mathematics.
Ether.
There is no mathematics in nature.
Nature doesn't use...
Like this guy, Ken Wheeler.
Mathematics is man-made, purely man-made, just like rap music is.
That's fine.
I mean, I didn't say that it was in nature.
I'm saying that it is an abstract thing, right?
So we have to imagine such things with our imaginations.
Well, let's backtrack.
There is an ethereal archetype that is purely metaphysical and non-quantifiable in itself.
I had a one-hour discussion...
But due to different structurings with our own things that we're able to tangibly hold on to...
Like, for instance, weather modification.
You and others have found out that different structures manifest things better for certain purposes.
The way you do weather is the same way you train a circus bear.
You don't know what a bear is, but you know that you can train him.
Or you know he has certain characteristics that you can negotiate to put on a show.
So when I say let's drop rain or a tornado or make a hurricane or take out a hurricane or stop rain or stop a tornado...
It's based on...
We know that metal reflects the ether and non-metal slightly absorbs it and slows it down.
And depending on where the layers are and the length of the device and certain geometries...
You're going to evacuate...
The secondary part of the ether is the weather.
You're going to drain that area of that effect.
Right.
And you know that the ether moves from west to east.
Low to high.
Yes.
The potentials go from low to high.
It's the opposite of the potentials we taught.
One day we'll do a weather engineering 101.
Everybody just start doing it.
Yeah.
Why not?
I was told by Trevor James Coswell, don't tell anybody ever how to do it because they're just going to mess the weather up.
And I said, well, what's wrong with that?
And before he died, he was like, you were right all along.
Go ahead and mess up the weather.
These bastards don't deserve good weather.
No, I'm serious.
He told me a lot of...
Did you ever find that tape?
I have it on a hard drive.
Yeah, that's right.
I got some gear if you need it.
I've put out there the use of silk, the use of layering, the use of mirrors.
Those were his tightest regarded secrets.
It's like breaking into Lockheed Martin and going through their vault and bringing out all their secret technology.
Trevor is like, don't ever tell anyone what I'm going to share with you.
And I said, well, let me ask you, if you die, can I share it?
And he says, well, I'm dead.
It doesn't matter.
You do what you want.
And then I thought about it with someone else.
And I said, you know, if we start telling people about this, they don't know how to handle it.
It'll be like literally giving monkeys guns.
And they're just going to mess up the weather.
And we started laughing.
We're like, great.
Anybody who wants to know how to affect the weather, I'll do a 101 on how to build a simple device that you find in garbage.
It's too easy to go to the store and spend $20 and get the parts.
Just take your time.
And when you're driving around or walking on the sidewalk, you look and put some mirror out or a metal tube or whatever on the street.
Just hoard some of the list, what's on the list to make these devices.
And it even makes it even more satisfactory when you build something that makes a hurricane 2,000 miles away out of garbage.
That's like thumbing the nose at whoever is telling you that there's weather engineering going on.
But anyway, back to Sam's point, when he was mentioning that about how the.
We're not even addressing this point.
We digressed completely.
Give me in 30 words or less.
Give me the.
Let's make an outline and underscore it so we can go back to it.
What I'm saying is that there are forms of stability as part of this reality that transcend our capacity to observe.
Right.
So we're adapted to a better reality, which means something that remains constant across time.
That's not the same things as what you see around you.
So what I'm saying is that there seems to be layers of existence that create patterns.
And then there are patterns within the patterns, within the patterns.
And that's what makes everything harmonious.
And that's these sort of archetypes.
So I'm confused as to why the Greek can be so averse to the idea of this.
I mean, in the past, you've made statements to the effect that these things exist anyway.
And it's not just because you said it.
I mean, these things can be seen, for example, because of the loathing of knowledge in society and man's decadent behavior.
Those who do gain the knowledge almost always retract away from society.
But this is already embodied in the archetype of the ancient sage or the ancient warlock or ancient masters.
When they reach a level of mastery of their knowledge, they don't want to be in the center of the town.
So they live in the desert.
For everyone, it's also portrayed in Hollywood.
Yeah, like Obi-Wan Kenobi or whomever.
So most sociological narratives have these constants, which usually start with some kind of a duality.
Like in the Eastern traditions, they always posit that there's a natural world.
Like in the natural world, there's an aspect of order and an aspect of chaos.
Sorry, stop.
When you say the word tradition, that's like a four-letter word for me, right?
Yes, the impression of Eastern traditions, but the people in the Eastern traditions are assholes.
I'm not talking about the people.
Just like the Western traditions, the people that follow those are assholes, which I just narrowed it down to about 7.5 billion people.
But here's the thing, Sam.
It's not that simple.
You'll rise up to get your point across eventually, but my point now, I have to interject, is when we say that according to the Eastern traditions, there's nature in that, anyone that goes and does a cursory investigation or in-depth in the tradition, it is all bullshit.
It has nothing to do with the scripture that they have.
So go ahead.
Whether you want to consider that the people are following the correct meaning of what their original texts are putting forth or not is beside the point.
No, it's not beside the point.
It's beside the point in this case.
It's really myopic to veer off on a tangent like this.
It's not a tangent.
It's this tangent.
No, it's not.
Just like, for example, when people are screaming about CERN, I'm like, well, they're not doing anything.
They're trying to shoot particles and electrons, and they don't even know what they're doing.
It's a show.
It's like a circus.
Right?
So that, you see?
So anyway, go ahead.
Well, are you, I mean, CERN is something else.
Like, if we're talking about…
No, it's not.
Because it's about physics, and if you go study the physics, you'll see what they're doing is nonsense.
Oh, so you're saying that the idea of there being chaos and order in the natural world is a complete fallacy?
No, there is no chaos and order as we, as the common pedestrian would reckon those two terms.
No.
Which common pedestrian?
There's no common pedestrian here.
The chaos, what is, I'll tell you really what's going on.
What's called chaos is simply the unidentifiable, the unqualified, it hasn't been grasped even to be qualified.
The other aspect of order and chaos is the order is the order that they're familiar with.
Yeah, but Greg, what else would it be?
Like, you just said a very obvious thing.
Well, again, if you could pull yourself out of the society that you live in and look at it objectively, now you're going to see what order and chaos is on a different level than those that are within that society.
You know the headhunter analogy?
Here's a simple way.
Do you feel like you're a foreigner?
You like visiting a foreign world?
Not just geographically, yes.
When you live, let's say you were brought up in London and you go visit Madrid, you feel like a foreigner, you visit and you feel a foreigner, whatever, no, no.
No matter which society you go to, does it feel foreign and wrong to you?
Yes.
Yeah, okay, and notice I said feel, right?
Now, once you start qualifying and quantifying those feelings, then you can say you know what's wrong, it no longer feels wrong, right?
That's order and chaos.
The feeling of chaos is that.
But once you understand and study it, you'll see there really is no chaos.
There's a book a while back, it's kind of rubbish, but what you get out of it is chaos theory.
Things that look orderly on the surface look chaotic when you look at them closely, and things that are chaotic on the surface have a high sense of order when you look at them closely.
It's very similar to that.
Right, but I mean the contrast between the two things remains the same, regardless of whatever level of detail you want to apply them to.
You grasp order pertains to the things that can be grasped and understood, and chaos the opposite.
Well, the contrast might exist, but there's a seamless transition.
There's no gap.
That's fine.
I mean, nobody said there was a gap.
So we end up addressing things that are self-evident anyway.
That's fine.
We can move away from this archetype thing, because we don't…
Hold on.
There is an archetype, and it's the ether.
In this condition that we're in and have been in for a long time, other than deep metaphysical study, not what you think or opinion, but study what's been accumulated on it properly, and also with experimentation, you will understand how to work with the ether.
But just like the concept of counterspace, when you see a point on a piece of paper or a point, they tell you it's one-dimensional.
Well, when you're dealing with counterspace, that's actually the end of a line.
So now you have to start thinking in a different form of geometry, which is the actual geometry.
And it depends on what you want to get done.
Let's say you're working in the health fields.
You're a nurse or a doctor.
You should understand, like Bruce said earlier, it goes from low to high.
Low potential to high potential, because all living things are functioning with the ether.
If you're plating metals or making weapons, if you're doing weather work, dealing with water, yeah, the ether is an underlying archetype to all of that.
But if someone asks you to show me the ether, I can't, but I could show you its effect.
No, I get that.
That's all very fine.
But what you're doing is that you only seem to be willing to examine the utilitarian aspect of certain functional systems in the physical reality, like the ether, like science, how things can be applied in a certain mechanistic way, which is valid.
But we're talking about sociological things, and you want to completely sweep that under the rug, because…
There is no such thing as sociological things, because it depends on which…
Because it depends exactly, you have to be very specific, on which society.
Like if you go to the headhunters…
No, society doesn't matter.
Well, then you cannot discuss society, then you have to talk about it as humans on the planet, what they all have in common.
We're doing that, but human beings live in society.
You're not excluding…
Well, once you say society, it's like eggs in a carton.
They each have their little compartment, and they're very different.
No, but the eggs are the eggs.
Not a good analogy.
Sociological is concerning the development or structure or functioning of human beings interacting with each other.
So that is constant everywhere.
Well, it depends on which society you're talking about.
Like the headhunters, you know, they'll interact with each other basically on how they're going to get more shrunken heads.
That is…
Well, let's go back to ancient times.
The people that lived in a Baal worship society, based society, had different…
I didn't say the…
Things that they did.
Yeah, but I didn't say the…
The ones that were lawful.
We're not examining the culture.
It's the same.
Culture, society, same thing.
What's the difference?
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
No, go ahead.
If I'm wrong, this might be the shortest stream we've ever done.
Go ahead.
No, we're going to shift topics to something else.
No, no, no.
Hold on, because get your point across.
Get it out.
I still don't see what you're trying to say.
Maybe go ahead and roll with it.
Maybe develop your thought a little more about what you mean about society and sociological whatever archetypes, I guess.
Go for it.
No, we've done this.
We did this last time.
It didn't work.
Maybe we'll get somewhere with this next thing, because I wanted to talk about games a little bit.
Anyone who's had some exposure to New Age or Theosophic or even Far Eastern belief systems may have heard of the idea that, you know, life is one big game and the gods are engaged in the form of divine play, which though it may be fatal for people, is just cosmic sport for them, the gods.
And the scripture sort of does back that idea up.
And you see that in mythology as well.
But it is observable if you contemplate things a little bit of finesse, that one of the substructures of human society is a game, by which I don't mean something as socially trivial as a board game or video game.
But a game, technically speaking, is a limited system in which two or more participants engage in an agreed upon conduct and decisions in order to manage resources or behavior.
And then according to a set of rules, you get a quantifiable outcome.
So when you strip away the genre differences and the technological complexities, all games sort of share the same defining traits.
You have a goal, you have a set of rules, and you have results or feedback system, and then you have voluntary participation.
So I've been thinking about how games matter to human society in human existence.
The fact that human beings have a specific type of embodied form imposes both possibilities and limitations that you have to exist with.
I'm not too familiar with the Tao Te Ching stuff, but I think one line in there is like, the space inside a pot is what makes the pot worthwhile.
Or more specifically, I think we mold clay into a pot, but it is the emptiness inside that makes it useful.
Or it's the space between the bars that keeps the tiger in the cage.
That also.
So perhaps in a more liberal sense, I look at something like that, and I think that you could read out of it that the things that limit you give you as much form and possibility as the things that enable you.
So more broadly speaking, that means that when you arrive at any circumstance that has a set of possibilities and limitations, it's those two things working together that allow you to impose a form on the situation.
Okay, let me just interject something.
You have to understand mental modeling, which is how people assume things on a minimal amount of information, a snap judgment.
It doesn't matter what someone approaches in their life, whether it's a baby, a game, work, a dangerous object, a precipice of a hill, or something that they haven't seen yet, they have a mental model in their mind that's already been established.
And if you can, again, go through that, the game has to work according to the mental modeling and then expand on that with the set of rules for the game.
If you were raised and had never seen a baby before, never heard of a baby, no one discussed it, and the first time you saw one, you'd be like, what's that?
You might even be afraid of it, you might be cautious, but you would seem strange because your mental model, you have nothing to compare it to.
In order for a game to be successful, there were some games that came out in the 70s that were complex, like Risk or something else.
It took a little bit of learning and strategy, and it didn't do as well, actually some of them did, as the ones that conformed to the existing current mental models, like Battleship.
Because the American society was brought up with war, and glorifying war, so if you put a game out with war, the mental model for using weapons and having an enemy, uniform, camaraderie, patriotism, that's already set, and the game just fits very well, dovetails into that mental model.
For example, Greek-speak, there is no mental model for that, that just completely destroys the assumption that most people have.
And the other thing is that in order for a game to be successful, it has to feed upon and build upon the people's ability to assume, the cut and dried war games.
Oh, we're patriotic, oh, we like weapons, oh, we're the greatest.
So the mental model has to be taken into account, and that goes back to your culture, your society.
Yeah, I mean what you're talking about is something that's created within you.
It's taught only by assumption.
Very rarely do people – in Victorian grammar school, for example, they were pretty blatant about mental modeling.
One example of mental modeling is etiquette, or how to sit at a dinner table, all the placements and all that, and just basic etiquette is forthright, overt teaching of mental modeling.
Like still today, when I'm out in public and I see a man and a woman, and the man goes into the driver's door and the woman's in the passenger, he doesn't open her door.
I really get out and I open the door for her, and I give him a scowly, dirty look, like you should be opening the door for women.
Now, some men do, some men don't, but in Victorian days, that was overtly taught, that you do that.
They sat you down and taught you that, where now it's assumed, and because that assumption is so loose and light, it's okay not to do it, right?
Church is another one.
I heard about a year ago this idiot patriotic alternative media guy, I can't believe Hillary Clinton went into a church and she didn't get hit by lightning.
It's like, oh, how do you work with somebody like that?
There's like 15 layers of shit in this guy's mind that you have to scoop away before you even start to rationalize.
When you hear something like that, that's a case where you just say, okay, just pull the handle, this one's got to go down the drain next.
You know what I mean?
Because where do you start with the guy?
He thinks church is something good, so he thinks Hillary Clinton is something bad.
Yeah, she's bad, but she's not any worse than most people in her position.
When I hear about people in power doing bad things, I try to examine what they did, how they did it, when they did it, and how easy would it be for anyone in that position to do that?
And 99% of the time, anyone in that position would do that.
So anyway, go back to the game.
No, I follow you.
I guess the point of bringing up the pot and stuff is just to draw this parallel to reality.
There are certain things that you can do and can't do in the physical world, and obviously that goes for games as well.
When you're playing chess, there's virtually an unlimited number of things that you cannot do and only a narrow number of things that you can do, and yet none of the seemingly arbitrary rules of the game seem unfair.
They're part of the structure that enables you to play the game.
So the point is that there's a parallel between games and reality, where games shade up into reality so that game structures that we engage in sort of undergird things like social being and even like child's play and things like that, that makes them analogous to real life.
So the first thing I wanted to ask is that with your studies in scripture, have you come across a sort of reference there in an explicit way?
There meaning specifically what?
Game or the loose assumption of things?
Well, the idea that life is a game, essentially.
Yeah, which would be a loose assumption because it doesn't say anywhere life is a game, right?
I know, but just something that you can sort of read out of the language.
I haven't seen it there either.
Nope, I see it as a process, and I see it as, believe it or not, usually scripture, believe it or not, is very light-hearted.
Occasionally it gets a little heavy-hearted, but mostly it's light-hearted.
Even when 85,000 Assyrians are killed in their sleep, it's still fairly light-hearted.
When you read that, you're like, oh, good, I'm glad they killed those bastards.
You're like, oh, yeah, the Israelites did kill every man, woman, and child and animal.
Wow, that was great.
See what I mean?
Not because you're saying that, because it's done in such a light-hearted fashion that it almost ends up with a ta-da, you know, in the end, when you read it.
And most people don't grasp it, that this is being done in a light-hearted way.
I don't think it's really a game.
But not in a trivial sense.
No, we won't know.
I'm not saying that life is chess, but I'm saying that the parameters that define a game seem to define reality as well.
Well, it's life copies art, or art copying life, I think.
It seems like a big lab experiment.
But it's not an experiment, because the reason you do an experiment is to see if your conclusion matches your hypothesis.
You started on the difference between Adam and the human.
No other mention of human after that point in Genesis, is there?
No.
And it makes you wonder.
Well, yeah, there is mention, because he says he created them Adam, male and female, and the terms that are being used are like for animals, male and female, or a ship, male and female.
And their task was to be fruitful and multiply.
Right.
Later on, I'll recap again, another 2,000 years later, 1,000 years passes by, and half of that 1,000 years figure, some were thrown in, because in one day, another day, and then another day, 2,000 years later, or 1,500, this Adam guy is not created, he's formed.
And from material taken from the earth, in the garden, and by himself.
And he's tasked to work the garden.
Mow the lawn, cut the trees, cut the bushes.
Name a couple of animals that we bring to you, a few.
How many animals can you name in a day?
A few hundred, maybe?
And not all the animals.
The animals they brought, just like Noah, Noah didn't have all the animals in the world, he only had the animals that were brought to him.
So, and his job, you know, his guy's just hanging around, I don't know what he's doing, jerking off, you know, whatever, by himself, you know.
And it's not good for you to be alone, let's make a helper.
So they take from his body, and they extend a polar woman.
You know?
Where before, the male and female were made together, they'd go out in the world, they were all, you know.
So, anyway, you know, this is a...
Some interesting metaphors, you know.
If you were to adhere to historicity in Genesis, you have to see it this way.
Or, ignoring this is fine, but negating it is not.
In other words, if you've read Genesis and not picked up on the historicity of this, that's okay.
But if you hear it, and you're like, it can't be that way, well, you're an asshole.
Because it has to be considered.
Right?
The tradition is, oh, that's just a repeat of what happened on day six.
That's a tradition.
But where's the historicity?
So, anyway.
Is that a game?
I'm glad you brought that up, Bruce.
Because here we got this, I would call the man that's made in day six, a stoic type man.
Because we don't know anything about his character.
And he's made...
What happens later on with him?
Yeah, well, we know what happens later.
We know what happens because, without it being said, because Noah was a descendant of Adam.
Right?
And only Noah survived.
So those other guys didn't survive the flood.
You can presume, it doesn't say that.
Yeah, that's true.
But Noah's sons' wives could have been of that extraction.
Oh, yeah.
Right?
Now, does it seem plausible that when day six man was made, there were different races of man made?
You know, squinty eyes, dark skin, medium skin, white, redhead, blond.
Right.
So, anyway, that's another discussion.
But it doesn't say that.
So I'm not going to say that it does, and I'm not going to say that that's how it was.
But you can step back.
Like Sam's asking, is this a game?
Well, if it is a game, well, you know, we're given rules, right?
The law.
Yeah, clearly.
If you sat down at a game, Sam, to play, and you said these rules don't matter anymore, what happens?
You get booted, right?
Eventually.
That's exactly why people are saying...
See, and you know, doing the law, by the way, biblical law, is voluntary.
You don't have to do it.
That's absurd.
If anyone...
Nowhere in scripture does it say you have to go out and convert anyone to a religion.
It's not in the Bible at all.
As a matter of fact, it's very voluntary, even in Yeshua, or the book of Joshua.
It says, tell us who you worship.
Not, you have to worship.
Like, you know, all these conversions, like ISIS or the Christians.
And by the way, you know, let's just bounce around here.
You know what ISIS is doing now?
Like, they're real radical.
If you don't follow their brand of Islam, they kill you.
That's exactly what the Christians were doing in the medieval ages, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
If you want to know what early Christianity was like, just look at what ISIS is doing.
Have you ever heard of the Inquisition, where they torture you to death?
Break all the bones in your body?
They don't talk about this.
They had some nasty people back then.
Yeah, there was an old book I found out.
Part of the torture was to break all 1,250 whatever bones in your body.
Oh my.
That's the Christians, you know.
So what ISIS is doing is what the Christians are doing.
So, you know, if time were to go on, ISIS would mellow out and be just like the Christians.
But the point is, back to the law.
You might say, well, the rule, you know, Scripture does qualify in some condition.
There's a playing, we have the playing field.
We have a law, but there's only, the law is only for one group of players.
Who want to do it.
Well, what happens to the rest of the players?
It's a very, what would you call it, unilateral game.
It's a game where one person plays like solitaire almost.
No, I mean, yeah, I did want to look at that a little bit later.
But first, I just wanted us to be able to objectively, to say that it can be objectively seen that life is a game.
But once again, not in this sort of trivial board game thing, but just in the sense that you have a system in which you have, you know, players, and resources are limited, and they have to be managed, and this is what it is.
So that does pretend to lie.
Yes, the pawns, the knights, the kings, the rooks, bishops.
Okay, so just to look at one of the implications of that.
Because as you're growing up, you hear certain things like we've all heard well-meaning, but perhaps naive parents tell their children to play fair, quote-unquote.
And things like it's not about winning, but it's how you play the game, right?
And then eventually the children come to realize that the parents are just mouthing off platitudes, and they don't really know what it means, but somehow they know that there's a rationale behind that.
But for the most part, you ignore it because you can't see how to apply it.
But there's something there.
So what I've come to thinking about it is that as far as human beings are concerned, life is not one game.
Maybe for the Most High God and his consorts it is, but for human beings enclosed in this physical state, life is not one game.
It's a set of games, right, all of which compound to create a sort of metagame.
And the most important rule to the game seems to be this, never sacrifice victory in the metagame for victory in just one sub-game.
So in other words, there's a victory to be had across a set of games that isn't the same as just winning one round, right?
And we've heard that articulated in the concept of a pharaic victory, where you win the battle but not the war.
So this kind of thing would then point to…
Or you don't win any battles and you win the war.
That would be the best, the most efficient military strategy, is to strategize tactically to harass and injure and then retreat from the enemy, so there's no definitive win or lose until they're so worn out that they surrender.
And the way that you get them to surrender is not by attacking them, but by hiring some of their inside people to sabotage.
Sabotage is…
War is not taught, even in war school it's not taught, because it's just bullshit.
To do real war, it's all deception, that's what the word means anyway, polemikos, polemis means many memes.
You injure them, you confuse them to the point where they're…
You cut off their supply lines, food, clothing, shelter, and then you sabotage them internally with spies, and then you just walk right in.
It almost…
Remember how the Persians took over Babylon overnight?
How do you think they did it?
They just marched in there like that?
Scripture doesn't give us any real detail, like some detail, but not enough to…
How did they do it?
So…
Yes, that's all very valid and interesting, but we're also talking about how this works in a social setting, as far as there being a larger victory than just in one little sub-game.
So to connect that back to playing fair, not just in terms of strategically, but also ethically, there seems to be an ethical component there.
Because in a world where you live alongside other people, and we're all playing various games, you want to play in such a way that other people want to play with you, as your allies, and also continue to…
inviting you to play with them, because that's how you would ultimately win the metagame, by being invited to play the largest possible array of games.
But of course I don't mean that in a humanistic sense.
Well, the metagame is post-resurrection.
Are you implying that, or am I implying that?
I think you're saying that.
We know that there's that aspect of things, but I'm not talking about the grand narrative of human existence.
I'm just talking about a sociological phenomenon.
And that's not going to go away post-resurrection either.
That's why I'm trying to connect this back to the archetype thing, because this seems to be a constant regardless.
But it will go away, because post-resurrection you're going to be in a completely evasive condition, no privacy, and you're going to be ruled by a police state.
Greek, it's not going to matter.
But it's going to be benevolent, right?
No, it doesn't matter.
Unless you're saying that to be a human being, at this point, what we know of it is just null and void.
Oh, okay, so what you're saying is that people are still going to do bad shit after the resurrection?
Yeah.
Whatever constitutes humanity still goes on.
The dynamics don't change.
Right.
Well, hold on.
Since we're on the topic, just to entertain this for a moment.
The resurrected beings will not be doing this, most likely.
It'll be the survivors and their progeny.
The resurrected beings are less than 10%.
It's nothing.
Well, 10% is 700 million, if you were to go that way.
But remember, even after the first resurrection, everything is destroyed and cleaned, and everyone is taken out again.
If you remember the book of Zephaniah.
So, anyway.
So, when I think of a game, when you say the metagame, I get the game part.
Explain the metagame.
Or give me some more detail on the metagame.
What do you mean by metagame?
Well, I'm still talking.
I'm not talking narratively, because in that sense, obviously there's a conclusion to this whole thing, and we know that it's the resurrection.
Not that, but in a sociological sense, as far as how people interact, when you go out into the real world, Which is the fake world, but go ahead.
Yeah.
But everything presents itself as a game.
And as far as you interacting with other people to reach certain goals, and there is a consensus, as far as cultural norms, behavioral norms, and there are various interest groups, and everybody wants different things, that's what friendship is about.
You create a bond with somebody on the basis of a mutual point of interest, whether that's humor, or pastimes, hobbies, whatever.
And you're working towards different things alongside different people.
Now, if you choose to be antagonistic, then obviously people won't want to associate with you.
Which is the same thing as saying, I'm not going to allow you to play this game with me.
Whether it's this game of friendship, or it's this game of working in the same work environment, or it's this game of, you know, whatever.
The courtship games that teenagers and even adults play.
Whatever it could be.
And so the idea of the metagame is the sum total of all these other smaller games that exist in society.
Oh, I see.
What do they have in common, you mean?
What's their underlying cause?
No, in the sense that…
How can I say this?
Yeah, you are saying it.
Just spill it out.
I mean, a little drip at a time.
The sense that the person who understands that being able to win at all these smaller games in life, whether it's how you manage your friendships, or how you manage your professional relationships, or your romantic relationships, or whatever, the sum total of all of that constitutes the metagame of social being, or social interacting with people.
So in other words, the asshole is really bad at playing games.
Nobody wants to play with the asshole.
And it's not that the asshole just loses one round like he goes to work and pisses off somebody today.
The asshole, because of his character, is going to continuously lose across multiple rounds in such a way that everybody gets to know you need to stay away from that person.
He's a loser.
We don't want anything to do with him.
Right, and they get enough of those losers together and you make a Saturday morning cartoon.
Or whatever.
Like when you watch superheroes, they're the villains.
They have their own group.
Like the old Dick Tracy.
I don't know if you remember Dick Bruce.
You probably remember the Dick Tracy.
All the villains used to hang out with each other.
Or the Batman.
All the assholes used to come together and made an alliance.
Yeah, but they would always betray each other.
Yeah, but even though they're ostracized as assholes, they don't end up in a singular singularity of assholedom.
They actually create a consortium of assholes.
Right, but that falls apart in the end because of their character.
Yeah, it's called the US Congress.
You never heard of that?
But anyway, just go ahead.
I was trying to connect this initially to the idea of why playing fair matters.
Because you have to be able to play with people in such a way that they want to continue to play with you.
Oh yeah, you do that through deceit and flattery.
Oh, that's the opposite.
Come on, man.
I mean, how many times have you heard a relationship of people together, even husband and wife, and all of a sudden they decide to divorce.
Why are you divorcing on the most trivial bullshit reasons?
Yeah, that's because they don't know how to play.
They're immature, and they have not understood the play plan.
Yeah, that's like 99% of the people.
Right, okay.
That's why it's all based on deceit, and game, which is flattery.
Right, so they're just immature, and they don't play very well.
But I think that this also applies to the realm of the Elohim, obviously, as well.
I mean, ultimately, all of creation seems to be playing a game under the auspices of the Most High.
I mean, how else can you prophesy the future from the start?
So actually, it's a rigged game.
Right, it is.
Sort of like your analogy of life on a cruise ship.
It goes where it goes.
There was a physiologist studying the brain, and she got a PhD.
I think I've said this story before in public.
And she went and got a job at a lab in Germany.
And she was very naive.
She was in her late 20s with a PhD in brain science or brain biology.
And she went to the biggest lab in Europe, in Germany, and they tell her, this is the experiments we want you to do, and you have to structure the experiments so you get this conclusion.
Experiment.
Right?
So then she kind of freaked out and communicated here.
And she was like, oh, I can't stand it.
In three months, I'm coming back to the States.
Then she gets a job with a Canadian research company.
And she goes there, and they said, okay, great.
I'm glad we got you.
You have very high marks, good recommendations.
And she freaked out.
And then she quit all of that and she just went to teaching to create more people that will be deceived in the same system.
Do you see?
Wow.
So I just gave you several things there.
One is, he declares the end from the beginning, which is, if you go to do research and they tell you structure the experiments so you get this conclusion, isn't that declaring the end from the beginning?
But it's structuring things to get that outcome.
That's why when you understand prophecy and watch geopolitics, no matter what they're screaming about the cause, you know what the outcome will be.
And I've even gone public saying, I don't know exactly how, for example, Assyria is going to be formed, but I know it will be formed.
I don't know exactly how Israel is going to expand and be about 150 to 175 times bigger than it is now in territory.
So what I'm watching now is the experiment being structured to meet that conclusion.
So from that point of view, when it was brought up it's an experiment, I keep saying no, well that's the analogy that would support the term it being an experiment.
In terms of it being a game, when you say a game to most people it's like all fun and games.
But some games are not fun and games.
Some games are pretty serious.
There are the games.
Basically they were called in Rome, let the games begin.
The gladiators and all that.
If there was a gladiator that was tired of the game and he wanted his family to be wealthy, he would actually bet against himself and allow himself to be killed.
And by the way, just to throw this in, lions were thrown to the lions as a crock of shit because there was no Christianity back then at all.
That didn't develop until hundreds of years after even the Colosseum was finished.
Who they were throwing into the lions as sport were the ones that had too many traffic tickets you know what I mean?
Or too many misdemeanors like they would do inspections on the Pope's or the Emperor's work schedule or Athena or Jove and if you didn't produce or perform they had violations against you.
And of course they threw people they didn't like also but there was no Christianity back then.
The best thing that you had that resembled Christianity was the Mithra worship that spread from the East, went to Rome and went underground hence the catacombs.
That was Mithra worship.
If you understand Mithras, the temples of Mithras 90% of them are underground.
You know?
So don't...
It's kind of like the memorial you know there was no airplane in Flight 93.
It's even mentioned on the news.
We don't see it.
They say there was an airplane crash here but nobody sees it back then.
And yet these idiots are building some hundred million dollar memorial for the airplane that crashed there.
So when you look at these temples and the catacombs churches, cathedrals none of that ever happened.
That's just like a Flight 93 memorial.
It's just something to make money or put something in your mental model.
You know?
So maybe that's part of the game, right?
When you sit down don't they give you board pieces and doesn't the board have a topography?
Right?
Yeah, sure.
I'm not denying that that could be it.
But once again but let's look at the rule aspect again because you did bring up the law.
And I guess you could paraphrase that perhaps into the rules of the game according to the Most High God in a sense.
But you also have other gods and they have their own rules also.
And there seems to be some anomalies to the rules like when Abraham marries his sister for example.
So there's a dynamic there.
But like I said a core part of society seems to be not just adapting yourself to a single game or a single round but to this sociological metagame and victory across as many of them as possible or at least the most important ones.
And as far as human society goes whether you acknowledge the gods or not you win by manifesting the ability to play in a reciprocal manner repeatedly regardless of who you're dealing with because like I said nobody wants to play with an asshole.
So you don't stab people in the back you don't play dirty and you don't manipulate or deceive people at least ostensibly because who wants to play with that kind of person which is why you always have this honor among thieves problem where people, you know bad guys get together to do things but in the end it all comes tumbling down on them.
Not always.
Most governments in the world the satanic system is based on that system being reliable believe it or not.
But it's like a phoenix it collapses and the same thing comes out of the ashes, you know.
But it does collapse.
Oh yeah.
Well you know let's say you have a mob boss he collapses when he gets old and dies and his son takes over and then he collapses and dies and then his son takes over.
Yeah but what they don't say is that he actually collapses because he gets taken out or shot.
It's not usually that he dies but anyway the point is that there's a mode of being that transcends the particularities of the localized contest and to act in a wise manner is not to win today's game at the expense of the rest of the possible contest.
So the person who's a master of participating in or being invited to the most significantly or qualitatively superior games and winning them is for lack of a better word a god sort of.
Like he occupies the apex of any hierarchy.
If you're a son of God and you're walking around in a human form how are you not that guy?
You're that guy.
Like you are the most good looking the most charismatic the most has all the social currency stuff that everybody wants to get around because you just have that otherworldly quality to you.
Right.
Because there are many different games that could be played but there's only really one person that other people want to play with or you're not.
And if you're not that makes you a loser.
Like when people say you can't define the word loser that is just as pejorative like no it's not because regardless of culture or background you always have that phenomenon.
All cultures have different games but the set of all games is common across all cultures.
You have the guy that people don't want to play with because whether he's the nerd Well certain people he'll eventually find others to play with.
In other words there is no definite black and white in this.
They form groups and subgroups.
But losers can band together and do their own thing but they're still losers.
Yeah.
Look at most boardrooms of big corporations.
Most people think these people are like Superman like you mentioned Sons of Gods.
I've met enough to know that these guys are major losers.
And that's when I went back to look at scripture I was like oh yeah it's an upside down world of course.
The worst are going to be put in.
The most based men are going to rule over you.
So when you say these losers you cannot negate the point that these losers are your leadership and your captains of industry.
And even inventors.
I don't know how many inventors you know that have patents and come up with ideas.
Those are like the worst characters I've ever met in my life.
And the only reason I communicate with them is because to help them all I'm intrigued by the invention and how it could be used and through life I've found out I have easy access to people.
So I could look up some invention by an inventor that's still alive and within three months to a year I've got him in my Skype contacts and we're speaking.
So when you say losers these are your inventors your captains of industry your religious leaders your presidents So I'm not saying this to be antagonistic I'm saying this to be considered.
Yeah, I'm not denying that but they're there because the gods put them there.
People don't like them.
That's right.
The only reason I made the conclusion that the losers are rightfully there is because the gods have set it up that way.
It's rigged.
Yeah.
But based on all this there seems to be something gained by looking at least in some sense at least from a social sense at the purpose of life so to speak as having something to do with learning how to play a set of games.
But let's not conflate that with knowing what the rules of the game are because obviously humanity has never known in any wholesale manner what the rules of life are outside of laws given by some god that's not the most high.
So I'm talking about once again just to use the word loosely in a metaphysical sense I mean maybe we can look at how children play games to understand what I'm getting at.
Like children under the age of eight or nine are able to teach themselves how to play games with each other.
But that doesn't mean that they all know what the rules of the games are.
So if you put them in a room or in a playground they'll come up with a game and they'll play it but if you pull one of them out of the game and ask them to explain the rules they can only tell you a few of them usually at a very low resolution.
So the seven-year-old will tell you his rules and the eight-year-old will give you another set of rules and the nine-year-old will tell you what he's grasped.
But if you put them all together again they'll play the game as if they're a lack of cognitive...
Well, they're novices.
...on an issue.
Well, it's their novices.
So the point is that the novices embody...
Well, that's why I have to go back to what Jack Fresco says.
Children are a pain in the ass until they're taught.
Who wants to be around a small person that throws up on themselves poops and pees in themselves doesn't know how to tie their shoelaces doesn't know how to...
They're a pain in the ass until they're trained, right?
There's nothing mystical or magical or wonderful about a child at all.
And I've always thought this by observation when I heard Jack Fresco talking about it I was like, finally someone else I could verbalize has verbalized this.
Think of yourself.
Think of children.
You couldn't wait until you grew up, right?
Some of your young youthful thoughts are like, oh, I don't want to be a child.
A story with that is one thing that Jack Fresco the way he trained his son is he made him a small car and he didn't want him to be dependent like a child.
So anyway
a child, he was about
four or five
the wheel falls off
the little car
that they made
and he brings it
to the dad
and the dad says
the child is crying
oh, the wheel fell off
so he brings it
to the dad
and the dad says
okay, well give it to me
we're going to throw it
in the garbage
and I'm going to go
to the store
and I'm going to buy you
a car that they make
for babies
because those wheels
don't come off
and the child
immediately said
no, no, no
let's fix it
because he didn't want
a car made for babies
even though he was one
you just tell him like that
I've seen parents do that
if you don't stop crying
I'm going to put you
in the chair
that we put babies in
and it's a baby
you know
okay, okay
you see
so they don't want
to be babies
even children
don't want to be children
and adults
don't want children
to be children
I'm not talking about
the airheads
that are like
look how wonderful
they are
or whatever
yes, they are
for like five minutes
out of a year
you know
but anyway
so the noviceness
of children
I don't think
children are just
small people
and if you want
to look at the game
look at the game
that's been created
around them
the subculture
the movies
the books
the way they speak
the bullshit toys
you know
it's just sick
I was having
just to interject
in terms of society
I was talking about
America
I said
oh yeah
I'm glad you're here
I want to talk about
you know
Trump has been in
for almost two years
or whatever
and not much is getting
I said
there's nothing
you can do to fix
this country
because
if you leave
there's two ways
leave everything
as it is
or try to fix it
either way
it's doomed
because if you leave it
as it is
it's going to be doomed
obviously
but if you try to fix it
it's going to be doomed
because you're going to
the change
will not survive
you see
it's like an inoperable
brain tumor
if you leave it
in there
it's going to kill
the victim
if you try to remove it
it's going to kill
the victim
you see
and that's not being
pessimistic or optimistic
that's just being objective
so children
are the same way
there's nothing
you can do
with children
until you
until they're
disciplined
educated
skilled
now
that's why
I've always been
speaking for over a decade
on how ridiculous
the education system is
and how ridiculous
society is
and you know
the culprit
is the parents
most people
shouldn't have
the right
to have children
because they don't know
what they're doing
right
and someone says
well who says
what they should do
they're going to
you are going to
decide what's right
and wrong
based on you being
informed
but right now
you're just
a knuckle dragging idiot
so
it's like years ago
if you
when you know
the turn of the century
19th century
there was a boom
in mental hospitals
right
do you remember that
like bedlam
and you know
terms like that
bedlam means
complete madness
and you know
there was
all across the coast
of the U.S.
is where the boom
happened
there was a boom
in England also
mental hospitals
and people
that were
considered to be
morons or idiots
in a medical way
were sterilized
right
to not have children
so you don't
have more
you don't have more
morons or idiots
and that's actually
a good thing
but is it
no because
there were
the ones that
made
if you ask them
what makes them
a moron or an idiot
the person that was
making that determination
was also a moron
and an idiot
you see
so
in other words
you have to rise
above the society
in other words
it's like the headhunters
you know
one headhunter
doing something
to another headhunter
they're headhunters
you see
it's the society
it's the culture
this is all
very true
it is however
a point onto itself
what I was trying
to get to
was the idea
that knowledge
is embodied
within a group
like with children
that play games
but then
novices
yeah
but then it diffuses
when you isolate
the players
right
so
as the children
get older
say 12 or 13
then they extract
the rules
from the group
onto themselves
and can learn
how to play
fully by the rules
as opposed
to when they're
eight or nine
and they don't really
grasp the rules
singularly
but only when
they're in the group
but
as they get older
they do learn
how to play
by the rules
or
they learn
how to break
the rules
as they see fit
I think the Greeks
talked about that
before
or it might have
been a private
conversation
but it's not
that people
just play
by the rules
but like
with the CEOs
who run companies
or whatever
or the higher ups
in certain
organizations
eventually they come
to realize that
they're the ones
who make
and break the rules
so it's kind of
like a progression
first you can play
then you can play
by the rules
and then
after that
if you're so
inclined
or gifted
you can become
the master
of the rules
to break them
or to generate
new ones
based on the
dynamic of the game
right also
let's go back
earlier
believe it or not
most industry
and corporations
are subject
to what's called
industrial
espionage
and sabotage
every major
company
has
a cross
pollinated
group
or a cross
placed group
you know
like there's people
in Apple
that are spying
for IBM
and vice versa
oil companies
car companies
they're spies
and that's what
keeps them in check
so a lot of these
decisions that you see
being made
that just don't make sense
are actually a form
of you know
sabotage
due to you know
blackmail
secrets being let out
secrets not being
let out
you know
to those that
need it to make the work
you know better
I mean it's just
a mess
yeah
humanity is in a
total mess right now
so that's why
you know you just get
little things that make
people more narcissistic
and egocentric
so and you're not
getting anything else
but
the game is like that too
right you have a winner
right it's usually
an individual that wins
and if it's a group or a
team that wins
even that team has a
captain right or a
leader
true
yeah
I mean my thought
around the whole thing
is that
could it be
that
could it be said that
playing the set of games
that comprise this
existence
or life
that comes in the
first
incarnation of
things
and even though
the Torah
or the
law or the rules
so to speak
have been given to
mankind
no one really cares
or takes them
seriously
but then
the end times
and the antichrist
comes along
and only then do people
start learning the
rules although not
completely
yeah he imposes it
in a way that's not
really lawful
but yeah
and then
learning how to
perhaps
this is what
this hypothesis
just a guess but
learning how to
break the rules
or to generate
new ones
perhaps comes later
in the millennial or
the post-millennial
scenario
and the new
well the new rules
are usually assumed
unless they're done by
the highest authority
known
right
you know I
and you have to interject
that there's also
a game master
Satan
which is sitting on top
of this game
given to him
yeah
right
like a
Sephirot
that's a whole
different
pile of wax
there too
well like the
book of Job
is do what you
will to him
just don't kill him
right
he didn't say
go make this guy's
skin break out
and kill his
children
and have him
lose all of
his flocks
and all this
he didn't say that
he just says
go do whatever
you do
that wasn't Satan
but whatever
that was just
one Satan
one yeah
it was an angel
one of those
destroying angels
or one of those
yeah
go do whatever
you do
just don't kill him
well you know
then it was
the discretion of
what was done
that we read about
the actual
manifestation
you know the
malevolent
things that
befell Job
that seemed to be
of up to the
discretion of that
you know lower
entity you know
yeah
so it's when you
talk about the
Satan game and all
that
how much is he
actually using
you know proxy
spirits
and the actual
manifestations that
we see
are you know
based on these
proxy spirits
discretion of what
they want to do
right
how they want to
do it
you know we
have to take out
this guy
do we have him
like you know
get in a car accident
does he die in his
sleep
does he you know
food poisoning
see that's the
discretion of those
that are doing it
yeah there's this
all this stuff can be
understood
believe it or not
it's quite finite
the realm of the
gods is a finite realm
it's just vast
yeah
right
because you know
one of the first
things you learn
in studying scripture
there is no such thing
as forever right
that's the first thing
you should learn
when you're doing
word study
it's ages upon
ages upon ages
when does it end
no one knows
like in
Vegas when you
spin the wheel
where does the wheel
go you know the old
roulette wheel
you know whatever
or the big
wheel where does it
stop no one knows
right
so but then you have
a little brake pedal
you know
so
yeah
it is finite
but it's just vast
that's all
yeah that's knowable
yeah
the quantity may not
be perceivable
and you know
rationalized
so
you know
the amount of
grain of sand on the
beach is a finite
number but go ahead
and count it tell me
what that number is
you don't even want
to try that
so
that's a
counter spatial issue
by the way in terms of
mental modeling
so
well I do
let's wrap up the game
stuff I just have one
last thing
here
the idea of an
iterable
game which
I think
might be
important in an
archetypical sense
so if we're talking
about imagining
or understanding
what the rational
underpinnings of
the world
is or reality
is
a large part of
that seems to be
having
a large part of that
is having in place
like a joint frame
of reference
or shared
game rules
that allow multiple
people to pursue a
range of desirable
goals in parallel
with each other
how can you have
shared game rules
I don't understand
that
well but this is
like obviously you
have to have shared
game rules or you
can't have a society
where people live
together because
then there's always
going to be a
fight oh I see
there's a set okay
okay it's not one
game sharing rules
with another game
no you mean
no not that
because that's
possible when someone
emigrates and then
you open up
Chinatown because
you have enough
people from China
emigrating you
know and then
the people that
didn't weren't
familiar with Chinese
stuff go to Chinatown
because they like it
now I mean that's
a way of sharing
like a culture
but sharing one
rule I mean can
you do various
card games can
you yeah I was
just thinking like a
card game would you
integrate the various
rules you can't
no the game falls
apart quickly
you know right
no I mean having
whenever you play a
game or whenever you
interact with people
there there's a
there's a shared
frame of reference
for what's going
on or no or
okay common
common knowledge of
what's going
yes of the rules
okay and
and the rules
have to allow
multiple people to
play and to
pursue you know
a range of desirable
goals for themselves
but not only that
they have to be able
to do it iteratively
so it's not
something that can
just be like one
round and then it's
over so in other
words the way that
you live your life
has to work today
and it has to work
tomorrow and next
year and years to
come if it's a
valid lifestyle
right obviously
not all frames of
references or games
can manage that
only a few of them
can like for
example what do
you mean by
irritably like to
irritate or
iterate to iterate
over and over
to iterate
oh iterate okay
gotcha
irritate
all right as an
iteration yeah
yeah so for
example like smoking
crack redundancy
yeah smoking crack
is not iterative
like you can
even if you can do
it for 50 years
like people who
smoke cigarettes
until they're 95
it's going to impair
other social and
biological functions
right so smoking
crack is a bad
game it's an
unplayable game in
the long term and
most people won't
want to play with
you you go and
tell somebody let's
smoke crack most
people say no
well yeah by the
way I just want to
interject something
with with that crack
we hear that a lot
right you know it
says a crackhead
right it means that
it's a pejorative
the what it's an
it's a very
interesting psychological
thing why people
smoke crack because
when they first
first first smoke
it they get this
blast like an
incredible high and
then they just want
some more and
they get some more
and it's not they
don't get it's
like a click
something in the
brain that you'll
never get again
and the second
time they smoke it
wasn't as good as
the first time because
oh then they're like
maybe because they
I need to get a
different variety of
crack or maybe I
need to do more or
maybe and they keep
experimenting with
they're never going
to get that initial
blast where that
initial endorphin
whatever the the
the things the
endorphins and the
brain whatever
connected to you
know they're never
going to get that
again and they're
seeking that it's
a very endorphins
yeah it's a very
immature like
spiritually lazy
drug because it's
not that they like
the crack it's they
are always yearning
this is the majority
of people that
have interviewed
about this they're
they're yearning
for that initial
high and then
they're never going
to get it
it's the same with
tripping it's the
same way if you
ever took LSD
the first time
you know the
second time you
do it you
know then you're
like okay you
know what to
expect but it's
never quite exactly
like the first time
you know that
becomes the more
you do let's say
LSD that becomes
just more of speedy
for you not trippy
you know but
anyway
hmm
how do you know
these things
yeah
but either way I
mean you can't
show me well maybe
you can but you
know rhetorically
speaking you can't
show me a society
built around smoking
crack that you want
to live in right
like
no I can't show
you that I want to
live in this society
credit-based society
ruled by attorneys
and judges
justice religion
no I don't want to
live in that society
either
but go ahead
so the point is
that you have
playable games
and then you also
have non-playable
games right and
examples of
playable games
I mean
things like
carpenter
stonemason
plumber
you know those
things like you
have entire societies
that are built around
those professions
because they are
sustainable games
that you can
continue to do
iteratively
also you know
different people
want to play
different games
like an extroverted
person might want
to play a social
game a neurotic
person might want
to play a safe
game agreeable
people might want
to play a generous
game and so on
and so forth
but they all have
to be parameterized
playable games
which frankly you
know just on a
side note
flies in the face
of a lot of
today's prevailing
bodies of thought
like relativism
or post-modernism
or even the new
age movement
a lot of that
stuff
like it almost
seems like one of
the main goals of
the adversary is
to make non-playable
games attractive
through these
ideologies and
religions and stuff
like it's self-destructive
but people do it
anyway
right and it's
voluntary
you're right
but anyway
so one of the
characteristics of a
playable game
is that it is
iterative
meaning you can
play multiple
rounds without
degenerating your
condition
so what that
means is that
there has to be an
equilibrated state
where the rules
or the law
or the morality
is iterable
because it is
progressive
right you can't
play a degenerating
game because then
everybody loses
eventually
so it at least
has to be stable
across time
right
you're in that
humanity is in
that degenerative
game
but it's only
being sustained
by brute force
because of the
gods
you know it
doesn't really
work
no it's actually
I disagree
it's being sustained
by the passive
ones
there's many
Voltaire made
some sayings about
it and others
when good people
do nothing
that's what keeps
evil going
right
it's not the
ones with the
brute force
I disagree
the brute force
is like scratching
an itch
when you see a
military campaign
or police action
that's scratching
an itch
the underlying
body itself
is the
cause of it
no I don't mean
that the people
are keeping it going
I mean the gods
in the sense that
in a world full of
so many contradictions
you would think that
the whole thing would
just topple in on
itself
but it doesn't
because the gods
are sustaining it
yes
behind the scenes
that's what I mean
well the thing is
there's several
aspects to that
if you understand
that it's pretty
obvious that we're
supposed to be
doing what we're
doing for a certain
amount of time
and then go to the
next level
like a waiting room
yeah
right
and also when you
couple that with
how little
regard the gods
have for our bodies
and our well being
in general
all the way up
then hence
the descriptions
whether you're
through
literature
or art
the misery
and the suffering
you know how many
times people
you've heard that
ever since you were
a child
why does god
allow
all this misery
and suffering
duh
because like
they don't really
think much about
your physical
existence asshole
maybe
do you ever think
of that
but anyway
whenever I hear
questions like that
it just makes me
want to barf
but
so
no that's fine
but
where was I
yeah you were
right
things are
um
right
the idea that
things are
have to be iterative
is what I was
initially saying
which is why
you know
doing things like
hard drugs
is a problem
because eventually
you're likely to die
or like robbing people
for a living
is not sustainable
or beating your wife
sure it is
ask an attorney
any attorney
some of them
live to a ripe old age
and they're quite wealthy
and they're quite revered
I mean like
mugging people
like come on
yeah they do it
they do it with a pen
they do it in a
in a courthouse
yeah okay
no I'm serious
I've never seen a mugging
I don't know
I've
some people used to call me
and say hey I'm going to court today
would you please come in
or somebody that I know
has an interesting case
might be good educational
you know
and I always go
look like
like I work there
you know I wear
an Oxford shirt
with a tie
and slacks
and shoes
and you know
I don't dress like the people
from around here
a little better
taste in clothing
and a clipboard
and you know
and I sit in the courtroom
and they're like
oh this guy probably
he's probably in law school
or he's probably
from an insurance company
by the way
you ever see in courtrooms
you see people sitting in there
in the back
those are usually
insurance people
for both sides
because if they
screw up too bad
you know
there's
insurance issues
in many court cases
even traffic tickets
believe it or not
so anyway
I would go in there
and actually
this
I saw
a 78 year old lady
get mugged by the
not the way you see it on TV
but literally mugged
the
the attorney
and the judge told her
sorry woman
it's just business
nothing against you
you know
and they forced her
to sign papers
that would give up
you know
certain property
and things like that
you know
and if you don't want to sign it
maybe
three days in jail
you'll think about it
we'll bring you back out here
you know
they mugged her
basically
it happens
you know
millions of times
every day
right
I mean
figuratively
you could
take mugging
and apply it
to a variety of things
but I'm sure you know
what I mean
as far as
doctors
doctors mug people also
but go ahead
another aspect
to this whole thing
as far as
because what I'm
talking about
in this sense
is the idea
of an equilibrated state
another aspect
of that
is
an equilibrated state
is like
the result
of an agreement
where people
are
honestly
yeah
so collectively
people decide
how to move forward
in a way that's beneficial
for the groups
and the individuals
when you have this
equilibrated state
and
you know
what I'm working towards
is this sort of question
I mean
based on how
how much tug
there is
sort of from the Greek
I doubt we'll get an answer
but the
my original
question was
if you think
like what kind of
what do you think
is the kind of
iterable game
that improves itself
across time
that seems the most feasible
like is that something
that can be conceived
working with
working with the ether
and it's
utilitarian or not
what does that have to do
with society
like creating a society
a lot
or create
you know
I mean
if I drop a hurricane
on Puerto Rico again
do you think anybody
will be there
you know
yeah
it has a lot to do with it
I mean
the electricity
is pure ether
and
it's not electrons
or any of that
do you think electricity
has an effect
on society
you know
electrifying a society
sure
I mean
I'm talking more
of creating
a system of
laws
and understandings
whereby people
function together
in such a way
that they're able
to play games
with each other
in a
productive
way
yeah
later on
I'd say that
you could tag that
as
partially
or if not
mostly
in the
unknowable file
ok
based on
the Venus project
perhaps
yes
that was his idea
I don't think
that would work
it was an open
architecture
though
what he did
he didn't want
any notoriety
yeah
and it was open
he didn't want
any claim
because that would
limit the other people
he said
they should change it
as they need
but he didn't know
about
lawful
yeah
he didn't know
about lawful
and unlawful
he doesn't know
that the current
system is
he doesn't know
anything about
the gods
he doesn't know
anything about
money
he doesn't know
how the human
body works
how that
would change
if he did
though
huh
oh yeah
he wouldn't be
but I'm glad
he didn't
because he
wouldn't be
he wouldn't
be vocal
right
you know
the advice I give
people is do
absolutely nothing
do the bare
minimum to
live the life
you want to live
based on what
you want to eat
what you want
to wear
and how you
want to live
in terms of
your abode
or what car
you know
in other words
it's ridiculous
to want an
eight million
dollar house
let's say
you know
a McMansion
so figure out
what level of
quality you want
and then go out
and into the
credit based economy
and gain whatever
you can to maintain
what level of
food you like
clothing you like
and what level of
living you like
the rest of it is
completely irrelevant
even you
are completely irrelevant
to the gods
in the state
that you're in
right now
how do I know
because he says
he destroys the
righteous with the
unrighteous
so when destruction
comes
just because you're
being lawful
and you think
good thoughts
and you pray
to the most high
he's going to
save you
he has no assurance
for that
yeah I mean
he might
save you from
that destruction
personally I wouldn't
want to be saved
because what
then I got to
walk around
and it stinks
you know
and all the mess
so there's
another level
that's where
Mishrach
Shadrach
and Abednego
in the book of Daniel
they're like
well our Elohim
can save us
from your furnace
but if he chooses
not to
that's fine
with us too
you know what I mean
so there's many
there's many levels
to it
but like Sam
I think he's trying
to bring out
like I'm saying
the level that
we're on
we didn't discuss
game levels
I think that's a
video game phenomenon
right?
yeah
but the level
that we're in right now
is a shit level
and it's a novice level
and
there ain't no
two ways about it
that's why I tell people
do nothing
do not get involved
with any religions
any philosophies
any politics
any
whatever
if you like to be social
be social
if you don't want to be social
there's nothing wrong
with that
if you
you know
you're going to need
a certain amount of skills
to interact with the pricks
on this planet
and be good at it
yeah
be good at it
you know
like even today
most people
you know
the way I comment
to people at Nomad
is that
I wouldn't bring that guy
to a fancy restaurant
that says a lot
like they don't know
how to act
like if you
I don't know if you guys
have ever been to
a hot cuisine
like especially
the old school style
they'll throw you out
if they don't like the way
you know
you're acting
unless
what happens
if you brought in
like a country boy
that didn't know how to act
in a really high end restaurant
years ago
they would bring a screen
and they put a screen
around the table
so no one else could see
the barbarian sitting there
yes
right
yeah
and when you see the screen
come out
you're like
oh I wonder
it's because
someone requested it
or because the host said
this person is bringing down
our establishment
right
these type of establishments
don't exist anymore
I think I mentioned
one of the sonic events
there's some
in Scandinavia
some
the world's best restaurant
four years in a row
I wouldn't even do
take out from there
so this is
what I'm talking about
is finished
you know
so anyway
I don't want to rant
so what else about gaming
you guys still there
oh yeah
well
yeah but
you know
food clothing and shelter
this all went nowhere
fire
that's hard
yeah well
if we can identify
nowhere
then it must be somewhere
do you remember the old
was it the old
Abbott and Costello
is like Coachella
in the Greeks
yeah
Abbott and Costello
who's Abbott
who's Costello
you figure it out
but
do you remember the
you got
lend me 20 bucks
do you remember that
and how about
I can prove that
you're not here
do you remember that
yeah
that was a classic
those kinds of things
those
that's what it's about
you know
so in terms of
we didn't talk about humor
Sam
what about humor
right
well humor is
is several things
gives a good emotional feeling
some people believe
and might be good for health
reasons right
and it alleviates the
it's a distraction
alleviates the
the drabness of
continuing
you know
takes the edge off
yeah clowns
so
by the way
clowns originally
were not the way
that we use them now
or you know
they had a purpose
they were
ward off evil spirits
to relieve tension
you know
other things like that
but now
the church
you know
there was a big split in the church
by the way
you know
one went the religious route
and the other one
went the circus route
like Barman Bailey
because they're both circuses
or churches
you know
so anyway
I did not know that
well the word church is
circ or circus
Cirque du Soleil still
the Circus of the Sun
Cirque du Soleil still exists
I had gotten someone
to give me some tickets
to go see it
it was pretty good
very acrobatic
good show
yeah like I said
they're doing the
it was
it was funny to see
Shanksville Memorial
for a plane that never crashed
this is the American government
doing it
never no plane there ever
and they're building a memorial
so when you look at a cathedral
or the Vatican
or a mosque
or a Buddhist temple
or you got those idiots
out in the Himalayas
what are they
the Tibetan monks
all that crap
that they have built there
you have to wonder
is it another flight 93
yeah
and if you actually study
the writs that they're supposed
to be based on
yep
none of that shit
that they're doing
ever happened
but it sure is
a lot of stone work
just like this flight 93 memorial
has got a lot of stone work in it
right
yeah
so yeah
it's bizarre
what kind of game is that
not to mention
I think
what was it
the 54 million dollar jet
for that fella
in his church
oh that's
yeah that's fine
when a pastor
yeah his fourth one
yeah
when a pastor
when they say
oh this pastor wants
like here locally
there's a big mega church
and they
they were
just constantly hammering
the
congregation
for three and a half million
and they ended up
expanding the parking lot
right
and doing
solar panels
and some other stuff
and people got upset
and I said why
why
the guy asking for
54 million
yeah
that's what
what do you think
that people are there for
because if they were
not idiots
they wouldn't be there
and this is a fact
this is not from
a humanistic point of view
oh Greek
you're too harsh
on them
you know
they just don't know
I'm not saying that
I'm saying the fact is
if you were to take
a cross section
of what's going on
yes
these people
this congregation
are all morons
all of them
and he
sees no purpose
in what he's doing anymore
because
either he's realized
everything is a lie
that he's telling them
or he just doesn't know
so the only thing
left to do
is buy a jet
there's
I see nothing
wrong with that
nah
I
I don't object
let him do
what he wants
yeah
they're not
in other words
they never claimed
to be doing anything
truthfully
or anything like that
you know
here's the other thing
I've been turning on
TV late at night
to see what they're
putting out
and there's this thing
called
it's like a Christian channel
and
the guy
there was a
priest or pastor
I've seen him before
he's got a
thick mustache
tall slim guy
I forgot his name
and he's doing
he's preempting
like he's going to give them
a heavy truth thing
about the Sabbath
for 10 minutes as well
I know most people
you know
this is the
this is the seventh day
it says
it doesn't say
take a seventh day
it's the seventh day
so what is the seventh day
you know many
and he goes
you know many of us
have been brought up
in the church
thinking it's this and that
and he's going on and on
and on preempting it
but the Sabbath
really is on a Saturday
and I was just cracking up
I told the wife
I said look
this moron thinks
it's on a Saturday
wow
you can't
you see
because
because he's a headhunter
he doesn't know
he can't think outside of
you know what I mean
yeah
it never occurred to him
and it never will occur to him
that he's on the Pope's work schedule
it's totally fictional
13 moons
or 13 moons
basically months
jammed into 12
that's why you have 52 weeks
if it was 4 weeks in a month
it's 48 weeks
but why is there 52
because they jammed
an extra 4 weeks in there
and they try to make it work
so
this guy
he's like going to the headhunter
these preachers or pastors
even the Pope
he's like going to the headhunter
they don't know anything
they're stuck
they're products of their culture
I mean they know a lot about headhunting
and shrunken heads
you know
you ask him
are you glad you found out
that the true Sabbath is Saturday
yes
they're like oh
it's like the guy
you can't
you can't work with them
so
it doesn't mean
you can't inform them though
I mean if you want to
well it comes
yeah
I'm constantly informing people
and I just walk away
it scares them
it scares them too
yeah
but they're like
Wilhelm Reich said
they're so heavily armored
emotionally
that it doesn't get through that
and they react
one of the
interesting
especially in this culture now
because
they could look stuff up right away
you know
they have a little stupid rectangle
in their pocket
they no longer just
they don't scoff at you
or laugh
or I don't want to know
they do act
you know
you have a rectangle
yeah I do
okay look this up real quick
I'll show you
so they act more
there's a new form of armoring
and it's the agreeableness
now
which I've only seen
with the devices
you know
because it's easy for them
to go on the internet
and look up what I'm saying
where before they would scoff
now because they could look it up
while I'm there
they have this sense of agreeability
and the minute you walk away
they forget about everything
and I said
they said thanks a lot
I learned a lot
I said no
when I walk away
this is the asshole right
you're not going to remember
a thing that I said
they're like no
I'll remember it
and I actually ran into someone
that I said that to
about a month later
I said do you remember
we were talking
yeah I remember
do you remember anything
that I said
not really
but you said you would
so this
I've already come to
that conclusion
see
and of course
this is the great majority
Sam and I will
and others may discuss
who cares about them
it's just ourselves that we're
because the real reward
is knowledge
right
so
in itself
but you know
if knowledge is a reward
in itself
then sorrow will be the reward
won't it
yeah
I don't know about that
I could die
from person to person
mhm
I'm not particularly
sorrowful
and I feel sorry
for myself sometimes
but
I'm not sorrowful
you know
I don't think
that's possible
can you forgive yourself
they tell people
all that stuff
you can't do that
I think it's best
those kinds of things
are best avoided
not avoided
but put in a place
where it's an anomalous
thought
and anomalous thoughts
always vary
I mean like
when
this is funny
I'll tell you soon
when I was in L.A.
we had a
oh
we lost
Sam
I was working with
several people
in the water business
and
people
ok
no
there are many anomalous
thoughts
through my life
running into people
and when I got to know
them personally
they said
did you ever think
about this and this
I'm like no
never crossed my mind
is that something
you're dealing with
yeah I do
I said wow
you know
so it is very subjective
right
like dreams
by the way
I had to explain
dreams to someone
recently
because of the
a little more detail
when you
for example
are having a dream
of something
that was very personal
that happened a long
time ago
let's say as a child
or you're
you're
shown someone that
you know let's say
your granddad died
when you were 8
and you still remember
what he looked like
and you're shown that
that is a spirit
that's been following you
around all this time
or a spirit
that is doing it
that is relaying
that knowledge
from another spirit
because they have a
hive mentality
you know they might
send a spirit
to send you a dream
and they're like
I want to get creative
with this motherfucker
so let's
let's go real
let's go as far back
as private as we can
anybody
I got this
this is the idea
on this jerk off
can I
anybody out here
in the
in the collective
got any
anything I could use
against this guy
and it could be someone
all the way up in Tibet
or China
or a spirit under the ocean
or way up
in the skies
says yeah I got something
on him here
this is it
boom
and he relays it
and he
you know
so the more detail
you get on how they work
the more you can
control these things
you know the dreams
and the
especially when you're
approached
with that
if you are
one thing I haven't
mentioned
is these spirits
do have a hive
mentality
just like you would
like let's say
the three of us
are out in the field
somewhere
and we want to know
what someone in chat
is doing
we just go to chat
or email them
right
and we get it back
and we tell the rest
even though we're
in a different part
of the world
so they do have
a hive mentality
it's not always
the same spirit
it could be
but once you start
getting a little more
detail
the less they want
to mess with you
like you know
I think I even
on
recently
I went on
somewhere
and I did
talked about
unhaunting a house
you know
you don't do it
like the way
it's shown on TV
or the movies
or on the internet
so
basically just
rebuke the spirit
but you must include
in the rebuke
that it's not fair
and it's not kind
and well it's not kind
because how could he be kind
meaning the same
it's not proper
and cosmically
to be
taking advantage
of stupid people
like these people
that you believe
that a little girl
died in this house
and they see her
which they do
are ignorant
and you're taking
advantage of
their ignorance
so stop it
you rebuke them
like a child
right
and the haunting stops
but if you go there
and you start saying
oh a little girl
that died here
please go away
they're going to
tear you up
they might even
if you rebuke them
so you have to be
discerning
you know
either way
yeah you can imagine
like a house
is being haunted
by you know
the old man
the one legged man
he's got a wooden leg
and he died in the house
and how do we know
it's being haunted
well because people
in the house
hear him walking
with his wooden leg
and we've seen him
in the window
you know even though
he died a hundred years ago
that bullshit
there is no
disembodied spirit
he's dead
you're dead
you're not acting
on anything
right
it's a demon
playing a joke on you
if you go there
and start talking
to supposedly
a dead man
with a wooden leg
they're going to
just keep playing with you
you know that's what
you see in Hollywood
by the way
and on the internet
but if you rebuke
the spirit
taking advantage
of stupid people
who think that people
can do that
after they die
well now that spirit
has a problem
and they could lash out
at you as well
but usually the
haunting stops
that's how you do
a professional grade
unhaunting
versus
I'm telling you
anything else you do
will not be successful
they'll just come back
and play with you again
because you're just
too damn ignorant
and if you actually
look at the word
in scripture
that supposedly
Samuel
came to Saul
and told him
he was going to
lose to the Philistines
the next day
it's called a
familiar spirit
or you know
a common spirit
meaning the ones
that deal with people
it wasn't Samuel
right
so
I don't know about that
because I've looked for that
and I have not
gotten clarity on that
but maybe you can
show me sometime
well it was someone
that took the visage
of the image
and the persona
the identity of Samuel
yeah I know you're saying that
but I'm saying
it does not say that
in the text
it says Samuel
came up
right
by identity
because the setting
is already there
we know that when you die
you're asleep
so here Saul
what's your first hint
that this is
something's about to go bad
not
most people think
the bad thing
is that when he's told
that he's going to lose
to the Philistines
right, no
the bad thing is
that he proclaimed
that there will be
no divination in the land
then he ends up going
you know something's
going to go wrong
right
yeah the setting
is understood
I'm just saying
what the text says
is Samuel
it doesn't say
familiar spirit
hmm
there are other places
in the text
that bring up
that there are
lying spirits
and familiar spirits
and things like that
oh yeah yeah yeah
but I'm just talking
about that context
oh yeah yeah
no no
but the scripture
is I wouldn't say
full of those references
but there are enough
references in scripture
to define
if you are
looking at it
with a sober mind
that when you die
you're done
you're dead
there's absolutely
no animation
and
anything that is
interacting with mankind
from that realm
is a demon
an angel
you know a god
period
you know
mmhmm
yeah I won't
I won't argue that
point too strongly
without exception
there are a few subtle
unless you're a
post resurrected being
now if Samuel
was resurrected
he could do that
by the way
yeah
because you could
shed your body
and act like a spirit being
once you're resurrected
sure
but he was not
resurrected
Sam was dead
Samuel was dead
so
mmhmm
alright
nah I won't argue it
it's simple
it's just like
this is
but the problem is
let's say we're sitting
you know in a
in a
what do we call it
a junior college
and we're discussing
you know elementary math
and you get in second grade
we don't want to talk about it
it sounds too simple
right
and by the way
the
if you read
the Rig Veda
actually not the
the Rig Veda so much
as other writings
that do get more
into very short writings
that get into the
the what happens
to the soul
and how it's external
they call it
the translation
of spirit
and other
ancient writings
um
all of these things
are outside
of your identity
when you die
you know
until you're brought back
oh
you know
meaning that
there is no
there is no way
in all the ancient
writings are similar
when you die
whoever has died
cannot come back
it does not come back
to interact
with the living
but there are spirits
that interact
with the living
using those
deceased identities
you see
hmm
it's basically
identity theft
is what they're doing
if that makes any sense
yeah yeah
no I understand
what you're saying
um
I'm done
with the game stuff
let's just
look at one
last thing
in another
sphere of things
and then
maybe
we can
wrap up
on this
degree
because of
the things
but um
I did want to
touch on the
say what
I've always got
other things
but go ahead
I wanted to
touch on the
issue of
um
phenomenology
so
is a
method of
inquiry
in philosophy
which is
based on
the premise
that
reality
consists of
objects and
events
that is
phenomena
as they are
perceived or
understood in the
human mind
and not of
anything independent
of human
consciousness
so basically
the world is
constructed in
your mind
through your
central perceptions
and not by
the physical
material out
there
and um
the greek
seems to have
made reference
to this kind
of idea
when you
say things
like
a room
isn't a
room if no
one's in it
well
or is a
room a room
if no one's
in it
is a city
a city
if no one
lives there
well it's
phrased as a
question
but you're
making a
statement
it's always
phrased as a
question
because it's
just to
jog the
mind
what i'm
trying to
do is
jog that
mental
modeling that
people have
right
yeah but
you're also
making an
indirect
statement which
is that a
room is not
a room if
no one's in
it
is it
don't ask
me
if a
secret room
was built
and no
one knew
about it
because the
people who
made it
died
does it
exist
i mean it's
an empty
space encased
by four
walls but
perceptively
it's not
because no
one's there to
perceive it
i i get
that so the
question then is
is human
experience reality
or is the
physical world
reality like
do things
exist separate
from people's
perception of
it in an
explicable way
this human
experience in
this reality
like for
example take
eyesight what
you see and
what we even
scientists haven't
grasped this yet
what they consider to
be light is
strictly based even
you know when
they're studying light
they're still using
their eye to study
the information and
if they're blind
then they're using
braille and other
means it's still
relying on the
the fleshy eyeball
and if you don't
have that fleshy
eyeball the world
looks very different
to you like a
fly sees very
a dog sees very
different they have
cryptochromes in the
eye that see
differently birds see
differently you know
yeah the birds use
magnetic fields to
guide because the
South Pole the
magnetic field in the
South Pole has a
reddish hue and the
a bluish hue sorry
and the North Pole
has a reddish hue
that's how they use
the magnetic you
know one end of
the magnet has a
reddish hue the
other end has a
bluish hue and
they use the
cryptochromes in
their eyes to
guide not the
actual magnet
to guide the
magnetic field in
their brain right
so my point there
is we don't see
that some people
can there's a guy in
Australia Joe
Booker he says he
can see magnetic
fields and I'm
like yeah I'm not
going to say you
can't if the guy
can prove it you
know so the
thing is what we
call reality just
even based on the
eyes because of the
type of fleshy
eyeball that we
have and
so and let's go
again back to
scripture a post
resurrected being if
you decide to shed
the body for a
moment or however
long and you're a
spirit being do you
still see yes but
do you see the
things the way that
we eat with a
fleshy eyeball no
you don't
stop and think I
was the first time
I'm saying this
publicly all right
you know when you
read in the law you
know if this
you know if you
garment touches
meat it's unclean
but then you you
wash it and in
noon by noon you
know next day then
it's clean again you
know well you can't
see that right you
can't see that you
get it but but the
spirits could probably
see when something is
clean or unclean
I've never mentioned
this publicly before
now we're getting
into the stuff that I
think about you know
when you read
scripture it's like
oh yeah you know
when you read the law
those are all like
imagine a road with
road bumps speed
bumps every five feet
and wherever I talk
to about scripture
usually it's like
they're driving over
these things at 60
miles an hour as it
isn't a bumpy ride
like yeah that's where
my head keeps hitting
the headliner slow
down man think about
these things you know
that's why when you
read any ancient
philosophy which really
was philosophy as as
it was done within the
you know the group
was earnestly seeking
out wisdom you know
even scripture says
the Greeks look for
signs and wisdom and
through philosophy and
you know knowledge and
the Israelites look at
it through revelation
from the God something
like that I'm
paraphrasing right
different culture but
could it be that when
something is unclean
even a human that
spiritually it looks
different when you don't
have this eyeball with
this eyeball can't see
that so
it's kind of like
bridging when you study
the law especially the
most the first five
books of Moses what
it's you know what it
really is in a sense
it's a bridge between
what the spirit world
is doing seeing and
and trying to
accomplish with what
man sees and is doing
and is trying to
accomplish you know
it's a bridge so you
know the concept of the
double-edged sword right
most people think well
that's a double-edged
that's a good thing to
go and battle with
you know it's one side
you know you dull out
one side at a time
you always have a sharp
edge whatever cuts in
both ways but the
double-edged sword I
would suggest in
scripture is to dual
purpose like in what
it's on what with one
edge swing to the right
you cut someone's head
off and on the swing
to the left you're
buttering your toast
even though it would
be unclean but you
see I mean it's
completely totally
different things not
not it yeah not only
that it cuts excuse me
in both ways but
which is obviously what
it does is there's
always the obvious
function when you read
the ancient text and
then there's the the
allegorical the metaphorical
the insight and the
bridge there's a there's
a bridge language in
scripture which I've
never discussed also once
you understand the
limitations of the
physical body and the
way you understand the
limitations of your
physical body is very
simple if you've ever
had a cat right you
you want to go to the
front of the house
you're in the back and
you have to go through
the gate and all that
and the cat will beat
you to the front of the
house because it just
goes over the gate and
over the house and over
you know you see it can
do that it can climb
walls vertical walls and
you can't so then you're
saying oh you know okay
so basically what I
comprehend as as reality
is limited to this you
know physical body
you know the human you
know there are animals
you know dogs they can
hear you know deer
whistle right if you
ever blow on a deer
whistle can you hear it
nope the deer can hear
it though you ever see
those uh you put them
on the car if you go
hunting or whatever
um bruce look a little
chrome things a little
whistle yeah you just
yeah as you drive it you
know it's like uh is that
thing working makes a
lot of frequency pitch
no yeah it's like a 28k
something like that
40k up to 40k way up
there yeah so yeah so
we're limited to that
reality so when you're
reading scripture it's a
bridge between the
spiritual state and the
physical state and just
what I mean by a bridge
language is for example
um let's say you speak
english and spanish and
you run into someone who
speaks uh chinese and
spanish right well you
can't communicate with
them in english they
don't know english but
you can use your spanish
and they could use their
spanish and you can
see so it's a bridge
language and i've done
that several times i've
when i'm out or traveling
and especially in a public
space and some tourists
come in and they're asking
questions i try to say in
various different languages
that i would speak you
know
you know i mean and then
like you know some people
philippines were like yeah
i speak you know or from
china would say yeah i
speak spanish i'm like
great now we can now we
can communicate you see
so um are you picking up
on what's crossing over in
the law because you know
how many times have you
heard people read scripture
you know to try to be
objective like oh that the
law stuff doesn't make any
sense or you know why does
or they try to rationalize
it oh i see why they didn't
eat pork because they
didn't have refrigeration
yeah how many times have
you heard that before right
i've heard that several
times
they're trying to rationalize
it based on their mental
model oh those are like
health laws you know um
you know because they
didn't have refrigeration
or you know pigs need a
lot of water you know mud
and they didn't have the
water it's like what are
you talking that you know
they're they're using their
mental model you know like
the headhunter you know
what i would suggest that
one of the easiest ways to
look at it is when you see
what's being implied in
especially you know because
when i say scripture it was
really the first five books
of moses all the rest of
the stuff was not really
known publicly and openly
as much as we have it now
right you know even if you
went back into the days of
um you know the christ or
even slightly before very
few people knew the
prophets and the psalms all
of it but they had known
about the first five books
of moses they were exposed
to that they might have
heard of the prophets but
they were not familiar with
the text you know unless
they went to study halls
either called synagogues or
whatever you know but i
would suggest that it's
about you know the insight
beyond the human insight
because the human insight
is limited to the human
body we can't hear what a
deer does we can't climb
like a cat we can't bite
like a dog actually some
people might but you know
we don't you know we see
what we see based on the
fleshy wet eyeball so when
you look at scripture and
it doesn't make any sense
that the mental modeling
that we have from the
culture and from the
physical body is two steps
removed from comprehending
what's being shown there
you know you know there's
another way to look at it
let's say a garment you
know you have a clean
garment touches a piece of
a carrion right or a piece
of meat it's still clean it
just touched it you know
let's say the meat was
wrapped it just touched the
wrapping you still look
clean right but you are
unclean you see or you know
if someone had sex for
example ejaculation is
considered unclean or a
woman menstruating but no
one else can see that so
you see so that's there's
there's something there's a
field that's changed that's
quite visible to the spirit
world because they don't
have a field that they made
mention of yeah they make
they make mention of it so
much that we don't you know
when you see when you hear
clean and unclean that's
almost undiscernible by us
a very some things are
discernible but it's a very
personal thing because when
it says you know if your
garment touches a piece of
meat it's unclean well if
no one was around when it
touched it who else knows
right who else knows nobody
but the spirits can see that
I'm not saying that it says
that they can't but I'm saying
that it's mentioned so much
that it seems to matter and
if it matters they can
perceive it if they if we
can't perceive it it's it's
because we're limited to
this fleshy eyeball or this
fleshy perception you know
again I keep saying do
nothing food clothing
shelter and if you see the
possibility of fire and
genitalia being compromised
you're finished as long as
no matter what collapse in
society happens or level of
destruction or disarray if
the if the ability to create
fire exists and there are
still people genitalia guess
what you'll be just fine but
if the ability to not make
fire and have no genitalia
you're screwed you're you're
f you're done you know I had
a while back I bring this up
as a someone a computer
programmer guy speak to
sometimes and make a long
story short we don't need
fire anymore and it kind of
kind of caught himself you
know because he knew I would
pull I would pull what I
pulled on him when I said
humans are agricultural base
he says no we're not because
he's a computer programmer I
said okay I'm gonna leave you
in this room with no food I
didn't say no water because
water is not really
agriculture an elemental
ethereal thing right I said
no food and by the way those
those are blue jeans right
they're made of cotton right
yeah I want those give me
give me those back right that
that undershirts cotton right
give me that give me that
cotton back no agriculture
right and he was like I get
your point I get your point
you see because he is
operating on the mental model
that we're advanced and
modern and when I say
agriculture you think of like
some guy in a horse and buggy
horse cart you know drawn
carriage with a plow or a
oxen right yep green acres
yeah they were protesting a
mine here about a decade
green acres about a decade
ago on a sarco mine was being
protested and I pulled over I
stopped and there was a food
truck there it was a good food
truck so I stopped it and it
was um so you guys are
protesting uh the mines I
said well yeah we shouldn't
be mining any metals I'm like
those are blue jeans right you
got a metal zipper right give
me the metal zipper back I want
the metal zipper back give me
the metal button back oh that's
silver earrings give me that
give me the silver earrings I'm
gonna go give it back to the
miner give me you see what I
mean you get it you get what
I'm you know because their
mental model is is very loose
it's like oh there's really
nothing to do here this is my
parents are stupid the schools
are stupid but I can't tell
anyone and there's a protest
going on here and I want the
world to be at a better place I
still don't know what's going
on I'll just Gustav Le Bonnet
you know I'm gonna go Gustav
Le Bonnet right you know just
go be part of the crowd and they
don't know what's going on
they're functioning on a very
low-level mental model very low
level that's what I keep saying
it's toy in ghetto and in mob
talk they call it toy you know I
don't know if you've heard that
you guys might have heard that
back in the days in the ghetto if
something was like cheap or you
shouldn't take it seriously he's
toy or that's toy right it's like
bullshit this is a toy existence
back to your game our games toys
are toys games you know
toys toys you don't know what is
the etymology of toy anyway it
doesn't sound good I've never
looked at that one who gets the
most toys in the end wins right
that's the capitalist
mean
circa 1300s it's kind of like a
sport or a piece of fun or
entertainment or thing of little
value yeah okay perfect so the
ghetto usage is pretty accurate
almost on the latter part of the
definition
deal carelessly trifle 1520s
what's the verb right so you grow
out of the small so the small
people the children get this stuff
and then all of a sudden at one
point there's a cutoff and they're
told now do they have to act like
adults but all their formative years
where they would have it would have
been most efficient to train them and
discipline them and educate them
enlighten them was wasted on trifle
shit right no anyway yeah I'm telling
you you know you don't want me as
emperor of the world that all right
everyone all the babies would stop
everything would stop you'd go through
three months of training on how to be
a parent you know I'm extremely
evasive of there I can't stress how
important that young small people are
treated right out of the children are
treated properly you know like fresco
says your little children don't want
this bullshit stuff that they give a
Walt Disney Mickey Mouse toys and all
that you know they're like as soon as
they begin to speak they're like daddy
what makes airplanes fly was that I
don't know you know daddy when you what
makes when you turn the switch what how
why did the lights come on I don't know
right daddy what makes the car go you
know where does oil come from yeah I
don't know just play with this toy
they're they're ready soon as they're
ready to communicate they want that you
know they like I said earlier you know
if you remember being young you four
five six seven you didn't want to be
called a baby that was an insult right
you want to grow up so you know why
don't those desires satisfied it's just
foolish it's the parents that are at
fault and if you want to educate well in
a better setting a more harmonious
homogenic setting were for children
would be they're raised by women you
know from breastfeeding you know all the
way to the nurturing right if you want
the children to be educated you have to
have the women educated first because
they spend the most time you know
whether it's the mother or the
relations or the nanny even the women
must be highly you know educated and be
able to communicate and I say educate
music loosely because the word educated
etymologically can mean training animals
so well then you got that point that
Richard Day made him that was all
sliced away from us and strategically
implemented on a society yeah yeah yeah
we yeah what's shocking about that
interview it should be shocking if it's
if it's if that interview is not
shocking to you some people say just
hearsay but and they made they did it
after the fact you know but it doesn't
shock you yeah yeah you should check
your pulse because or your moral moral
compass because they were mentioning
that people will have VCRs in their
homes to watch pornography and movies
and yeah right and this is before you
know those things the VCR back in 69 was
about three you know $1,000 and 69
monies is 10,000 now he was a weight
about a hundred weight about a hundred
pounds and maybe there was maybe a few
hundred of them in the world if that back
then so how would it how would you know
get to people's homes and so anyway you
know that was very prophetic it shows
you that there is an underlying but
those but by the way those are the
underlying society you know the people
the people that are in control by the
way they don't know what we're
discussing 99% of the stuff that we
discuss here on the streams and on
Greek speak these people do not know
like what's coming they don't and I was
naive in the beginning let's say 15
years ago 13 14 years ago let's say
15 years ago now or more so wow I've
been at this now going on 17 years but
anyway I was naive I fell for the for a
short while you know Illuminati Freemasons
you know the bank families are really
know what's going on they're guiding
mankind you know until I started
studying scripture and then not until
about less than a decade ago I started
working with people and introduced me to
your captains of industry and I noticed
that these people were morons and I said
Wow you know so they're not it really
in control right Wow
Sam is a Sam are you can you mute Sam or
are you are we
your daughter I might sound like it
sounds like anyone okay yeah so so
here's the thing the stuff that you we
talk about on streams and the points
that are brought up that anyone can
check up on usually is not known by the
the elite and the people that are running
society it and I'm saying that to
whoever's listening and can comprehend
what's being said here or any has been
said a sense of confidence but on the
other hand it should be unnerving
because the people that are controlling
let's say piloting are incompetent right
so but what again should give you
confidence is the gods are in control
and the and the most high God has got
your back to make sure that you know
there his plan takes place from that
sense in other words he's got your back
and they don't have to ponder doom and
gloom and we're just going to be a big
black cinder forever right like I just
said there's no forever but you know in
scripture right yeah there is no ultimate
total complete destruction so you're
fine on that because the plan doesn't
allow that so yeah yeah but you know the
other thing is you know no matter how
faithful quote-unquote you are if you
get up in the middle of the night to get
a drink of water and you stub your big
toe on the on the kitchen chair and it
hurts yeah that that sucks doesn't it so
you don't want to be put in a torture
chamber right because you're susceptible
to pain so you know there's things that
hurt you know speaking of which things
that hurt I just want to give a little
another I don't have to about the human
body I was sharpening knives yesterday
and you know you always have to you
always have to you know say respect you
know the knife you know it's because it
could hurt you know it's very sharp
right well I got a little careless and I
kind of like swept my hand across the
counter and the back edge of above the
hilt of a Japanese blade hit my finger
and like imagine a 90-degree corner of
the knife triangulating and I made that
that that that the slushy sound you know
when you're cutting an orange you know
so you know it's not good it went in
pretty deep you know when you hear the
flesh slushing like you're cutting for
you can hear the flesh getting cut went
in pretty good and I said oh shit that
went in pretty deep because I saw how
deep it went when I pulled it out and
first thing I did is I grabbed a small
piece of paper towel you know about an
inch wide three inches long wrapped it
around and then electrical tape which I
have electric I have about ten rolls of
electrical tape when I buy electrical
tape I buy the ten pack I get home I
open it and I toss one on the counter I
toss one in the drawer I toss one in the
kitchen table one in the bedroom I toss
one outside on the counter one in the
car so if there's an injury you know
you've got electrical tape it's flexible
and you can make it really tight right
right so that's why I said electrical
tape it wasn't specific you know other
than all I have that around that's like
the you know thing that I have for for
multiple uses especially for this
purpose and I made it really really
tight the tip of the finger this was the
right forefinger it was at the second
digit down and it turned blue I removed
the removed the after 15 minutes I
removed the entire the tape and the
paper came off the reason you want to
put paper is it's a bond breaker so the
tape doesn't stick to the skin so when
you remove it it doesn't pull the pull
the wound open you see that's why you
need a body it's called a bond breaker
you know something that if you put
something sticky on something that
shouldn't be disturbed by the stickiness
you need a bond breaker you know in
certain industries or fields we you
know if you use a masking tape we put a
piece of some wax or oil you know and
then area you know it's not going to
stick there right a release agent is
another term for it and it came off
perfectly and I looked at it and it did
you could hardly see it but I knew if I
were to budget it would just be an
opening into the finger and then what I
did is I switched to paper towel and
band-aids because I had time because you
know initially my point here is that
when it initially happened within 30
seconds it was already wrapped tight
well today it's not wrapped and I'm
looking at it it looks like a very minor
paper cut and earlier while we were
speaking I was making coffee and I wrapped
the lemon and I got some lemon juice on
it and boy did it hurt from that so I
wrapped it just now yeah Wow now
typically I would say if it were just a
little bigger someone would go to the
hospital for that and you know when you
go to the hospital what they want to do
oh yeah so and it's just bear and so in
two more days it'll be completely gone
and no evidence of it so I just want to
give a little testament to wrapping it
tight methodically you know amazing it
is I don't know if you've ever I don't
know if Sam or Bruce either one of you
have first-hand experience with what
I'm talking about wrapping it tight and
having very rapidly extremely rapid
healing cuts and occasionally I get a
little pain in the finger or something
I'll give her a wrap and oh yeah it
works does it where you get it very
rapid healing with a cut broken skin is
what I'm trying to say something more
evident overnight to two days or you
know three days for something that
normally take two weeks it also works for
burns by the way or anything anything
that will damage the vacuum of the body
that could you imagine if the medical
technicians in their schools were to
acknowledge that the body is under a
slight vacuum and you know you know what
that would do right it would collapse
their system because now all of their
research and study would be starting
from ground zero wouldn't it or to
ground on that ground zero that's a
place of a nuclear explosion
ground first level they would be like
they were a hundred years ago or 75
years or one yeah isn't that kind of
scary for them to admit that yes that's
why they're never going to do it I
recently had someone email me revenue
well yeah because they don't even know
you know years ago I used to prank the
doctors when so when I run into someone
who had just come out of medical school
and they'd say that I'd say oh so you
want to heal people you know and they
look at me like huh what no I don't
know what you're talking about so enough
of game playing um anything else Sam
speak but by the way before I ask you
that I want to interject something
speaking I've I haven't been hearing I
haven't been active on the internet or
speaking with people on stuff but I
noticed two or three years ago or if not
maybe four there was a big boom in
video game stuff what happened to that
did it just die like like hip-hop or
what no I mean hip-hop not dead either
no I know it's not it's not hitting no
video games or is I haven't looked at
the recent numbers for the last couple
years but I believe that it is as popular
as ever have they got more I think
they're more migrated being just on the
net now rather than going out and
purchasing they still have small lay on
walls yeah I can't attest to that I mean
what's happened over the past maybe
seven eight nine years is that the mobile
gaming has taken over so people play
games on their phones and their iPads a
lot more than they used to so kind of
lesser quality less cheaper more cheaper
made games come out on mobile platforms
and you know children find that to be
just as entertaining as anything else
because obviously they can't discern
anything it's equally as engaging but
your console game still selling the
millions I mean the PlayStation 4 still
had very good sales numbers and the
culture is still vibrant but it's just
that things have moved things have
moved into the realm of the iPad and
the iPhone where it's like you download
you know crappy games off the App Store
and children don't have any problems
with playing that right so in other words
it's effect on society is is in trend
it's not it's entrenched but it hasn't
it's not you know digging away anymore
it's just kind of leveled out well it's
it's standardized in the sense that it's
expected to be there so no it doesn't
have the same cultural impact others
don't know that in the late 90s versions
are always coming out new updates and
something to keep people in right yeah
yeah but in other words they're not
making movies about video games like
they did a while back right not as much
I don't really keep track of them people
much yeah cuz I you know here's the I
was at a at the shops recently and they
had some virtual reality glasses that
you put on I thought I was thinking that
was for video yeah that's a new a new
fad that's coming out I don't know if
they really hit a plateau with that one
yet I think they're still in creation
mode and more bigger I think they're
like the beta that's why I'm gonna
VHS that's why I'm gonna stick to the
statement that all this stuff that's
been going on with the internet is just
to get everyone ready for what's really
coming you know which is just
interconnecting everyone with audio
video so they can see certain things and
there'll be no excuses that I missed
that you know same thing that Richard
Day said you know connectivities yeah
yep yeah and then the other thing that I
think they brought up in that interview
was the discrediting of those that don't
go along with it you know you know they
call you a phobe yeah I never understand
like arachnophobia is people that are
afraid of you know spiders but homophobia
what are you afraid of homos right I
mean is he gonna is he gonna like hit
you you know well I mean I don't
understand you know so these are things
that people are not thinking when they
say these things you know what I mean
or Islamophobia well you're afraid of
Muslims you know they should they should
be afraid of themselves but you know
nonetheless yeah the discrediting and
the other thing I've noticed especially
when you're dealing with attorneys and
doctors people that social rank when you
bring up like something like in Greek
speak they say oh you have extremist
views you know that's yeah that's just a
very general term is it extreme how you
know is it do you you know what's in the
middle that you're raising well they
expect you to go to a defensive posture
and yeah it's like you're being set up
the minute to get the last word out of
their mouth yeah they're just morons
you know how can you sit through law
school how can they sit through law
school or medical school and and absorb
all that bullshit literally it is
bullshit bad science BS or just you know
bovine extramen or whatever and then go
into a field that you know is further on
controlled by you know bogus industry
it's just amazing you know it could you
know
you know the other simple thing to look
at is you know the higher up you go in
human society the higher and more
specialized the training the more
removed it is from the thing that it's
supposed to be you know focusing on or
working on yeah
modernized Gustav Le Bon
yeah it's just yeah autopilot just oh
you know one other thing I looked up
some of the inscriptions you remember on
the last sonic event I brought up in
something what's called the New
Testament that the gates of hell will
not prevail yes you know against the
this is the rock in a minute because
remember when you look at those gates of
hell those are that's a rocky air it's
you know it's kind of like Petro you
know where they carve into the mountain
mm-hmm right so it's the rock statement
also goes back to the time of Moses you
know what the cleft in the rock past
behind me hit the rock get water you
know but the theme was when he says this
is the rock or the stone that I will
build my group on Ecclesia which is just
my mob or group in the future right and
the gates of hell will not prevail
which was kind of ironic because the
gates of hell were prevailing at the
time you know it didn't make any sense
you know so he if you used it in that
day contemporarily he was obviously
speaking of the future but what's
interesting if you start looking at some
of the inscriptions I didn't bookmark it
but I went to images gates of hell and
it was very it was up quite a bit I was
looking into what was inscribed on there
is they were in in Greek it said things
like do as thou wilt Alistair Crowley
said that you know the law you know yeah
law is that as it will so that's where
Crowley I would suggest that you know
people say Oh Crowley should do this I
will that's not Crowley and that's comes
from the gates of hell and how I propose
right now because when you when you know
people think that you know Crowley was
dealing with Satan and he would go he
was into hell and even these people are
you know they don't know the people in
the occult just like they call certain
people Satanists like the Church of
Satan the church of said all that if you
talk if you not you know hopefully
they're too dumb to really sit down and
talk to but if you watch an interview
with them and all that they don't know
anything about these the spirit realm
other than that what they narrow deity
they can evoke they actually think that
Christianity is biblical you know they
had those if you ever listen to gates of
hell and lots of locations sure yeah so
so in other words how can these idiots
get away with it because they're all you
know you know how it was humanity is so
stupid from the bottom to the top how
are they getting away and getting things
done this is the miracle of it you know
hmm but yeah again that the New
Testament yes it's external input
they're being guided like got drones I
think the term drones was used well for
bees and the insect world and then on
people and before they actually the
predominant term when you hurt you the
mental you know image of drone now is
one of these remote-control helicopter
things or you know whatever right but
people were called drones for a little
while also there but something like for
example I always shy away from discussing
what's called the New Testament for the
reasons very simply I said it was never
meant to be a worldwide you know thing
it was a bunch of letters and testaments
it will be in the end right but in the
interim it wasn't but it's fine to do so
because no one will understand it anyway
right because of its most people have
subscribed to some religious cult which
prevents them from you know the mental
model that they have prevents them from
comprehending it objectively so and
then again if you start just discussing
the Old Testament most people think
you're old-fashioned and it's part of a
cult anyway you see so the entire
scriptural context to go in that
direction and discuss topics is very
difficult to do it as a venture or you
know full-time or make a living doing it
which is appropriate by the way if
you're going to teach on any subject you
can teach on any subject right and you
should be compensated but like I
mentioned with here in Tucson this is
where a guy who's that evangelist
started the UCG United Church of God the
little little short guy looked like a
little pugly and a little guy with the
way Armstrong oh he when they ousted him
our Herbert arms when they asked him
when he came here to Tucson a bunch of
his people were here and Ernest L
Martin also graduated from his
worldwide college or whatever I forgot
what it's called Ambassador College and
so there was a big enclave of Ernest
Martin's people and his people here and
when I started learning about Scripture
and I brought some studying Scripture oh
you need to meet this guy or this guy
because he worked with blah blah blah
blah blah so my I don't know who the
hell that was oh great at the time I was
naive is 16 17 years ago I was like oh
great maybe if I go talk to these people
who are twice my age and have been doing
it all their lives they'll help me along
really fast right wrong so actually they
did in many aspects the foundation work
but you should have seen what happened
after maybe a year or two when I
approached them and I said you know
there's no Saturday in here there's no
Sunday or Monday or Tuesday that's the
Pope's work schedule and it's not the
and you know why are you keep saying
Jesus why don't if you're going to use
the letter J why don't you just say Josh
Joshua that's more accurate right because
Yeshua right or Joshua same name like
the book of Joshua so what they did was
when you hear the word Jesus that's
creating a different mythical figure
that's extra biblical by the way you
know because if they were to stay
biblical they wouldn't be a Jesus it
would be Joshua through the New
Testament but because they needed to
create an extra biblical thing they call
it Jesus but when I brought up about
three or four salient points that were
just blatantly obvious but you know
again you know they were also very
pro-christian or real they said they
kept using terms like a real Christian
what do you mean a real what show me
what a fake one does that you know well
when I approached these old heads that
were you know Ernest L Martin people
and worked with him and also the
Armstrong people they sat me down one
day and they I thought they were going
to kill me they thought they were going
to put violence on me because they
brought me into an area I couldn't get
out you're like listen we cannot do and
we will not consider what you're saying
you have misunderstood what you're
saying we've been told that if you say
if we you if we do or say the things
that you're saying you know regarding
timekeeping and names and all that that
divides people and it break and you
cannot build an organization on it and
also we won't be able to sell any books
and we won't be able to be paid for our
work and I looked at him and I'm like
wow that's pretty honest but that's
pretty scumbag II too you know what I
mean
Wow yeah and if that left me an
impression so for like two weeks I didn't
do anything and I was like you know what
fuck these old heads man I'm sticking to
it you know this is not the family show
anymore right raising medical terms but
forget about these old heads it Pope's
work schedule forget it
these people on the I ain't I ain't got
no allegiance to no Jesus you as you
denying Jesus shit ain't nothing there
deny or accept yeah you know it's like
you know once you use the names once you
figure out how to keep time you know so
what this means is you know and here's
the other thing like Jack Fresco says
you know don't put a statue of me don't
name it because that puts a straight
jacket on the future how about other
people looking at Scripture and
examining stuff that's obvious that you
know beyond what I've done you know which
is you know the Pope's work schedule and
the concepts of these things
significant you know or not yeah how come
you know where I like to see more
advancement on it you know where is the
advancement being done where is it
you know what you know I'd scan these
I don't have a notion I'll put on the
internet I mean I think Thomas on the
chat put and I commented a guy with the
judges it was probably very few articles
I don't think that article is more than
a few years old but the repeat of judges
and I hate going nothing on you know
Thomas I'm glad that he put it up and
he's very thoughtful he's diligent but
why I hate going to these mess ionic
websites these these guys I think if they
mix Judaism and Christianity they got it
that's like mixing you know horse cow
and dog poo all together and making a you
know that's better no it's still poop
you know but the interesting thing about
that article repeat of judges I found
that the guy was I said he was asleep at
the wheel but on the road right he he
didn't I don't think I didn't I tend to
just glance over stuff like that but he
didn't mention there was a similarity
between the fourth Prime Minister and
the fourth judge did he in that article
no no and I stress I've been stressing
that for a while you know the repeat
right right he says there might be a
repeat but he that's like so obvious
right that the fourth judge is a woman
Deborah and the fourth Prime Minister is
a woman right Golda Meir and he didn't
mention it at least to the readership
is he asleep yes well he had a lot of
Christianity in there with himself and
some jewelry to you know yeah it's
sickening but at the same time you know
at least he did it you know what
sickening is that you have people that
are aptly trained and they're not
retarded or idiots or morons medically
you know what I mean if you put him
under a CAT scan you know their brain is
working right it of course there's
cosmic censorship and all that other
mental modeling is running fine yeah
everything's fine how come they don't see
you know a little just a little bit more
and start getting some momentum well
it's not time yet or it's sickening to
same thing can't sell books yeah yeah
that's the sickening part of it you know
also you know I'm not going to win a
popularity contest if I if I start
noticing things you know very often you
know for especially in America you're
told to be individualistic and do all
this express yourself but if you're ever
an individual by yourself dealing with a
doctor a lawyer a cop a judge you know
what they always tell you private you
have to be like everybody else
yeah they do that all the time I hear it
all the time I've seen it done you know
you have to be like everybody on what
they do schizophrenic yep but they but
then they say that you could do
anything be yourself express yourself on
one side the other side so which one is
it it's schizophrenia is what is it's
tearing the psyche apart right tearing
the mind used to say settle two plates
one for each face you know yeah there you
go it's kind of just put up with it don't
do anything food clothing and shelter and
that you know that in order in order to
get the level of quality that you desire
or want to afford for food cloth or
shelter you're that's when you should be
doing something you know what I mean and
then whatever of knowledge that you want
to be rewarded with in study and
hopefully you're not so censored that
you can't see it like the guy who wrote
the article with the judges and didn't
even bother pointing out even in a
footnote that the fourth judges look like
a pretty direct repeat you know yeah or
we won't say this because we're no one
will want to buy our books we have to
yeah yeah JDS us and Chris and Christian
stuff oh shit not time yet sad also by
the way those people like the Martin
people in the Armstrong people and the
other similar people that come from those
called whatever no matter how much they
study you know they're always still
going to give a political reason for
what's going on you know that right
you see it all the time I've been
around these old heads that were around
these guys and we're like oh yeah this
country yeah you know whatever you know
at the time it was Bush jr.
was an
office right it was like this country you
know whatever I was in trouble yeah I
didn't have trouble because of Bush
you're in trouble because you do you
ever you're under the goddess religion
oh no we can't say anything about that
because they're not saying it's a
goddess religion I'm like shit man
they're putting a statue in front of you
and they're telling you you're serving
it that's all enough for me and if you
go to their courts they tell you we
don't go by those laws that's enough for
me you know so you have you ever seen a
film called founder I was about the
McDonald's um if you have a wait it's
called what's his name the guy who
played Beetlejuice the actor this place
found shows you how he swindled he
actually the guys was the McDonald's
brothers were jerk offs and they he
basically took the company from it's one
of those things if you just heard the
story that this guy comes in crock Ray
crock and he takes the company from the
McDonald's brothers I feel sorry for the
McDonald's because when you watch this
movie tends to be pretty objective you
don't have any sympathy for the
McDonald's founders they were real
assholes from a business perspective so
you kind of mix you kind of hate yourself
for liking the villain you know what I
mean it's like it's like watching a mob
movie and you find yourself sympathizing
with the mobster more than the victims
you know you feel like something's wrong
you shouldn't be doing that you know but
if you see the Ray Kroc movie the found
movie called founder it's about
McDonald's was done a few years ago he
says America is about America is about
the do the Pledge of Allegiance and the
US Constitution in the church yes that's
actually from the 50s and 60s
illustrations of people doing the Pledge
of Allegiance and in church I think they
still do when they have like their little
get-togethers and stuff and Bible
studies some places yeah so yeah this is
this is why they retain using the JES
US and the Christian memes and the
church memes I'm telling you whenever
you hear the JES US either laugh at them
or run or you're listening to some
stupid shit the reason why is because
it's so obvious that in order to adhere
to even a loose adherence of a modicum
of what's biblical it should have been
Joshua if you're going to use a J and
not JES US by using the J the J wasn't
even invented until what 500 years ago
that's right maybe a little earlier but
yeah around the 13 to 1500s but I would
suggest that if you have to use the J
because what's the sixth book in the
Bible the book of what Joshua is the
sixth book right okay which is Yeshua
was so what is what is the Christ's name
Yeshua right now it's spelled Yahshua
but in in Sephardic Hebrew you pronounce
it Yeshua or Yeshua or Yeshua not
Yehoshua and all this other stuff it's
Yeshua the the YA SHA you know becomes
a sound you know because Sephardic Jew I
think was was is the chosen dialect of
modern Hebrew so to communicate with
someone in Hebrew you would say Yeshua
you could say Yahshua it's close but
they would say Yeshua so if you have to
use a letter J like Jeremiah or Job or
Judah or Joshua there is no Jesus it's
Joshua sorry now what they're doing the
mental modeling and the mind fuck and
the brainwashing is you know how they
have to tell you what they're doing
before they do it to you but you don't
realize it right what they're doing by
calling him JESUS they're telling you
this is extra biblical stuff it's not
really part of this but we can't use
Joshua and portray him the way we're
portraying him you know nailed to a cross
wearing a diaper and church and all
this other bullshit we can't do that
because that'll get us an even deeper
trouble at least later on we can say
well it was JESUS everybody knows that
didn't exist see along with the crowd
nor did make money yeah but if they
called him Joshua right well now they
can't they can't stick a guy with long
hair wearing a diaper on a crucifix now
right they can't have a little manger
scene with the three wise men you know
and they have the loose team they put
out they can't do Christmas now yeah
least wise guys the three wise guys
right and they can't do it but because
it's JESUS obviously that has nothing to
do with anything so we can now we can do
the rest you see it so it gives them
license and this is I'm not being there
I'm not representing them and I'm not
sure this is the methodology behind it
but this is what I can objectify from it
it is so blatantly obvious that it
should be Joshua and not JESUS that the
reason why it's not Joshua and it is
JESUS so they could get away with the
rest of the stuff they are and later on
if they're called on it they could say
well this was for JESUS not Joshua you
see yeah always a fallback yeah it's a
it's a sick fallback but these people
you know there's a what was I used to
say I've looked high and low for you like
but obviously enough look low enough
yeah you know so this is a yeah a level
of insanity that even a semi-rational
mind won't find you know that's why you
find plausible that's why the banking if
you start understanding the banking it's
so insane that no wonder it's a secret
because if you just told the person
average pedestrian about Zelle that's
that's too crazy I've told many people
through the years like oh no that what
you're telling me Greek can't be true
because the public would have an outcry
if that was true oh boy oh boy so you
can't work with someone like that when
they put that up as a comment I'll throw
the USC 12 for one one just see if
anybody bites on it
oh no they can't they don't even
copy even though it's written on a fifth
sixth side maybe eighth grade level tops
they can't comprehend it because those
words you know just like different
colored beads when you string them
together in different orders you could
form different patterns right so they do
understand they understand the words each
individual word if you were to separate
from the title 12 section 411 they do
comprehend the words but once you string
them the way together the first 20 words
as they are in the code all the
understanding goes away because how
could it be yeah how could it be you
know that doesn't how can I be you know
it's so blatantly obvious but it's so
blatantly hidden the two don't go
together you see what were you gonna say
Sam I was gonna say that I'm probably
gonna bow out just because it's getting
late on my end okay I think we will to
have been going for three hours yeah
something like that yeah so yeah that
that's that's the game and the hierarchy
and all that I hope we've satisfied
about 12 people streaming out there
listening few posting in blog so I was
very very very involved that's like me
that's 12 people that's eight more than
can understand what we say I found that
there's usually three or four people
within you know earshot that get it you
know and out of those three or four
people that get it point three of them a
third of one person might actually do
some homework or tell someone else well
let's hope that I'm not this is factual
I'm giving you the fact this is not to
be disparaging or Greek is an asshole
this is just the facts you know so sure
this is this kind of talk doesn't go
anywhere won't go anywhere right now and
yeah food clothing shelter I got myself
a big-ass raised big-ass raised glazed
donut I'm gonna warm it up just slightly
I'm gonna enjoy that with some of this
chicory coffee I'll take care of that
finger oh it's taken care of already
good good remember it's the first the
first 30 if you can get it immediately
minutes no no 30 seconds three minutes
seconds for the wrap yes yeah well
immediately if you can do it immediately
anything within arm's reach or 30 seconds
or just time is the enemy on this not
your body and not the kind of time is
the enemy I have your advice and picked
up many rolls of black tape for myself
also good yeah something now this is
more advanced if you run into someone who
didn't know about squeezing or anything
and they have like a keloid or a big-ass
scab or whatever I use an analogy you
know when a someone's leg breaks or arm
breaks and they don't set it right how
do they fix that they have to do what
break it again right yeah yeah so what
you have to do is if someone has a wound
or a scar or whatever you actually have
to get in there and cut away at it get
it pull out all the tissue with a
tweezer or whatever you have to and
basically create the wound all over again
and then make it tight and wrap it down
like a plastic surge that's where the
plastic surgery comes in where they you
know if you have I know a plastic
surgeon and it's I looked at some of his
technical manuals I said this is
basically like sculpture you know if you
make a bust if you make a bust out of
clay and you don't like it you come back
and you chop away at it or add some more
right yeah literally so yeah okay so
alright Sam thanks Bruce yes thank you
Sam good night Greek and thank you very
much for for all this oh yeah great
thanks guys take care ciao folks have a
good night