Okay.
Should we drop a link on the chat.
Okay, noise level in the background has gone up by you.
But that's fine.
This is a, this is a prototype anyway.
So we are so, so it is going.
Okay, cool.
All right, so this is another still beta testing because there hasn't been anything scheduled yet.
And I would say that.
It'll, it'll be scheduled some kind of sonic events schedule schedule as the Brits say, and probably just continue on more information, I guess, things on discernment right and because there still seems to be a lot of it lacking out there well I'm not noticing any change not because I'm expecting it.
That's a foolish thing to expect anything other than what you've seen already.
Other than understanding what the times are about.
So, I would say that we'll keep the sonic events going will be some kind of schedule.
Maybe once or even twice a week or more let's see how it goes and redoing of the uncommon radio site I'll send out an email.
I guess alert or, you know, email blast everyone on the list let them know that it's a new Sasonic event that's being scheduled, probably be using the Zulu time wind up toy thing, you know, yeah, as a general time for coordinating.
And, yeah, that's pretty much it.
I don't think there's anything in in the chat tango chat anyone asking any questions or anything to spark off a one way conversation or something, other than you and I having a conversation.
I couldn't always go to the emails, and there's been a lot of email questions constantly.
I wouldn't say the email questions are anything to you know the answers to the being questions you know that I refer back answer back with an answer best I can.
I think there's a lot of stuff in there that's challenging I think it's all very basic.
There have been a few interesting comments coming through emails.
You know just real minor stuff, but still there's communication back and forth.
So if anyone wants to get in touch with the Greek it's uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com.
And that's a numeric one.
And, you know, get back to anyone who wants to query through the email as well.
But essentially things are still moving along it's the it's the northern hemisphere is going through fall and then winter.
Right now we seem to be have started the fall season, which is the breaking down period and there's events you know almost predictable right when you understand that, that lead to more critical changes in society typical typically happen in the fall.
I think here in America there was another shooting, you know, of course, if it's on TV, or if it's in a comes through as an official story it's quite the opposite of what you're being told, or not a polar opposite, but it's not the way it is.
It's really sifting through poop to get corn that's edible.
So, anyway, it's good to look at the edible corn at a distance.
Right, don't try to eat it.
That's basically the the aspect of official stories and, and such only because they're like that because the quote unquote and officials authorities, the entitled classes are accommodating the society.
If the society was ready to accept higher quality information or presentation.
They would have to present it as such and, and otherwise they wouldn't last.
So the reason why, when you go to university or turn on the television, or look at official stories, or anything in its official capacity whether it's religious academic legal governmental scientific, it's a dummy load.
And they're providing it in such a poor fashion to accommodate the people, see if the people were accommodated with better quality stuff they would have to change, they wouldn't last if they didn't so that that's an interesting thing there's a lot of criticism on how poor, the, the quality, well, I wouldn't say much criticism or a lot, but there has been on the criticism of the authorities of any field on how poor it is but.
But essentially still people have fallen for the, the major, the, the more, more pranking oriented.
The entity is or the part of society is the more people still fall for it they don't see it like what you know most people will say yeah it's just television yeah of course you know or yeah it's they lie about this or whatever, in the entertainment or the news or the government will but the people still take very seriously the medical society the legal society.
And the unit and the academic society and because, very simply, their, their pranks are still very high order pranking, you know, people have still fallen for the concept that without the current medical society or system they are before into ill health.
Most people, and without the current legal society they're going to befall to lawlessness, and without the academic society they'll be, be befallen to ignorance and it's quite the opposite.
Those are still the legal medical and academic society are the most high level pranking and of course you must throw in there the religious ones whether it's the Christian faith, the Jewish faith Judean, the Muslim, the Buddhism or any of the Hindi Eastern culture, and all the derivations thereof they are also engaged in severe and heavy pranking.
So people still somewhat take it seriously.
So it's unfortunate to see that, but it's unfortunate to say that basically as well.
Only because you're looking at it, it's planetary wide, you know, it's, you know, again, this is a cosmic thing.
When you're looking at the entire planet at this point the way it is.
People years ago used to migrate to other or emigrate, I should say, to other countries for a better life and that is finished.
Now the only time people are moving around is because of a quote unquote job, or because they're just simply blowing the place up.
I just want to throw this little bit of things of discernment.
This is nothing planned just making some comments here.
What's interesting, you know, if you look at what's going on in the Middle East just to toggle back and forth various societies.
It's very easy to see this Daesh or ISIS movement that's been going on for a few years now is a Western capitalist based agenda.
And all of, not some, but all of the people that are fighting for the ISIS and Daesh are mercenary types, or heavily alcoholic, heavily drugged out.
I wouldn't say all of them are as a general rule, yes, you will engage in those things if you're in that type of army.
But the reason why I'm saying that it is a capitalist tool is very simple.
One of the definitions of capitalism is that when you're finished using something, destroy it so no one else can use it.
And then we're going to bring this up as a discernment aspect.
If you want to understand if there is a capitalist tool behind something, you will see complete destruction, material destruction, and also, you know, a level of social order being destroyed.
Because, again, just to repeat, one of the definitions of capitalism is that when you're finished using something, you destroy it so no one else can use it.
There's very little charity or consideration or anything like that.
And by the way, people still want capitalism and they don't even know what it does.
But again, back to the Daesh and the ISIS concept.
It's very easy to see that they are a capitalist tool because they are not going in there, as said, to change the minds or inflict a new society of radical Islam, let's say, or very conservative Islam, but not at all.
And the main reason why is because they're simply just blowing everything up.
People that want to go in and change a mindset or a society or sort of make it more conservative or whatever, as they proclaim, do not destroy buildings, roads, facilities, and all the things that you see there.
If you look at photographs of places that they've been through, they just are into utter destruction, which also, on a personal level, these guys are on various forms of drugs.
It's almost mandatory that they are, and alcohol and various other things, even though they say they shouldn't be doing it.
So it's very easy to see that it's a capitalist tool.
And when you do see, for example, a militarized movement going through a society and they do not destroy all the buildings and roads and just outwardly kill everyone, there is an aspect of what you might consider, okay, this is more of a reformist movement now coming through.
But yeah, people have been so – I wouldn't say brainwashed, but you could say brainwashed or enticed into believing this boogeyman called ISIS or Daesh or whatever, the caliphate system that they're trying to install.
That is purely a Western capitalist movement.
Again, simply just look at the photographs of the places they've been through.
Everything is just completely and utterly destroyed.
The Americans, by the way, that is their military thing.
I mean what they're good at is – they're not good at facing other armies in the field.
That's a fact.
You can look at the history of that.
Very rarely, if you look at all of the wars that the Americans have ever been involved in, there is a very small partly sum of battles that have been recorded where the Americans are engaging another army or military force.
The majority of what you hear is that they are bombing civilian targets.
That's why behind closed doors, the Americans since World War II have been known as a terrorist nation or terrorist acts.
That's why you had the Marshall Plan and stuff and the rebuilding of Japan.
They had to come in and clean up all the crap they did.
It's not under the engagement of enemy in the field.
So basically, the Americans are just good at blowing up stuff, women, children, elderly, hospitals, schools, buildings, and you'll never really hear them engaging another army.
Of course, unless it's something that's utterly disorganized and whatever.
I'm not saying ever, but most likely ever, you're not.
So just keep that in the back of your mind because the Americans are still being touted as being the military police force.
I wouldn't say – well, they're keystone cops if they are the police force.
I'm not trying to be pejorative to them or whatever, but it just happens to be the truth that you could just assess on your own.
So you can see one of the trademark results is this ISIS Daesh movement in the Middle East is very, quote-unquote, American.
And also you've seen there's been a lot of reporting in independent media of how there's always some kind of American special forces behind the scenes directing it.
So yeah, it's quite interesting to bring that up as well because it's just ongoing and there doesn't seem to be much awareness of that.
It's just everyone still goes about whatever they want to do and think, oh yeah, I've heard of ISIS.
I see, yeah, they're trying to do this or that.
Well, not really.
Can you just rely on a conspiracy theory that it's really an American, French and Western English tool?
Of course Israel is thrown in there for intelligence because they're the best in the world still at it.
Or can you just not have heard those conspiracies, theories or conspiracies?
It is really a conspiracy and just look at the results of what they're doing.
What I'm trying to suggest here is that if you hadn't been listening to any investigative work on what's going on behind the formation of Daesh or ISIS and all that behind the scenes, you just simply need to look at a photograph of places that they've been through.
And bear in the back of your mind, if you see utter and complete destruction as you see what they're doing in Syria and places of Iraq and Mosul and stuff like that, you will see that that is a capitalist, trained, motivated operation, not one that is, let's say, there to reform a culture as stated.
So I just wanted to throw that in there because that's something that when you look at the Middle East and the ISIS-Daesh story comes up, you just see utter destruction and most people still don't know how to recognize the fingerprint of something like that.
I guess they're too oblivious, but that's okay.
That's just the way things are on planet Earth.
So anyway, going back to just stating how it's unfortunate there still are some major, major pranking institutions that are on the planet.
The Legal Society, Religious Society, the Academic and the Medical Society are probably the most pranking.
And they've captured the spirits or the minds of the majority of the people on this planet in a very, I should say, critical way.
Of course, there's what are considered alternative movements in all of those, but the wholesale majority still does not comprehend the level of pranking that the Religious Societies, the Medical, Academic and Legal Societies are putting on them.
And I'm just bringing this up because this past week I've been more and more aware of it,
simply just because I've been on a conference call or two regarding some of those societies, let's say the Legal and Medical ones,
and I've noticed how even the most advanced thinkers, quote-unquote, still have bought into the falseness of what's being put forward in the Legal and Medical Society, especially.
One of the biggest pranks that you will see, let's say, with the Legal Society is the concept of an attorney or a bar associate member.
What's interesting is I've said before, none of the attorneys or, quote-unquote, lawyers, because a lawyer is not an attorney, but an American, there is a code that says that they are, right?
Okay, but that doesn't really matter because no one reads the codes.
Anyway, none of them know any law.
They give the impression that they do, and they don't know law as defined.
I'll give you an example.
I took some scribbling notes, and anyone could look this up on their own.
See if I could dig them out here.
I just have a clipboard.
This is like the past week's rations.
I thought I'd throw them out there.
Let's get some cheaters and see if I could pull up the code.
There's an interesting code.
Have you ever heard, for example, I think I still have Bruce here, that the courts are administrative, right?
These are administrators.
The judge or administrators are administrating justice and all this other stuff, right?
I remember that.
Anyone looks up, I think it's 28 U.S.C. 607, which is United States Code.
I'm going to do it right now and read it.
It's going to be quite interesting because these guys are administrators.
I just want to show you something, how I can prove everything.
When I say these guys don't know any law, there's not an attorney that knows any of this.
They don't have to.
If you bring it up, they'll just say, well, that's not what they do.
They don't use law in there, and I'll tell you why.
I'll show you right now.
I'll show you how the pranking works.
It's very simple.
28 U.S. Code Section 607, Practice of Law Prohibited.
An officer or employee of the administrative office shall not engage directly or indirectly in the practice of law in any court of the United States.
June 25, 1948, Chapter 646, 62, Stat 915.
That's it.
It's just 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 15 words.
28 U.S.C. Code Section 607.
It's titled Practice of Law Prohibited.
It's just one sentence.
And this is it again.
An officer or employee of the administrative office shall not engage directly or indirectly in the practice of law in any court of the United States.
That's it.
I know.
That's why there are attorneys at law, not in law.
You're at law.
You're not in law.
Like your in-laws are in law.
Get it?
Right.
So I have a whole – I have these little anomalous codes that are still viable and they should know.
There's not an attorney on the planet that knows that by the way.
Now, if you said to an attorney, do you know 28 U.S.C.? They'll say, yeah, I've heard of it.
607, they might lie and say, yeah, I know, whatever, because they're all liars.
I mean not some of them, all of them.
But okay.
So I just wanted to bring up a little thing like that.
But they all are administrative.
By the way, when you go to the legal society, a traffic ticket or anything else, they take you to a judicial court.
There are no judicial matters really.
The only time you have a judicial matter is when a neighbor's dog jumps the fence, bites your leg.
You go back to the neighbor and say the dog bit the leg.
You need to compensate me for that.
And he ignores you or tells you to go screw yourself.
Well, that's a judicial matter.
But if someone writes you a ticket, a DUI, drug possession, tax stuff, stealing, all that stuff is administrative.
Now, stealing could be judicial if the person you stole from goes after you because you asked them to pay back twice and they didn't, you see.
So there are very few judicial matters.
Anything that any government, state, city, local, federal or whatever approaches you that is nonjudicial, but they always stuff you into a judicial court.
You see, so there's the level of print and there are no attorneys that know this, by the way.
Now, that doesn't mean that they're capable of knowing it.
Yes, of course they are.
But once they start bringing this up, they will become disbarred.
The same reason a medical doctor will lose a license to practice if he brings up how the human body works and which is a fact also.
So now with the doctors, just to harp on them a little bit, they still have this thing going on right now.
It's a subculture within their culture.
When they have a patient that takes up too much time and they can't properly diagnose, their biggest excuse now is you probably have some kind of virus.
That's their latest fashion trend.
And I would say it's been going on for about a decade, but it's still going on.
And none of these idiots, meaning the MDs, ever stop and think, has anyone ever seen a virus?
The answer to that is no.
You will never see a virus.
The closest thing you're going to come to it is an artist rendering, just like black holes with the academics.
No one has ever seen a black hole, just artist renderings, right?
It's theoretical.
And it's quite the moneymaker, too.
Right, yeah.
And also there's been people that have challenged the establishment, you know, show me the virus.
Well, it's smaller.
It's so small we can't even see an electron microscope.
It's so small it doesn't exist, right?
So, and actually if you, I've mentioned this to several doctors, they go blank because they wouldn't, if they had any sense, they wouldn't be doctors, right?
In this society, at least.
Actually, there would be a yearning.
I would advise anyone, if you wanted to go into that field, refrain from it because you're going to be subject to a level of idiocy that is, you know, befuddles anyone that's even halfway rational.
Of course, there are people still needed in the emergency services, you know, obviously, but I didn't say doctors.
Again, you know, why isn't there training on how to sew a leg back on?
It's not that difficult, by the way, if you have a local place.
I notice that there are more and more trauma clinics opening up in malls and storefronts.
I don't know if it's by you as well in the Midwest.
Yes, it is.
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's interesting, but they still follow the same routine in many ways.
But, you know, they still don't know how the body works at all.
They don't know how the body ingests anything.
You know, they still think there's actual absorption.
They don't know how the body heals.
They don't understand.
They've been fooled themselves.
That's why you don't get the best and the brightest people going to those fields, you see.
So that is just bouncing back and forth here between the medical and legal society, or the leticals.
Bouncing back and forth between those morons.
And they're pretty evil, by the way, as a group.
I wouldn't say every single one of them in the medical society and the legal society are evil, but as a group they are classified as such, with the slightest discernment, very easily.
The other most evil group, it would be the religious groups, in terms of the position that they're in.
If you look at any of the ancient writs, it clearly states that this planet and everything within its society is underneath the powers of a malicious or malevolent, I should say, malevolent spiritual entity.
This is pretty clear in almost every ancient writ.
Yet, they fail, in every religious group, they fail to acknowledge that in a way where they self-assess what they're doing.
And then you end up falling back, just like the legals, the legal and medical society, the religious leaders and those that hold, I guess, clergy and things like that, they fall back into the thing, well, it doesn't matter, and they don't have their black holes and their viruses yet, the imaginary things that they can blame things on.
They just blame it on, they say something like, treat others like you want to be treated, or all you need is love, and these empty, esoteric things like that.
But if you actually look at what they're professing and teaching, it's hollow, empty, it's baseless, and it's actually a corruption of what they're supposed to be doing, which is kind of difficult to say what they're supposed to be doing, because there is no legitimate aspect to what they're doing anyway.
But the bottom line with these guys, with the religious people, is harsher than the legals and the medicals, simply because the legal society, well, the legal society is religious, and so is the medical one, they do show religious overtones with their symbology, especially the legal society with justice, that is a revived religion.
But the religious leaders, they strictly do tell you they represent G.O.D., let's say, or one of them.
And when you get into such a high order representation, not that you're actually doing it, but you're doing it with your mouth, even if you don't know what you're doing, you're going to be held to a much higher judgment call later on.
So these guys, from a cosmic point of view, or a divine point of view, the worst people on the planet right now to the G.O.D.s are the people that are in the religious field.
Because the doctor doesn't tell you he represents G.O.D., or neither does the attorney with his own mouth, right?
But the religious people do.
And that's their main screw-up, not necessarily from directly, because you won't have pastors and priests and rabbis injecting people with mercury, like vaccines, and telling them they should go home, and we can't figure out what's wrong with them because of a virus.
Or the attorney, who doesn't know any law, who is just going to put you in the market.
By the way, the attorney is a D.K. G.O.D.O., which means D.K. G.O.D.O. Agora, putting the law on the market, is what the Greek term for that is.
So he's the law merchant.
So the law merchant, they have you plea, and make you admit to things that you didn't do, for a lesser cause, right?
So it's like a law merchant kind of deal.
So they're operating on that level.
And both the medical and the attorneys are sort of like retribution from the G.O.D.s to mankind.
But the religious guys, they don't have any, they are sort of standing alone on their own retribution.
Which is interesting, you see.
So you can easily say that what the attorneys are doing by imprisoning people and stealing their property legally, and what the doctors are doing by poisoning people, is divine retribution on an evil society.
And what the religious leaders are doing, they're more like taking it on themselves.
Obviously they're accommodating the ignorant people that happen to also be evil, whether they know it or not is irrelevant.
And the mess there is that they're in the worst shape of the rest.
Meaning those that are in the religious professions.
And that is more than a criticism, that's a fact.
If anyone starts to look at the level of harshness that the G.O.D.s put, especially later on, on people is based on how much they say they represent that side, you see, that divine side.
Now of course, the interesting thing is, you're in a situation right now on the planet where there is a couple of places you might want to research and find out that there is a little bit of harshness also on those who have never inquired about the G.O.D.s. Right?
If you want to go find it, I'll give you a hint, it's in a book called Zephaniah.
So, but could you imagine those that are actually working in the professions, supposedly, representing, even though we know, say we, anyone who's spent 15 minutes on the subject knows that all of the religious leaders represent the malevolent spirit, in essence.
When you do look at what they're doing, you will see that they're in really shit shape compared to the rest, from the divine side.
You see?
Simply because with their own mouth and their actions on that side.
And what I mean by that, I've given this metaphor before, if you live in a little country neighborhood in the Bible Belt, and you've got this little pastor, you know, who wouldn't even harm a fly, he hands out food to the poor, and all that takes in whatever, that guy is going to get a worse off treatment than a serial killer.
Even though he's never harmed a fly.
Do you see that?
Because he's hanging around in this, you know, sex temple, church, chapel, whatever, and he's talking all this smack about G.O.D. Right?
And he doesn't know anything, and he's misrepresenting it.
Right?
Now, the same smack is being talked about the barber, the old granny, the guy at the supermarket, the painter, the attorney, the doctor, talking the same smack.
But their job is different.
See, this guy's job is set up, or in this case, it might even be a yob, is set up to represent the divine on this planet.
Do you see?
Even though he's never hurt a fly, he's going to be held at a much higher, it's going to be one hell of a thing to watch, like the worst or the most heinous criminals that ever lived, huddled around, and they're like, man, I'm glad we weren't a pastor or a minister, because what that guy's going to get ain't nothing compared to what we're getting.
You know?
Have you ever heard the point that everything is backwards?
Yes.
This is why I'm explaining this this way.
The gods don't view your society the way you view your society.
This is like, I used to do sonic projects with someone before, I said there's a big difference in doing a sonic event and speaking on what you like to know, and there's a big difference between that and speaking on what can be known.
You see?
Because one is subjective, one is objective.
So when you're going through the world, and you keep to yourself, let's say, a minimum interaction, and you think you've been grown up, that attorneys are there to help you, doctors are there to help you, priests are there to help you, and you have minimal interaction, you're going to view them your whole life as being fine.
But let's say you don't, you have a child, and the child got some strange disease that it didn't have before, and then you figure to try it again with another child and the same thing happens.
Okay, that person's going to be very embittered by those professions, right?
They're going to say, watch out for those attorneys, they'll steal your property, or watch out for those doctors, they'll inject your children and they'll get sick, right?
So they're going to be making a foot, but no one is actually giving those doctors, ministers, rabbis, whatever you want to call them, priests, bishops, the effect of what they're doing, directly.
Well, the indirect effect is that you have the doctors doing what they're doing, the schools doing what they're doing, the attorneys doing what they're doing, the government doing what it's doing, it's because you have these guys representing the divine falsely, or they're representing the malevolent deity.
See, very few people, especially in any religious whatever, unless of course they were an altar boy and they got shafted up the butt or something, right?
And that's really what's going on.
Because that's also part of the religion, by the way, which is kind of going to be, I think I've gone into some detail about it.
These are small entities or demons that require attention.
The way you summon them is by inflicting pain on a child sexually.
And this is part of the Catholics, this is part of the Scientologists.
It's the same entity, by the way.
Now, when I say Catholics, I don't mean the idiots that you see in the parking lot every Sunday, talking about the higher level ones, you know, the administrators.
That's an ancient entity.
It came out of Egypt.
It's also out of Babylon.
It's moved around.
And the Scientologists have the same one, by the way.
I'm not going to use its name.
So this is just how strange and bizarre it is.
But I figured I'd bring up, there's a level of discernment on what is going on.
I think I want to always give that level of discernment more than just talk about things like all the other morons do on this planet.
Because you don't really have to spend a lot of time to figure out what's going on with most things if you can cite them clearly.
One of those revisings of a citing of Mary, mid-Wisconsin again, what was it, almost 1,500 people coming through to this thing.
Mm-hmm.
All coming to see this where she apparently manifested herself or gave somebody some special trinkets or some such.
I'm not sure of the whole detail.
Sure.
It could have been...
You see, what these entities do is they look at what the people's desires are and then they play on that.
Just like when someone sees a ghost of their grandfather.
It's not their grandfather.
It's a ghost, a spirit that knows, that has been monitoring the family.
But they also have a high mentality that it could be a spirit that just met you.
He taps in and says, okay, here's the information and go play with them, right?
Right.
They're just being played with.
There's also morons that go around the Philips stadiums or public venues.
If you have a dead loved one, you go to the show and you put your name in a hat or whatever and you ask him a question and he refers his question back to your dead loved one, which is when they're dead, they're dead.
They can't say anything.
That's the experience that he has following the performer.
It's quite real, by the way, that taps into this high mentality where they have records on anyone who's died, let's say.
It could be fixed also, but the concept is very real.
They're going to have sightings all the time.
I'll give you an example.
There's a fellow, he does YouTube, not a fellow, but some moron actually.
And he says that, you know, the power of J-E-S-U-S, right?
One day he said that he saw this satanic, he saw Satan, right?
And he described it as he is in Hollywood, right?
And then he called him the name of J-E-S-U-S and Satan went away and the J-E-S-U-S looked just like the J-E-S-U-S they give out in the Catholic Church or TV also.
You see what I mean?
And none of that is true at all, but they will produce whatever image is popular because, you know, these spirits that do this to mankind, they're aware of what's on television.
They're aware of what you're thinking through iconography and imagery and things like that.
They're quite technologically advanced in their own right to be able to not be visible and tangible and produce these things.
And they produce them in a way that when you combine it with people's traditions and cultures where they think they can contact the dead and they think that, you know, like Mary or whatever, you know, will come around back because it happened before.
They believe in it.
They don't question it.
What happens is what you'll see in the world with ghosts and the vision of Mary and all this other stuff is that you have two sides.
You have the side that wholeheartedly believes that's what happened, as described.
Then the other side that doesn't believe it and they're totally skeptical.
But there is no one describing exactly what's going on.
Which is very simple.
Which is that you're being pranked by the spiritual realm and they're actually producing...
Now, there'll be a bunch of people out there for years saying, oh yeah, that's fake, it's really a demon.
But they can't give you any details.
I'm giving you the details.
It's very simple.
What makes the gods different from mankind is technology.
Electrical wires, technology.
It's a level of tools and a level of lifespan also.
It's not just technology.
Their lifespan is astronomically greater.
And they're able to perform and exist interacting with mankind in an intangible way.
I mean, they can exist around you intangibly.
But yet, create things that are tangible.
So they're very, very highly advanced beings.
This is not really diminishing their ability or the respect they require or command.
I'm just telling you in simple terms how to think about it if you're going to approach the subject and be successful in rationalizing what's going on.
It's very, very simple.
And in essence, the majority of the entities that have been dealing with mankind have been pranksters.
The high-level ones are hands-off.
This has been declared a long time ago.
I like that.
Interesting subject, as always.
Yeah, it can be.
But the thing is, the pranking is still going on.
We have an interesting thing with timelines or this timeline, meaning where we are at the end of the credits or approaching the end of the credits.
This next seven years is going to be an interesting one to see how things develop because by the next seven-year period, you will have a Middle East Union in place.
So there's a lot of hurry up and stop that's going to be happening.
There's going to be a lot of knowledge and information about that part of the world spreading to the rest of the world.
You still have a lot of critical events that have to take place with the toppling and changing of societies and governments in the Middle East.
So it's going to be quite the time starting in the springtime.
And I wouldn't say to be concerned but it's been a very quiet fall.
Privately, I would say I would have expected a little more action this fall, like bigger events, breaking down events, whether the financial, geopolitical, on and on, cultural.
And there hasn't been much other than the one we mentioned earlier.
There was a shooting that happened in America a few weeks ago or a couple of weeks ago.
Well, of course, poorly done, poorly reported.
The point here is not whether it was what it was, it's what it is.
And it hasn't turned into a major event socially, where it's changed anything.
Any questions out there?
Let's see.
I'm going to just go in front of the chat board here.
Remember, we're still doing a beta test.
We're on for about 40 minutes.
So far, just a couple of folks still having troubles connecting, which we're going to try to work the bugs out on that.
A while back, there was somebody.
Oh, that's fine.
Okay, well, I think 40 minutes is a good, I think it's a good wrap.
I was not intending to complain or rant about the entitled classes, but that's not the intent.
But the thing is, there is no discernment still going on with the legal, medical, academic, and religious societies.
The people are just still sitting back and taking the crap, right?
Now, one thing to consider is, yeah, I do call the Internet the stupid rectangle, just like the TV is the stupid rectangle.
They're more rectangular than they were when they were CRT tubes, now with the flat screens especially.
I would suggest that there's no need, even though the information on the Internet is, in wholesale, is far better than going to university, any university, by far.
I mean, it's just geometrically and astronomically times more than anything you'd get in the university, which doesn't say much for university.
You don't need the idiots in the academia anymore, right, by using the stupid rectangle, if you have the discernment.
But on the other hand, the only thing the universities do have an advantage of is stockpiles and the warehousing of older books in print.
And I mean before what's called World War I prior to early 20th century.
That's the only thing they have going for them.
And even in this day, like they say, day and age, people still have not noticed the heavy pranking of the legal society, the religious society, the academic and the medical society.
So part of the thing tonight was just over this sonic event is to just bring that up out of the blue, so to speak, and how these institutions that have been pranking mankind for centuries, if not millennia, are still in place.
And the people have not noticed.
And let's just say in a quiet way or an indirect way, when the society, before it reaches its peak, before the kill shots come, there's going to be strict criticism of those societies.
And that hasn't happened yet.
So that's something to be on the lookout for.
Those societies have been pecked away at since the past 50 years.
There have been more and more alternative movements, I wouldn't say contrary to, but parallel to, the legal, medical, academic, and religious societies, more and more.
But I wouldn't say that the public at large is at all complaining about the pranking.
They have wholeheartedly noticed that the level of pranking that is being put on society by the academicians, the legal society, the medical society, and the religious society is still in full blast.
And still people haven't noticed it.
And that's one thing to watch for, a harsh criticism from the public at large regarding them.
And they're really ramping it up too.
And I can see it only getting more and more.
What they're doing is that they're resting on their laurels now.
Because the academia is so poorly done, and the rest of the societies, the attorneys and the doctors are so poorly trained, if you're enthralled and amazed by the machinery they have in hospitals and in courtrooms and things like that, that's just there for the typical idiot.
But the actual aptitude of the people that are working in those fields is at an all-time low.
And especially for the religious society and the scientific society, they are also at an all-time low.
Very easy to see that.
Well, I shouldn't say it's simple to see that, but not easy, because you're going to have to delve into that field yourself to notice the contrast of the truth of what I'm speaking on.
But again, I just brought this up because this week has been an interesting week.
I've sort of been interacting with all of those fields indirectly, and I've noticed that people are buying the same bullshit, so to speak, and the people are still buying it wholeheartedly, except for a very small variation that would be considered the alternative medical, the alternative legal, the alternative whatever, religious stuff.
But when you go to these naturopath practitioners, they still think there's blood pressure.
They still think there's a virus.
They still think that the body absorbs things like a sponge.
paying attention to efficiency.
And perhaps a subject on the lymphology system in the future would really be a great one.
Oh sure, we can do a little bit right now, if you want.
Let's just do a few minutes on that.
It's very simple.
The fact is you have more lymph fluid than blood in the body, and yet, even though it is a quantitatively based society, Sympathetic side is because they don't understand that the the body is under a biological vacuum I've mentioned many many times before over and over that you're not a filter bag, right?
This is what they're been putting out
Verbally if you look at what's been memorialized in anatomy
They don't necessarily say you're a filter bag and they don't necessarily say
You're the body is under a vacuum
But by studying anatomy, you could clearly see nothing goes in and nothing goes out
The body is completely sealed right except for several ducts here and there in several organs
That are valved very tightly valved just like you would have a valve on a car tire or a bicycle tire, right?
So when you understand that the lymphatic system Basically is the majority of the fluid in the body and the body is under a vacuum condition Whenever there is a fault in the body, whether it's by disease or by injury an injury would be like a cut Laceration or bruise, you know impact, right?
If you know physical trauma to the body the lymphatic the at the properties of the vacuum and the lymphatic system have to be considered first
and
And actually have to be addressed throughout the entire aspect of addressing
The trauma to the body not just first but continually and that is to understand that
when you
Have a trauma to the body
you the cells are
jostled from their position
generally and
Lymphatic fluid where there was none before tends to flow in
Between the interstitial spaces of the cells and that's what causes swelling
Whether you see that around a cut
After a day or two or whether it's a bruise or something, right?
so one of the main things to do with the lymphatic system initially is to
Apply pressure but apply pressure in such a way that it is extreme
But temporal where the pressure is relieved so blood circulation can take place
At the extremities of the limb and then once there's some circulation reapply the pressure and keep that
Pressure on at least for 15 minutes to an hour and
This would be over a bruise or a cut no matter how severe and you will see extremely rapid healing from five times to a
hundred times faster than normal right of several examples would be someone dropped a very sharp kitchen knife on their foot and
It turned out that the cut was much much much much much worse than initially had
Appeared to be and the person was heavily encouraged to go to the hospital
They decided not to they did the very very tight wrapping
Slightly released at every 15 minutes
So the toes would go back to normal color instead of blue or purple, right and kept the pressure on for several hours
You know, obviously you're not gonna be able to do much the rest of that day if you're gonna have to go between
Loosening and tightening a bandage, right and within the next day or two.
It basically looked like there was just a scratch On the foot not being cut open The same thing recently was someone who was reaching into a freezer to remove a bottle that had frozen they had put the bottle in the freezer because they wanted to show the water rapidly and It cut sliced their hand open.
They tightened it again.
And the next day it looked like the thing had happened You must maintain it as tight as possible.
And when you
See the extremities turning blue or going numb you must release the bandage
It just enough to let pressure back to the extremities
All right
And then up once the extra without movement because you don't want that to open you want the skin to be held very tightly together
So it starts to fuse and grow back together
It almost it's almost like have you ever seen in the sci-fi movies when you have a alien or a cyborg or whatever?
They cut them open and then right right right in the next five frames the the cut heals itself automatically You've seen that right in sci-fi.
Yeah, we're just Yeah, it's it's almost like that but not instantly like that it happens within a day or two, right You'll just look at the where the wound was and there's just basically a not even in the finest paper cut evidence there, right?
So that is the the essence of the treating the lymphatic system the worst thing you could do is start rinsing it and pouring hydrogen peroxide and doing a band-aid or getting stitches I I know what you might say.
Well get sometimes you do need stitches
Yeah, and surgeries and things like that, but I wouldn't say you do either but I would just suggest that
I've seen people run to the hospital for the most minor things
and they get what they deserve right a scar exactly and an infection, so
The now the other aspect of the lymphatic system is many things are reproduced in the body
And if you what I mean by that is, you know, when you eat food, it doesn't go through the intestines at all
It's reproduced on the opposite side of the intestine through induction
and when these things are reproduced there is a factoring of things that are
reproduced in the lymphatic system as well and
If you there's a fellow that that has been around he's a Mormon guy from the 60s and 70s pushing all this lymphatic
lymphology stuff
Very dogmatic in essence.
He he the golden mean seven or something.
He has a book and he's selling classes
I think someone here on the chat posted the they're offering classes and all that
Yeah, I mean, it's pricey and all that's most of the stuff does work, but it's not necessary
There there's a diet side of the lymphatic system
The
The the study is don't that these lymphatic people have done is
Do not go into like extreme things like they'll tell you
Like onion and garlic is toxic because of the sulfur, you know
Those are poisons.
Don't eat them.
Well, obviously there's people eating much of that and they're not being poisoned You see right.
So that's I would say that's a little bit far-reaching.
I mean there's in the Hindu culture, there's a aspect, you know, the the Gurus or whatever their level of spiritual leaders They don't eat onion because it drags your spirit down to the ground.
So they had they use hen instead of onion Yeah, you'll you'll always see criticism of certain foods right But the answer to that, let's say if there was a question about two foods infect the lymphatic system.
Yes, they do
And the thing is to avoid extremes
One of the worst cases of when infects the lymphatic system is all of the processed food that's in the in the
food supply
The reason why is
You know how you've heard
sugar rots the teeth, right
And people that eat a lot of sugar
Yeah, they tend to have worse well, but it's not because you'll put sugar on your tooth and won't rot it
They don't they can't tell you the mechanism
How does sugar rot the teeth and there's none of these morons in the medical field or scientific field could give you the mechanism
Right.
They think it's the saliva this or that or whatever.
It's very simple When you when you eat white sugar that's been bleached and stripped away Let's say you choose a quackademic term as a molecule, you know, you have crystalline sugar in a packet or at home you spoon out Okay, that's that's been removed from the sugar cane.
And while that was in the sugar cane It was attached to water.
It was attached to minerals.
It was attached to carbohydrates.
It was attached to plant proteins, right?
It was attached to plant hormones and plant enzymes you see So now that all that's refined all that is refined out when that now that is that sugar crystalline sugar is vibrating Let's say it has a frequency or it's oscillating in the in space All right here in the earth at a certain frequency that it's that frequency is like Give me I'm alone.
I'm naked.
I need water.
I need protein.
I need carbohydrates
I need minerals to attach to me as soon as possible
So you end up putting it in a drink or food and you eat that processed sugar and once it gets into the body
The body says, okay, we're going to reproduce the sugar, but it also has the frequency demanding that we reproduce a mineral
We reproduce a protein we reproduce water
We reproduce this other stuff too that is not in the weather that we're not getting the signal from
In in the abundance that we need so we're going to have to reproduce it in the body and take materials from the body to do
that
You see and that happens and that happens to also starve
The aspect of the tooth where the tooth needs to reproduce itself
See because teeth are always reproducing if you've ever known anyone
Let's say a young child who you know the tooth they get their second set of teeth or an adult
That's had a tooth pulled once it's removed from the body
It goes it gets very brittle after a few days or a few weeks.
Sometimes you can crush it in your hand, right?
if because it's a living substance, so
So what happens is when you eat these processed foods, the body is is getting the demand to reproduce
All the other substances that were around that processed food when it was in a natural state
And that throws a lymphatic system off of course because now you have a dumping of all these other
constituents and removing of all these other constituents from the body in order to
Supplement this demand you see because the sugar never enters the body through the intestine
It's the vibration of the sugar that allows the body to create it, but it just doesn't create the sugar
It creates everything else that the sugar wanted to be around around it now
It gets kind of sci-fi
To say that the nothing goes through the intestinal wall and all that because most people think that they're still being told by the most
Alternative naturopaths that you absorb things, right?
You hear that all the time You know an interesting point also, how did you know the body knowing?
What actually was in that sugar that it's trying to Replicate the sugar the sugar has the negative impulse of it This the sugar is this tell it the sugar is vibrating at a frequency that is denoting it Just like a just like your laundry list Yeah, all all refined substances What's interesting is?
Metals are very similar.
You know when you when you mine metals in the earth From the earth they're attached to minerals and oxides and things like that, and then they're refined right and that's what gives the metal their vibrancy sometimes is because once they're stripped and Refined from all those other things they're vibrating out of at a different level You see and also they've been they're metallic.
They're not water-soluble the body will not be able to reproduce most of them
And that because the more water-soluble it is by the way the more readily the body reproduces it
But that's what gives like gold and other metals once they're refined their vibrancy is they are actually vibrating at a frequency
That when they're isolated is a much higher frequency than when they're let's say in a in a mixed state
So that sugar I mean how many times just you could make it really simple.
You know somebody a child You know you give them a candy bar and a soda, and he's bouncing off the walls right very high frequency very like agitation and then he crashes So or she so right They're not you'll notice that the more processed the food the less relaxing the effect is You know unless it's an induced Thing like alcohol which induces that to the body or certain drugs opioids.
Let's say will induce that relaxed state
So the the processed foods meaning removed from their natural state
Are taxing on the lymphatic system, and of course you can go to more extreme
concepts of foods like a lot of people in lymphology are against onion and garlic and hot peppers and
Various things that I just want to bring this up because some people want to order their stuff like like once someone in the lymphology
Movement suggested someone do a lemon juice diet up to 40 lemons a day
I mean these people they're just still guessing so I don't that's why very often when someone says well Greek
I can't find anything on lymphology.
I might shoot a couple of links of something over YouTube's I said bear in mind.
I don't endorse any of this
You know these people are crazy
You know you're picking you're gonna have to pick edible corn out of their poop
You know but the problem is that most people want you know
Information out of a can you know I just opened the can right away dump it out eat all of it
You know that's not how it works even with myself
When I you hear the Greek speaking on things go check up on what I'm saying or meditate on it.
You know You shouldn't just believe it You know it's what I'm trying to do is give hints.
I don't I don't go into great depth I mean occasionally I have with for example a rudimentary ways to increase the quality of water I'll go into depth on that, but just the rudimentary aspect of it right or I'll get into the rudimentary aspects of how Lymphatics can help someone, but I won't go into great depth because there's just after a while a person Listening might say well.
This is too much to check up on I'll just have to trust what he says So I have to give things out in Parcels where people can take the parcel and manage open it you know and and manage it Right and measure it because if you can't measure it you can't manage it if you feel like there's too much there Yeah, and you just want to trust it because the Greek is saying it.
That's a It's a mistake in the mindset actually you'll be pretty well off if you did I'm just just saying humbly here, but the mindset that I would invite is to be critical about everything so Not hyper critical because then you're wasting too much energy and being critical you want to be critical in the way you handle it But you want to handle the information properly.
It's just again.
It's a mindset That's why I keep bringing up when I bring up the the body In a sense you have to knock what they're putting out there, you know knock put down because it's so ridiculous, right Because people are still stuck in the mindset I've been in invited to several let's say group calls and conference calls regarding health and Everyone I should say not everyone, but let's say in wholesale.
Yes at large everyone still thinks Any of these calls or conference groups have been on that the body absorbs and you have blood pressure and there are viruses I can't you can't work.
There's nothing there to work with these now
Obviously there is if you just keep it really really rudimentary like you can run into someone who thinks that you know
They've been terrorized with viruses blood pressure and absorption and all this other stuff and you say hey listen idiot
If you get a cut no matter how deep it is just wrap it super tight and just make sure you don't cut off the
circulation to the finger or the hand just loosen it a little and you just you know for 15 minutes or so and then
Keep it tight for a few hours and keep repeating it, you know, depending on how severe it is
you the next day it'll look like nothing happened and
They're like, okay.
I'll try to keep that in mind and if they do that Guess what?
They report back.
They'll call me back a day later or two days later Greek I cut my hand wide open.
I did what you said and today it barely looks like I got a scratch And I'm like great and then you know, they still think the body absorbs They'll go out and buy stuff because they heard someone say this this vitamin Supplements got great absorption and they say oh great absorption.
I think it must be good and they believe in viruses, you know
Like are the cause for all these things, you know, and they think there's blood pressure
But so what you know if they but at least they they got some rudimentary information that if they wrap it super tight
You'll get a quote-unquote miraculous healing in two days or three days or less
Things that would normally require let's say emergency room treatment or stitches what they call suturing
Leaving a scar in weeks or you know, whatever
You can you can heal relatively instantly by just putting pressure on it
Even fungus infections.
I've can give first-hand knowledge of a small
Fungus type thing on the side of the ring finger nail
Right where the the nail started flaking away and it was very sore
And if you look at it with high magnification, you can see the nail is deteriorating and there's a little discoloration
Right, it would be like, you know something growing there
I typically you know
They'd run and get all these ointments and things and basically wrapped it tight and the next
Slept on it in the next morning.
Actually.
I had it a little too tight.
The finger was numb the next day
But by the following day it was gone completely
Because remember nothing lives on nothing lives on the skin what they call bacteria infection all that it's produced by the body
Obviously if you get what's called a which is very rare by the way to get a true infection where it's
Contagion in this society, you know, unless you because there are very few contagions in the environment right now
Because of sanitation you don't have raw sewage running down the street I
Know it sounds kind of funny to say that but that
Historically has been the case in cities if you go down south of the border in Mexico when it rains
You'll see raw sewage running down the street or places like Vietnam by the way
Right in the cities.
Yeah, people are not aware of this even today
I'm not speaking all the time, but when it when this suit when it gets slightly
When the system is
Overwhelmed by rain, it'll you'll have raw sewage coming up the storm drains in the street
You'll see raw sewage, you know stuff that people flush down the toilet coming down the street
There's a higher chance of infection infectious diseases have pretty much gone away
at this point
because of hygiene
Simply the use of laundry soap and washing machines frequent use of let's say
Things like that right in case of in case of
Embattled communities like if you go to Syria Yemen
Mmm other places you can mouth off that have been under capitalistic conversion lately
People are coming down with what you might call, you know medieval diseases cholera diphtheria things like that
You know, even though there might be an upsurge of leprosy or some things like that in places like that as well
So, yeah, you know and I think we've gone over before the common cold and the flu is not a
Contagion in most cases as in modern society unless of course
It is designed to be a contagion and put out into society and most of these flus that you hear of our
designer even back in ancient times
It is very simple.
I'm not going to get into how to create the bubonic plague.
It's not easy, but it is simple
You know these plagues that you hear about
Right, those are all man-made going back thousands of years there are people that was known to men on how to do that and
fortunately
It has that is not common or even uncommon knowledge now
You see and I'm not going to do no, I will never do a public or even private
Discussion on how that is done now, so don't ask
But it is very simple.
It has to do with animals and things like that.
So well, it makes a lot of sense, you know
generating money
Yeah, the basic you know, I'll give a hint on how it's done basically just improper practices and I'm not sexual ones either
I'm speaking on I mean
improper things that you just don't do if you do those things and it has to do with hygiene you will have a contagion emerge and
Once that contagion emerges you will have what's called a carrier type person
Who can still inflict the contagion amongst others, but doesn't get sick with it immediately
They could have and then you and then you have the others that get sick immediately from it and die from it immediately.
You see
and all these things whether you're looking at the
Bubonic plague on forward to the Spanish flu where Woodrow Wilson killed over a hundred million people
So when you hear about Stalin and and all these other people killing millions Woodrow Wilson is the greatest mass murderer that ever lived
You know a hundred million plus in two years because he's the one that
Gave the order and the okay on the
Spanish the American army flew or the Spanish flu
Killed 25 million Americans in 18 months.
You don't hear about it though.
Do you know?
Yeah, yeah, that's all these things are yeah stuff like smallpox has been retained and kept around and When they wanted to do that, they just put the word out Do you know anyone is there a smallpox quarantine colony anywhere?
You know and someone says yeah, there's one here So they go there and they take articles of the clothing and maybe one of the individuals and they start Spreading it that way you see.
Yeah
Yeah, and this is this mankind's been involved in this but basically hygiene
And sewerage and and water practices have pretty much eliminated most contagions
The majority of the contagion of people considered be contagion right now is based on diet and environment
for example, if there's
aerial spraying going on and
the the there's a factoring on how those aerial spraying is are
Put together they know let's say with one factor
It'll affect 10% of the population or 5% or 20% but give you an example on the early days of chemtrailing
Right you would they notice that
The emergency rooms would start filling up with people with respiratory problems
So they went back and started they started adjusting the formula as you see
So again, be be careful
If you you know, and if nothing gets in or out of the body unless the body produces it
So, how are you going to rub up against someone get a virus and then show up in your blood if your body's
Completely sealed.
How did it get in there?
No, no one answers that by the way, they can't answer that what I just said Only the deepest darkest black laboratories of the deepest darkest, whatever know what I'm talking about the the average academic addition academic Quackademic and that man on the street doesn't have any clue at all on how the body works at all Not even close Replicating Mm-hmm Precisely.
Yep And if you if you you can do two things if you if something gets put out that the body can't replicate Like if you swallow a piece of plastic or a penny guess what?
Your body's not going to replicate much of that and next day You'll be able to sift through your poop and find it on unadulterated, right?
Yeah All right.
So if you can somehow Show the body that it's unreplicatable or adjust the body.
So it doesn't replicate it.
You'll be free of that or Render the the substance unreplicatable within the environment And all these things are possible, which I will not discuss publicly ever on any sonic event But but that's something that needs to be considered again.
Why is it all propagate?
Why is the the level of bullshit in the on the planet right now across the ages and across?
Societies is is so insurmountable that you you know, you well, you know In other words what people believe is true is so ridiculous that you going contrary to it is is a futile cause the only thing you can do is Say what's going on have other people examine it find it to be true and then back off and say hey look You know, no one is without excuse.
No, you can't say you have an excuse now because it's been said You see it's very simple.
And by the way, no matter how big the pile of bullshit is it only takes a small shovel to move it a Small shovel constantly shoveling.
It will move an entire pile of bullshit no matter how big it is So hopefully that helps with the lymphatic system Like the pastor and give a little bit of talk more on the lymphatic system the pastor Institute which was heavy on Contagions and biologicals and things in France.
That's where you get pasteurized from and all that
Later on especially in the mid 20th century
They studied the lymphatic system more than the blood for you know, various aspects of the health of the body
But then that was abandoned later again because it was just too effective
Things that they were looking for in the blood that took hours or days to show up in blood tests showed up immediately in lymphatic
fluid tests
see
Amazing.
Yeah Yeah, so they didn't you know, you could always I've said this before if you put You know two things in front of any human of any of any level at any time One of them is deathly fatal.
They both look the same One is deathly fatal and malicious and malevolent.
The other one is beneficial.
They're always going to pick the one that is Malevolent not always but enough that you could say they will pick it.
Yeah, if you bet on it, you'd be quite wealthy You know if the two things are look the same or similar.
They're always going to pick the worst of the two
so
It's a fact with humans, yeah, so understanding, you know, these things are not to be
Reckoned as oh, well, it's just temporary or it's just subjective
Those things are the way that humans have been for a long time
once you comprehend that you deal with that just like years ago people used to go on safaris or
Or, you know scuba diving trips and things and whenever you go to a different environment
You're you should you know, you're made aware of what?
What is critical and when you change you go to the environment you're changing from the environment You're used to going to another one.
Now, you got to watch out for snakes.
You got to watch out for this or that, right?
so what I've been speaking on for the past decade or so publicly lightly is You got to watch out for the what the humans are have in their society And most of it is everything that you are subject to and it's right in front of you that you haven't noticed You know you meaning the listener, right?
So basically with lymphatics, it's very simple.
If you if you have a good moderate diet
and
Good rest the lymphatic system tends to go through most of its healing through what I call sleep therapy
And
Also understand that the body's under a vacuum and basically when you have a cut on the body or a bruise it's losing vacuum
Just like in the cartoons in the old days, you know
If you car tire was leaking immediately you put a patch on it, right or something, you know
But it's not just for the topical patch.
The purpose of the patch is to stop the leaking Yeah, so So getting the body into that vacuums condition.
I've got I mean tons of stories
I mean not just actually accounts not just you know, that's the sound like stories but accounts of
various things
people with pneumonia paralysis cuts burns broken bones
Sores all kinds of things simply by just addressing the vacuum in the body
You know give an example like for example
When someone is under a quote-unquote disease state whether it's inflicted through trauma or otherwise
It could even be
Hereditary the body's losing vacuum one at a greater pace when they start deteriorating their condition deteriorates
so one of the ways to increase the vacuum in the body is
by
Initially decreasing the volume of the body
By putting weights on the extremities.
Let's say
Let's you have someone laying down and you put sandbags or books wrapped in blankets on their legs feet arms
You know avoid the chest obviously and stomach because that's where you're breathing and that needs to be kept loose and
for about an hour or two and and what happens when you
Compress the body like that the volume decreases slightly and the body equalizes to that decreased volume you see
and
It actually decreases the vacuum even more for a short time
But the body is more readily to adjust to the smaller volume
Now once you remove the weights off of the limbs the volume increases
Suddenly and then increases the vacuum as well
Just like with a pump when you're pulling the piston out.
You're creating a vacuum because you're increasing the volume
Right with the same fluid
Yeah, so doing rep repetitive squeezing or wrapping of the body the limbs
Especially all the legs all of the arms like that you could be done with tight bandages
Also, you know start at the hand you always wrap towards the heart
So you would start at the foot and wrap towards the heart all the way up the leg very tight
each leg each arm very rapid very tight and
Then release it after 15 minutes or an hour
Depending on how tight it is if you see the tips of the extremities getting very dark and color and numb you should release it
Immediately, but then repeat it what that does is it allows the body to?
Almost you're mechanically inducing a vacuum because every time you release it the Again, the volume of the body expands and the vacuum expands with it and that allows that rapid healing to take place And not unlike but it's very unlike but not unlike do you remember the iron long people who had a collapsed lung?
They would put you in a sealed chamber It wrapped.
Yeah, it would basically seal it off at the hip and at the neck and it would be a diaphragm It would actually move your body the same way the plan, you know breathing the same way the plera does That's how the plera works.
There's a there's a vacuum layer between the diaphragm and the lungs.
It's called the plera That's why people who have severe pneumonia.
It's called pleurisy pneumonia
When that vacuum in the plera is disturbed you have you get the pneumonia condition, you know water in the lungs and fluids in the lungs
right
So anyway it this this it's not really in the lungs it's around the lungs so there's there's much to discuss
But you must comprehend the lymphatic system, which is basically more fluid than blood and it will rush into any area
Like for example when you see a blister whether it's from a burn or from a callus that is lymphatic fluid
You know, the tear duct is lymphatic fluid, you know
any clear water like fluid so
These things need to be considered if you want to be able to at least self heal quickly, right
And of course the processed food aspect and again just to the the food.
I want to give a little antidote There's something called Macrobiotics, which is I don't recommend even though it's a good study.
Yeah, it's good.
It's too strict on the juice
It's it's the it's the Gustav Le Bon group mentality again
Very Japanese and very dogmatic, but one of their things is to eat whole foods and eat seasonally
But you'll see that they stress
Japanese
Cuisine or Japanese type stuff and you know you end up, you know, it's a marketing scheme now these days
But I would suggest that's a little bit of a study and one of the I know
Michio Kushi who passed and Shizuko Yamamoto recently passed and other people in that field and when they first came
to America in the 70s, they were landed on the west coast and they started doing seminars and
They had all walks of life attending the seminars, but after about a few weeks it was only the hippies that were showing up
So after it was just the hippies showing up.
They stopped and asked us.
Hey, what why do you guys keep coming here?
You're like you guys are the only ones that keep coming back And the hippie said oh, yeah, I says because we don't have to get high anymore.
We get high off the food now Right.
Oh So what I'm trying to say here is that when you eat whole foods like for example Macrobiotic stresses that like brown rice and a certain proportion of rice to beans and it's primarily vegetarian You will have a sense of euphoria and I've recently done this with other people.
I've suggested Even recently I said listen if you you know, you know, you have a pressure cooker like yeah I do as I well, even if you don't you could you know, make a rudimentary one with a tight lid We'll get some brown rice cook it properly I go over how to cook the brown rice and eat that for a few days and by the third or fourth day You should have a constant feeling of euphoria Right.
And anyway, this is every time I do that with someone they come back and said yeah I do have a constant feeling of euphoria from eating these whole grains, right?
So so I mean how simple is that, you know?
But what will happen is if you go into a major diet change like that, you might get into a violent craving session and what I mean by that is If you stop what you're eating now, especially if you're eating sad food, which is standard American diet If you if you go to something like microbiotics or vegan or whatever Vegan, I'll tell you what vegan is by the way vegan is can be good.
I
Wouldn't suggest being emphatic about it the veganism by the way, and I want to get back to the violent cravings, but
There's no way to be completely vegan
I mean I was in a restaurant a long time ago and they were touting that everything in here is a vegan
There's no animal product whatsoever
And I'm sitting with a group of people and this waitress is going on and on and on and on and on about it
I said this is a new restaurant, right?
She goes.
Yeah, I said is this new sheetrock?
You know drywall and she goes.
Oh, yeah.
I said, you know, they use animal glue in the paper for that And I said this latex paint, you know uses alphatic resin, which is basically animal based product too, right?
So she just shut up right away, you know, I mean you see we're already here.
You don't you worry.
We're already here You don't have to sell us, you know on any on your crap So but basically I used to go to visit people say I'm vegan and the food tasted terrible And if you have really well prepared vegan food like with the Krishna's and stuff They used to go out to Thompson Square Park and give out the food.
It was delicious
But when it's traditionally done and if you know what you're doing, but typically I found out it's an excuse for
Middle-aged or young white people who can't cook they say well everyone thinks my food sucks
So at least if I cook vegan and they don't like the way I cook I'll just say it tastes bad because it's vegan
You know
That's it's like this is what I've discovered for most Westerners.
It's like this stuff is Tastes like crap.
Well, I mean, you know, it's not very pleasing like what's vegan?
Like why would you say that?
It should be pleasant and delicious no matter what style of cooking it is, right?
So anyway, I just wanted to mention that the world if you go vegan or macrobiotic and you do have a drastic diet change Without slowly switching over you might go through what's called violent cravings At a much younger age.
I remember doing that
I said well
This is I'm gonna try this and I you know got rid of all the regular food, which I always ate
Well, but then I went to let's say a strict macrobiotic vegan regimen and after about a week of that
I got up in the middle of the night and I had this thought in a sweat
I was like, I've got to get some chocolate chip ice cream right now and
And and I got up I went to the stove
And on the way to the store to get the chocolate chip ice cream if anyone if anything
Got in my way.
I was in a murderous frenzy to get that chocolate chip ice cream.
You better not get in my way Yeah, and even what happened is when you get to the store you see the ice cream You will immediately rip open the lid and dig into it and start eating it right there in the store That's what I mean about a violent craving.
So is this the body wanting to replicates the body?
Exactly.
Yeah, the body is needs training gradual training and change Yeah, the body just needed that right away.
And by the way, I have not forgot our discussion about the brown waste
brown rice and the beans
Yeah, one of the rules about eating whole grains and beans is five to one or seven to one
So if you're gonna eat seven ounces of rice one ounce of bean, you know in most cases
Let's say people when you say rice and beans
It'll be a quote-unquote at a Hispanic venue and they'll serve almost 50 50 or two-thirds to one-third, you know beans to rice
I mean rice to beans
You always have typically you'll see more rice than beans, which is correct
But I'm saying even make the disparage or the proportion even higher or lower meaning more rice than beans
so if you have ten tablespoons of ten tablespoons of rice
It should be two or three tablespoons tops of beans
Very very little of that and you'll see and and with the brown rice after a while
You there's various types of brown rice.
You could also add a little bit of millet a Very small proportion of millet or a very small proportion of barley or a small proportion of rye Right to make it more interesting and flavorful, right?
See based on season like certain grains retained water Like barley certain grains are drying like rye If you want to get into there's a connoisseur level I mean, there's something called red rice also, which is a rare form of brown rice.
It costs more than steak
Right the rice and but it's it gives an extreme euphoria
right, so people who like a rich or a state and the reason to tie this into the lymphatic system the reason you
Feel euphoric when you eat these whole foods
vegetarian, of course
is
Because they are soothing the lymphatic system and I literally mean soothing the lymphatic system
On the body doesn't have to work as much because it's got it right there
Well, yeah, it's it's extremely compatible with the lymph fluid.
So once you you present that the
You're you're achieving very high level of harmony and and many people have healed things
I mean, there's some there's I haven't seen it in years, but I remember going online and searching about
microbiotics and there's a whole slew of
YouTubes and other things about you know people saying look I had stage four brain cancer or whatever
I was nothing left and I heard about this microbiotics and I did it and I'm fine.
It only took about three months to turn it around, you know, so Yeah.
Now the other thing I said vegetarian, of course is you know, I'm an Old Testament kind of guy I think you've gotten the hint by now There's something about that that says that you are unclean if you touched a dead body or carcass of anything.
Yes.
Yes Right, so Indirectly promotes vegetarianism because you might say well, you know, I didn't touch any dead bodies of anything But I had a chicken sandwich for lunch well We're okay.
Well, what is that chicken sandwich made from?
You know, most people think well, I don't know it comes from the store Right.
Well, what is chicken what in order for chicken to be in a sandwich doesn't it have to be a dead body first?
Yeah
You see even fish in that case, so I
Would I you know, I've said I'm not one to tell people what to do or what they should do
I'm just saying things because no one else is saying them and we're saying them in this way
But well, I what I will say clearly very clearly and emphatically is that the biblical text does promote a vegetarian diet
indirectly
And I say indirectly it doesn't say be vegetarian
That would be direct
But when you tell someone in a text or informationally that if they touch anything dead
They're unclean that is a very indirect way of saying that well
You know that tuna fish sandwich or that roast beef sandwich or that whatever meat sandwich you had is touching a dead body
Now there usually was a timeline with that right?
You're you are in clean till noon.
Yeah.
Yeah till noon.
Yeah
Mm-hmm
And then if you're going to do that there are you know, there are things that are more they're fit and proper to eat
you know shove a cloven hoof to the cut of scales and fins comes out of the water and
chew the cut and
You know a double stomach if it flies
But I would suggest at least an oval lactic condition
Or a lactic, you know cheese and milk because that's not dead
Now a chicken egg, you know, you can look at it three ways
Well, that's not a dead chicken.
But on the other hand, it is a chicken embryo and On the other hand as well, if you're you know, there's Star Trek now, we've got three hands, right?
The alien creature here you on the other hand again the third hand you When you eat an egg, you're not only just eating chicken.
You're eating everything the feathers the beak the feet You see because it's the it's the entire it represents the entire chicken except for the shell You see what I mean?
Yeah, that's what if you know any one from Asia Especially someone in the gastronomical art.
So they always say Oh eat egg very seldom.
It's very strong very powerful
I'll eat egg only if I need a lot of power because they understand I mean whether they do or not
It's in their tradition that an egg represents the entire chicken
No one and no one has ever sat down and eaten
Well that I know of the entire chicken feathers bones guts meat beak head
Everything now, that's what you're doing when you eat an egg
energetically ethereally
You know just for just a sec
The the fact on that timeline again until noon
You know is light involved on this then
That helps a cleansing
No, yeah, it's washing.
There's a lot of washing
Okay, that makes sense let's say let's say you have a chicken sandwich in the afternoon
Which is the beginning of the day, right and
You
you
Go to sleep that night and you wake up in the morning take a shower put on some fresh clothes when noontime comes solar noon
You're clean
but let's say you have that chicken sandwich in the afternoon you go to sleep and
You wake up, and you don't take a shower and noontime comes
And you still haven't taken a shower now you have to wait the whole entire next day again
Even if you take a shower in the afternoon
You you go to sleep that night, and you have to wait till the noontime the next day again to be declared clean
You see so you so that's why when you when you look at some of the priestly functions
They had the morning and evening sacrifices
So they would have the morning they would eat some of the meat in the morning in the morning
Wash immediately right after they eat the meat now.
They're clean after they eat the meat right they're washed and that noontime comes
They're they're declared clean
The second shift comes in and they have the evening sacrifice in the afternoon
They eat they rest they go through the night and the next morning before noon
They wash because remember back, then you did all your washing before noon
We because the Sun you see if you're in the desert location with the Sun and you wash before noon
Like an hour before noon everything dries very quickly
You know that's why in some religions.
They say this the day starts at sundown Well, it's sundown you wash before sundown.
Can you imagine you know in the desert you can have 30 40 degree temperature difference between Daylight at night.
Could you imagine washing washing at night right?
Before washing in the late afternoon and trying to drive you there wouldn't be anyone left from that part of the world that did this
Because they all would have died of pneumonia
The hypothermia right or something yeah, that's what I mean, so so this ridiculous
So it's what you see in the Judean religion at this point which I call Egypt Oh Babylonian religion
Very little of it is scriptural if not any just a few things and by name
So at this point
That's why you know
It's it is righteous to knock these religions in some degree and another degree
It's not because you shouldn't just even be addressing them.
They're so ridiculous So I would just suggest that Giving the biblical aspect of it in this society.
It doesn't make any sense right now
Even though there might be people interested you could go look at it yourself and figure out what you want to do
But I just gave the technical aspects of it that you can see for yourself
But I would promote a vegetarian diet and you know here's someone that had a t-bone steak roasted over mesquite coals for dinner, right
but I will
so I
Would suggest that for a healing diet and to be really fit and proper yeah, no animal products
I would I would avoid them if you could for whatever reason if you found it to be convenient
Or if it made you better and stronger you see there's a lot of people say well
I can't be vegetarian because the nutritionist the doctor said it's not my body type.
That's complete bullshit
That's just an excuse that the quackademics have
The only problem that I see with that is when people go to an all-vegetarian or vegan
Type lifestyle, and they lose energy or don't feel well is because of the quality of the food
That's available in that in that aspect you see and a lot of that was something else you brought up with that
Checking the quality and how to go about doing it
right right and the thing is to win an
Let's just say the most formidable enemy will start a war of attrition on his enemy on their opponent
Right so that's why the food system is in decline.
It's automated and It's removed, and it's not it's not Sustenance type meaning no one grows their own food.
It is a commercial type Right in other words the majority of people who are in the food business are not eating that food or you know in other words Anyone that's in the food business is only eating a very very small aspect of it.
They're producing it for others
Very few people are producing their own food
So you have no control and it I try to put this with on a previous sonic events with food
Very few people know the people that provided the food or grew the food or slaughtered the food for them
Right just like you know when you go to the store and buy
Food you don't know who produced that right you the best is the store clerk or the manager or the cashier
That's all you know about the food, right
And they have nothing to do with it really in most cases and many of the aspects of the quality of it
Unless it's something that's very perishable, and how they handle it
That's what most people are aware of and it's gone to the point now where your average
American child if you ask them where milk comes from they say it comes from the store.
Yeah see So from one aspect I'm not saying that you're going to be able to seek out a lifestyle where you know who is growing the food It is good for example here where I am in the American Southwest.
We're quite fortunate to have a bakery down the road that Bakes his own bread it breaks about a thousand loaves a week of various varieties of bread, but he gets the wheat locally from an organic farmer Just down the road again Who and then they grind the wheat and make the bread?
At the same spot, you know and so he knows where you know the wheat He actually goes and visits the wheat in the field that is going to be bred in a month Because you know it needs to dry out and all that right cure out a little bit, right?
So fortunate to have that so if you eat that kind of bread if you have the ability to get whole grains And have a an auger type crusher Where you can turn the grain into flour and then either leaven it or unleaven it and make some buns or bread and bake it That is radically different.
You can live on that That is that has almost all of the nutrition like the whole grains that give you the euphoria that I mentioned earlier You see right?
Like in the ghetto if you know if you made your own bread from your own wheat that you ground It would be like ghetto why you'd say well.
How does that taste you can say oh, it tastes like steak
You know
So so yeah fortunately if you can find something like that you're fortunate
but I would suggest that it is going to be I wouldn't say painstaking, but it is going to be
Not an Olympic event
But it is going to be quite difficult to figure out what high quality food is in this society right now unless you're already geared
towards that
And you already have the avenues and the discernment and the wherewithal to find it
You're going to have a difficult time in the beginning.
That's for sure in the beginning so Okay, so we're about an hour and a half.
What do you think we call it for a night?
I think so okay?
Okay, as always I've been inspired again and well informed Good well this will be up on our archive on the server you provide and We'll see how it goes and hopefully in the near future.
There'll be some scheduled events with more in-depth stuff like this Thanks everyone Take care