And I'm doing well.
Little technical issues at the beginning here.
There was a comment a couple weeks ago that the Greek doesn't get into scriptural stuff unless he has Seth or Sam on.
And Seth grew up in it.
He says it's a non-denominational church.
I had to laugh at that one.
And Sam has his own excuse.
But it's one of those things that you don't learn overnight.
You need to spend a lifetime on it.
I'm just going to kind of mute off to the side here and check the stream and see how it's working.
God damn.
Okay, seems to be working.
Drop a link in or I'll drop a link in.
Let's see.
Okay, thanks.
What is it again?
I'll pop it in real quick.
You pop it in.
Yeah, I don't have it saved.
I mean, is the stream a live thing or is it just being recorded?
Yeah, we're recording and live.
There we go.
All right.
Oh, I hate it when they update Skype like that.
My goodness, changed everything.
All my configurations.
Holy smokes.
Yep, we're hot.
Yeah, we're hot.
Because I just heard it said we're live and recording.
Oh, good.
So anyway, I'm going to relax.
I'm here in the office.
I'm going to lay on this futon.
And we'll go at it.
Inquiring minds want to know.
Balance out a little bit there.
It's all Sam's been doing lately.
Sam's fine.
Oh, good.
Anybody that's still alive, you know, if you haven't been raped or had any organs taken out of your body, right?
Yeah, it's really that drastic.
And it's amazing how that's escaped everyone.
It's getting there pretty well.
No, it is.
It is that way.
Oh, yeah.
That's how it is.
Yeah.
Just not aware of it.
So.
All right.
No, we could get going.
We're streaming, right?
Unless now we're streaming.
We're good to go.
We're waiting for some kind of a build up or lead up or intro song.
No, Bruce was.
No, we were focusing on Bruce.
That's why.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Well.
Yeah.
All right.
Kick it, man.
Apparently it said that I'm good for ratings.
Yes, yes, sure.
I guess.
So, usually when we have these kind of public appearances, I feel like sometimes the conversation ends up being a little sparser when it comes to biblical material, but I'll be focusing on my regular lines of discourse and hopefully we can talk about some interesting things.
The cherubim, or the cherubim, is a subject that we've brought up a few times, but it's a bit harder to delve into something that's narrow in that sense, unless you've looked into it before.
So there's endless speculation and myths on the nature of the cherubim.
And if one comes to scripture.
Sam, your Wi-Fi.
It's together, but it takes a little bit of time.
So, first of all, you have to Genesis.
Sam, your connection is sporadic, by the way.
Is it?
Am I cutting it out?
Yeah.
So you want to repeat everything you said?
I got the last thing about mythical and then I lost you.
So go ahead.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
I don't think I can do much about it, given where I'm sitting.
Just to mention, I had him.
I had him good here.
He's a little weak.
That way, you know, could stand to come to you closer to your mic.
But other than that, I had a good copy.
Why don't I hang up then?
Okay.
And I'm going to go into a different device.
How's that?
Okay.
And Bruce, you call me on the other Greek.
Okay?
Okay.
Sounds good.
Let me know when you're ready.
Right now.
Okay.
I'm also going to hang up and go look at something real quick, and I'll be right back.
Sounds good, Sam.
Yeah, because I'm trying to see if I can get a better connection.
Okay.
And we're ringing them, folks.
We'll find out what's going on here in just a bit.
I think we got Greek back.
Let's see.
Greek, are you there?
Okay.
There we go.
Got you now.
That's better audio quality also, right?
Yes.
And are you going to bring Sam in, or do you want me to bring him in?
I could do it right now.
Okay.
There we go.
You said he was going to check on something while you were getting over onto the other unit.
All right.
I'm just going to kick back and …
Just one second, because I'm trying to check on my Internet connection to see if I can make it work.
I'll be back in a minute.
Okay.
Oops, and it's time for me to invest in another headset, it looks like.
This one's getting a little knackered.
I might have to go and borrow my grandson's.
I'm not liking this.
I usually take those things apart and put them back together.
Yeah, this one's been apart a few times.
I think she's finally coming to her end.
Well, you just need the circuitry and the wiring and the transducers.
You got hot melt glue?
I do not right at my disposal at the minute.
I'm just going to mute off for a second.
We'll grab the other headsets and be with you in a moment.
Okay.
Well, let's see how that sounds.
About the same.
There we go.
There.
That's good.
Good.
Oh, I got a much better copy on you.
That other one was definitely dying on me.
Yeah, okay.
We're still streaming, yeah?
Yeah, I believe so.
Let me mute off and check it real quick.
Okay.
Yeah, there she is.
She's up and running.
I'm just muted sitting back.
When Sam comes back, we'll see.
Yeah, I understand.
I guess we're going to be waiting for his arrival.
Did you get any feedback on the last Sonic event we did?
Well, a lot of traffic on the servers, that was for sure.
What's like a lot of traffic, five people, ten people?
It was continuously running for a couple good two days, two, three days easily.
Like a hundred?
Pretty nonstop.
I could look at the logs later on and just see how much actual people were coming on based off of IP and all that kind of stuff.
I'm just curious because it's good to get the info out, but it's not really good to get the info out, you know what I mean?
Right, right.
There was good steady traffic, I should put it that way.
So there was numerous people that came aboard to fetch it.
As far as comments, people were grateful that we did this.
And as far as details, specifics, not a lot.
I think there was probably a lot of digesting going on, chewing the cud.
Yeah, okay, good.
I know I spent my good part into it, looking into things.
Panthurians, what a subject.
Wow, wow.
There's nothing, no one really discusses their significance or their presence or their mark.
And those people, wow.
And then, of course, it got me onto other explorations.
What was it, Mithra?
Was it Mithra, I believe?
Which is?
Yeah, fascinating.
Now, would Satan actually be controlling these lower gods to do the bidding of him?
Because I noticed, what was it, Mithra had her hand, had its hand in justice.
Yeah, well, it was the Eastern.
You see, that's why most of what they call Christianity has come from the East.
Yeah.
And then later on, mixed with the West, the Odin, which came from the East anyway.
Right.
You know, the Norse, they were the Babylonian exile, early ones, from after the flood, let's say.
After Nimrod, but no, I wouldn't say Satan.
I think there's scripture in there that tells you that, in Genesis, that the Most High put the sons of gods over the nations.
Oh, okay.
And divided the nations according to them.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And remember, the adversary is following marching orders from the Most High also.
Yeah, yeah.
It's despicable when you look at Western documentaries, God versus Satan.
It's no such thing.
It would be like you versus a six-month-old baby.
Yeah.
No such thing.
And then when I started looking into the, what was it, the nativity thing, and then I just happened to just type it in just to see.
And the number of movies that are out there, and then you get into all these different pictures of the J character.
Asclepius.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Mithra.
And all these different things.
Mostly long hair.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's fascinating.
Well, the god of health was Asclepius.
I think he's mentioned they were at a temple in the Book of Acts.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not 100% sure, but I have to go refer exactly.
But it's a Greek god, Greek-Egyptian, Greco-Egyptian.
Well, that's why I've always been saying anything is a secret.
You know, look at the human body, how it works is a secret.
Go talk to any medical technician about the biological vacuum in the body.
Look at the look that they're going to give you.
Yeah.
The expression on their face.
I tried that one on my daughter who was going to be, what is it, an RNA.
No clue.
Oh, my.
And if you press it in any way, shape, or form, the little twitch in the eye, and you can tell that there's some hard feelings there.
Yeah, where they get the look on their face.
Well, like a seal right before it gets clubbed, like a baby seal before it gets clubbed.
You can see the defense mechanisms just brewing in the eye, and I'm going to back off.
Well, you don't have to.
I mean, it depends.
Well, if I'm going to keep some form of peace and not press it.
It depends.
It depends on the setup.
It requires almost what they call a con man attitude.
The term con man, you know what it's an abbreviation for?
Confidence man.
So you really have to be, here's the thing, and don't take it etymologically.
Right.
You have to be a confidence or a con man to get this point across.
Because what's happening is when you're giving people the truth about stuff, it's so varied and different from what they understand that they're starting to lose confidence in what they think they know.
Right, right.
And my articulation on the subject isn't as well formulated as yours, and so I found myself not fully prepared either.
So that was the other half of that.
Here's an interesting aspect to it.
I found out, and this is from a personal note, but I haven't met too many people that can articulate things like I can, and I pondered on that for a long time.
And I realized, again, back to the confidence thing, and the only reason why it appears that I can articulate it really well is because I know it really well.
Right.
So if you're hearing it from someone and you accept it to be true, whether it's the group mentality or whether, well, it's better than what you've been told and you don't really know it, you also are not able to articulate it, right?
So how do you know it?
Well, something like the human body is pretty easy.
Everyone's got one, let's say.
So, I mean, how can you not know your own body, which you've spent with?
You're going to be spending every day of your life with it, right?
Right.
How can you not know it?
But, you know, knowing it meaning working it back and forward, you know?
Right, right.
And most people that hear this stuff, you know, Greek speak or whatever, they don't really know it.
They know it because it makes sense logically and whatever, and then they begin to use it usually, and then they begin to realize that it can be known.
Right.
And, you know, I'm just speculating that one of the things about communication is, you know, how much of a depth, you know, like a depth of field perception, you know, vision.
You ever notice, like, you know, the person who has better vision can describe more things?
You know, if you're looking at binoculars, you know, or a microscope, you can give a more better, right?
So it's just a matter of – and here's the interesting thing.
This is not like, you know, what you see on the rectangle about, you know, stories and news and all the, you know, the stuff that everyone is engrossed in.
There's not much depth to it because in another week there'll be something else that they're going to be, like a pet or an animal.
They're like cats.
You know, when you give them a toy or a child, it's their whole life for a week or two, and then they want another one.
It no longer does it matter anymore.
The desire is lost.
Yeah, that's exactly how you see everything going on in society in every field.
But this stuff that I'd like to discuss, it takes years to – once you hear it, before you get it, you know, before you – years minimum.
I mean, you could see with the timekeeping.
I always tell people it takes anywhere between three to six months to a year to two before you start to get a handle on it.
Yeah.
And I'm not going to rush it.
I'm going to take it at my pace.
And if I can't share it, I will to people who, of course, don't get that – how did T.
Bender put it?
Violence face.
That's been going on since time immemorial.
Yeah, yeah.
That's been going on since this incarnation of humanity.
It's an influence.
It's also an environmental thing.
The amount of pressure that we have, not physical pressure, but that too, you know, like the barometric pressure, right?
Not that, but I'm sure that's a factor as well.
The pressures that you have, you know, you're awake, you're tired, you have a lot of energy, you're hungry, you're satisfied, you're an emotional creature, whatever.
All the things that you can experience in the human anthropomorphic form and the type of emotions and all that, you don't want – actually, people are lavishly enjoying that, their senses.
They want to know because they've been told they should know.
But outside of that, they really don't care.
They just want to experience the sensual stuff.
Last time I went to what they call the movies was about 10, 12 years ago, and I don't want to go.
I walked out after five minutes because the picture was terrible.
I mean it was supposed – it was a new theater too.
The picture wasn't very good and the sound wasn't very good.
So I just left, right?
I mean because I like – I'm used to watching a plasma TV.
It looks better than a projection and I have high-end audio stuff and it's going to sound better than just some wooden boxes strapped to a wall with a commercial amplifier.
So I have a much better experience outside.
But I ask people like, why do you still go to the movies?
Oh, well, I just like to get away.
I escape.
I just sit there.
It's dark.
It's quiet.
It's cheap to escape.
I'm like, oh, so it's just a very basic sensorial experience.
Not even the context is not important.
It's just the sensation.
But it's the most basic thing.
It's like you're comfortable and the lights are flashing and you don't have to do anything else.
It doesn't matter if the movie is not that good.
I'm like, what?
It's like that when people are eating.
Yeah, it wasn't that good but I was hungry.
How many times do you hear that?
Yeah.
What?
You know?
So, yeah, it's just.
It's amazing what boredom will do to a person.
Get them to do some very odd things.
All right, I'm going to mute.
I'll be back in a couple of minutes.
I don't know if anyone else is on the chat or listening.
I don't know what happened.
I'll be right back.
Okay, sounds good.
If you want to play some music, you could, too, if anyone's listening.
Let's see if I can find something that's wrong.
Click here.
Hello?
Yep.
Hello there, Sam.
Hi.
Hey.
Sorry that I had to drop out.
No, don't worry.
I tried to get my connection to work better.
I don't know how much of an improvement it's going to be, but let me know if I cut out.
Okay, will do.
You're sounding good.
Cool.
Were you guys talking about anything?
We had a little bit of discussion about – I was discussing with my – talking to my daughter, who's on her way to try to become an R&A and bringing up some of the stuff that Greek has mentioned.
And I noticed the so-called violence face starting to come about, and I figured I was going to back off.
And then Greek went into some explanation on things, and it was a rather good discussion.
But I figure for now it's better for me to leave the sleeping dog lie until I'm much more abreast of what I want to speak about and have better articulating skills would be beneficial, I think.
But she did promise me that she would listen to a couple of episodes, and I handpicked them for her when her school work is coming to a close for the break.
And welcome back, Greek.
Okay.
All right.
Is Sam here?
Yes.
All right.
Let's do something.
People in the chat, that's the only time I remember we did one a couple of weeks ago.
I enjoyed it.
I got a couple of comments that it's kind of difficult to get someone on to spark off a biblical conversation unless I want to come on and pontificate on the matter, so go for it.
Sure.
So I figured we'd broach the subject of the caravan to start.
I think you can find clues as to their subtleties in Genesis 2 and Noah's covenant.
So starting off in Genesis 2, it says that, So the human, I'm reading from the ISA, So the human was calling the names of every beast, of every flyer of the heavens, and of every animal of the field.
Yet for the human no helper was available as to his complement.
So obviously it's talking about right before Eve was created.
And I think it's interesting that Adam names three classes of animals, the beasts, the flyers of the heaven, and animals of the field.
But what you don't find is the fish and the creeping things.
Those are left out.
So clearly there's something exclusive about a particular group that doesn't pertain to the other.
And you can see this because he also overlooks them when he's doing his covenant with Noah in Genesis 9.
And it says, Now I am setting up a covenant with you and your seed after you, with every living soul that was with you, flyer, beast, and every animal of the earth, that came out of the ark.
So out of the six created beings, which are the beasts, the birds, the field animals, the creeping things, the fish, and humankind, you have those six.
Two are excluded and we're left with only four.
And I don't think that it's a coincidence that when you look at the caravan, they have four faces that represent beasts in the form of the lion, birds in the form of the vulture, and animals of the field in the form of the ox and then the human being, the same ones that the covenant concerns.
Also, you see that the rainbow, which serves as a reminder to the covenant of Noah, surrounds Yahweh's throne where the caravan presumably reside.
You see that in Ezekiel 128, like the appearance of the bow, which comes in the clouds, so was the appearance of the bright light around Yahweh's throne.
So, I'm not sure how all the information correlates along all potential lines of thought or points of intersection, but it seems safe to say that these are bits in a larger matrix that are ultimately tied together and that the cherubim are tied to these earth groups of living things.
Yeah, and it seems like the cherubim were before the other creation or remaking or formation, I should say, right?
Yeah, I mean, that would be a presumption.
I don't – yes, it's just a presumption.
Yeah, we're presuming – well, we're presuming like the outline of the creation is not being withheld or the reformation, right?
So then, because there's no outline on the formation of the cherubim during that time of creation process, it's safe to presume that they were around before that.
Yeah, that's a good presumption.
I'd go with that.
If you're going to see that they're not withholding much from the recreation, that's the point, you know.
I also think that the phrasing of Genesis 3, 24 with regards to the cherubim is notable for its use of the definite article.
So it says, after he drove – this is when Adam gets kicked out of the garden – after he drove the human out, he made him tabernacle at the east of the Garden of Eden, and he set the cherubim and the flame of the revolving sword to guard the way to the Tree of Life.
So it says kind of clearly, and I've looked at the Hebrew, it's definitely there, the cherubim, which is suggestive of specific ones.
It's not like he just has cherubim on hold that he pulls out to use in innumerable measure.
So it says the.
Also, cherub is the singular and cherubim is the plural.
So we might be able to assume that this is the same four that guard the tree, that stand – And the throne as well, yeah.
We don't know how many cherubim there are, though.
It's like the wise men again, you know, everyone thinks there's three.
It's just we know there's more than one.
I don't know if it's safe to assume there's just two or four or eight or a hundred or a million.
I think the number is nuts.
I think with more investigation, we could find out that if it's the same ones or just that class keeps showing up, are they the same ones or not?
I don't know how much it matters because to us, they might seem identical.
And I think it's the fact that you brought up the history about who they were to begin with.
So they had a reputation way before they got to Herod and everything.
Right before they got – oh, the magi?
No, we're talking about the cherub.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, that's fine.
Yeah, we did a sonic event about certain – the Parthian Empire about a week ago or a few days ago, Sam.
And I got into like who the magi could have been and more strong presumption and based on historical facts, right?
Secular history and biblical comments.
But in terms of the cherub, yeah, there seems to be a closed system with this Adam the man, right?
Versus Adam meaning anthropomorphic, right?
So give you an example how the mechanisms of communication follow through from the gods to us.
Cars have tires, right?
And in England, they spell it with a Y.
Well, a tire was – when you had a wooden wagon wheel, because it was wood, if you had a hole in the cobbles on the stone road, it would smash.
So what they did is they tied a piece of iron or brass around the wood to hold it together, right, under tension.
So later on when the automobile or the engine-driven wagon and motor-driven wagons developed, they switched from – they went to hard rubber and pneumatics.
But they still call them tires because they serve the similar function.
It's what met the road.
But they're extremely different, right?
So what I would suggest in terms of when you read Adam, it's kind of like it's a carryover phrase that can mean several things.
Now, when you look at cherubim, the cough, rush, bet, right, cherubim, right?
The K sound, the R sound, and the B sound.
I think that's a good way for non-primacy, let's say, language people to make a sense of it.
Just like in English, it's the cherubim.
They use the CH.
The K sound means the hand or the work.
And the R means the head or the top of in a physical way usually, peak.
And the B sound means the house, right?
Or from a group or a very specific group.
So cherubim is obviously when you – if you didn't even know what they were, if you just look at the K sound, the R sound, and the B sound, literally it's the hand, something that does work or manipulation from the top, meaning physically from the top.
And the house, like a house meaning like a family house, right, or a specific group.
Interesting, right, how it's almost in the self.
Now, another way to look at it is like Sam brought up, you know, the animals that – remember, those were animals in the garden, right?
So it's a very good metaphor because the cherub were in the garden as well.
So in other words, all the animals that were on the Earth were not necessarily in the garden, and they wouldn't be.
Just like if you were to manifest a garden now and it was large enough, it's helpful to have what's called farm animals or domesticated, you know, field animals.
It's very helpful, right?
You've heard of weed killer Monsanto, you know, that – what is it, glyphosate and stuff to kill weeds, you know?
Right.
Well, years ago, in between farming, you would have shepherds come by, you know, in between planting.
You would have shepherds come by with their herds, and the herds would go through the field and eat all the weeds, right?
So you didn't have to have people pulling them out or – right?
All the grasses and things.
Now, they don't do that.
Now, they just spray it with defoliants.
Or you could just keep tilling the ground as another way to prevent them from growing, right?
But if you overtill, you know, you can do that.
You can keep tilling it with things like alfalfa and other things, but there's a layer in the ground that needs to develop.
The soil develops capillaries just like the human body.
And if you keep tilling it, they don't form.
So in other words, there's a lot of parallels.
You know, the physical world mirrors the archetypes in the spiritual world.
But here, believe it or not, this Adam, Mr. Adam, let's call him, he was physical, and he was in a physical garden.
And these carob were physical as well, manifesting at that time.
You see?
I don't remember.
Do we know that, that they were physically manifesting?
Well, how would they keep him out?
How would they – if they couldn't physically manifest any attributes, how would they keep him out of the garden or stand guard?
Well, you – yeah, I was going to ask about that.
It does bring up some questions, but there's also the aspect of there being a flaming sword there.
So my thing is if the carob are non-physical, how are they going to stop Adam?
But you have the flaming sword.
Hold on.
Are you sure that word means sword?
Or does it mean tiller?
I've taken it for granted, to be honest.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's interesting, yeah.
When you start looking at these things, they start forming a picture very different than what we've been told.
So you would say a pillar of fire.
Yeah.
It's just like – here's another example.
When you look at Lot's wife being turned into salt, that word that they're using, salt, in the versions in Hebrew just means powder.
So you know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
So if someone, let's say, were to be exposed to a nuclear event, let's say an atmospheric nuclear explosion, do you know how they get dustified?
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
But a pillar of fire is still a physical manifestation that would serve to keep Adam out.
So what I was thinking is if the cherubim are there and if we're presuming that they're not physical, then what are they guarding?
They're guarding against Elohim.
They're not guarding against Adam.
Mm.
So why are they trying to protect the tree from Elohim?
Well, I wouldn't say – it doesn't say they're protecting it from Elohim.
No, it doesn't.
But if you're presuming that they're – I mean, you're presuming that they're physical, but if they're not physical, then they're not protecting Adam.
I'm presuming they're just as physical as they were during the exodus.
In other words, when they were led out of Egypt with a pillar of smoke and – a pillar of fire and the smoke, right, that is a cherubim-type manifestation.
Whenever these guys show up, those things show up around with them, you know?
Mm.
Yeah, that's the point.
How much do you – here's the interesting aspect of it.
There's – like from – you know how people talk about the universe, right?
There's only – there's one dimension, but there are multiple universes, which gets confusing to people.
In other words, you have the – everything is in one – everything is happening at the same time, let's say, right, that what you see and you do.
Just because you don't see or are aware of something doesn't mean it doesn't exist, right?
But what I mean by a universe, meaning like a collective of organizational – you know how they call the laws of physics and thermodynamics and all that other stuff, which is not – which is very spurious, but let's just roll with it for a second.
That works in this physical world, which is universe, and there's another universe that's within this universe that is the unseen world.
So, you know, like the concept of a thousand angels dancing on the head of a pin, or, you know, is it possible that if you understand scripture, you understand that you can have a spirit being in the room that you can't see, right?
Right.
It's very comprehensible.
But he – in his realm, he sees his realm and your realm at the same time, but you don't.
You only see one.
So he's in a different universe in the same universe, in other words.
It's not another universe adjacent.
Like, you know, this universe is like room behind curtain A and the other universe is behind curtain B and so on.
There are many universes, you know, meaning they're just as vast and just as complicated or just as simple or just as much variety as each one, but one does not perceive the other.
You see?
Yeah, that makes sense.
And you can perceive, you know, and the superior ones, the ones that have more power can make the lesser one perceptible into the lesser one and vice versa, but the lesser one is very limited.
Right.
The physical – I mean, the very fact that you need a physical body to remain animated, it shows you that, right?
You know, if you just – if someone just walked into the room right now and disintegrated you into a pile of dust, your consciousness goes away.
You might see a – you might recognize that's being done if it's done slow enough, like in a second, right?
Because a second is a really long time in that kind of situation.
A second would feel like maybe a minute.
And you would then see a bright flash of white light, which is the ATP, which is the phosphenes in the body, you know, the motors inside the cells.
They would implode and you see the bright white light, you know.
That means you're done.
And then you go into – it's just like being asleep.
And no matter how hard you try or how hard you wish, there's no consciousness.
Now, you can't do that with a spirit being, as far as we know.
They have their own methods in their universe, you see.
How would you kill a spirit being?
Well, you know, in Psalm – what is it, Psalm?
One of the Psalms in the 80s somewhere, it talks about killing the sons of gods like men.
So that gives you a lot of information there.
So what is it that you would extract as far as a – I have to find the words.
With Lot's wife turning into dust, what is it about that situation that's revealed about the physical reality when she turns to dust just by looking at what the angelic beings are doing?
Well, she looked back.
She went back, in other words.
She looked back.
We don't know of how fast the angels were moving them.
And we don't know when she looked back, if she stayed back long enough to be exposed to it.
Because the event that happened at Sodom was immediate.
It was instant, momentary.
It only took a few seconds.
It's just like, you know, you ever see a nuclear test?
You know, everything's fine, and then within a second you see the flash, and then the mushroom cloud, and that's it.
How long did it take?
Well, you don't want to count the mushroom cloud.
That's after the fact.
You know what I mean?
But if a nuclear bomb goes off, it's not going to discriminate.
It's going to take out everything in its vicinity.
Yeah, that's right.
She's the only one who got taken out, though.
So I'm saying that her vision seemed to have something to do with the effects of the…
I think it's less supernatural for her turning into dust than we can imagine.
Just like, for example, when you comprehend through the information that we're given that, for example, the Israelites crossed the Sea of Reeds, which is a confluence of salt and fresh water, walking on an ice bridge.
It doesn't seem very supernatural, does it?
The timing makes it seem supernatural, obviously.
But even then, it's not, because, you know, the sun came out, the sun was shining, and then Pharaoh pursued, you see?
So the point here is, yeah, it's not very supernatural.
I don't see much other…
I think that the timing…
See, the gods always use natural things.
Even the pillar of smoke and the pillar of fire is very natural.
It's not supernatural.
What's supernatural about it is that it follows you around like it has a mind.
See?
But the thing itself…
There are very few things in Scripture that are supernatural, but the timing and placement and cause of them is.
You know what I mean?
She was given command not to…
Well, I guess the best way to put it is…
Angels.
Yeah.
Don't dawdle.
Keep going.
Get out of there.
So not only to her, to everyone.
But you're right.
And she didn't and paid.
You know, I don't know how a person could mix that down to make any sense out of it, but she voided that contract, you might say, or that assurance.
You know, get out or face the fact.
Without going to mythological metaphor, the concept of fate.
Remember, when Adam and Eve were made aware of the tree of knowledge of good and evil, they saw Lot's wife turning into salt.
So it was meant for her.
Yeah.
See that?
How many times have you ever heard me say, you know, it's wonderful to be in the presence of the gods, but you really don't want to be, essentially.
Because if they pick you to do something, it's not going to end up…
Well, yeah.
And in most cases, you're also not going to end up very well.
So, in other words, if, let's say, you threw all common sense away and we went back to the very beginning and looked at Scripture, before any of these people were born, you would say, oh, I don't want to be Lot.
I mean, personally, I don't want to be Noah.
I don't want to be one of the apostles.
So they had access to that information way back then?
Of course.
Wow.
It's all prophetic.
I was having a discussion about prophecy recently.
About 25 to 30 percent of Scripture is strictly prophecy.
Strictly.
Strict.
I mean, there's no other way to look at it.
But I would say 90 percent of it is because, if not more, because it's all been predestined from that perspective.
That's the interesting thing.
There's still a lot of talk about free will and predestination.
If you're in Scripture, you have no free will.
You're predestined to do all those things.
The people that are not in Scripture are the ones with the free will.
Do you get it?
Okay, yeah.
That makes sense.
And on a national level also.
Wow.
So when you see a nation being destroyed, they have no free will.
They can't change that.
You get it?
Right.
Their destiny is chosen.
But within that, there is free will.
Like, for example, if you look at, you know, I posted some comments now.
It's around the 10th or 11th day of the 10th month.
Yeah, I see that.
That's the time.
It was a bad time.
You know, the 10th month is the number of judgment, right?
You know, Jerusalem, that's the beginning of the sacking of Jerusalem and all these other things happen in the 10th month, right?
You know, and it sounds, you know, from a comic book level, you might say, well, he came in and killed everyone, took everyone captive.
Not really.
Not everyone, because there's conditions there.
The conditions were if you fight Nebuchadnezzar, you will be taken captive or killed.
So don't fight him.
And, you know, you'll just stay here.
And then there was another group that says, oh, we have to go to Egypt.
He's like, no, don't go to Egypt, because if on your way, you will be killed by the sword or by the beast or see.
So there's a little bit of free will there.
So if you look at the picture, there was still a pretty good amount of people, a minority, albeit that stayed in Jerusalem in tatters, obviously.
Just like if you look at any war, when a city is attacked, a large city, even though Jerusalem's not that large, it's only like 20 acres or something.
There were people that still inhabited.
So, I mean, is it clear cut?
Yeah, it's pretty clear cut what's going on here.
Yeah.
But let's go back to what Sam, the topic that Sam brought up about the animals.
Right.
Is that what you wanted, Sam?
The carob?
Yeah.
When you're saying that the sword is not a sword, but a flame.
How do you get that?
Because the sword, the word for sword is carob or cherub.
And I'm seeing the pillar is more like a yield.
So, so where exactly?
Because cherub is always rendered sword everywhere else.
Right.
And what is carob?
Doesn't that sound like carobim a lot?
Yeah, it does.
Yeah.
But notwithstanding, it's still a sword.
It's, yeah, it's still, but you see, they go together almost, don't they?
Yeah.
Flaming sword, carob.
I mean.
If you read it, it's.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
Well, that's, that's the idea is to see that, you know, the sword, what's the sword?
It's, it imposes your will through your hand, doesn't it?
Yeah, I can see that for sure.
But let's not call it something that it's not though on the, on the English side, because it makes for communication errors.
So, it's a sword though.
So far, I would say it's a sword, but it's open.
Because they don't have swords like men do.
But the word that it's using for sword is the swords that men use.
Good, that's why I said go look it up.
Okay.
Are you sure it's a sword?
So, if we're saying that it is a sword, I'm suggesting possibly that the sword is a physical security presence.
Right.
And the carib are not, maybe.
They're invisible.
Yeah, that's plausible.
Yeah, I could roll with that.
I'm not sure.
We're not given that fact or that detail, I should say.
But the fact is that they do remain there.
In other words, from, you know, they took post, took up a post.
Right.
But if you have both a physical and a spiritual security presence, then it can't just be for the sake of keeping Adam out.
That's what I'm saying.
And also, I think in the earlier parts of Genesis, I don't have a bit pulled up in front of me.
But he says, Yahweh says about the tree that Adam has taken from the tree to eat and become like us.
And there's also the aspect of him.
He also says about the tree of life.
He mentions it in connection to Elohim.
Hold on.
Go back.
Stop.
Go like us because he now knows the differences.
He knows what good and evil is.
Right.
How does he become like them?
Well, just knowing good and evil make you like a god?
No, not really.
Right.
But maybe that's one of the reasons why we don't understand it.
Because if we did understand, truly understand what was in Scripture, maybe we would be like them.
And that's not a good thing, right?
Because like you pointed out once before, the more we get from them, the more we get in trouble with them.
Right.
Just like you got a four-year-old.
Give him a Bowie knife, a book of matches, a 9-millimeter, a hatchet, and a fire truck, a real one.
And what do you think is going to happen in like less than five hours?
Someone is going to get hurt.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
Not every time, but just about every time.
Yeah.
To be specific, it says, Man has become like one of us in knowing good and evil.
Now lest he should stretch out his hand and take also of the tree of life and eat and live for the eons.
So what's interesting here is that at the end of the verse, it clearly uses the word also.
And I can look at that in the Hebrew.
I'm pretty sure it's there.
So stretching out your hand is stretching out your influence, right?
Not just your physical hand, right?
Okay.
But nonetheless, you are moving into the presence of that tree or the presence of that force to partake of it.
So it seems to be indicating that not only can the man go and eat of the tree of life, but also the Elohim can eat of the tree of life.
Because it says also, now lest he should stretch out his hand and take also.
So maybe one of the ways of killing the gods is separating them from the tree of life, access to the tree of life.
Yes, that could be.
I haven't thought about that per se, but yeah.
Yeah.
So in other words, he couldn't take from the tree of life directly.
He had to view the tree of life as a form of redemption.
He can take, in other words, man was, this Adam was made to do bad and then be redeemed for doing bad.
You know, here's something to think about.
And this is a little divergent, but it adds more meaning.
Do you know that the creator is physically, I mean, in his realm, you know, as the words show very clearly, going to ransom us from Satan?
Right.
Now, it does not sound like we're being held hostage or taken control over.
When someone, when you ransom someone from someone else, isn't it, you're releasing them from their control, right?
Right.
So this was all, you know, I mean, I tell people don't take it personally, but how can you not, right?
So that's part of the whole process of this tempering.
You ever see when new cars are designed, what they go through?
They have these torture test labs where they're testing the windshield and the wipers and they put the car under high pressure water for 100 hours straight.
And that's supposed to simulate supposed to simulate a few years of brain or something.
And then they put it under heat lamps to simulate being in the sun for five years.
This is kind of like a simulation that we're doing that they're putting us through a big test.
Yeah, yeah.
It's pretty harsh, too.
We don't realize it because I think everybody you'd have mass suicides of people realize what was really going on.
Right.
So.
But anyway, to go back to the subject at hand, go ahead.
The Tree of Life bit is interesting because I think it says, you know, I was going to save this for later.
But since we're here, if the word that they're using for also, which I think is GAM, G-M, is accurate, then that would indicate that, first of all, the Elohim also eat from the Tree of Life.
But if the Elohim being non-physical entities partake of that, then the fruit of that tree can't be physically either.
It has to be informational because that's the medium that spans both the physical and non-physical world.
Yeah, it's both.
It's everything.
It's both physical and informational.
And it's physical in this place called the Garden.
You ever heard of children's books, The Magic Garden?
Where things happen and there's a secret garden, right?
And all these things about a garden and children's stories, you know?
It's not magic in a sense.
But even though magic is real, by the way, you're not supposed to do it because it is real.
Right.
But it's not like they say in mainstream portrayals, this tree with physical fruit like apples or something.
You can kind of pretty conclusively surmise it's something else.
Say that part again?
I said you can pretty conclusively surmise that it's not physical fruit that's being taken, as the mainstream portrayals are.
It's something else.
Because here, Elohim are not going to be eating apples.
Or yeah, it's not a fruit, but it's a meta...
Yeah, it is informational.
Right now, a lot of these things would be choked up as being best illustrated in a fantasy way.
When I mean fantasy, I mean literally.
The way you see anime and fantasy stories being done in the media, right?
So, it would be like that.
It would seem very mystical, and quote-unquote, I'm putting this in quotes, mystical and magical.
It would look like a tree, but it would have attributes.
Again, look at the talking trees, right?
And all these other things that have, through mankind, have come through, right?
Right.
Through stories.
Right, right.
Yeah, now, yeah.
But also, they're in this garden, which is in the New Jerusalem, you know?
So...
Also, what is interesting is that it says, Also, from the tree of light, and eat and live for the eon, in the verse.
So, we know that there's no such thing as forever.
Usually, they're translating the eon as forever.
And based upon what is said in other places, I think you can work out that eon generally tends to be around 2,000 years.
So, what it seems to be saying is that the tree of light would have allowed Adam to live for 2,000 years, at least.
But it doesn't say that it would have allowed him to live perpetually.
Now, the word olam, or eon, right?
Olam, I think they're using, can mean several things.
It would mean a long period of time, as denominated by the timing that we're given, right?
1,000 years is a day, or how things change every 2,000 years, because there's a witness, you know?
One or two, right?
From two or three, right?
But olam is also used as an age, meaning the way things are done.
It could mean, in some places, it's translated as the world, right?
Like, you know how they say Iron Age, Stone Age, Bronze Age, like that?
Which is a misnomer.
I've proven before, through history, not the history that they show, how you have societies like that.
You know, there is no Iron Age, or Bronze Age, or whatever.
Everyone knew about all that stuff.
It's just that they didn't use it, you know?
And then it becomes popular and available, and they use it.
And remember, the further away you go from that part of the world, the less it's pertinent.
Who sounds like a woodpecker?
Is that us, Sam?
Sorry, that's me.
I was trying to quiet it down.
So, going back to the cherubim, I'm trying to see it, but it's kind of cloudy.
What are they guarding from if Adam was kicked out?
The entranceway.
Yeah, but Yahweh knows he's not coming back.
I mean, what's the threat?
Well, what's interesting...
It could be the other humans.
Yeah, it could also be the spirits that were, you know, rogue at the time.
It was just to basically keep the place...
You know, the deed was done, now we have to clean up and stabilize, right?
Sort of like the end of a crime scene, you know, where they put the tape up so no one could pass?
Yeah, in its most sort of general implication, yeah.
Obviously, you'd get that.
But specifically, what they're guarding from isn't really stated, and I think it's interesting.
Because I don't think it's Adam, because he's not going to bum rush the place to try and do anything.
Right, and you notice what's interesting, there was a tapering off of this presence of the garden.
It doesn't discuss specifically if it just lifted off and went away, or withered away or left.
There's no departure scene, right?
So it was around for quite a while after that as well, I would presume.
Because there's enough mention, little bits and pieces here and there are mentioned by others regarding it.
Now, whether it's because it was still in their presence, or whether it was because they had a very strong oral tradition or records.
I don't know exactly.
Remember, this is something else to discover in terms of similar processes happening throughout time and whatever.
When you start off something, when you have a new thing...
And remember, this is not creation, this is a recreation, it's a reforming of the Earth.
That's why I keep saying evolutionists are wrong, and so are creationists, they're both wrong.
Because nowhere in scripture does it support either one.
Scripture supports a recreation, or a remodeling, a redoing, right?
So what's interesting is whenever you start something, reformed or created, you manage it in the beginning.
And then as it develops, you become more hands-off, and you let it do its thing.
Think of it, let's say you're going to have a vinyl record player.
You put the record on and you spend all this time cleaning the record or making sure everything is balanced.
You're anti-skate and all that, and you drop the tone arm down and it starts to play, everything's cool.
Then you sit down and relax, right?
And then it comes to the end of the song, on the record, what do you do?
You get activated again, you get up, right?
And you go approach it again, right?
You see?
And so the most active time in scripture for the gods directly, overtly, to mankind is when?
In the beginning, and...
you guessed it.
At the end.
So these processes happen all the time.
Let's say you have a popcorn maker or a coffee machine.
You set up the coffee machine, right?
And you go do all this work, you're there.
Then as it's brewing, you walk away, do something else, and then when it's done, what do you do?
You come back to it, right?
You see how all these processes are similar?
I'm not trivializing it, but if you want to talk about trivia, I mean, hey look, we've got these two trees that pretty much govern our existence.
I mean, that sounds pretty trees.
I mean, we chop down trees all the time.
We know they're just good to look at, but they're pretty trivial to us.
There's no big deal.
You see?
Why are they trees?
Why couldn't they be something else?
So there's an interesting thing here showing you there's a process going on.
There's a tree in the end as well, right?
And there's a tree in the middle.
That's very important.
And trees branch out, so maybe there's a metaphor that's going on there also, you know?
Yeah, and also there's enough of the tree based on the type of tree underground.
They used to show very rudimentary mirror images, that the tree is just as big underneath.
It's not true.
The tree has roots, and in order to have roots, it has to be in soil or some kind of firm material and watered, and it gets light from the…
it gets energy from what it's locked into, and it also gets energy from the sky.
You know?
Tree is ets, E-T, ets, right?
But I would say that, you know, looking at everything, there's a lot of, obviously, you know, you see the metaphor of the arboreal, what do you call it, dendro, dendric, or arboreal, you know, the tree concepts coming through is very crucial with the Christ as well.
What's interesting, even when you hear about some more well-read, quote-unquote, Christians, they call it the tree of crucifixion.
Have you heard that term used a lot?
You know, the real ignorant ones just say crucifixion.
You know, they think the Roman thing, the guy with the long hair wearing the diaper.
But the older ones that are more studied, and they discover what's going on, and they can't come out and say, you know, you've all been defrauded with all your imagery and your names and all that, because they'll be eating out of a garbage can if they do that.
So, they start incorporating the tree of crucifixion.
And then they'll say, oh, what do you mean by that?
Oh, well, you see, you know, the tree was whittled down.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was a tree.
It was an almond tree, because we're not stupid, right?
So, and there was three men nailed to one tree, and there was a stoning.
And I don't use the term lapidation much, but that's the technical term.
And it follows suit with the accounts given in the text.
Why did the people, where were they hanging around for six hours?
You know, and, you know, all this other stuff.
So, anyway, and then there's metaphors throughout Scripture regarding the tree and that event, and the tree and the first event, and the tree and the last event, you know.
So, what you see in other eschatological writings.
Continuing in line with the cherub talk, I'm looking at Ezekiel 28, which obviously talks about this malevolent entity that does his own thing and gets sort of spanked for it.
And it says about him, you were in Eden, the garden of Elohim, you were the anointed cherub that covered.
So, I don't know, I mean, what other cherub is mentioned as being in the garden?
It's only the ones that are protecting the tree.
And we know that the only mention of cherubs covering, per se, is on the Ark of the Covenant.
So, the cherub who covers, who presumably was also one of the ones tasked in the garden to guard the tree, could be the culprit here.
So, here's the other interesting thing.
Satan or the adversary, is he an angel?
No, he's not an angel.
Right?
Is he a god?
Yeah, you could say he's a god in terms of even angels being classified as gods of that kingdom.
But what was he exactly, you know, in that position there?
Well, that part of scripture would be very safe, seemingly, on just that little bit of scripture, is that cherub Satan, the Nakash, right?
I don't even like to use that name, but is it him?
Then why would he be given the metaphor, why is he given the name snake?
You see?
Yeah, I don't think it's him.
Well, there is no snake on the cherub, you see.
So, do we have another instance going here?
I would say there is.
Because there's so many instances that could happen, if you read out of the script, where it says that one third of that heavenly host or heavenly realm departed, you know, from the main line, you know?
Why not a cherubim going also, right?
Why not?
Why not angels going?
Why not sons of gods also being included there?
Why not other, you know?
How many species of gods do they, you know?
When I say God, you know, scripture uses, you know, the angels, are they gods?
No.
But are they called gods?
Yes, because it's that entire, right?
So, the entire realm is, you know, is god-like.
So, in that universe, let's say.
So…
It's interesting when you say that, because very rarely do you make the snake connection to the nakash, because I think it's sort of stigmatized at this point as being, you're trying to say that Satan's a snake, which he's not.
No, he's not.
The snake is obviously part of the, well, maybe not obviously, but I would think it's part of the creeping things category.
And the creeping things are not represented on the cherubim.
Well, it doesn't say that he's creeping, but it does say he's on his bill.
Creeping would be a lizard as well, a dragon, wouldn't it?
Yeah, anything that sort of moves on the ground.
Yeah.
So, they have to be represented by something though.
Just because you can't find creeping things or fish on the cherubim doesn't mean that they wouldn't be represented by something else.
No.
Hmm.
But you wouldn't really see, I mean, that would be delineated, wouldn't it?
Well, sometimes things are just omitted, and you have to read out of the omission.
So, for whatever reason, Yahweh has no covenant with certain types of animals, but that doesn't mean that they aren't under the authority of something else, because they're there.
They have to have, you know, they have to be controlled from somewhere.
So, who's controlling that aspect of creation?
Somewhere else.
Yeah.
So, it's an interesting thought to ponder.
What do you mean?
Yeah, well, the animal kingdom is also affected and represented on the other side, the realm of the gods.
They have animals there as well.
Right.
So, you know, why would the, you know, the stigmas and the prejudices of the Western world, you know, why would so many cultures, native, I'll use the term native, talk about the bear god or the horse god or the bird god, right?
Because they're ignorant?
No.
Quite well informed.
And also, for example, what we call giant lizards or dinosaurs, you know, if you look at even things that are in modern depiction, like let's say the Chinese zodiac, if you look at it, all the animals that are in there are animals that were common.
Why would they stick a dragon in there or a dinosaur?
All of a sudden, you know, they have a rat, a horse, a snake, a dog, and all this, and all of a sudden they put a dinosaur in there?
In their zodiac?
All of a sudden they put a...
No, no, no, no, no.
It's because it was common.
Also.
I mean, not in number.
You know, if you, you know, right?
At some point it came into their lives.
Oh, yeah.
It was known that it existed and it was alive and it was doing well.
It was, may not have been as frequent.
So, you know.
In other words, what I'm trying to show is that it's best to read out of what's going on based on the rationale of what you're reading.
And because sometimes comparing it to the rationale that you're used to in this current condition of society, it doesn't make any sense.
But if you clear your head and just look at it rationally, like an IQ test, like what do all these things have in common, you know?
Even though I don't like bringing the IQ test up, right?
You ever take one?
You know, eventually it gets into these abstract things, which then comes next or whatever, right?
They show you a pattern.
So if you look at something like the Chinese zodiac or zodiac and you see a pattern and all of a sudden they show you these common...
It's all common animals and all of a sudden there's a mythological creature there?
No, no, no, no, no.
Sorry, folks.
That was a common animal also.
So, you see.
So the interesting part here, like all these discussions and why I do enjoy speaking, is because the more we do this type of talk now, in the next few years, we're going to sound like we all graduated from the Mr. Peabody school of the incredibly clever, whatever.
Exceedingly clever, thank you.
Because a lot of the things that we're discussing now are going to be brought into the light in the near future as being re-examined.
So this is kind of like a head start, you know, on this.
But is there a lot more that needs to be discovered about this?
Yeah, and the irony of it is, like I've been saying for a long time, the last thing to be discovered is what's obvious.
I'm telling you that everything that we need to know is right in front of us.
We just can't see it right now.
It's a temporal thing.
It's not a practical thing where you have to go out and dig a hole to find something.
It's right in front of us.
We just don't see it, because it's not time yet.
So I think these discussions, and I'm just diverting a little bit here, I don't know, I should say that the Greek-speak type stuff that's been going on is, it's okay to ponder, and it's okay to get into it deeper and deeper, but I still have to raise my hand and say that I don't think it's time yet for all of this stuff.
It's not just time yet.
For example, what Sam has brought up tonight that we're discussing, it doesn't mean that it won't be known a week from now or a month from now or five years from now.
I'm just saying that right now, as far as we can see, or as I can see, or you can see, this is what we can see at the moment.
But be rest assured that as time goes on, especially in this time that we're living in, we're going to get an accelerated rate of knowledge and perception of what all these things are, even more and more day by day, week by week, year by year.
Now, when you said this would become more prevalent, is this across the whole nation, the whole world?
The whole world, yeah.
And are we talking vast numbers of people, or are we talking a selected few?
Yeah, yeah, vast numbers of people.
It'll be shown to them.
I don't know what they're doing, because that would disturb society too much.
But why is it important that everyone gets a handle on these things as being true, or enough of these things?
Why?
I've discussed this before, and the only reason that I see it now is that otherwise, if the destruction that is going to be put on this society, if the people didn't know these things, it would be considered unlawful.
Unlawful, yes.
Right, so just like when someone's on death row, and they pull the electric chair, or pull the trigger, right before they do that, they read out exactly why they're there, what they did and all that.
Again, you ever notice that?
Yep, just to make sure.
Yep, exactly.
Dot the i's and cross the t's.
So all of this, a realist will say, something bad is coming.
In other words, the more knowledge, I view it as being good, I have a genuine interest in these things.
But from a societal measurement level, it's very bad, because that just means you're getting closer to the trigger or the switch being pulled.
You know what I mean?
Which is well deserved, by the way.
I'm all for it.
I'm not trying to stave it off, and if it would happen in the next five minutes, it should have happened a long time ago, but I'm just saying, it's not good.
But most people that don't know will see it as being good, because look, we're learning more and more.
I'm like, that's good.
Yeah, you're learning more and more, but that just means now you're being set up for a more lawful termination.
Yeah, I'm sort of good with the caribou.
There's not a ton of things to really go through there, because you have to piece together little things to create a bigger picture.
But I think that in connection with them, maybe Satan is always interesting to look at also.
For example, when you look at the curse in Genesis 3, we know that it's not a snake, but somehow you have to make sense of the fact that he's associated with this animal language.
You know, cursed be you from every beast and from every animal of the field.
On your torso you shall crawl, on soil you shall eat.
But that's after he tempted Eve.
What was he before?
Before he was banished to the earth, crawling around?
Well, there might be a metaphor or indirect, I think.
I don't know how direct it is.
In Ezekiel, he was responsible for things of great value.
Hmm.
Isn't there some verses in Ezekiel?
Yeah.
He's managing things of great value, Sam, or am I...
I don't know that one.
Because I don't know if the word Nekosh shows up there.
I don't think so.
But it could be indirect.
Yeah, it's indirect.
There's more indirect...
Look, if you're being set up to be controlled by a malevolent entity to prove to these malevolent entities...
You know they're malevolent because of what their intent is towards us, right?
And then of course, you know, that creates a glitch and so that makes them just malevolent all around.
But there is no battle between these malevolence and the Most High at all.
That's the other thing that requires a very mature mindset to comprehend.
Although we shouldn't discard the fact that there is a battle going on between them amongst themselves, away from the Most High.
Yes, and it seems like a jurisdictional and a territorial or fighting or war in heaven, right?
So it's amongst themselves and amongst others.
And it stirred up an entire just violent sentiment all around.
Like in Daniel, when the angel says he was battling the prince of Persia.
Why would he be battling?
Why?
But this all started when Elohim made man.
Right.
Or was this going on before man?
This was going on before.
Okay, that's fair.
Because it's mentioned, the last book is really the first book, and there's a lot of discontent in that, let's say within the peace of that realm, you know.
So I'm pouring some more coffee.
So, yeah, you know, I think that in the next few years, and I don't mind being specific, I won't give dates, I'll just give blocks of time as I see them being lawful.
You're going to see more of a focus on what I call what's called archaeology, because it's physical evidence, you know, of these things.
And once the physical evidence of, let's say, biblical stuff starts to come up, and I don't mean like a caravan or anything like that.
Once it starts, once you start getting more and more physical evidence that the biblical narrative is true, then what's going to happen, the only thing that's left after that is information that supports the Bible from that time through archaeology will start coming out, and we'll get even more.
Like, for example, the Dead Sea Scrolls that came about in the mid-20th century, right?
Notice how they just popped out of nowhere.
Well, we're going to be getting more and more and more as time goes on, and I mean on a weekly, monthly, yearly basis, that will start supporting more information.
In other words,
there's hundreds of books,
literally hundreds,
that are mentioned in Scripture
indirectly that we don't have access to,
because no one knows
what we don't know publicly
where they are,
and I'm not just talking about
the Book of Asher,
or the Book of Yasher,
or the Book of Enoch that's mentioned,
which is basically giving
honor to the priests,
because that was written by them,
the people in the Temple.
But essentially, what I mean by hundreds of books is you read about, let's say in Chronicles and Samuel and other places like that, that is it not written in Israel.
You ever notice that there's books mentioned there?
Where are they?
You know, they're buried.
So, where are they buried?
Well, guess who goes out with a shovel and carefully digs and looks for old stuff?
Archaeologists.
I'm not saying you should be an archaeologist because you'll be spending your life in ruins, right?
Right.
So, but you see my point?
So, I've been mentioning this lately.
If anyone can take a hint, I've been mentioning archaeology more and more lately, and how important that is.
But it wasn't time, you know, five, ten years ago, it wasn't time, even though it's been consistently on the upswing.
It's very gradual.
It's just like a bucket.
You ever have a leak somewhere and you say, I'll take care of that tomorrow, and you put a bucket under there and you check on it, like, instead of tomorrow, like a little sooner than tomorrow, and you're like, oh, it's full already.
How could it be?
Right?
You see?
So, there's drops.
Every day there's a drop, every drop of falling out of this archaeology thing.
One of the things that I do now on browsers when I go out to see what's going on, I put in archaeology on a browser search, and then I hit past 24 hours, or past week.
I don't want to, you know, you see?
Like, every other day or whatever, I'll just put in a browser the word archaeology, past 24 hours, past week.
Because if you don't do that, you'll get the definition of the words and museum sites.
So, now, instead of looking at certain newspapers, I just put in Middle East, past 24 hours.
You know, on the tools, on the browser, what happened, 24 hours.
That's what it's like now, you see?
People ask me, what site do you go to?
I'm like, no, no.
Just search the subject, go to the past 24 hours.
Make Google work for you.
Yeah, and that's really, like, that's quote unquote hot off the presses, right?
Right.
And only, that makes more sense now because these guys out there, they got the silly pods and the smart phones, right?
So, you could be out, as long as they have internet access, they could upload photos, they could put a story, you see?
Right.
Where 10 years ago, that was impossible.
Like that, 24 hours.
You might wait a month or two weeks or.
Well, you got satellite phones now and the whole nine yards, satellite modems, uplinks.
it's amazing.
Yeah, you know, all those satellite, as all Motorola and Boeing.
Yeah, that would inspire me a bit.
Yeah, well, I'm not going to get into too many details, but if you, let's say, you have one of those, it's, you take it apart, it's Boeing and Motorola.
It doesn't matter where you are.
Motorola's got their hand in a lot of stuff.
Yeah.
The Russians have their own thing in the American, everyone, you're either using the Russian, the Japanese and Chinese have their own brands also, but, you know, if you get one of those, it's Boeing.
Anyway, why did I just bring that up?
I don't know.
Just, okay, so, archeology is going to be very important.
And, of course, while getting into the primacy of the scriptures, which is the language of preservation, and I'm still just always, if you've listened to Greek speak through the years, I've always hammering on the Hebrew, right?
And I say Hebrew and Greek, but I never really discussed too much of the, what they call the New Testament, because that is, even in Greek, that is a mess.
It is a mess.
And I mean, the Greek preservation is just as bad as the English King James is compared to the Hebrew.
That's how bad it is.
But, it's better than nothing.
So, you're going to have to go to Hebrew and Aramaic on the Greek, on what's called the New Testament.
And that's been sort of closeted away, believe it or not.
And it's still, I mean, it's out there.
There's some Aramaic stuff.
But, yeah, and I don't get into it much.
And that's why, if you, you will never see the problems in the Greek New Testament, or the New Testament in general, unless you know what?
You need to know two things.
The law.
You need to know the law.
That's right.
And you need to know that it was not written in Greek, but they didn't speak Greek.
And they didn't write Greek.
Yeah.
Right.
So, you need to keep that in the back of your head all the time.
That's why when you run into something in the New Testament that goes against what's the law, you're like, oh, that can't be correct.
And you go, and you look, and you look, and you see it's a mistranslation.
Think of the law as like the law of physics.
You know, I mean, I don't fully subscribe to that.
But if you're designing a bridge, you know, F equals P over V, and, you know, all these basic formulas, you know, they work.
They usually do work.
You know, if you're working with hydrology, there are certain formulas that work, that constantly.
I don't believe this, you know, 0.43 psi per foot on head pressure.
I don't believe it.
You know, so I start setting up all these columns and measure it.
Guess what?
It's 0.43 psi per foot of water.
You know, basically half a pound.
Every time, I'm like, oh, okay, that's a pretty good, you know, so when you look at, it's a standard.
So the law, if you don't know, that's why so many people are told, forget about the law.
It's done away with.
How many times have you done a Greek speak thing and I bring up secular laws that are the U.S. codes that are very relevant and no one knows.
Right.
Like you're not authorized to use the money, right?
And even if you do try to, even if you did try to fight it, you'd be battled by both sides of the, of this equation, which is either government or business or, you know.
Well, they have plausible deniability.
If you go into court and you say, well look, you know, all these titles have been decriminalized, you know.
Right.
Like I always bring up, you know, how many, I've showed the code that Title 21, which is narcotics possession, drug possession, all that is not criminal anymore.
It's civil.
How many people are being busted today as we speak per minute on drug charges?
Hundreds.
Criminal.
Yeah.
Per minute, yeah.
And you could show in the law and if you know the law, they'll just pull you aside and they'll say, yeah, you know what, we're just going to dismiss it this time.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So anyway, could you imagine going to some of these people that are active in that business and say, listen guys, it's not criminal.
I can prove it to you.
You know, and that wouldn't be really a good thing because they're tied into other things also.
Right.
So my point here is this.
If you go to court on that, they'll just say, well, everybody knows you should go to jail if you do that.
It's plausible deniability.
Just like with scripture.
Oh, everybody knows, you know, Walt Disney or Mel Gibson did a movie about it.
Right?
Yeah.
How many times have you heard that?
I've, a few weeks ago, I went in some of these forums.
I was looking at biblical stuff and there was a guy writing an article into a forum.
It was absolute trash.
It was written about, you know, something about Christ and he actually cited Mel Gibson's movie and I'm like, you people are, it's been fire and brimstone for a long time already.
anyway.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's pretty sad.
Actually, I spoke to someone a few years ago that worked on that film who knows Mel Gibson and Mel Gibson actually, you know, he, this is according to him, he personally invested in a mini church or a mini chapel in his private property, Mel Gibson, like his house.
He actually had people build a little Catholic chapel there.
Wow.
He's so faithful and I said, that movie is a piece of junk.
That whole storyline is false and all that and he just went off on me.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not going to hold, you know.
Right.
So.
Wow.
So, back to the Satan talk.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
We're not, so we're not really able to, or at least I'm not, and we don't seem to have looked at it really, the animal language, we can't really see what is being referred to there since he's not talking about actual animals.
Well, it could be.
Well, you're going to crawl in your belly, you're going to eat from the dust.
The eat from the dust thing I can sort of get a little bit because I see that being talked about elsewhere like in Isaiah when he says that the snake will still eat from the dust in the latter days and things like that.
I can see references there but other things are a little cloudy.
Well, looking at it this way, who partook, who broke the rule first?
Eve.
Right.
And did Adam, Adam could have just looked the other way and said, you're on your own, B-I-T-C-H, right?
Like they do in the ghetto.
Actually, this creature was the one that came in there and started the whole thing off.
That's not breaking rules, though.
He could have done whatever he wanted.
He had a license to do that.
I mean, I don't think Elohim would really, would have been approving of it.
Well, he was the one that set it up in the first place.
True.
So he knew.
He doesn't have to approve it because he set it up.
But look, it's just like when you do martial arts, you have a young boy that's trained really well and he's all, you know, cocky about it and you're like, you know what, when he make a phone call and, you know, when the boy is running to go to the store or school, make a call and he says, you know, he's ready.
He's ready to be jumped.
I want you to get a bunch of guys and just come and jump him and see if he really knows his stuff, if he's surprised.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Is that plausible for a parent to do that?
Sure.
Of course.
So, it's not a pretty thing.
Actually, in some of the martial arts, it's done and if you don't survive it, well, you weren't ready.
so, let's just say Eve partook first, right?
Okay.
And, you notice that when that dialogue goes on, you will be dust of the earth, you'll be eating this, and her seed and your seed, right?
Right.
You notice it's her seed and his seed, right?
But Adam is the accomplice, isn't he?
Right.
So, okay, who was the accomplice to Satan then?
Secondary.
Right.
They were watching by and they were hurt by it.
Look, this whole thing about coming out of the side, you know how I talk about it's lateral?
Right?
You know, Eve came out of Adam's side, right?
Mm-hmm.
And we come out of Eve through water, don't we, when we're born?
When the Christ, when they realized his job was done, didn't they put a, didn't they pierce his side and water came out of his side?
Water and blood, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, just like water and blood, placenta, right?
Right.
Do you see all the metaphors here being used?
I'm seeing the metaphors, but we still need to get the definite correlation between everything, which is a little harder.
Hmm.
But they're metaphors because we're not being given all the detail.
Right.
So, it's still a metaphor.
You see, actually, there are places in Scripture where there's tremendous detail being given, like in Exodus, for example, you know, on the construction of certain things.
Have you ever noticed that?
Because that's not a metaphor.
But on other examples, like for example, on how the temple was to be built, instructions on that, we're not given any of that, but David was given that, you know, and it was given to him on stone tablets.
How do we know?
Hmm.
Well, because usually when you write stone tablets that are continuing a story, not where the story ends on one tablet, when you go to, you put the stones in order, the order based on the last sentence in one is also the first sentence in the other.
So when you read in Chronicles or other parts of Scripture where the sentences are repeated exactly, that just means that it's another stone.
They wrote it exactly as it was written.
That's like a marker to show you, you know, so if the last, if you're writing a stone, the last sentence is the cat is black, the next stone to continue the story, you write again, the cat is black, and that means that's where it continues, you see.
Right.
And what's another reason you write, it's a marker, and you'll see sometimes things being repeated in Scripture, and that means that is actually being transcribed from a stone, something that was written on stone, and why stone and not clay?
Permanent?
Stone is permanent.
Well, you could throw stone and clay and fired clay, they're pretty permanent, both of them.
You could break them both pretty readily.
If a woman who's menstruating is in the room or touches the clay, what are you supposed to do with it?
Oh, destroy it.
It's unclean, right.
If she touches a stone, does the stone become unclean?
No.
Hmm.
That's why you read about hewn vessels, doesn't say pottered vessels, because if you had a vessel made of terracotta or clay, and a woman who was menstruating walked in and closed the door, or touched it, does all that water, because some of these cisterns were as tall as you were, you know, 80 gallons or so, 50 gallons, is that vessel and that water clean?
No.
Or if a piece of dead flesh touched it, or someone ejaculated on it, is it clean?
No, it has to be clean.
But if it's stone, is it unclean?
No.
Is the water unclean?
So things were made out of stone based on what?
The law.
Versus clay.
Now you have a lot of this Babylonian cylinder seals and stuff which are intended for clay, that's because they were not as hung up on the law, on these things.
But you know what's interesting is the seal itself is made of stone, isn't it?
It's lapidary.
Hmm.
Very rarely are the cylinder seals made of clay themselves, right?
They're usually carved into stone.
Right.
So there's what I'm trying, it might seem like I get off the subject or whatever, but I think the mindset is important here as well.
Yeah, it is.
It is.
Yes.
Because when you rationalize, okay, how many times have you heard like that person's irrational or rational?
You know what we base that on?
On how normal they are considered based on social norms.
Right.
Right?
Think about it.
Mm-hmm.
So screw that.
You know, that's why I brought up the zodiac as an example, like some Asian zodiacs.
You have a zodiac with all these common animals and all of a sudden here's a dinosaur.
Why would they do that?
It doesn't, on an IQ test it doesn't work.
Okay, all these are common and this one's uncommon?
No, that doesn't make any sense.
They're all common animals, commonly known.
You see?
And it's normal.
And it's normal, but it's not normal now.
Now all of a sudden, you know, it's not.
You see?
So, in other words, can you escape the rationalism that is imposed or accepted within your day-to-day life, meaning since you were born?
Into looking at all these other things, because really, you know, you also have to consider that if you took someone from the past thousands of years ago and brought them into the future, here, it wouldn't take more than a day or two or a week, max, for them to completely adjust.
I mean, obviously, they'll be missing certain things and be impressed by others, but they're pretty much the same.
I think right now, mankind is severely genetically downgrading Oh, yes.
Big time.
Proof of that is just go look at some black and white films from the 30s or before and look at how robust people looked and then go look at how they look now.
Just visually.
And I'm not talking about phrenology and all that other crap.
I'm talking about just obvious health.
Health and the spirit.
And that's just in the last century or less.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
So...
Severely downgraded.
Yeah.
And it's meant to be.
It's meant to be.
But it doesn't mean you throw your hands up and say, well, it's meant to be.
I'm not going to, you know, I'll go along with it.
Well, you can do that too.
Right.
But...
Speaking of animals, as you were mentioning before, I also think it's interesting that when the curse is placed on the Nakash and we know that there's definitely some kind of a serpent or a snake connection, he's not really cursed from among the creeping things, though.
He's cursed from among the beasts of the field, which are represented by the cattle or the ox in the case of the caribou, which is a bit confusing.
It says, for the likeness of...
Sorry, that's in Ezekiel.
But in the curse itself, it says, cursed be you from every beast and from any...
from every animal of the field.
What does the Nakash have to do with oxen or cattle?
He's separated, that's for sure.
Well, the living creation, you know, the sentient creation, because the only thing that's left there is aquatic and air creatures and plants.
Yeah.
And crawling things.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
And also, there's a similarity there because we're talking about this is the reformation or the creation of life as we know it.
And do you know how interchangeable the internal organs appear to be amongst creatures?
You know, if I took out a pig's heart, liver, and whatever and put it right next to a human one, unless you were very highly trained, you couldn't tell the difference, right?
Mm-hmm.
So, we're...
we're looking at a delineation of a time period when all these things were put together.
You know?
Where now, those delineations wouldn't hold, I think.
But there's still a clear demarcation between the beasts of the field and the creeping things.
And the serpent has nothing to do with, ostensibly, has nothing to do with cattle.
And yet, he's cursed from among the beasts of the field.
The cattle.
I think that needs to be re-examined, what's memorialized there in the...
Oh, come on.
No, seriously.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
I need to do a thing on Genesis to go all the way through.
I've been threatening this for a long time.
And you and I, Sam, have had private discussions on it.
But it needs to be done very specifically.
And I really haven't sat down in front of the text as it's memorialized in Hebrew.
Were you on a...
We had a...
I think, Sam, you were on a conversation once I had someone who was a native Israeli Hebrew speaker.
And we started...
And I think you were also able to bring up some of the fine points of what he was bringing up on certain difficulties, right, and comprehending what was in Scripture.
Mm-hmm.
Right?
So that needs to be...
All that needs to be reexamined because...
Is it...
Who's speaking?
Who is it being directed to?
Why is it being spoken of that way is more important to get a grip on that than exactly what's being said word by word.
You know, we have to put this thing into more context.
And there is more context to it.
Because that's why I'm trying to show there's...
These are not only actual events in a certain sequence, but they're also metaphors that are carried through the rest of Scripture.
You know, it might sound, you know, like, you know, why did they pierce his side and water and blood came out?
Why did Eve come out of his side?
You know, why did...
You see, all of these things keep following through over and over.
There's an archetype here.
And I think that once we get an idea of the archetype, this will be more 3D, you know, more tangible.
And the archetype here is very simple.
This is not happening on the earth.
So how many...
How many of those archetypes are here right now with us?
You know, not all of them, most of them.
Obviously, we brought up the discussion of the trees.
Yes, we, you know, pretty much as a child, most people can discern what a tree is when you say it, right?
But why are we having such difficulty defining the trees in the garden?
Well, what was their purpose we need to define, right?
You know, the mindset and all that stuff.
And are they trees?
Yes, they're trees.
Just like if you said dog or cat or bird.
You know, yes, they're dogs and cats and birds or whatever, right?
But are they...
But you've got to remember the context.
They're in this supernatural and ultra-natural place.
And I think you mentioned one time it wasn't even on earth.
No, it's not.
So let's look at that also.
If I'm more specifically looking at the garden itself, which I think is more of a narrower...
But hold on.
Let me go back to what Bruce just said.
It is on earth, but it's not part of the earth.
So let's...
So we're...
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, here's a real simple way to say it.
Remember that film Independence Day when I first saw that?
I was like, oh, wow, this is great.
Thank you for doing that.
These ultra-large spaceships, right?
Well, that's nothing.
Like those ships that you see, saw on Independence Day, are literally, literally, now I'm saying, in proportion, really a grain of sand in size compared to what I'm talking about here.
Oh, my God.
The size of this other ship.
We're talking it's a thousand miles plus wide.
You see?
So...
Then this means that this tree could bend just about anything.
You know, that...
No, it's a tree.
Okay.
Well, okay.
It's a tree.
Just like I said earlier.
Right.
Can you imagine going into a fantasy-type situation like they do in anime or children's fantasies?
Where you have talking trees and magic trees and magic gardens and secret gardens?
Okay, well, it's like that times ten.
It's that times ten.
I mean, Jack-in-the-Beanstalk stuff is normal kind of stuff.
You see what I mean?
Right.
Isn't it interesting?
Jack-in-the-Beanstalk grows up, up, up, up.
It's just like taken from the plant that grew by Jonah.
Remember the story at the end?
Right.
And it grows up and there's a whole other kingdom up there.
You get it?
Aren't you putting it together here?
These things have lasted in the imagination of mankind with the lack of accuracy, of course.
Right.
I'm not trying to say that I'm super accurate on this, but I think that all this needs to be reasoned with because what we see here is we have a garden not in a wilderness because if you have something growing in the wilderness you never call it a garden.
The only time you have a garden is in a city or when you've manicured or changed the natural environment enough you go back and make a garden, you see.
Right.
You don't have gardens in the wilderness.
No one has ever gone to a rainforest and said, Hey, look at this garden.
Right.
Unless you've cleared it and you see.
So we're talking about something that is a fixture inside of a highly developed, highly manipulated, highly formed edifice Yeah.
or community.
That's your first giveaway that it's a garden.
And there are other things that you can read out of the text itself if we're going to look at more precise details.
So the word for garden
is a garden
is gun
if I'm not mistaken
which is spelt in Hebrew
with two letters
gimel
and nun
so if we can conclude
that gimel means
to walk
or foot
and nun means
the serpent
then the garden
would actually mean
the walking serpent
or the foot
of the serpent
or
I mean
that's not a bad conclusion
so that would mean
that the garden
technically
you could assume
that it was the name
which explains
why he was there
in the first place
because why the hell
is he there
if it's not his place
to be
and it could also explain
why Eve was not surprised
to interact with him
she didn't ask him
what he was doing there
Right
and also
what's the first letter
in his name
right
nun
and she seemed
to know him
Yeah
if you want to focus
the thing is
I try not to focus
too much
on the reptilian side
because people like
David Icke
who stole my bike
and all these other idiots
Right
reptilians have over
I've overdone it
yes they're idiots
with a capital D
but that's fine
that's what's
you know
they're supposed to be doing
what they're doing
there is a
there's a big play
on that
spiritually
the dragon is held
as a
malevolent
benevolent
auspicious
omen in Asian culture
right
which is
you could say
is unchanged
I think more
there's more discussion
I think it requires
a level of maturity
that most people lack
to discuss this openly
but I think it will
I'd like to get into it
more
in the future
when I just need to go back
and look at notes
and things that I've
pondered on in the past
to put it in a more
rational perspective
than what is
the way
this whole reptilian thing
is out in the world
right now
again
the
it being specifically
reptilian in nature
is again
metaphorical
look at the
what qualities
do reptiles have
you know
they change their body temperature
according to their environment
they're very adaptive
right
so
and many other aspects
right
they have protective layers
some of them shed skin
other ones are
you know
yep
so
there's many elements to it
but I think
the metaphor
is very strong
cannot be avoided
and should be
considered
you know
the reptilian metaphor
because you know
you know
when I say reptilian
not only a snake
as we say snake
but it's also a dragon
right
so
that needs to be considered
were we created
by reptilians
I don't know
I'm not going to say
but no
but they do play
a major role
you know
and I don't want to go
into that too much
because that
all that's been
muddied up
too much to
deal with it
on a maturely level
yeah
but there is a lot of
interest in it
yeah
and I think the interest
will come to a peak
in the future
more rationally
sure
but what I think
is interesting here
is that the
garden
looks to me
to be
a domain of the Nakash
it doesn't seem to be
some place that Adam
was placed in
because it was his thing
I mean even if you
read the text
it says he was put there
to keep it
right
to tend to it
you're tending to
somebody else's thing
and so if the owner
is walking around
living his life
you're not going to
find that to be
out of the ordinary
which explains
his presence
I would say
the owner
even well
let's say
let's say just to grab
for a second
that it was the domain
of the Nakash
right
of the serpent
the adversary right
he's still not the owner
he's granted that
he's there by privilege
okay
so you have another
level
a tertiary
he's secondary
and then you have
a tertiary level
of Adam
that's your hint
right away
that should have been
a hint to Adam
that well he was
naive
but not naive
enough to not
name the animals
obviously he was
educated
he came
he came with
downloads
or he was taught
it doesn't say that
he was taught
so I'm presuming
he was given
downloads right
we don't have
a time frame
on that
to relish
how long it took
to get the
download complete
and all that
presuming
Sam I think
we discussed roughly
he was in the
garden roughly
a hundred years