And we don't have a time frame on that to relish how long it took to get the download complete and all that.
Presuming, Sam, I think we discussed roughly, he was in the garden roughly a hundred years of our years, let's say.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah, you'll find that when you get into more detail.
A hundred of their years or?
No, our years.
Our years.
A hundred years.
Well, a hundred of the years that you would number as a year.
Okay.
All right.
Which is.
Yeah.
Okay.
So remember, they live to they could live up to a thousand.
Some of them were very close to that.
Right.
Okay.
Well, nine sixty seven or something like that.
Right.
Or so.
So anyway.
So roughly he was roughly a hundred, which would have made he was still a young buck at one hundred.
He would have been in today's math.
He would have been a teenager.
Yeah.
You know, like 17, 16.
That's an immaturity level.
Right.
I would suggest there's a there's a relativistic problem because we cannot comprehend that kind of longevity at this point.
But you have to imagine it is, you know, that's one thing about scripture.
Well, let me just preface this.
You know, everything is happening in the imagination.
And just because you can see and hear in real time, it doesn't mean that you're not processing it in the imagination also, because you could be looking at the surroundings that you have in your room where you are listening to me right now.
And as you're focusing on what you're perceiving, you can also think that you're sitting on a chair at a beach somewhere.
Right.
You can do that while you're in.
And then.
Yeah.
So what I'm saying is that everything happens in the imagination.
That's why when you capture people's imagination, you could you can have you can do magic in front of them.
You know what I call that magic.
But the tricks, sleight of hand stuff.
So it's beyond distraction.
So when you're reading scripture, you need a very strong imagination, not meaning fictional, but you need to be able to take what information is given and create a picture from it, a setting, you know.
And you know, you're getting you're good at that when you open up scripture and it scares the hell out of you, because you'll be, let's say, you open the book of, let's say, Yirmeyahu or Jeremiah somewhere, and you're, you know, he's here and he's doing this, and you're there with him, you can tell what's going on.
You know, the time, what time of day, you know, the culture, you know, you see.
But when you're reading stuff that is deep in metaphor, but even though it is still actual, it requires, you know, even more thought.
And then that requires, like, get as much information as you can and continue, because guess what?
It's going to be filled in other places.
As you continue reading, you'll see things that are in other parts of scripture that are out of place where they are, but fit in with this.
And you can't make them fit by whittling it down or changing, you have to see if they directly fit, you know.
Makes the picture more complete.
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
Because remember, all of this is a secret.
How would you publish a secret and keep it a secret?
Plain sight.
I can hear a slight bit of intermittent breakage on my end, so let me know if I'm ever cutting out.
No, you're not.
You're doing well.
Yeah.
Also, one last point on the sort of the belonging of the snake in the garden, or the serpent in the garden, is the fact that when Eve gets blamed, or Adam gets blamed for doing what they did, I think he describes Eve as the character who was put there.
The woman that you put here in the garden, she tricked me to do that.
When Eve blames the serpent, she never says the serpent that you put here.
She just says the serpent tricked me.
Right.
So there's an inherent understanding that he had a place in that domain.
It's not somewhere that he was put into after they were made, or that he just intruded into unexpectedly.
He was already there, and then they got put there.
She already knew him.
Well, put it this way.
The idea that, let's say, let's mix things a little bit.
When you say this, in most people's minds, they still think of a reptilian-looking creature.
And if he was a reptilian-looking creature, it didn't scare her at all, did he?
Did she say she was frightened by him?
No.
So this is all normal.
So the easiest conclusion, because it was not mentioned, he's not only mentioned by his name, which is translated as the serpent, is normal.
So it's safe to also presume that he was completely anthropomorphic.
He got around.
Well, meaning he looked just like a regular, you know, Adam.
He looked just like...
Right, right.
Yeah.
Yeah, we have no idea what kind of creature it was.
Greek, are you familiar with the Nomoli figures from West Africa?
Somewhat.
It sounds vaguely familiar.
You know, Klaus Donner talks a lot about those kind of little statues that were found.
Yeah, and some of them are very frightening looking.
Yeah, like they look half human, half snake.
They're anthropomorphic, but they have reptilian skin and reptilian teeth.
Chimerian type, yeah.
Well, there's actually something like that on the base of the actual menorah itself.
Well, there are chimeras.
I think those are...
Chimeras, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know how helpful that is, but...
I mean, I point to it only to illustrate that there has been memorialized this idea of reptilian beings, or reptilian-human hybrids, a significant role.
There could be lower level entities on that end that manifested to people as real, as physical, because just like I give the thing, you know, metaphor of, or direct explanation of how you have cathedrals, both in Western and Eastern artwork, you have contemporary depictions of living creatures, including what we call dinosaurs today, right, in great detail.
And it's not because these people conjured these things up as myths or whatever, because they actually had seen them.
So I would suggest that whether these things existed as animals and procreated themselves, or whether they were low-level entities that manifested, it's real either way.
Right.
You see?
Just because an angel can come through a wall and sit down next to you and leave, and have a meal with you, let's say, and then leave and just disappear, doesn't mean he's not real.
Right.
But let me just make a little bit of humor and sarcasm here.
To most people today, he wouldn't be considered real because he doesn't have a social security number.
That's how degraded humanity is, you see?
So, moving on, what I also think is interesting is that the serpent, or what they want to make synonymous with the snake, is seen in the Moses account of the staff with the copper serpent.
It's seen that—and I'm just making some assumptions here, but it seems like this ostensibly—that Moses is shown holding a staff with a snake that Yahweh controls.
Right.
And it seems to be illustrated in that account that the serpent represents some kind of an evil, and that Moses is holding the staff and Yahweh is exerting some kind of a dominance over it.
So, if you run with that, then the garden, if that is more literally meaning the foot of the serpent, doesn't that make the garden an evil place?
That's a long deduction.
But not completely groundless.
Both evil and good come from him.
If evil and good come from you, can you turn something all into good, or all into evil, or a mixture of both?
Sure.
That's the thing that people don't understand.
They think that only, let's say, they say G-O-D, only good comes from him, and only evil comes from Satan.
I even almost got into a public argument with a guy who was a pastor in his 70s about that, and he didn't want to look at anything in scripture that says both good and evil come from the Creator.
So, that's fine.
Also, sort of touching on what I said before, if you read Genesis 2.15 and it says that Yahweh the Elohim took the human and settled him in the garden to serve and keep it, specifically using those words, that seems to designate a servant status and not this sort of exalted king-priest thing that the Christian dogma runs with.
I mean, notwithstanding that he was a son of G-D, I'm not saying that he wasn't that, but we know that he didn't have an intimate relationship with the Creator, because they're never shown interacting, really.
No, they're not.
And he wasn't given free reign to live at his own leisure, because he had a job.
You're supposed to take care of the garden, so you can't just go and do whatever.
Now, hold on for a second, because I thought man in the sixth day was told, was made woman, male and female, or man of remembrance, or memorial, and female as an animal almost, the term used, amikavah, and they were told directly there to be fruitful and multiply and fill the earth.
But later on, we have another man that's just made as a man, and he says, don't worry, you're going to just stay here and work on the garden.
What happened to the ones that were supposed to multiply?
Where after the seventh day does it tell Adam, go out and multiply through the whole earth and be fruitful and multiply?
Where?
Where does he ever say that to Adam?
Well, I thought he just said you cursed will be that you will get your food, your bread with sweat and thorns and all that.
Oh, and by the way, go out and multiply the whole earth.
Did you get what I'm, you feeling me?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Who was Cain afraid of?
Anyway.
Yeah, yeah.
And what were these people doing when did they know that Adam was in the garden?
Presumably.
Yeah, and did Adam know about them?
Yeah, because Cain knew about them.
Yeah.
So and then we have this reptilian type theme in the garden.
Don't we?
But it doesn't mean that it's everywhere else in that realm, is it?
Just in the garden.
It's very interesting.
And why are the two trees in the garden?
Why?
Can't you have trees in the wilderness?
Yeah.
In the forest.
Why do you have to plant trees in a garden and a deliberate sequestered?
You see, because doesn't man always start off in a garden and end up in a city?
Or how can that be when the garden is part of the city?
You don't have you can't have a garden unless you have a city.
So we have three aspects here.
We have the wilderness, the natural.
Elemental form, then you have a city that's made, you know, change, you clear an area and you develop it, and then you have you can revert back to the wilderness by making a controlled wilderness inside of it known as a garden, which is usually for a specific purpose and for a specific person, as opposed to the wilderness, which is for everybody or public domain.
Right.
It didn't say agricultural farm.
No, it's a garden.
No, right.
But it also it also proves that there was a test to see about our curiosity.
I mean, he gave him he gave Adam and Eve a explicit order.
Do not mess with this stuff.
You can have these two.
Leave that other one alone.
Or you could have anything except for that.
Well, children, you give a child a mansion with anything he wants in it.
You tell him, well, you can do whatever you want, but just don't go into this one room.
The minute you leave, what's the first thing they do?
Go right.
Speaking with that.
They did a test on that.
Yeah, I'll be right back.
Tell us about the test.
I'll be right back.
There was a test where they put what was a marshmallow on the table, told the child, you know, you can have two marshmallows in five minutes or if you can or take this one that you get now and the guy would leave the room.
They had cameras on.
They're watching the whole thing and the kids who are the children who ate the marshmallow right away.
They followed these children for like 40, 50 years and found out that the ones that ate the marshmallow right away did not do as well in the 50 years and the ones that waited were more successful and productive and better income.
It was a fascinating little study.
What was the name of the study?
I can get that to you, Sam.
I'm right off the top of my head.
I'm just I'm not remembering.
And as a matter of fact, I think they did a show on this.
And well, it's one of them.
Podcast was called Radio Labs, and it was one of their earlier ones.
I think I have the archive of that, and I can pull up the name of the person who did the study.
Fascinating work, though.
See if you can discern the invalid data.
You also just the word of caution.
Very often when they do these studies, they're fake.
But on the other hand, it's a good thing to contemplate instant gratification.
Those that are looking for instant gratification tend to be less disciplined.
And the fact that 50 years later, they're looking at the preponderance of evidence after.
Well, that's the part.
Yeah, it's me.
It might be not accurate because these people in this community have a they're like cats.
They can't focus on anything more than a week.
So if they come back and say 50 years later, that's suspect to me.
Right.
And of course, we're dealing with academics again, too.
So yeah, I mean, they couldn't care less what happened a month ago, really.
And I'm not saying this to be critical of them in a negative way.
I'm trying to be critical of them in a realistic way, because I know a lot of them and I know how to operate.
Now, the other thing that you but tying that into Adam and Eve, though, that that's yeah.
Well, let me just tie this in the way we have.
Roughly, he was rough.
They were roughly around.
Well, Adam was 100 years.
So 100 years is 100 years in anyone.
Even if you live a long lifespan, it's not, you know, it's not overnight.
Well, you know, it's not really instant gratification still.
So that needs to be.
That's a nice question.
How old was Adam and Eve on this?
100, roughly.
We don't know how old he was.
OK.
Oh, and I would say you might we might want to say there are metaphors given between the distance of ages between men and women throughout Scripture, not often, but often enough.
We might want to start looking if there's a pattern there.
Yeah.
Consider the pattern and say that it's safe not to presume presumption that there was an age difference.
Well, we know there was an age difference that he came first and the and you'll see that there are certain usually it's roughly around 10 years that you'll see.
So consider that because remember, he he he doesn't just because something is a secret.
In general, when you.
Discover the the material of the secret, it's no longer a secret, even though you don't understand it, you see.
So if I tell you something is a secret and you say, well, what's the secret Greek?
And I say, here it is and it's written.
Whether you can understand it or not is your problem.
It's no longer a C, even if it's written in code, right?
It doesn't matter.
It's no, it's it's it's still my habit.
Yeah, now you have to figure out.
So that's why in Scripture it's a secret.
But he says he doesn't write in secret.
So, but we don't see the codes.
We don't see the metaphors tied in.
We don't see the.
Well, that's not our when he and also he gives a solution for that.
All right, what's the solution for that?
But he does.
Well, he hides things.
So the sovereigns of the world, those, you know, we'll find them.
Yeah, he does hide things, yeah.
But but in essence, what he's given us, because it's not going to change, it's not secreted, meaning like secreted, I should say.
And it's more of a test of our abilities to deceive, you know.
Well, it's a it's a yeah, it's an ability, just like a skill.
You have to work on it.
And he says here a little there a little and you have to be a workman.
Workman doesn't mean, you know, yeah, it means you have to make it a full time job.
And discipline full time or part time job.
What's full time hours?
What's part time?
You know, six or seven.
Yeah.
So, I mean, I don't know.
Interesting.
So does it sound unreasonable that you have to dedicate a decade of your life nearly full time to get a grasp of this?
No, it's not unreasonable.
Do you know any?
I mean, I know someone who's done that.
So I remember you talking about when you talk to these guys and giving you little little pieces of information that they took them a lifetime to get.
Great.
And they still do Christmas and all this other stuff.
You know what you call that?
Getting edible corn.
Out of someone's poop.
Yeah.
Wow.
So just to wrap up on the serve serving bit.
I also think it's worth noting that when you're told to serve in a particular place.
Am I can you guys hear me?
I'm like, yes, you're fine.
Yeah, I'm walking outside and I'm going out of zone and it might start beeping.
So I just mute out just to preempt that.
So I'll be done here in about five or six minutes.
So go ahead.
Cool.
So, yeah, when you're told to when he's told to serve and keep in the garden, I have to ask myself, serve for whom?
Because I don't think he's serving a bunch of plants.
I mean, Yahweh doesn't live there.
So you still have to identify somebody who is the higher up in that in that area.
It's not Yahweh because he comes and goes and it's not Adam because he's a servant.
But there's a tremendous population also.
Well, no, in terms of the gods and angelic beings and all that, if you can see into that realm, here's the other thing.
How much were they able to see?
Because they heard Elohim in the garden, right?
It doesn't say that could have been the angel, right?
Physical form.
So that's right.
I've never I don't see.
Yeah, I don't see him interacting with the spirit world.
Right there.
Unless they want.
Yeah, he doesn't see the spiritual world unless they want.
He only sees what they want him to see.
Put it that way or allow him to see lawfully.
So when he entered the tree, then was his eyes open to this?
Well, just meditate.
I'm suggesting here.
I'm presuming that the tree of knowledge of good and evil is the scripture itself.
So he saw everything down, you know, when you know, when you read scripture, right?
You know, when you read, you know, from all the way from all the way through.
Just just in other words, just grab a Bible.
Doesn't matter what it is right now.
Just open it to any page.
Put your finger on it and whatever you're reading.
He saw that, too.
Think about that for a moment.
Uh, future.
Oh, so going the metaphor language again, just to bring that up one last time.
The car is cursed to crawl in the dust, metaphorically speaking.
So then how can he simultaneously also be the prince of the powers of the air?
Those two things feel opposed.
Yeah, they do.
And what makes you think that he has to do everything by himself?
No, that's fine.
But we're still talking about him.
We're not talking about his associates, right?
Yeah, but we don't know that for sure.
I mean, he has many associates, doesn't he?
And all those associates seem to be fixing on making it difficult for men, don't they?
In many different ways.
You can you can go and look at well, don't go and look at this.
I mean, specifically, but throughout history, when you look at all of the various cultures and what they discuss in terms of the gods, don't you find that most of the stories tend to be malevolent interaction?
Right.
You ever think about that?
Proportionately, you know, a high proportion of malevolent interaction in any culture.
Right.
And it seems to be true here in scripture as well.
Sure.
But what's interesting in scripture, like I said in the last sonic event, what you don't get anywhere else is in scripture, you're always going to get geography, history, meaning there's a timeline.
You're going to get people, you know, like a name or a nation, what they're doing, why they're doing it, and the outcome almost every time.
And it's the only ancient writ that has that.
You can't show me any other ancient writ that even comes close with that kind of consistency with that much information and every time.
Right.
We're given details in geography, history, people, names, intent, processes, and outcomes.
Consistently, over and over and over and over.
And I'm telling you, just like when you start to look at what those names mean etymologically, you fit them into the text for context.
Not only do you do it with the names, you do it with the geography.
It tells you this place is named this because of this.
Remember?
The name of the book?
Yeah, what does Sinai mean?
No.
Right.
What does Sinai mean?
It means fire.
Mount Sinai, right?
What was up there?
You know, what scared everybody?
So you have to fit these things in there also.
And then you start to see there's a repeat.
And there are archetypes.
I keep, ever since I've been speaking publicly, I'm like, the mindset that's required to look at this is very different than the mindset that we carry through our lives.
Through our lives, for example, we think the king is at the top and the street sweeper is at the bottom.
But on that end, it's lateral.
You have innermost circle and then the inner circle, right?
And then you have the outer circle, then the outermost circle.
It's lateral, you see?
Yes, on a certain plane.
There's also a top-down hierarchy because he's the most high god.
You can't be the most high unless people are under it.
Right, but the way the functions are usually lateral.
The way things work and are made and go back and forth and in and out.
But yes, the authority is always up.
But he seems more separated, though, out of them all.
Well, here's the other interesting thing.
Okay.
And I don't like getting into this too much publicly, but I've said it.
I used to shy away, if you ask me.
I wouldn't forget about even volunteering at it, which I will right now.
But people used to ask me, I used to shy away from it.
But I'll volunteer it.
Do you know how we here are discussing the gods?
Okay, because they're the gods compared to us.
When you go into their realm, the god's realm, they have a god also.
People used to ask me, I said, never mind.
And that god is the most high.
Now, that's going to be a shock for most people.
Think about that.
It's not too hard to comprehend.
No, but it's not spoken of.
That's why it's so easy to knock the world religions.
When they just say god, I'm like, that's nothing.
About the god of gods.
Do the gods have a god?
People just ask me, do the gods have a god?
I'm not going to talk about that.
Because now we're starting to get more into the inner circle of things.
It's beyond that.
So put it this way.
Let's just ponder this for a moment from a presumptive point of view.
The Garden of Eden and all of that was the gods.
And if you're around there, you say, do you guys have a god?
Yes, we do have a god.
You get it?
Right.
Doesn't that help put things in more perspective?
What's going on with the Garden of Eden?
Well, yeah, I mean, obviously, the gods have God, but no, no, but hold on.
Let me let's just keep this in a material in a way that we can ponder it.
Let's say you go into a large ship or a vessel, whether it's an airborne vessel or a ship or whatever, you know, a and you have a group that has put that together and is operating it and dwelling in it, whatever, whatever features, however big or how small, in this case, very vast in size.
And you see these beings and they have homage or honor to a god.
On that vessel, right, which actually I'm using this as a direct metaphor, because typically you do see this in a lot of the pagan cultures anyway, don't you?
Right.
Mm hmm.
Does that help put things in perspective?
Oh, yeah, that's clear to me.
You know, it shouldn't be too hard for anybody to grasp, really.
I guess more specifically, you'd have to understand what that implies.
Well, that's why many, I think there's a level of, you know what this is like, but I know this is doesn't the people that are probably going to be listening to this is a very, very small group.
Let me give you a metaphor of what's going on and what's been going on with Greek speak for a long time.
Let's say it's 1995 and you say, well, look, there's going to be something going on.
It's going to be a world event.
And you're going to be told that it's a bunch of Arabs with box cutters hijacking planes and flying them into the World Trade Center.
And the World Trade Centers are going to collapse to that.
You know, everyone's going to laugh at you.
They're going to say, Greek, that's not going to happen, because there's too much security in the airports.
And those buildings were designed to take hits, albeit it was a slightly smaller jetliner to never come down and all this.
You know, right now it's like, oh, yeah, Greek, yeah, shut up.
That's not going to happen, right?
You see my point?
It wasn't time yet to discuss.
And then the next level of that, nothing happened that way either.
It didn't happen that way.
There were no planes.
Only people on TV saw planes, right?
In other words, like there's no crucifixion, right?
The buildings were imploded using underground nuclear demolitions, underground, not atmospheric, way deep underground, transferring a wave to the surface and all that.
And those things were in place.
Otherwise, they would have never given them a permission to build them in the first place, if you understand the rules behind tubular steel construction.
So actually, those things did happen.
But again, not the way you're being told, you see?
And that sounds even more rational than the other thing.
But it's harder to grasp your mind around, because how could they get away with it?
Do you see the metaphor here with 9-11 and scripture?
There's a very direct metaphor between that.
It's a worldwide event, you see?
Everyone knows about it.
No one sees what, no one understands what's going on.
And the best thing is to accept whatever bullshit they get put out into the world, right?
Just like someone I was listening to has a daughter, and he was doing some 9-11 research.
And a young daughter, he says, what are you doing?
He's like, oh, Daddy, I'm doing 9-11 research.
Tell me about it.
And he told her the official story, and the daughter said, I'm a child, but I'm not stupid.
I mean, that's totally stupid, the official story.
If you look at what religions tell you about the Bible, or even biblical scholars, listen, I don't know about the Bible, but I'm not stupid.
You see, it's the same thing.
You see, so now we're at a quandary, because we've got things we want to do in our lives.
We don't want to spend eight hours a day, or five hours a day, or even three hours a day every day studying this thing, and learning what it takes to learn to study it, right?
And then what happens is when you start doing this, you're going to start leaving other people so far behind that you won't be able to communicate with them.
What does that mean?
Well, it's not time yet.
So now you have to find a middle ground, constantly be speaking with people, because as you start broaching on this subject in the beginning, yeah, it's important.
Yeah, everyone agrees on it.
Everyone starts agreeing on the bits of information.
But as you go and get more and more and more into it, now there's a big drift that happens.
And I've talked about this a lot.
That's why when you look at a lot of people who have done good work in Scripture, they still go back to the religious side, because if they don't, they're going to lose everyone.
And no one will listen to them.
So they have to use terms that people are used to.
And I'm telling you, those terms don't apply, because what is defined, those other terms that people use are false.
You see?
Again, so that's why it goes back to, you better have a very good imagination.
And I don't mean, usually when you tell someone you have a good imagination, that means it's fiction.
That's not true at all.
Right.
Imagination is a function of the mind, where you can walk and chew gum, right?
Yeah.
So, you know, you could be in a room or in a crowded street, walking through, being on a phone, speaking, and someone says to you, do you remember that thing that I sent you?
You're like, yes, I do.
Well, how, you know, you see that thing, once it's mentioned verbally over the phone, while you're navigating, you know, what you see in front of you.
It's all in the imagination.
Even when your eye is processing what you see, that's happening in the imagination.
And the people that do trickery and deception know that, and they know how to distract you from that.
It's all in the imagination.
But the word I'm using doesn't make, when you say imagination with people, it has to be fiction.
No, not true.
Like I was mentioning earlier to Bruce, about, you know, conveying information.
I said, well, you have to know it.
And because if you don't have the confidence of knowing it, people, you know, will shy away.
But if they see you're confident, they're maybe a little bit more open, but you can't be confident until you know it.
You know the word con man, you know where con, the con and con man means confidence man.
But that term has been taken to be a negative thing, right?
Totally twisted.
Completely, yeah.
Now, isn't a good football coach a con man?
Doesn't he want to build confidence in the team?
In the team.
So they can perform, so they could always, you know, the spiritual side performs, you know, better now.
So the only way you can be confident is by knowing it.
You know, years ago, people say, Greek, you know, I don't know much about what you're saying, but you speak with such authority on it.
And I'm like, well, because I have a level of stress and a level of urgency that I try to bat down, tamper down when I speak, because these things are very important.
But the reality of this subject matter is so different than what people think, that you can't always seem too urgent, because then they're going to pick up on that, and they're going to want to feel the urgency instead of what you're saying.
And they don't like that because it disturbs their calm.
So you need to learn to convert that sense of urgency into a sense of authority and confidence when you speak, you know.
Right.
But you also have to...
Very well put.
But if you don't know the material, knowing it...
Well, not only the material, the history, all the intricacies that go along with it, which helps make a better picture.
And fortunately and unfortunately,
a lot of these things to just to lock the censorship,
the cosmic censorship and whatever else is going on
in that influences, when I say whatever else,
meaning that all the things that it takes to censor
an entire society,
it comes to a point cognitively
where you can no longer use words
to describe these things anymore,
and you can only circumvently describe,
you can't describe them directly.
And actually there's verses in scripture about that, right?
Some of the prophets and apostles, they said they saw things they could not use words to describe.
I mean, we'll give you another secular example.
When I discussed the ether, you know, how heat, light and electricity are all the same.
They're interchangeable, right?
They all come from the ether.
It's a physical manifestation of a certain quality of ether.
You know, an academic goes, no, they're not the same.
I said, well, yeah, they are interchangeable, just like mathematics.
You can take heat, make it electricity.
You can take electricity and make it a heat.
You can take electricity, make it to light.
You can take light, make it back to electricity, right, solar panels, right?
You could take heat, make it light.
You can make light and heat.
They're all interchangeable either way, like math, you know, like two plus two equals four, four minus two equals three.
You see, it's all, it works perfectly.
And it's so simple.
And once you grasp that, then all of a sudden everything opens up, but it's going on already.
Like for example, you can take light and turn it into electricity with a solar panel.
You can take electricity and turn it into heat.
It's a toaster oven.
You can take heat and turn it into electricity.
It's a thermocouple.
You can take electricity and turn it into light.
It's a light bulb.
You can take, right?
They're all interchangeable either way.
You see?
So once you start looking at how these things that are not being considered interchangeable and how it just hits you across the head like a baseball bat, of course.
Now, of course, all these things are, the only reason they're interchangeable is because they come from the same place, archetypes, the same thing, different manifestations of the same thing.
When you start looking at scripture that way, you're like, oh yeah, this is, you can explain it in just a few, well, just a few words.
But it does, obviously, it doesn't give you the richness of it.
It's very simple.
You know, how can a benevolent, the most benevolent being in the universe put you through such crap and don't take it personally?
Well, how can you not?
You see, that's where, that's part of the character building, you see.
Teaching us discipline.
You're supposed to take it personally.
How else are you going to develop your personality and your character?
Right.
Think about it.
But you can't tell people you're supposed to take it because they don't know how to act.
They lack the maturity, right?
Duly noted.
Definitely.
To get back to the Satan stuff, so all the references are talking about an attorney function carried out by some unnamed agent.
Some of them sometimes also seem to be working for Yahweh or within his, some kind of a dynamic that he's a part of, like in the Job account.
So from what I'm seeing, there is no chief adversary per se in the Old Testament, if you look away from the Genesis Nakash account.
And certainly he's not directly or overtly given that role.
In Genesis, in fact, if you look at the curse language, he's actually demoted.
I'm going to read out of that exchange.
Because if you're going to crawl in the dust and eat dirt, I mean, you're not better off than you were before.
So if you look at the rest of the Old Testament, you don't see the Nakash appear or reappear.
Secondly, the sons of Elohim are put in charge of the nations after Babel.
They remain in place until at least Daniel's time, when you see the princes of Grisha and Persia.
So there's no chief adversary being talked about in the Old Testament, really.
And we don't see any such thing until the temptation of the Messiah in the wilderness in the New Testament.
But there's a line in Paul's letters that talks about the God of this world, which I think is interesting.
And people quote it like that, even though the original line doesn't say that.
It doesn't say the God of this world.
It says the God of this age.
And indeed, if our use has been veiled, it has been veiled in those who are perishing and whom the God of this age has blinded their minds.
So that seems to be a specific thing.
So what's an age?
Well, I mentioned that before.
It seems to generally be a 2000 year period or as you said, Greek, a certain age.
Type of society.
Society, right.
A type of society, yeah.
Sometimes it's consecutive and sometimes it's not.
Like you can have a stone based society, a bronze based society and an iron society, all coexisting side by side.
And depending on your own bias, you might go to the stone society later on and say, oh, these guys came first and the bronze society came second because that's more evolved and the iron came later because that's more evolved.
But in reality, they all existed at the same time.
Mm-hmm.
So you have to delineate that aspect of it.
Right.
Because, you know, I keep hammering that for, to go back to scripture, there's no such thing as a stone age or a bronze age or an iron age.
There were societies, even in scripture talks about that, how the Philistines had iron chariots.
What, the Israelites couldn't?
Of course they could.
They just decided that was not a material they worked on for whatever reason, you know?
Mm-hmm.
So look at the construction methods in Japan, wood and bamboo and paper and silk.
I'm talking about construction materials now, not arts and crafts, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So in a sense, there's a metaphor here.
I mean, not a metaphor.
Is it a consecutive thing that happens through the ages, the 2000 years that's witnessed by the astronomical?
Signs, or you dare might say astrology, which means knowledge of the stars, which is correct.
That's another thing that's been corrupted.
Astrology is completely lawful, but not if you're using it for divination, you know what I mean?
Not if you're going to substitute the right and wrong with it.
But I would suggest that there is a linear function to when things take prominence, but it doesn't mean because they're not prominent, they're gone.
Right?
Like one of the things about like the statue of Nebuchadnezzar, you know, what the various kingdoms.
Remember, they're all existing even till the end, because only in the end is the whole thing destroyed, right?
So some people say, well, it was Babylon, and then it was Persia and then Greece and then a split, you know, and the iron mixed with domeric clay, which everyone still thinks, the majority of people think is European Union, which it's not.
And people say we're in the Greek age.
Now, even I say that, you know, we're in the Greek world, predominantly the Greek, because you could look at it and see what's going on, right?
All your math and science and all that still uses Greek, you know, government and all that, but it still has all the rest in it.
And is the Babylonian age still here?
Yes.
Is it in its prominence that it was there?
Because Alexander, you see, came after, you know, you see the linear aspect to it, then you see the prominence aspect to it.
So there's two things going on at the same time.
You see, why would a council, you ever notice in scripture, how you're given names of people that are considered to be neutral or good, but the ones that didn't do well, you don't get any names or anything.
You notice, I mean, you do get, that doesn't hold true in the book of Kings, because they do mention the bad kings.
But in usually in other places, if you're not righteous, the scripture doesn't mention you as part of the history.
This is a Middle Eastern cultural thing anyway, you know, and actually Western also, if you really investigate.
But when you go into, so I just jumped derailed tracks here on the thought here.
Let's see if I could get back on.
Okay, when you go into the scripture again, and you look at the various linear aspects, and it doesn't seem like any of these, like the Nakash or the Satan entourage has been done away with, just not mentioned in detail.
You see, they could have a council of their own, a minor council, right?
They could have a tribunal type situation, but they're not mentioned, because they're not considered, because just like other people are not mentioned in Genesis, right?
Because they're not considered to have done good things.
This is a trait that we see repeated over and over and over.
The only exception I see where you had malevolent acts and things like that, people that is within the lineage of the kings of Israel and judges.
You see?
I mean, the evil personas and characters are definitely mentioned to illustrate a point.
I mean, it's not to the extent that they're completely ignored, so that it obfuscates what's going on in the communication, because if that was the case in the Jonah book would never be there, because it's pretty heavy on the Assyrians, as far as what they're doing and needing to be judged for it.
So you can think of the, but hold on, think of the sons of gods also.
Are they doing what they're supposed to be doing, or are they adversarial in most cases?
Look at most of the gods.
When the people got involved with them actively in culture, weren't they sacrificing children and doing all these other things?
So wouldn't you say, what council would they be part of?
But anyway, you're saying about Assyria, I would say, I would suggest that Assyria had a covenant that, a mild covenant, or a covenant indeed, because you wouldn't send a prophet to them to tell them to repent.
If the Assyrians didn't have a covenant with Yahweh, why would he send them a prophet to repent?
Repent from what?
No, that's all very well, but they're still evil.
That doesn't change.
They never really, they never inhabit any other function other than to be troublemakers.
And similarly, if you've created the Nakash, don't you have a covenant with the Nakash?
Indirectly, just by having created him and given him authority.
So their covenant's with everybody, not withstanding.
I think a covenant is slightly different than just creating someone.
But he has authority.
You can't give somebody authority without there being a contract.
There's a contract with the Nakash.
Either a contract or he's taking orders in real time.
And in his real time, meaning, and then he gets distance away enough that he's just following, you know, whatever modality.
Because you can see there's a modality of interaction in the book of Job, which is after the flood, which is pretty late in history, by the way.
I mean, not late in history, but it's way down the line, right?
You can put Job in Genesis, by the way, in the time.
In other words, if you put Job in the book of Genesis, it wouldn't be out of, wouldn't be that much further out.
You see what I mean?
You'll probably be in, tucked in there before Israel, you know, and Joseph, the story of Joseph and all that, probably be somewhere around there, if not earlier or, you know, than there.
So I wouldn't say that, I don't know how late that is, but it's late compared to, you know, the garden.
I think it's Abraham-ish.
Yeah, Abraham-ish, patriarch.
Or the Chaldeans, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So, and even then there's interaction, direct interaction, and interrelation with the adversary, isn't there?
No, but come on, that's not the adversary.
That's just the, that's just one adversary.
That's not Satan, Satan.
Yeah, it is one.
Yeah, well, the thing is, come on, I mean, who is, again, these, we were not given detail, right?
Right, but that's not the chief adversary.
And how many of them?
Well, now it's like discussing the Magi, were there three, were there, no, we just know there's more than one.
Mm-hmm.
Right, we know there's more than one, that's shown, because one is shown by name and others are not.
If it was the same one coming around later, why wouldn't they just use his name?
Right, so there are different adversaries.
And usually they have to fulfill some kind of accusatory function or attorney function.
Well, yeah, like attorney or sergeant or colonel, you know?
Mm-hmm.
How many are there?
You have the Dixter's fraternity, who's the boss, and then you have a bunch of other attorneys that do what he tells them.
Yeah, the assistant TA, yeah.
Anyhoo, to get back to the age thing, so you can either go with the age as delineated by the Zodiac, or you can go with the more general societal happenings to nail down what the age is.
But if you do go with the 2000-year general period, I don't know exactly what Paul would be referring to, but presumably, if you're going to go with that, then he's actually saying that there is an Elohim that has come into power for this particular time period specifically, which would explain why he's not really mentioned a lot before.
Because let's not act as if evil gods are not mentioned.
Moloch is mentioned.
The different balls are mentioned by name.
So if you're not going to bring up the name of the chief adversary during this period, I have to wonder how active he's being directly.
During the first 4,000 years, I don't see the chief adversary being mentioned during Noah's flood.
I mean, they're supposed to be going crazy and doing all these things, but it's never really attributed to any one Elohim.
And once again, I don't see him in the Job account.
I see some other adversary whose name isn't even important.
So I thought the chief adversary was against the whole of mankind.
Well, can you objectify what's there?
If you objectify it, he's given as Hasatan or is he given as the adversary in the Book of Job?
He's just given as Satan or as you say, Nakash.
I believe it does use the term Nakash, doesn't it, in Job?
Fuck no.
Sorry.
No, there's the word Nakash appears.
That's when Job is complaining later on.
It's definitely Hasatan.
That is unequivocal.
The adversary, yeah.
Absolutely.
Yeah, right.
But Nakash is mentioned in Scripture.
I mean, not Scripture, in Job.
Yeah, somewhere.
Yeah, that's like Job chapter 30 something.
That's fine.
But in other words, it's evoked.
The title, it's not just the title, but the name is actually brought forward.
But here's the other thing that I want to...
Can you imagine, you know, the idea of primary, secondary, tertiary.
As you go from first to second to third, things tend to diminish.
When you look at us being secondary, and I'm suggesting this is a strong presumption.
If you look at the variety in the number, just the sheer population of anything, even if something that is rare still is in high population to it, unless it's going what they call extinct.
And we're secondary.
Can you imagine in the primary world how populated they are?
You know, an army of 100 million is no big deal on their side.
Where an army on this side, 100 million is, you know, very difficult to comprehend, to organize that.
So why is it difficult to, especially when, again, like I said earlier, a third of the host, you know, of the beings up there decided to, I don't know if rebel is the right term, but to become adversarial.
Right?
And fight, right?
A third of them, of what number?
Trillions.
Forget about billions.
Why would there just be one adversarial being?
No, we're not saying that.
I'm just referring to the chief one.
Why would I care about the lesser adversary?
I don't know how much of a chief he is.
I think taking...
You say chief.
Yeah, chief.
Well, chief, like the boss of them during this age.
Yes, I say that also.
Yes.
And he's sitting in the throne of the earth, believe it or not right now.
You know, the earth does have a throne type authority.
But to bring it down to the point where there seems to be a level of interchangeability, you know, from the angelic aspect, you know, when an angel or another being does is very plausible.
And it seems to be because, you know, usually scripture is very specific with names.
If you don't see the name there, it leaves one guessing and wondering, is it the specific being or someone in agency?
And I would suggest what you're saying.
There's a lot of agency on this.
Absolutely.
And I think that we harp on the chief adversary to the point where we're making it hard on ourselves to discern who he is, even though that can't be read out of the text directly anyway.
But there's so much nonsense that swirls around the subject of it.
I mean, in the Old Testament, we don't see any wholesale tactics of deception targeting the whole earth.
I thought this guy had a problem with the entirety of the human race, but I'm not seeing that there.
Each nation and empire has its jurisdiction and does its own thing.
And actually, Yahweh is actively involved in these other nations, as you've mentioned with Jonah and the Assyrians, and also Egypt and Babylon.
So, you know, Yahweh never said that the nation of Israel should stop following Satan.
No, stop being...
We're not given a lot...
Bruce, is Sam breaking up or just for me?
No, that's Sam breaking up.
Am I breaking up?
Oh, sorry.
What, did I just start or before also?
Just maybe about the last few sentences, yeah.
Okay.
But no, let's just go back.
We were not given specifics on why to repent from what specifically.
I mean, if you look at it close, it might pop up somewhere.
Like, you know, why was Sodom and Gomorrah destroyed, right?
That's an interesting concept.
It's not what you think.
The reason is given for that in other places, you know, and it's compounded, obviously, by their actions.
So there's many aspects to it.
So when you say there's a covenant there or something, on the last sonic event that I gave, I discussed that one thing that you'll find before a place is destroyed, not always, but often, is that you'll have the neighboring nations complaining through prayer about them also.
Right?
Yeah, I mean, that's very clearly shown.
Well, not that specifically, but it's very clearly stated with regards to Sodom and Gomorrah that there was a cry coming up to heaven about them, like somebody was complaining about them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Can you imagine?
And well, like, they were any better?
I mean, how much better would they have been?
Not much better.
And I kind of made that as a metaphor to the American listeners, you know, because the Americans have been at the basis of the criminality and corruption in the world for the past century, you know, 100 years by number, as they said, well, is destruction going to come on America?
I said, yeah, well, when it comes on the rest of the world, unless there's something I don't see, and if all the other nations are praying for it, then even though they're just as pagan, that might also be a surefire way to watch for that.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, that'll stir things up.
Oh, yeah, on that.
So I said, I don't think America is going to be just strictly a conversation with someone about that.
When she'll be destroyed when everyone else is, but unless there's something I'm missing, and you start hearing a lot about Canada, and Guatemala, and Russia, and France, everyone praying for it, then I would say, you might want to move, or unless you're so confident that some angels will come in the middle of the night and tell you, let's go.
You see, but that's not going to, you know, I'm just using that again as a...
Yeah.
Are we reading what's there?
Are we seeing the patterns here?
You know, but it's not going to happen.
I'm just doing that to shake up, to jostle people into, like, realizing how real these things are, you know?
Well, guys, we chewed up three hours already.
That's what happens with Sam.
Three hours is nothing.
This is why I resent doing the call.
I know.
Oh, Sam's throwing a little hissy fit.
Oh, hold on a second.
No, no, no, no, I was just...
We could stop, or we could keep it going.
We're all...
Well, it's up to Bruce, really.
He's the one that's...
He's got the rubber on the road.
So far, I'm good.
I'd be up by nine tomorrow.
I'll be doing okay for a while yet.
Okay, so let me just recap on stuff that I've been looking at for years.
And I think this is an essence of what Sam is trying to bring forward.
One of the things I've been saying, and these are general terms, because remember, to start rationalizing...
Basically, the rationale that's in Scripture does not interlock or dovetail very well with the rationale that the typical walking man or woman has these days, right?
So that's why I try to keep things in general terms.
And one of the general terms that I've always been saying in recent history, and more than recent history, is that this is a secondary world.
It's not primary.
It's an expression of the other side.
I mean, the world of the gods, right?
And whenever you have that secondary aspect, again, it is safe to presume that the population of everything, species, animals, beings, colors, shapes, whatever, is greater on that side.
And this is beyond Platonism.
Plato always says, well, when you look at the color white, well, what's white?
You got a white polar bear, white snow, white t-shirt.
Which one is white?
They're all different.
There's gotta be a representation.
Somewhere else of a pure white.
Well, yes, that too, let's say, if you want to encompass that thinking, which is very secular, reaching out into that.
But I'm telling you that because this is secondary, it is very safe to presume a vast plethora of variety that we can't even imagine.
Even though I said, keep the imagination vivid, you see?
So also, I think Sam and I have had discussions off the thing about how can you have, for example, verses where people know if you see the creator, you die.
Right?
Very often that comes up all the way through the text.
And then in other places, allegedly, he shows up to certain people.
It can't be, which one is it?
As it sounds contradictory, doesn't it?
No, it's not.
No, it's not contradictory when you understand that he has angel, he has an angel that might be more than one, but he's referred to as the angel that is his direct representative, just like you have a body double.
You ever see, like years ago, they had the Saddam Hussein body doubles, right?
You know, like six of them, you know?
I think they still do for most of the leaders.
Yeah, well, it would be smart.
They have unlimited budgets, so they can do it.
So now when you comprehend that and you pick up that in scripture where he says, I sent my angel, my angel, the angel, right?
You start to see there is no contradiction there because people know if you see him, you disintegrate.
But in other places he's sitting, you know, having lunch with them.
Which one is it?
No, it's someone directly coming.
Now, do you see?
So these are things that I try to bring up on the vast variety and population of what's going on there.
And that's the problem that we have when we try to bring looking at scripture.
That's why Sam likes to bring these things up because we hash these things out.
It's very good.
But people try to bring what they were taught in church or in school or by the government or by a university, and all of it is false, you know?
If you go look at what's been told about the other side, first of all, you're crazy.
It's a matter of faith.
It doesn't matter.
It's religious, right?
It's religious, has nothing to do with this, right?
Or there's this very lonely God and he has a son, a rebellious son His son is so rebellious that he actually comes to earth and tells everyone to undo all the laws of his father, right?
Think about that for a minute.
Ridiculous.
You know, this is like the 9-11 thing now.
You know, you have, you can't go out there and discuss what happened.
You just can't.
The rationale is just because and also you got to throw in the cosmic censorship, right?
And the dummy load and the adversary, right?
And the sons of God, whoever's left of them, right?
And the balls, the whoever's left of them.
I mean, it's a lifetime's worth of study.
Look, you can take, you can spend a lifetime on just one book of scripture if you want to really study because it's not just reading that finite number of words because it branches out, it hyperlinks into the rest of the text and that hyperlinks into your history, into your geography, into your nationalities, right?
So this is a really big, big subject.
But here, the other thing that I always discuss is the censorship and it's not time yet.
That's not being defeated.
I mean, I think that when you try to force things out of time, that's why I always, you know, it doesn't work.
You end up falling on, you know, error.
If you try it too hard, you'll be rewarded with error if you recognize it's not time yet.
That's why I always stress read out of it.
Don't read into it.
You know, read out of it.
Don't read.
There's nothing that you've been told that you can take and bring in there, you know, from the rationale that's in the society.
You have to just strictly read out of it unless you have a good, you know, you could bring what you could incorporate in scripture and dovetail is good history, good geography, right?
Good accounts.
Yeah, that stuff.
But not what you're being shown at large.
Right.
I mean, I'll tell you from a personal note, which I don't, I try to be, someone said Greek, you sound like a robot.
I hope I don't.
But my personal note, I'm looking forward as time goes on that more, you know, what's the very, let's say, let's say something like the book of Daniel, which is a finite number of words, right?
Because it has the first chapter and the last chapter, first word and last word in that book.
To read that and get 100 times or 10 times or 50 times more out of it than you do today, even if you read it every day.
Because when the time chain, when the time is right, it will be revealed to you, not through some divine personal revelation, like some people try to say.
It's just because the entire scope of the cosmic censorship will change and you will finally see what's really there.
And I'm just going to, yeah, go ahead.
No, go ahead.
Go ahead.
No, I'm just going to say, and still the truth is, is a, is not a, is been soiled very much.
You can't use that term too much still.
And that's another thing that's going to be changing in the future.
You know, you can't, like I've said before, you can't have two people with different stories, both tell you that they're both the truth.
Can't be.
They're either both wrong or only one is correct.
The word truth is actually been very discolored.
Well, very much so again, since, since 9-11 again, this axial period, this is a post-9-11 world.
And it's a very interesting thing.
I use scripture and the 9-11 event is very, very similar.
Everyone see, like, just like scripture, you can very easy to get.
Everyone could see, go anywhere.
Everyone seems to have heard about it.
You know, majority of people on the planet.
There's imagery and all that, but how, what really happened, even though it's right in front of you, is false.
And it's a fight when you start discussing it, just like scripture.
Everything that's put out about it is false.
I say everything, but yes, if you were to say wholesale, throw it away and start over.
Yes, that's a good.
That's a really good premise.
Yes, you have to start all over right now.
Still again, and the people that have done good work regarding the scripture, you're definitely looking for edible corn out of poop for sure.
Still today, because they knew they could have gone even a more pure route, but you would have never heard of them if they did, because they couldn't afford to publish a book.
No, well, there was greed involved too.
No, but the thing is, you wouldn't, but it's all meant to be this way, because in vanity, I should have said vanity.
Yeah, yeah, well, no, so this is still a pretty rotten situation we're in humanity.
Right, but it's going to get better.
And when it gets better again, it's only because it's, so you get the law, the kill shots lawfully.
So how much better is it?
Right.
You know, I mean, you had to bring that up.
The ghetto and ghetto, you'd say man up, man.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, there's nothing good here.
Just man up, right?
So and woman up.
When I say man, it means humankind, humankind and woman.
So these are the simple things.
On a personal note, one should also be careful not to be too disregarding or disparaging of these characters who we don't need to mention their names, because we know who's being spoken of.
But, you know, they've done quite a few good things.
And if we're going to use the searching for corn in people's poop, I would say that, you know, from what I've been able to look into, you could probably afford to ditch the hazmat suit and just keep the gloves, because most of that poop is dried up at this point.
And there's quite a few good things to be found in there if you're willing to look.
Yeah, and also, by the way, if you're willing to look, you can go back hundreds of years.
You know, actually, I would say even recently, I can't bring it up.
I was looking at some things that I was compiling, let's say four or five years ago, and there was some good work done in the late 19th century as well.
Albeit it wasn't prominent, because imagine back then you didn't have the internet and printing was still expensive.
And, you know, the level of education was higher, but the conformity into normal religion was still very high.
Anything that went against, you know, against the church was not considered, you know, right?
So, no, it's been around.
Let me give you an example.
If you study American history, there's a website called Rare Articles in Newspapers.
And they don't have an archive section, but if you look at it, you get some interesting stuff.
And for a while, a couple of years ago, they had a lot of anti-Catholic publications in the 17 and 1800s.
There were magazines in the US circulating.
They were anti-Catholic.
And the reasons that they gave for being anti-Catholic very sound, biblically sound, and all that, right?
Which is not hard to do.
I mean, it's pretty, you know, it's pretty, actually, it's very unsound to be that Catholic.
So, but anyway.
So, yeah.
And when you read some of these articles that were written in the late 1700s and early 1800s, these were anti-Catholic magazines.
You were like, whoa, I didn't know this.
You know, this person did some pretty good research, you know, in scripture, you know?
So it's been going on.
It just has not reached prominence even today.
Look, some of the people that we're mentioning indirectly, you know, also had done work on others that came before them.
But ultimately, these contemporary ones that had done work, and you could even bring up the WCG with Armstrong, Herbert Armstrong, right?
He was in the hundreds of, you know, millions he would raise from people and all that.
And he would basically tell them, you got to keep the Sabbath.
He thought it was Saturday, really.
And he actually would fire people because they, certain days, they argued whether it should be a Monday or a Sunday.
They were so censored, they couldn't see.
There is none of that in scripture at all.
They couldn't do lawful timekeeping, but their job was to hammer forward that the law is not done away with, and you have to keep the seventh day off, and you, right?
And all these laws are still in place.
They didn't know about the Pope's work schedule and other things like that, even though it was very easy to see.
It wasn't time yet.
Kind of like a repeat of history again, isn't it?
You know, you had King James, and then you got this guy, vast resources, and hammering away on protocols.
Well, he got millions of people realizing the Saturday was the Sabbath, which is not true at all.
Right.
I mean, well, it can be because actually this past month, it was between noon and noon.
But I would suggest that there's a timing aspect involved, but I find it, when I say looking for edible corn and poop, you have to understand, let me just clarify that.
That's a 50-50 statement.
50% of that is objective.
The other 50% of that is personal.
All right.
Like, for example, it depends on how distasteful you find Christianity to be.
Right.
If you don't mind it at all, then it's one thing, but I find it extremely distasteful, very distasteful.
And it's just bad, you know, not good at all.
And so when I say, I might look at something and say, it's not that bad, but as soon as I see Christianity throwing it, oh, it's poop, it's corn out of poop, right?
Right.
You see, but someone else may not see it that way because they don't think Christianity is bad.
You see, it's not that bad.
You know, when you mentioned that about that fellow, that reminded me of when I was young.
Oh God, I had been maybe seven or eight.
And I remember different magazines coming around through our house.
And I was forced into Lutheran doctrine and all that kind of crap.
But I remember the magazines coming around and discounting other religions.
And when you said that, it struck a memory.
And I remember that I didn't really glance it over or anything, but I remember titles that were professing the Lutheran religion versus this other kind.
And so, yeah, that was an interesting thing.
But all of that is, you know, I was having a discussion with someone recently, something similar to this.
And he said, well, it's divide and conquer.
And I said, well, not really.
It is because the reason you divide to conquer is you don't have to put a lot of energy because when they're divided, it doesn't take much influence to control them.
What's happening now is no more division.
They're going to come together and be conquered.
Now, the difference between divide and conquer and ruling them in unison is divide and conquer.
Each one doesn't require a lot of effort once they're divided.
But once you have them all together, they have to be ruled with a heavy hand.
See, when they're no longer divided, divided, you need a very serious, you know, enforcement force.
One shot does it all.
Yeah, now you can't use propaganda anymore.
See, the reason you use divide and conquer is propaganda.
Right.
You take a population and you divide them and you get them fighting amongst each other and they're fine.
The technique that the United States has done quite well at.
For everyone.
Yeah, true.
Not throughout, but most known history.
So, other than the energy they use to, you know, various things that you do personally, you know, eat, sleep, whatever else you do, you're fighting someone else.
You have no energy to do anything else.
But we're coming into a time period now where that division will not be there anymore.
You ever think about that's why you're going to have, you're going to be ruled with a very, you're going to have a group of people who are very young and old people thrown in there, but they're going to be super charismatic.
They're going to rule the entire Earth from a certain part with a very heavy hand.
Anyone that tries to oppose them is just flattened out or fought against and does not prevail.
That's not happening now.
And what is uniting?
Do you know that you can, right now we're on Skype, we could Skype anywhere in the world as long as they have internet access, right?
And there's no time delay, virtually no time delay.
Correct.
You see?
So it's not, it's all coming.
The New World Order discussion, yes, it's not the New World Order that you've been told about.
The New World Order is coming.
It's being formed right now.
You know, so, yeah.
But here's the other thing.
I usually also say typically, when I say, for example, I have a personal distaste for this, I can give you so many reasons why I have a distaste for it that it starts to become seemingly objective again.
It's like Greek, you know, like if you ask someone, why do they like something or not like it?
They might give you one or two reasons and that's good enough.
That's just, you have the right to believe that.
But if you ask me why I don't like something, I'll give you so many reasons a week from now.
I'm still giving you reasons like, all right, Greek, that's enough.
I guess it is bad.
You see?
Yeah.
So, but I still have to consider it as being a personal outlook.
So.
Yeah, you're right.
Because for different people, it's, you know, I can bear really like the references either, but I'm not going for that information regardless.
So.
Well, no, that's, that's right.
You got a big pile of poo and you're going for the edible corn.
Right.
Manure.
But it's dried up.
You know, I can deal with dried manure.
It's the first step that you generally don't want to put your hands into.
Right.
Yeah.
Anywho, we can wrap up.
It is, we are going into quite a few hours, which might be objectionable to certain people.
But just to wrap up on the Satan thing.
So you said I was cutting out before.
So just to recap a little bit on that.
I don't see in the Old Testament any wholesale tactics against the entire human population.
I just see issues that Israel is getting involved in.
But the other countries have their own deities and they have their own jurisdiction to do whatever they want.
Unless they have particular peripheral covenants with Yahweh that they're supposed to be keeping, which is why, you know, presumably the Ninevites get involved.
But then you have a certain age, because these things go in approximately 2,000 year cycles according to the Zodiac.
And then you have the age of Pisces coming in, where the Christ is born soon after.
And from that point onwards, it's three days and three nights in the grave.
So if we're going to say that when Paul is talking about the adversary of this age, yeah, I can see that sort of connected to this current age, because it's three days and three nights in the grave, where you have malevolent entities that are ruling wholesale to do whatever they want.
Well, look, you could also look at it, you know, there's a metaphor about the bride of the Christ, right?
And the feminine and the masculine, and there's a counterpart, you know.
Why wouldn't the adversary have a counterpart within the Babylon whore, the whore of Babylon, or the mischievous one of Babylon, the goddess religion that we don't know anything about?
Why is she so set out on blurring the, let's say, the dipole nature of male and female, and blotting out man's ability to reproduce, not only man, but all of nature.
It's about destroying, right?
You think, right?
So there's stuff going on.
There's an interesting aspect to, even culturally, when something is considered malevolent or not, or just bad or evil, it's not to be memorialized in culture, you know.
So that seems to be following through to a certain level.
Moloch is memorialized.
Yeah, it is.
So it depends.
Well, it depends on what level too, you know.
I mean, we don't get any of other men in Genesis that we think we would, you know.
Other, you know, people.
We don't get a lot of the people that, let's see, even New Testament, we don't get a lot of names.
So, I mean, I don't know.
I think there's a sentiment here that also has to be regarded.
Also, there's, I think, a mathematical, well, I know there is, an underlying mathematical thing to all of this, you know.
And that mathematical or arithmetic aspect needs to remain pure.
And maybe that's why names and other descriptions are left out.
Because look, ultimately, and this is not to belittle or dishonor in any way at all, but this has to be thought, just like the word conman means confidence.
There's nothing wrong with that, but unless it's done wrong, right?
It's taken on, like the word nice is the opposite, right?
It means foolish, stupid, but everyone thinks it's good.
But to take the difference between the gods, their society and us, what's the difference?
What's the main difference?
It's technological.
They have a knowledge of the physical and non-physical world that we don't.
How many times have you looked at, for example, inventions that man makes, and some of his best inventions were already existed in nature?
From gears to mechanical things to chemical processes that he thinks he came up with already exist in nature, right?
Biomimicry or whatever.
There are creatures with gears on them.
There's a bug.
I mean, you can just go on and on and on.
If you study biomimicry, you'll see there are, and now obviously there's scientists and engineers that are saying we need to go see if this process or attribute is happening in nature and copy how nature has adapted a mechanism or a mechanism has adopted to this process.
Not through evolution, of course, but it's been put there.
So this is a technological thing.
We'll find out later.
I mean, what else could it be?
I mean, if you want to keep it in the woo, woo, woo, it's just, you know, we don't know.
That's fine.
We don't know.
It's technological.
That's right.
It's very nuts and bolts, but it's beyond, I mean, look at this point, they're not tangible to us if they don't want to be.
I mean, what kind of a technology does it take to do that?
Has it been imagined?
Yeah, it has been imagined, but can it be manifested?
Most likely, but has it been done so everyone can bear witness to it?
No, we will later.
It's best not to, that's why, you know, earlier on I mentioned it's best that people don't know how bad things are because it'd be mass suicides.
It's not only just how bad things are, but how good things are going to be because if people figured out really what's going on now and how it's going to be later, then we're like, screw this shit, I'm done.
I want the resurrection now.
You see what I mean?
So it's best, so people don't know about really how bad things are right now, what's really going on and how good they're going to be later because they would just put the butt, like, have you ever tried a video game and things aren't going so well and you just, oh, just screw it, just reset, start over, right?
Yeah, well, you don't want, you know, half the people or three quarters of the people figuring out the truth and saying, oh, this is, this is, screw this, reset, going straight to the resurrection.
No, no, no, no.
So you gotta, you can't, that people don't know how, so it's twofold.
They don't know how great
it's going to be later
and they don't know how bad it is now
and it's best that they don't
because they'll want to reset
if they have any rational
aspect to the situation,
just like you have a rational aspect
of sitting down in a video game,
you're getting blasted
in the first few seconds,
you're like, oh, reset,
I got to do this over,
I got to go back
and read the instructions, reset.
So it's best that they don't know.
And you've heard this a lot memorialized.
It's best that people don't know.
Sure.
I mean, that's a very clear way to look at it from a bird's eye point of view.
But when you want to zoom in on particular details, once you've gotten a penchant for studying these things yourself and you don't just want to be your average regular Joe, then you kind of want answers to specific things.
And even at that point, certain things are sort of still being blocked from access as pertains to Satan.
And by the way, when I said before, the God of this world, go ahead.
I just want to bring something up.
We're given an example on how to deal with that several times.
Actually, a clear one is when there was a fight over Moses's body, what was the response to the adversary?
Rebuke you.
That's it.
Right.
And also there's another example with the Christ.
So we're given examples on how to deal with that.
And it's minimal at best, isn't it?
As a result.
Yeah.
I mean, in a practical situation, but from a knowledge standpoint, you know, you still have to piece these things together as to what the actual character is.
Well, the thing is, knowledge of that would be knowledge of good and evil.
Or would it be knowledge of malevolency, murder, lying, you see, deception, right?
That's what it would be knowledge of, wouldn't it?
Yeah.
I'm not suggesting that people go out and do that, but I bring it up as a point of my own curiosity.
But I would suggest that people wouldn't even understand that level of it at all.
No, they wouldn't.
But because when you look, even today, how many people do you see going out and crying?
Oh, they're satanic.
This is satanic.
And when you look at what they're calling satanic is really a revived cult, an ancient cult of Sambal or ancient deity, and not the adversary himself.
You see what I mean?
No, it's fine.
And just to be clear, because the whole basis of this line of conversation was the Paul reference to the thought of this world.
Hold on, Sam.
You're really breaking up now.
Am I still breaking up?
Yeah, I'm crumbling.
There's not much I can do, unfortunately.
Is it if the device is hot, you know, temperature wise?
Yeah.
The resistance goes up.
The values change.
Kind of sort of you're audible, but with a little crunch.
Okay, well, then we might as well just wrap up.
But I was just going to say I'm not saying that there is not a god of this world.
I'm just saying that Paul wasn't referring to that before.
Because in John, it clearly does speak of a chief of the world or a chief of the cosmos.
So I just want to make that distinction.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's confusion.
You want to go there, you're going to have to be able to deal with it.
It comes through how confusing.
That's why I stated earlier, look how simple.
When it comes to these matters, you're to just to keep your interaction minimal with them.
And move on and just have them rebuked, you know, like I'm not going your way.
And that's it.
You know, no, no arguing.
You know, you just disqualify their position in your life.
Because they're way, way, way, way beyond how many times you heard me say that these beings have an IQ of 2 million.
You don't have a chance.
Yeah.
I would say I'm good for this particular round of talking.
All right, good.
I hope I look forward to the next time, Sam.
Yeah, this is really going to get you, Bruce, on the archiving.
So I'll just bid everyone till the next time.
And thanks.
Thanks for doing this.
Yes.
Oh, you're most welcome.
You're most welcome.
Both of you.
Well, you folks have a great night.
And we'll try to get this archive up in a little bit.
And both of you, be well.
Thanks, Bruce.
See you next time.