Elevator music.
Yes, it is.
Here we go.
Okay, we're online now.
All right, cool.
All right.
So we have the Greek Bruce and Sam.
This was this is a private conversation just happens to be streamed and maybe archived.
Yes.
So.
So what have you got on your mind, Sam?
Or Bruce.
I took Sam his wife's and went and got the ISO and started digging around.
And what a difference.
And then you compare it to some of the other interlinear years.
And my goodness, what did you have?
My God, what the difference.
So biblical stuff now.
Oh, yes.
So the biblical.
So a biblical interlinear.
Is it the ISA or the ISO?
The ISA.
I'm sorry.
OK.
And I tried a couple of different versions that they had available and put them on different machines.
Just to kind of get the feeling for differences.
And my goodness, what a Greek.
How in the heck do you know when you're getting the right stuff?
You know.
When you can.
Very.
It's a good question.
And the answer is very simple when you can explain it and you understand it.
OK.
Right.
If it leads to if it leads to understanding, it's the right stuff.
OK.
Yeah.
Unless.
Unless you're a retarded third grader like most people that are interreligious and they don't they don't ask any questions and they're happy.
Yeah.
Well, I've got I've got tons of questions when it comes to this stuff.
And but but just like retarded kids, like they say, they're super strong.
You ever been around a retard in a fight?
And this is not to offend anyone, you know.
Or I'm not politically correct.
And damn it, if I ever will be.
They're super strong.
So the same with dumb people.
They're super strong and there's dumbness.
So if you're getting understanding and, you know, you're getting an understanding, if no one wants to listen to you.
Right.
Let me know.
I mean, as a consensus, as a consensus.
Yeah.
Right.
So that's what we did.
As a matter of fact, a long time ago, I used to work for a group that took care of impaired children and we brought them to parks and things like that.
And I'll tell you, it was one of the more rewarding jobs that I've ever had in my life.
A whole different perspective on looking at things, you know.
Of course.
Yeah.
Because you're dealing with people that are not accepted in society or integrated.
That's a good it's a good parallel with this stuff, because if you want to be lawful outwardly, if you're immature, you're going to be just as if you are, you know, like that.
Now, what I mean by that is most people don't know what they're doing with the right information.
So they seem like they're doing the wrong thing and they are.
If you don't know what to do with the information, you're most likely going to do the wrong thing with it.
I'll give you an example.
You know what the I still the very few people that can understand how to make a demand for lawful money.
If you read the code, it says you're not authorized to use Federal Reserve notes, but a demand for lawful money can be made.
Blah, blah, blah at the banks.
Right.
Title 12, section 411.
But, you know, but, you know, your thing is that banks are what?
Federal Reserve agents?
No, no, that's why you hold on.
If I explain it a hundred different ways, maybe people will get it because it's so simple.
There really is no such thing as a Federal Reserve agent.
There's a Federal Reserve police.
There's things like that, but no one really exists as a Federal Reserve agent.
But there are people that work as in the agency of the Federal Reserve agent just means you represent a principal, right?
Through actions or through direct authority.
Now, the deal with that is that the banks can't give you lawful money anymore.
And if they did, it would be a waste of time anyway, because it doesn't matter out in commerce.
This is a legal aspect that has to do with usage fees.
There are some people that actually do the conditional endorsements with Title 12 and banks.
And then they go to the banks and demand lawful money.
The banks have to say, we don't deal with lawful money, which is funny because they admit they're not lawful.
And they tell them to go bank somewhere else.
The reason why you're asking for lawful money is if you don't, you're creating a huge liability.
Have you ever heard of something called the Internal Revenue Service?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, well, why is it not called the Internal Taxing Service?
Good question.
Fair.
It's a very obvious question because they're not imposing taxes.
They call it taxes because they know people are stupid enough.
You have to earmark it to go along with something that happened in history.
It's not a tax at all.
The most they could say is it's a tax liability.
They never say you owe a tax, never.
You can't prove that you owe a tax.
They say you created a tax liability, whatever, a liability.
What they are, they're collecting usage fees.
When you use something that's private, it's no different than going down and renting a jackhammer or a pump at the tool store.
Do you think you could just walk in and take it out for a day or two or a week or a year and then just bring it back and wave and say goodbye?
Or are they going to ask you for a rental fee or a usage fee at the tool rental store?
They're going to ask for a fee.
Yeah, so you actually want to pay a fee for using money.
Yeah, most people do.
Most people don't care.
That's all it is.
The reason why they take all that stuff and they're so harsh is because this is all private.
If a government can't function, the purpose of a government is to provide money and borders.
They're taxing you on private use.
They're not taxing you.
They're demanding a use fee.
A use fee, yes.
Because when you say taxes, taxes are supposed to go back to infrastructure and pay for all the things that the government has as expenses.
Right.
But not one penny of any IRS money that people have paid into have gone to pay for anything.
Social Security worked for nothing at all.
Forget not even the insurance companies are the same way.
Let's say you pay car insurance or health insurance or whatever.
Do you think that you send those premiums in and they get pooled together into a shoebox or an account and then when somebody needs something, they take it out?
No, they don't.
They create it on the spot from your signature every time there is a claim.
You could do research on this.
All the money that insurance companies get or credit goes directly where?
All of it, not some of it.
Well, some of it goes to public works.
Where does it go?
Where do all the insurance premiums go?
But is there a sense that some of that money – because I listened to this dude, Rod Class, speaking.
You probably know him.
He's done some good stuff.
But is there a sense in which the credits are supposed to go somewhere but it gets embezzled by the system or the lawyers?
Well, they're all embezzling.
They're double dipping.
For example, if you could go look at what's called a CAFR account, which is Comprehensive Annual Financial Report of Any City.
You can go online and look up one for any city.
Look up like a medium-sized city like maybe Orlando.
Don't do New York City.
But it doesn't matter.
They're all the same.
You're going to see a list every month.
There are hundreds of millions or tens of millions in the hole in debt.
They're showing you where they're getting their revenue and where it's going out.
It's blatant in your face.
Let's say a police department costs $10 million a month.
But it doesn't show any of the money that the police collect through fines, tickets, and poundings and things like that, seizures.
It doesn't show any of that.
It shows like attorney fees are like $30 million a month.
It's like, wow, for what?
The courts cost $5 million a month.
Well, where are all the fees coming in from the courts?
They don't show that.
Then they show you they have $200 million in investments.
Well, they're not showing you the return on that investment.
If you put $200 million on the stock market, you should be getting anywhere between $5 million and $10 million a year.
They don't show you that.
It's right in your face.
It's just like retarded third-graders.
It's like, I don't know.
These reports and these things that they put out, they are making fun of the people.
Look, I hate to say it, but I would be doing the same if I was there.
I would look at the people.
I would say, look, we're going to put out this comprehensive.
I'm talking about being unlawful, which I wouldn't do, but if I was unlawful that way, I would leave it just like it is.
Because I'd say, look, these idiots, when you mention – I'm talking about people in society at large.
When you mention to anyone, the police or the courts, one of the first things or second things that comes to mind is you're going to have to pay fees or fines when you're dealing with them.
These governments put out financial reports that show that they don't even show what they're taking in on that.
It's like in your face.
And no one is saying anything.
Well, how much did the court take in?
How much are the police taking in in fines?
No one.
No one is asking.
Not a one publicly.
It's like, holy crap.
This is a planet full of idiots.
And I say a planet full of idiots because, for example, if you're in Italy or Spain or England, they have the police.
And if you're speeding or what they call illegally or whatever, they issue fines there also, don't they?
And if you look at these international countries, they're not showing the amount of monies they're collecting in fines or credits they're collecting in fines or their authority to do so either.
So that's why I say it's a planet full of idiots, right?
So why are we streaming on a planet full of idiots?
I mean why are we even bothering saying anything?
We're supposed to ask for the mothership to come and take us away from this godforsaken place.
And I mean that literally.
It is a godforsaken place.
So next subject on a brighter note.
That was being bright.
You really don't want to hear me in a bad mood.
You don't want me to say what I really think is going on.
So anyway.
We had a question in the channel about lawfulness and unlawfulness.
You're buzzing out.
We lost Bruce, I think.
I don't know if he could hear us.
I can hear you.
I'm away from the laptop.
Am I still there?
You're popping in and out, Bruce.
Popping in and out.
That's not a good sign.
My eye's back now.
Lawfulness and unlawfulness.
Yes, what about it?
A question in the channel about it.
Yeah, what about it?
It's like black and white.
What about it?
They wanted some more in-depth discussion about it.
I believe was the topic.
You have to ask something specific, though.
Because I don't.
Trying to find it here.
I can't just shoot from the hip if it's not specific.
Right, I hear you.
If you're still taking questions, a deeper discussion.
If I hear lawful, unlawful, and in-depth, the first thing that comes to mind is I've got to come up with a lascivious joke on that.
Otherwise, I don't know what to say about it.
I think people have a hard time grasping that when you say lawfulness, you're talking about it from the creator's point of view.
Because they're still thinking in terms of legal.
Here's a maxim.
And a maxim would be something that everybody knows.
You don't have to write it down, right?
It's kind of common, right?
Look up what it means.
Your law comes from your god.
That's a maxim.
It might be a Greek maxim for now, because most of these other gents and people won't say, well, I've never heard of that as a maxim.
But anyone who spends time observing society through the ages will come up with that very quickly.
I mean, where do you get your law now?
The justice system.
Well, that's the goddess.
It's a god.
Okay, so there's always a god behind law.
So you have unlawful and lawful.
So if everything is hot, is there any cold?
No.
If everything is black, is there any white?
If everything is up, is there any down?
No.
So lawful and unlawful is a polarity.
So you want to judge what's lawful and unlawful, go to whatever god you get your law from and see where the do's and don'ts are.
Simple.
Okay, yeah.
I've been saying this for almost 15 years now, that your law comes from your god.
Period.
That was a question that was in the channel, and I figured I'd ask it for him.
Yeah, so I guess there's two spheres of things when you're talking about lawful and unlawful.
There's what your god says, and then there's what the Most High God says.
That's right.
But I think in human society, because they don't follow their own laws, it's unlawful across the board, both in their eyes and the Most High.
Right.
They're screwed if they go left.
They're screwed if they go to the right, no matter how they move.
And if they move forward, they're screwed.
If they move backward, they're screwed.
Look, I'll give you an example.
There's a story.
It was actually something I read.
It was probably written in the early 20th century.
If there is no god, we're all in trouble.
If there is no god in the universe, we're all in big trouble.
And if there is a god in the universe, we're all still in big trouble.
See, that's the lawful and unlawful side, right?
I'd be interested in seeing who's looking into the legal state of Europe, as far as how the European countries have handled their bankruptcies, because that's not really talked about.
It's mostly just America.
Well, they have a strange system.
There's an underlining of religiosity, let's just say, from the Vatican that runs through every country there.
Most people don't know this, but you can check on it.
I don't know if it's on the stupid rectangle or not, the Internet.
But if you publicly speak out against the pope, you get a fine from the government.
So let's say you're in Spain, and you're speaking out publicly or write something against the pope.
The government comes in and fines you for that.
And it's high.
It's like several thousand euro and jail time.
So I hope that helps.
There's a very strong underlying current of the Vatican throughout Europe.
Because remember, Europe was ruled by an emperor, and it was ruled by the pope for hundreds of years, since the 1400s, 1500s.
1400s, Europe was ruled.
All of the monarchs in Europe were either behest or subject to the emperor and the pope.
And the emperor usually was like the Austrian-Hungarian Empire, or they could have been as north as places in Norway, Holland.
There were several emperors.
I think they gave up the emperorship in the 1800s.
Most people never discussed the emperors of Europe.
Napoleon tried to take on the title.
Napoleon was trying to revive the primacy of the Vatican in Europe as a political power.
Because the Vatican started as a political power, right?
That's obvious.
And the Americans joined the Napoleonic Wars.
And when Napoleon lost, it was called the War of 1812.
That's all disconnected in most history, because it's too holistic.
The last thing you want is holistic investigations.
So, with the European Union, that was actually formed in the 50s, but pronounced in the 90s.
Because they had their 50th anniversary in, what, 2003?
Something like that.
But no one had heard about the European Union publicly until the early 90s, mid-90s, right?
Yeah, I think they started off as a coal union or something.
Coal and steel economic union.
So, they had a different name in the beginning.
If you really want to know what I think, they're just a bunch of jerk-offs in Europe.
They have the ability to do so much more than they do.
You mean like everywhere?
Yeah.
But especially them.
Think about it.
I mean, I don't need to get into it too much.
But if you want to think about it, if you look at who went out in this age, you had the Portuguese, the Dutch, the Spanish, the Italian, the French.
They went out all over the world for hundreds of years, right?
And what did they do?
They just colonized.
They lost their colonies, came back, and they colonized with savagery, right?
They said they called the people savages, but they were really the savages.
You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
So, I mean, the people that there was – you're ruled by a guy wearing a funny fish hat.
I mean, come on.
It's really bad.
That's why you have most technological advances happening in the states with electricity and engineering in the past 85 years is because of the more of a liberal point of view to that, right?
Mm-hmm.
So, okay, what else?
What else you got?
Well, if we move away from the law thing, I was going to bring up some different things about biblical history.
So, if we look at…
Not the Bible again.
Not the Bible.
No, I'm just joking.
Go ahead.
I've made it a point a few times in the past to talk about the Masoretic text because I think it's a bit more cohesive than the Greek stuff, which we obviously know is not primary because it's a translation.
But the Masoretic text is interesting because you can also delve into sort of the Judean-Jewish side of things.
So, the term Masoretic is kind of an umbrella term, I found, for what we consider to be the authoritative rabbinic text for the Tanakh.
All right.
So, when you say Masoretic text, hold on, just so I get a picture.
You're talking about 1020 A.D.? Around then?
First millennium A.D.? Yeah.
Around then?
Okay.
Right.
What stems out of the scribal schools of that time, which we know are two primary ones, the Ben Asher and the Ben Aftali?
And then they went with the Ben Asher version, or their tradition of how to keep the text, preserve the text.
So, you had these two schools, and each one had their own manuscripts according to their opinions.
All right.
Let me stop you right there.
How many times do I say it doesn't matter how much of this stuff you look at, do you understand what's being communicated?
And the answer with these folks here is no.
Do they understand what's in the text?
No, they don't, obviously.
Right?
Obviously, they don't.
But by looking at what's called Jewish, Judaism today, that stemmed from that, which has been reformed several times over, especially with the establishment of Israel, you know, because they didn't speak Hebrew until it was reestablished in the 19th century.
So, do they understand what's in their own book?
And the answer is a big, fat no with a capital O.
Right?
How do we know that?
Well, it's obvious.
You could look at them.
Saturday Sabbath?
Dark moon?
Come on.
You know, what are you talking about?
These objects that they put in front and what they do and what the rabbis are getting away with?
Are you joking?
So, let's just say before we get into the text, because we're pointing and emphasizing or underscoring that it's Judaic background, I'm telling you, they still don't know what's in their own book.
They did all that.
Let me just finish off with this other thing.
You know why they did all that work of collating and preserving and filing and putting it in some sort of relevance?
They did it for us.
Cosmically.
Cosmically, because they don't know what's in it.
I mean, they could read it all day.
They could bang their head on that wall, that Roman, that Syrian fortress, thinking it's the temple.
They could do all that.
They don't know what's in it, comprehension-wise.
They did it for us.
Us?
Who's us?
Well, you're going to have to figure that out.
So, okay.
So, go ahead.
So, is it technically valid is one point, and can you get comprehension out of that text is the other, and I would say you can.
Yes, and just to piggyback off that, the fact that the Jewish religion sort of developed because of the Masorite traditions is valid, but there's also truth to the fact that whoever they were in that era is obviously very different from the type of ignorance that's been put upon them today.
So, for example, if you look at the calendar aspect of things, they put that in place.
I forget the name of the rabbi.
Some famous dude whose name escapes me right now.
Laria in the 1500s?
No, some other dude.
Yeah, just some other dude.
I know his name.
Oh, that's fine because it is just some other dude.
No, I know.
Go ahead.
So, you have this big shot rabbi.
Once Jerusalem was destroyed, they convened and had their meetings as to what they were going to do about the calendar because they used to keep time from Jerusalem based on the aviv barley that would ripen at a certain point, and that would indicate the new year and things like that.
So, when they couldn't do that, they decided to go with the Babylonian calendar.
They computed the math, and I think they felt like it was accurate at the time, but then the problem is that it drifts as time goes on.
So, then a thousand years later, it's going to be off, and you're celebrating your festivals and feasts on the wrong day.
But I think that that was their reasoning because they were in exile, so they were just going to do that, and when they get back into Israel, they go back to the real calendar, which of course they haven't done.
But hold on.
They missed the point on how simple it is to observe time
because right now with this little super minor information,
what's actually major information the Greek has been putting out,
but a super minor collective of people that keep giving feedback on what day it is
from all over the world, they could figure it out from wherever they are
very simply by very simple sighting, once you understand it,
that the sun, the day starts at noon, and the full moon rules the month,
and the Sabbath is on each quarter, very simple.
So I don't know what these guys, they put their testicles in a vice for what.
Yeah, no kidding.
You see what happens when it's not time?
That's why I'm saying it's not time yet.
So yeah, they could try.
What they're going through is the emperor has no clothes.
They're completely naked and they don't know it.
They missed the point.
They still do sundown, the day starts at sundown.
How ridiculous is that?
Just as ridiculous as the day starts for measurement at dawn.
Dawn would be more intuitive, because look, hey, here comes the sun, new refreshed, right?
That would make more sense.
So yeah, they're very heavily censored because it's not time yet, because what happens is when a group of people get it right, whether it's an academic, legal, medical, or religious society gets it right, two things happen.
One is they could advance the cause beyond when it's supposed to be advanced as a whole, because the whole world will know they're doing it right.
And the other hand, also, this world is being ruled by a very powerful adversary to mankind.
So they're going to be a major target for destruction.
So when you do things correctly as a group, you have the good guys against you if it's not time yet, and you have the bad guys against you because they don't want the right thing done.
And you gave us fake money and the lust for it to really screw things up, because only money talks and bullshit walks.
There's no money in awful time.
It'll never happen.
Well, here's the thing about real money.
Why aren't you going to have real money in this current system?
It's a very simple question.
I'm going to pose it to anyone.
And so far, no one really gives me an answer.
It's a rhetorical question.
I'm not expecting an answer.
I'm going to give it like the arrogant son of a bitch that I tend to sound like most of the time.
You ready?
Ready.
The reason why you're not going to get substance-backed money, it doesn't have to be gold or silver or any substance, is because once that happens, you have to go back under law, not legal.
Right.
All of the attorneys in all the courts go away as they operate now.
Because if you've ever watched the induction of a bar association president in their speeches, they always mention that it's very crucial, in order to have a strong economy, that you have a strong legal system.
What he's basically telling you is that they are taking all of the signatures and all of your pledges and monetizing them.
So if you go under a substance-backed money, then you can actually buy the house.
You can actually buy the car.
You don't need a birth certificate for monetization and jurisdictional purposes to be monetized.
You don't need a credit line anymore.
So the police are not going to be – you could go look, for example, in history, when there was the ability to have redeemable money in silver coin up until the 70s.
If you look at the police cars and all that, they were the old, busted-down, under-equipped.
Since 9-11, if you look at the police cars, they have the newest, most expensive equipment every year.
Right?
Do you get it?
They're just short of a tank.
Not even that.
They have the newest cars and all that.
I remember growing up in the 60s and 70s, they were running those cars until they were rust buckets.
Yeah, yeah.
Now you look and they've got the newest and the greatest every year.
Because they're the ones controlling the money system.
In other words, they are monetizing everyone in jail, every ticket, every court case.
So what happens if you go to substance money?
They go away and it's not going to happen because the people don't want them to go away.
I remember reading a survey a few years ago.
What's the most important thing that society has to have that cannot be taken away overnight?
They're like the police.
I'm like, yeah, these savages are correct.
I want the police because these are savages in the society.
Now they've been reduced to that point.
Not just America, every country.
Except for the ones that are already living in some kind of fiefdom or what's like Somalia, for example.
Right, yeah.
They don't have – you're better off there.
Whether they have a credit or substance, not much is going to change because that's – but they've got their own problems.
Have you ever been into a black ghetto?
I don't want to hear about this racism stuff.
You don't want – even blacks in black ghettos don't want to be there, right?
There are certain conditions that are just appalling for any individual from the outside or the inside, you see.
So I'm not talking about that because Somalia is not necessarily like that.
But they don't have a centralized system like over here.
So it might be a little rough for some people by contrast.
But what I mean by that is that there's always an exception.
But I'm usually – even no matter how harsh I am with the commentary or the facts that I try to give is that it's generally the rule.
And a lot of times when I say stuff, it sounds like the exception.
Like just take, for example, lawful timekeeping.
You can't keep time with the pope's work schedule, whatever.
That sounds like an exception because the rule is everyone is using the calendar.
No, and I'm telling you the rule is for lawful timekeeping, it's the sun, the moon, and the stars.
An exception is some ignorant thing that has to be run under certain subjects because when you have people that are subjugated, any information they get is on a need-to-know basis.
If you don't need to know this, there's no reason for you to know it.
That's why you have the calendar in position as it is.
That's why these idiots, they think it's a birthday or anniversary or a holiday, Christmas, Halloween, whatever, Fourth of July.
And I could prove to you that day that you're celebrating was not so last year.
And you don't know when to celebrate it.
You're on a schedule.
No different than a bunch of five-year-olds in a school bus going down the street and the teacher and the bus driver decide, now we're going to stop here and do this.
It's by fiat or de facto.
Yeah.
There's no rhyme or reason to it.
And do you need to have that for four-year-olds?
Do you need to have a school teacher and a bus driver telling everybody to shut up and sit down or whatever?
Of course you do.
Structuring, yeah.
Exactly.
So they've got – this is the – the deception that people have in this society right now is the entitled classes and the academia.
Because academia is where you go to learn about medicine, legal, religion, science, all that stuff.
That's all deception, all of it, all of it.
Not some of it.
All of it.
That's the rule is deception.
And the reason why is because, look, we're going to suck money out of you or credits and take up more of your time in conditioning.
That's why they offer that.
And go out and make it better.
Yeah.
No.
The money aspect, if you look at the – if you try and compute the numbers as far as how much they're getting out of the system, that's in the several trillions.
Yeah.
If not more.
Easily.
There's no substance to it.
Right.
It's just numbers.
It's ether.
Yeah.
But it doesn't have purchasing power.
Only – it only has purchasing power because of the moronic merchants that accept it.
Yeah, because they're accepting it.
It's not the central banks.
It's the merchants that are the real assholes in this equation.
But we're talking about accounts somewhere that have these gigantic numbers on them.
So those numbers just keep getting bigger somewhere and they're not – because, I mean, if you deploy trillions of dollars into the real world as purchasing power, you would see a significant difference.
But we're not seeing that difference.
You don't destroy – you have to create the illusion of shortage because all of a – what happens if you've got a pot of soup with, let's say, two liters of soup, and all of a sudden you dump two liters of water into that two liters of soup?
You've doubled its volume.
Does it still taste like soup or does it taste like some kind of dishwash water with chicken flavor or vegetable flavor?
It's gotten less value, a soup, doesn't it?
Yes.
So forget about purchasing power.
Here's the thing.
If you run into people that are of high net worth in the billions, the whole idea is not to use the money directly but to use it indirectly.
It's called leverage.
What's leverage?
If you ever look at a lever or a fulcrum, does it even look like it's moving?
Hardly.
But it's got tremendous force behind it, right?
Yes.
So what they do is they say, well, we're going to do a project and we need some money.
Okay, so we're not going to use this guy's money.
He's got $50 billion in the account.
We're going to go to a financial institution to get the money, but we're going to show that this guy with $50 billion is behind us.
So they create the new $50 billion.
Yeah.
Instead of moving the old $50 billion, which can actually damage – because if you move the $50 billion chunk right away, it's like dropping the two liters of water in the two liters of soup all of a sudden.
But if you have to create the $50 billion, that's what they do out of credit, and they get the green light to do it because this other guy is backing them, right?
Now it's trickled out.
Let's say a $50 billion project.
You don't need all that up front.
You need maybe $10 billion or $5 billion up front, and then after six months, another $10 billion.
You get it?
Right.
So the money trickles in very, very slightly, and as it's being dispersed – Alan Greenspan wrote a pretty good paper on distributions and disbursements.
This is not what it was called.
I think there was a chapter in it.
Alan Greenspan, back in the 70s or 80s, made a speech.
We're fine.
They asked about the central bank.
He says, ah, we're fine because the people never understand what we're doing, what's going on basically.
He didn't call people stupid.
See here, on the other hand, between me and Alan Greenspan, I call people flat out stupid, and they don't understand, where he didn't call people stupid.
He just says they'll never understand, and I could prove to you I don't care what their IQ is or what degree they have.
I'll show you.
Sit them down for 10 minutes.
Explain how the money system or scripture or real science or real history – these people are bad.
They don't know.
They can't see it because it's beyond – it's something called cosmic censorship.
It's a bitch.
So anyway.
My curiosity is as to these huge accounts that are somewhere with huge credit numbers on them, and nobody is touching that or saying even on some greed – on a greed tip to say let me just take it.
No, they're not because that's the pinnacle of their achievement is to know that they have that on account.
There's nothing in the account.
It's on account.
Meaning – yeah, it's on account.
Just like attorneys are never in law.
Like in laws, they're always at law.
They're never – so the interesting thing is let's say you have someone who walks around and he's known as a billionaire.
That's because he has billions on account.
All of a sudden, if he uses all of that and it's no longer on account, is he a billionaire?
No.
This is all vanity.
Have you heard of that somewhere?
This is all vanity before?
Have you heard of that somewhere before written thousands of years ago, 2,000 years ago?
Maybe let's say that was about almost 2,800 years ago that was written.
Yeah, vanity, vanity.
Wow.
By the way, the name of the rabbi who put in the Jewish calendar was Hillel II.
That escaped me at the time.
Oh, wow.
That's late.
That's early then.
That was what?
600, 700, something like that?
Yeah.
It wasn't Masorete.
He came before them.
But yeah, the name – I remember.
It was around Mamonides, before Mamonides.
Yes, that is true.
Around 300, 300, thereabouts.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, because his name is kind of like the sun of the morning.
Hillel bin Shamash or whatever.
Right.
Hillel is usually translated into Lucifer in English.
Yeah, which makes no sense.
No, but let the little idiots have their fun with it.
Now, here's the whole thing.
I like looking into what these guys have done, but I always view them as clerks.
Just like when you go to a hardware store and the guy says, can I help you?
Yeah, I need a pound of nails.
Yeah, here it is right here.
Great.
Without this guy, I wouldn't have found it as easily, and he gave me some good service.
You know?
Mm-hmm.
They're clerks is what they are.
They're not the sages and the wise men that they're portrayed to be as.
Obviously.
You can see what they're saying.
Mm-hmm.
But they're very good at what they've done.
They're not good at what they do.
There's a difference.
They say, well, we know how this should go.
No, that's wrong.
But what they've done is very good for coalescing or coalating and, you know, putting it in context, organizing it, right?
Mm-hmm.
But they're not who they are portrayed to be.
They're just a bunch of clerks, all of them.
Obviously.
You know why I say obviously, right?
Because just look at it.
I mean, it's just like what they've put on Judaism is rubbish.
I was watching something recently about how they do the Sabbath, and I was like, where'd they get that from?
And I meditated on it.
I said, oh, I see.
This part came out of Egypt.
This part came from Babylon.
This came from the Samaritans.
This came from here.
I was like, wow, that's where they got it from.
Well, yeah, I mean, they're running off the Talmud mostly, it seems.
I mean, the rabbinic aspect seems to run everything.
Yeah, they're little Gestapos is what they are.
Yeah, go ahead.
Now the point vanished because I'm so tired.
But, no, I was going to bring up the scribal issue.
Because, as you mentioned, I mean, if you're a good clerk, at least you know how to keep notes, and we should be able to give them the ability to just copy a text.
It's not like they have to insert anything into the text.
Oh, what I was going to say before was that you have these Jewish communities in Israel, like the Karaites, who really just want to go by the Old Testament, and they're very adamant about that.
I know.
They're going with Karaitism.
Right.
Yeah, they're very adamant about the dark moon, yes.
Yeah.
And they don't even know how to figure it out.
They think the day starts at sundown, too.
Yes.
And they have this thing, like with the name, they pronounce it Yehovah rather than Yahweh.
Yeah, whatever.
And they get that from the Talmud.
Right.
But those are offshoots from the clerks.
That would be like the clerks, what do you call it when you have a tree house, and you have a gang or a group of young children that go to the tree house, and they have a pecking order?
Anyway, what do you call that, like our gang, a little gang?
They're part of the little gang.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're like a little gang they have there.
They've got the Talmudic, they've got the Karaites, and they've got the Messianic thrown in there.
It's not time yet.
Right.
So the text itself, though, if you go back in history a bit to the time of the Masorites around 920, you had this guy called Shlomo ben Buah, who wrote a codex of the Bible copying from the ben Asher codex, because you had these two primary schools, ben Asher and ben Naphtali.
They kept their own codices, and ben Asher was kind of a big shot who everybody seemed to trust.
And this Shlomo individual then copied his codex, with ben Asher reportedly finishing it and signing off on it, with his vocalizations and the notes in the margins, and that's how you get the Aleppo Codex, which Maimonides reportedly used for his landmark literary work, the Mishneh Torah.
And so that became their essentially authoritative text.
And then, of course, in 1947— But the question is, are they in harmony, and where are they not in harmony?
And if so, are we still waiting for more?
Well, it's hard to say, because no facsimiles have been made of the Aleppo Codex, because you had the 1947 Jewish riots in Syria, where they burnt down the building that it was in, and then it had to be transported to Israel, where it's currently being kept in some kind of a think tank institution.
But what happened was that pages—and this is still controversial, although I think if you look into it, it's kind of obvious what happened— but pages were torn out, and they're saying that, well, those 109 pages went missing because of the fire.
They burnt up in the fire, which makes no sense, because then the whole book would have burned up.
Right, it's too selective, yeah.
It had to be done by human hand, not by fire, you know.
Right, and there's a book, an investigative book, that's been written on that, it's called the Aleppo Codex by Matt Friedman.
But look, let's just look at it this way.
This is something that I've reckoned over the years of studying in pursuit of where is the most, what would you say, the text with the most integrity, right?
And a lot of times I reckon missing things and supplemental things this way.
The information, let's say the 109 or so pages that is missing, is there any information in there that would make our comprehension of Scripture so much worse?
And I'm not meaning more or less comprehension, but what we comprehend in Scripture, the matters of reality being actually less fortuitous and more malevolent than they are.
Or, let's look at it the other way.
Could that missing information actually show us in our comprehension that things in reality are actually much better than we think?
And either way does it matter, because right now we do know that we're being ruled by the adversary, and he makes everything bad look good, and we go for it.
And so how much worse could the reality be than that?
I keep saying, well, be thankful that no one came and ripped the liver out of your body while you were sleeping last night for no reason at all.
So I already understand that.
The other thing is, how much better could it be?
Is there information in there that's missing that shows us really how much better it could be?
Well, how much better is it going to be when you have all these religious institutions and attorneys and doctors roaming the earth doing what they're doing?
Even though they don't know what they're doing, it doesn't matter, they're doing it.
And how much better could it be knowing that when we have the resurrection, we're going to have God-like powers?
Could it show us anything even better than that?
I doubt it.
The only thing that would be there are certain details that would help us form better the character and the event if it was in place of something historic, or something more that was, you know, more prophecy, right?
But we already have, in a very holographic and limited sense, the whole picture.
So that missing stuff doesn't really matter, but it does matter because don't you want to know that you've got it?
If something is missing, you don't have it, you have it except for that, you see?
Would that be part of vanity on our part, that we want more, more, more, more?
Yeah, I would say so.
Because I keep saying this over and over and over, I never recommend anyone study this kind of stuff because they're not going to, A, understand it, and B, they're not going to understand it, and C, they're not going to understand it, right?
Right, but this is not vanity because it depends on your level of study.
I mean, if you're going to evaluate, as you often do, society from the most low-hanging fruit perspective, then yes.
But it's not the low-hanging fruit.
Look, I've run into rabbis that have said, tell me about prophecy.
These guys spend, these are Judean biblical scholars, and I said, tell me about what happens in the end times.
And he says, well, the big temple comes down from the sky with the Mashiach and Elijah.
It makes no difference.
That's still low-hanging fruit.
I don't care about their titles.
And I'm like, wait a second.
What about a list of 100 things that, you know, so, yeah.
Well, I think humanity is, low-hanging fruit is the highest you're going to go.
Most of humanity is on the floor and rotting on the ground.
The low-hanging fruit is the highest you're going to go.
Sorry about that, Sam.
Well, certainly from a societal perspective.
But, you know, I speak for myself, and I'm not interested in that.
So I want the whole text.
That's not vanity, because as you can see, certain aspects will not line up, because the text doesn't make sense.
For example, this is what my youth is.
Yeah, give us an example where it's missing from, and without dislodging what you were going to say again.
Go ahead.
Sorry, say that again.
Where the 109 pages from what section is missing?
The Prophets, the Psalms, the writings, I mean the writings, where?
And the other thing is, for example, you were going to say something as well.
Oh, the example.
Let's see.
I can't keep a thought in my head for a second now.
I was going to give an example of something.
Oh, right, the Book of Samuel.
So the Book of Samuel.
That's a major chronicle, the Book of Samuel.
That's important.
But it doesn't, no matter how much they put, what are they going to show?
Is there another king that's missing?
It doesn't really matter, because we know that there's a repeat of King David, not King Saul or King Solomon.
There's a repeat of King David and Solomon, really, but not most of the other kings, or before or after, you see.
So I don't think it will change it too much.
No, I won't say that it changes it too much, but it's an example of an inconsistency.
When it says that two different people killed Goliath, it's like, okay, you didn't copy that right.
Some scribal error was made somewhere, because they're saying, we know David killed Goliath, but then later on it says some other guy killed Goliath.
Does it give a name, or does it say some other guy-ish?
No, it gives a name, but you can decipher that it's a scribal error, because I've gone through that.
Okay, we can look at it.
Yeah, sure, does it resemble David?
No, it's not even close.
So here's what it is.
First in Samuel 17, 4.
Is it David backwards, where they count the letter positions, and then suppose, you know that, are you familiar with, do you know like Babylon, BBL, is also Shishak, right?
Because of the numeric positions, are you familiar with that?
Yeah, I'm familiar with that.
But no, this is not that.
This is just some ridiculous, what are they writing type stuff.
So in 2 Samuel 21, 19, you have an account.
When there was again a battle with the Philistines at Gob, Elohan, son of Jair, the Bethlehemite, smote Goliath the Gittite, whose spear had a shaft like a heddle rod of weavers.
So here they're saying that this dude, Elohan, killed Goliath, blatantly.
Okay.
Well, here's the other thing, Sam.
We weren't there.
So let's just take that as another account, but an unverifiable one, but both are unvalidated at this point.
You know what I mean?
To verify and validate are two different things, right?
Verification comes by statement, and validation comes by truth with proof.
So we have no proof of either one, but we have more verification of David doing it solo.
I mean, David doing it solo is pretty major.
You can't just be like, well, maybe.
Come on.
Well, no.
I would say that it would need to be valid.
Well, it will be validated in the future, I guess.
Here's one thing that I mentioned about the book of Samuel that ties in where you hear about David very much, let's say, is David comes up in many of the prophecies over and over again, but the house of David, as in the physical house, meaning some kind of physical structure regarding David, and very rarely when you see the house of David, does it rely on information on his descendants.
It's mostly the house of David, which was an important fixture in that culture and scriptural, meaning the actual tomb, you can call it, that was made for David.
It's underground right now.
I have a pretty good idea of where it is, if you know where the real temple is, and it seems there's a good chance that will be uncovered in the near future, and when it is, there are going to be a lot of validations in there.
Do you get it?
Yeah.
But right now, because they're actually going to find stuff in there that proves the Bible to be true, especially around that, so there's also going to be things in there that is going to prove that the Christ is from the lineage of David and other things.
So what I would suggest, though, if you're saying it's a scribal error, do you have anything to back up that it's a scribal error, or just by simply reading it as such?
Yeah, there's a case that can be made, so let me go through some of the stuff.
You have this first account in Samuel 21, where they're saying this guy, Elahan, killed Goliath.
Okay, fine.
I don't know what they're talking about, unless David and Elahan are the same person.
When you go to Chronicles, Chronicles obviously gives a lot of parallel accounts, so 1 Chronicles 20, you have the exact same account.
When there was a battle with the Philistines, Elahan, son of Jair, Smote, and now you have a completely different name, Lami, the brother of Goliath the Gittite, who had a spear with a shaft like a heddle rod of weavers.
So first they're saying the dude killed Goliath.
Then they're saying, well, no, he actually killed the brother of Goliath.
Right.
Goliath, there was a family of five of these guys, too.
Exactly.
So, yeah, okay.
It's not critical.
No, it's not critical, but it's an example that this is human error.
And when you look at the actual Hebrew letters, you can sort of decipher, oh, okay, that's where he fucked up.
Because, you know, I have pictures of, you know, screenshots of the thing, and then you can kind of go through it and see, okay, you can sort of try to rationalize how it went down.
Okay, so it's graffiti in a way, or whatever, or just scribble error.
And there are other places in Samuel where complete words in the Masoretic text are just unclear or not written down correctly.
So there's a lot of typography in the book is what I'm saying.
And you can find these kinds of flaws throughout the text in general.
So it's a B or a C.
An aircraft, when you're doing aircraft work, when you need a part and you get the exact part, it's called an A-fit.
But when you don't have the exact part and it'll fit and it'll do the job, it's called a B-fit.
And if it just barely fits and maybe does the job, it's a C-fit.
So this would be like a B or a C fit in aircraft.
Yes, but I think it's more important for what it indicates that those guys were still dealing with a certain flaw that's present in the text.
And, I mean, we can look at other things.
Let's look at the height of Goliath.
Okay, so you and I have talked about this in the past.
First you had Samuel 17 that says his height is six cubits in one span, right, which is nine feet six inches about, right?
But then we have to remember that that measurement comes from a specific Hebrew Masoretic text, right?
So the Dead Sea Scrolls has something completely different.
The Septuagint has something completely different.
The Septuagint has the height of Goliath at four cubits in one span, which is about six feet six inches.
And the Dead Sea Scrolls, and specifically Scroll 4Q51, also says four in one span.
And the Jewish historian Josephus also describes Goliath as, quote-unquote, a man of vast bulk, for he was four cubits in one span.
So you've got three against one.
Right, so a cubit, is it a two?
From what I take it, a cubit is around 18 inches from the Egyptian, and they use the Egyptian standard throughout Israel, except the temple standards that were used in Exodus, for example, that we don't get a lot of definition from, you know?
Right.
So you're basically, to figure out a cubit, let's say we need the Ark of the Covenant or one of the posts, something out of the tabernacle, right, to measure it.
And we know that people were not like Lillipuglians, you know, they weren't these little tiny, they were not five foot zero, they were taller, so we have mummies and things, so.
Right.
So you can either go with Goliath is this huge giant at nine feet, or he's six, six six, and...
Well, six six is not that, it's still tall, and if you're a fierce warrior, you would be head over, now he sounds more like Saul, where he's head above everyone else, right?
Right.
Anyone who's over six and a half feet, you know, in a crowd, you're going to see their head and shoulders above everyone else, right?
Their head pops up, right?
Right.
So I would say that, at a minimum, that still makes them pretty big, but not that big, so as we imagine a giant giant would be, and I say giant giant twice to mean that it's not just a tall person, it doesn't suffice anymore, it sounds like their cubit is more than two feet, then.
Right, so it would be eight and a half feet or so.
So, I don't know, because...
So this is what I'm saying.
Yeah, that's a standard, that's an issue of standard.
But it's also a difference in measurement, because the Masoretic Text says one thing, and you have two other sources saying something else.
Right, one says, well, the number six versus the number four.
Right.
So can they get it right?
Well, apparently not.
So there's some issues with that.
I mean, these are just two examples.
We could probably go through each book and find multiple cases of that.
I've sent you a screenshot at one point where an entire portion of text is just removed.
Right.
And it was regarding the sons of gods or something like that, yeah.
Yeah.
But let's also keep in mind that what we're currently using as the authoritative Hebrew Old Testament is the Leningrad Codex, so this stuff comes out of that.
I don't know what's in the Aleppo Codex.
You asked about the books that were missing.
So it's missing all of Deuteronomy, it's missing a portion of Kings, a portion of Jeremiah, of Amos, of Micah, of Chronicles and Psalms, and a few other smaller books.
Yeah, I need to dig out, I have a chart and I have some things in print, books on how the instructions of King James, and how they did the King James translation, and what access, what texts they had, right.
And also you mentioned something about order too, the order of the books.
Yeah, there's a specific order in the books and categories of the books, yes.
And it should be chronological and categorical, like you have the first five books of Moses, and then you have the Psalms and the writings, which would be the Psalms and Daniel and Job, and then you have the prophets, and then you have the major prophets and the minor prophets, and the minor prophets should all be read as one.
Hmm.
If you actually, yeah.
So, and the reason I'm saying that, it's interesting because there's 12, just like for example when you look at what the apostles wrote, there were four major apostles that really wrote, they should all be viewed as one, right?
Right.
And the same way with the minor prophets.
Okay.
Really, the minor prophets are completely full of detail about a very specific, they go narrow and deep into specific things and geographical places of the end times.
That's why I know very few people give them any understanding, or any play, because there's so little understanding of prophecy, that the last thing you want to, if you don't understand prophecy categorically, the last thing you want to do is delve into prophetic things.
Because you're going to show your ineptitude.
Hmm.
So, that's why the minor prophets are avoided.
But they should all be read as one, continuous book.
Yeah.
But there is a chronological, Ernest L.
Martin put together the Restoring the Original Bible book or something.
Yeah, I think I remember you mentioning him, yes.
There's a chart that he put together.
He is.
Here's the thing, he's passed away, he can't defend it, but some of the people that are alive, that work with him, I have spoken to face to face, and they all said to me, well, you know, I brought up certain things, you know, why are you saying this Christianity stuff, and God, and Jesus, I don't even like to use that word, J-E-S-U-S, and all this stuff.
He says, well, you got to understand, Greek, if we don't use those terms, we won't be able to sell any books, and no one will listen to us.
Oh, that's right, yes, yes.
If they don't use the word church, Christian, J-E-S-U-S, and God, they won't be able to sell anything.
I said, so, okay, so you have more faith in man supporting you with his lucre and his shepherds, and the Creator backing you up by doing more of the right thing.
So that's fine.
Good.
And I just had to walk away from that group, and I can't recommend this stuff wholeheartedly, but I would give it as a reference.
You know, it's basically eating undigested corn out of somebody's poop, if you really want to get into it.
But the magnitude of that corn, in many cases, the magnitude of that corn is a milestone.
Really, no one else has come out and published stuff like that.
Yeah, he had a lot of spoots, not forgetting it all.
Yeah, but he had to do it in the dirty way, you know, the religious, mixing in the Christian J-E-S-U-S and church and circus.
Otherwise, no one would buy it.
So it would be too radical.
For me, I draw a line on that stuff.
You have to.
Yeah, you have to.
Well, whenever money gets into something, it's not going to come out too pretty.
Well, that's not true.
Well, they say interest dies where money lies, you know.
Well, here's the other thing.
Let me just give you a little contrast.
Samuel brought up David.
If you study David, a talent is what, anywhere between 40 to 60 pounds?
Okay.
He had accumulated 30,000 talents of silver, 30,000 pounds, not ounces, pounds.
You have to multiply that.
Yeah.
Right, so he did that.
He accumulated that to develop the city of David and also for the future development of the temple.
So it was a strong cycle of money there, but was it something bad?
No.
This is going to happen again.
There are going to be edifices and institutions put together in the near future that are going to require in the billions, and it's going to be a tremendous amount of credits put together, and it's not going to be for necessarily just pure vanity.
It's going to be to show the world that these things can be validated, and especially when you're looking at it from an archaeological point of view.
Right.
You know?
Yeah.
I'll give you a personal understanding, all right?
What does the Greek think about it?
I have no need for that other than for doing something.
Like, for example, if I were a billionaire or whatever, I have no use for that.
I have no use for that at all for myself.
What am I going to do?
Go buy a yacht and a garage full of Ferraris and a mansion?
I have no use for that.
I can only drive one at a time.
I don't like going out on the ocean.
I like minivans.
An old minivan is best.
I just need a comfortable room to sleep in and a couple other things.
I have no use for that.
But if I had it, what would I do with it?
Well, obviously, there are two ways.
One thing is you say, well, what do you want to do with it that you think is good?
And the other thing is what does the world need?
Well, the world needs a hole in the head, needs a shot between the eyes.
So a billion isn't going to do it, and it has to be done by the gods.
Right.
Right?
So then what else can be done is maybe developing a place where people like you or Sam and others that have come forward in getting in touch, where they could actually, there's a brick-and-mortar place where stuff can be done to further it.
Maybe set up some experimental water experiment, electrical experiment, stuff to show others.
Yeah, you could build something the size of, like, say, put it on a trailer of a car that could run ten square blocks.
Yeah.
Electric, whatever.
No, that's not a theory.
No.
It's a fact.
Or you can change the weather patterns radically.
Right.
Very areas of what can be done.
Yeah, all these things.
So, again, I would have to, you know, the things that I think would benefit.
And I'm telling you, none of it matters at this point, because it's all short-term.
You mean for human society, it doesn't matter?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
And then you've got the adversary against you.
That ain't good.
Well, they come down.
The adversary is not a problem if the most high gives you protection.
Right.
But I assure you, you're going to lose both protection.
Well, the adversary will come on you and protection if you start saying you have to do this to make the world a better place.
Right, right.
Because it's not the most high's time to put these suckers through a program, as it is in prophecy, and the adversary just does what the adversary does.
There's no way you're going to get it.
So, yeah.
You can do good things, but just don't say you're doing it to make the world a better place, because the world needs to be violently destroyed, not made better.
Right.
This is what people don't understand.
It's kind of like, imagine this psychopathic serial killer that likes to pop the eyes out, including old ladies or whatever, and this guy's running away after he's killed a few thousand people, and everyone's like, oh, we'll just give him – he hasn't been loved.
He just needs to be loved, and we just need to rehabilitate him.
Yeah.
No.
If you really see what the world is – and here's the other thing.
Man always sins, right?
Right.
So, what's the penalty for that is death.
So, you already got the penalty for sin, but what is man getting involved in that's going to require an extraordinary act of destruction that you read about?
Right.
Think about it.
Yeah.
And those are – I've hinted at some of the things that he's doing, and maybe that would be another sonic event.
Because the penalty of sin is death, and everyone gets that anyway.
So, why do we need an extraordinary penalty?
That means that something extraordinary is going above and beyond what can be considered just dealt with, with the ultimate end known as death.
So, yeah.
No one's thinking about that.
I see most of it.
I see it, and that's why I keep saying there's no way you're going to fix this.
It's unrehabilitatable.
Yeah.
For the majority.
Correct.
Yeah.
Majority meaning just about everyone.
Just except for a few thousand, maybe, out of the seven billion.
It doesn't matter what race, nationality, religion, or age you are, humans are delineated as cosmic scumbags now.
Try and clean yourself up from that.
Now, scumbag, by the way, is an old Navy term, by the way, if you remember.
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
So, anyway, Sam, what else you got with your theories there, or my theories, or do you want to say?
No, you have a lot of theories, but I was just going to wrap up on the Codex aspect of
things, because the conclusion that I was trying to come to was just that what we currently
have is a very concrete encapsulation of certain people's efforts, because people talk about
the Masoretic text kind of like they talk about the King James, like it's a rabbit's
foot, but this holy thing that we got down from these very holistic scribes that did
such a great job.
And it's not really the case.
Yeah, but hold on.
Is it the text itself or the information held within?
If it's the text itself, it's just a bunch of paper with black ink on it.
Right, but it is the medium conveying the information.
But here's the thing.
What if we had it accurately in audio files only?
I take that.
Yeah, of course.
That's why I keep telling people that this is all pagan still garbage.
The text itself and the relic itself is meaningless if its purpose is to convey information.
We're not talking about a bonafide relic like they had, let's say, certain temple fixtures and what do you call when someone wears something, not uniform, but vestiges and things.
Those things were extraordinary, let's say, items that were part of the required vestige or they had to be present.
I'm not talking about those kinds of things.
I'm talking about if anything is supposed to convey information, that's all it is.
One of the most repugnant things I see is people putting their hand and swearing on a Bible.
That's why I tell people during the elections, how do you know the shit's going to go bad for you?
The president is putting his hand on the Bible and swearing.
The guy's an idiot.
You're not supposed to swear.
He doesn't know anything in there.
This is how you're showing that you're going down, but you're going down slowly over a few hundred years, not right away with one guy.
Ain't gonna be pretty.
Uh-uh.
So to look specifically at it a bit, you had this period in, I think, the year 1000, 1008, thereabout.
A scribe, you had a scribe called Samuel Ben Jacob, who wrote a codice also, and he claims that it was copied from the Aleppo Codex, but I can't find any evidence that Ben Asher himself signed off on it the way he does with the Aleppo Codex, and this is where the Aleppo Codex comes from.
But it doesn't matter.
No, it doesn't matter.
But again, it doesn't matter.
I'm just giving background for people.
You could take any of those guys and ask them to explain Scripture.
They might understand a few little bits here and there, but they can't see the whole picture.
They're doing all that work for us, meaning us, meaning temporal us, meaning in this time period.
Right.
So I don't expect them to explain anything.
Like I said, just keep the record straight.
All you have to do is copy the text.
If you can't even do that, you're a joke.
And what we're seeing is that they couldn't even do that.
That's what I'm trying to point out.
Well, here's the other thing about a copy.
It needs to be a true copy, so it's almost undiscernible from the original, right?
Right.
Because if it's not a true copy and undiscernible from the original, then it's no longer a copy.
Now it's a facsimile or a version.
Right.
And from what I'm seeing, I mean, we know the Leningrad Codex is a version, period, because we've already looked at some of those issues.
So this is what we have in the ISA, and this is what we're operating under.
So one of the things, I'm going to drop a picture into the Skype thingy.
That is the front cover of the Leningrad Codex, and I think that is the first recorded instance of a hexagram being, or whatever, Star of David, not a Star of David, being used on a literary work.
Yeah, Mogan David, they call it.
Yeah, there is no Star of David.
That's like something they put on people, like the Trinity or whatever, in Christianity.
I think you also have a nine-pointed star surrounding it.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight-pointed star.
People who are into Chatango can just Google Leningrad Codex.
You'll see it.
Well, not a lot of stuff.
You see also they had the documentary Hypothesis came out of that part of the world much later on, where they said, well, there is no scripture.
It was really a bunch of cultural phenomenon and traditions that were put together by certain sages and writers, and they formed the Bible that way.
You see what I mean?
Oh, I haven't heard too much of that.
The J document, the documentary Hypothesis?
Yeah.
In other words, they don't know that they…
Oh, yes, I read about that once, but I didn't pay attention to it because it sounds silly.
They don't think the scripture is a transmission.
Yeah.
Or a transmission, its source.
They think its source is…
You hear that a lot from Muslims, by the way.
Not about the Bible so much, but about their own book, which is interesting.
In that case, it's true, though.
But anyway, that's another thing.
I find it interesting.
Currently, the way it is today, the hexagram is kind of like the pentagram.
It's associated with things that are occultic and things like that.
That's what it's been propagandized into.
The Druid symbol.
Right.
The Druids used it.
It's just basically one triangle over an upside-down triangle, is what it is.
It's what you're talking about, right?
Yes.
Not the eight-sided.
The eight-sided looks like a seal, almost.
Right.
And they have some kind of a priestly blessing in the middle of the hexagram.
With the hands are written.
Yeah.
And one of them is the Star Trek Mr. Spock thing, which is supposed to make the letters, right?
The shin.
Yeah.
The sha-ta or whatever.
Sha-ta.
Yeah.
I mean, they got it pretty good in Babylon.
They still have not recovered from the Babylonian captivity, you know.
Hmm.
Clearly.
I mean, I find it interesting that nobody thinks that it's suspicious that this symbolism is on what they're currently using as a Masoretic text, because it indicates a very clear Kabbalistic influence.
And this is what we're going with.
Yeah, because it's during the Age of Darkness that was prophesied.
You know, what is this?
Three days, three nights in the grave.
Meaning, you know, thousands of year periods.
And what happens when you're in the grave?
Well, it's dark, it's cold, it's musty, there's no life, right?
There's decay, usually.
Yeah.
Scripturally, there's decay associated with the grave.
They call it corruption in some translations.
So this is a time, 2,000 years now, of decay, darkness, cold, lifelessness, corruption.
How do you like that?
And you live for what, 70, 80 years, 100 years, amongst a period that's supposed to last 3,000 years like that?
Yeah, I've had it.
Hmm.
How many times have you heard me say there are no benevolent gods?
But, in essence, the ones that have your most interest, I mean, benevolent gods in our time period that we are in right now, the ones that have your ultimate interests in mind, and the one that the Most High that is going to make us part of His family and take us to the next level, you know, as His children, direct part of His family, we will understand His benevolency then.
Right now, it's a lot of lip talk, you know, a lot of lip service.
A lot of people are saying, oh, yeah, I'm glad, you know, the Most High is watching over me and He answers my prayers.
I'm like, really?
Really?
I mean, I don't mean to knock anyone's faith in that.
You have to have faith of what's going to be happening in the future and that He's going to pull you through and give you what you need now once you have understanding.
But you're still subject to being shortfalling in everything that you do.
It's called sin.
You're still subject to death and you're still subject to all these morons around you, right?
It would have been better.
So ultimately, it would have been better if He never put you here and had you born later when He was ruling and Satan wasn't around.
Do you get it?
Yeah.
And this is not a beef that I'm putting out.
I'm just giving you the condition.
Stop deluding yourselves, people.
You were put here knowingly in the worst possible situation that would just barely keep you along this little existence that you have of 70 or 100 years or whatever.
Or as some people, a few weeks or hours or months or whatever.
This is not good.
We are not in a good situation, very bad situation.
But you don't want to be, you know, you don't want to dwell on that as just being that, right?
Maybe we get points for it later.
Oh, you do, extremely so.
And you'll be part of like an elite squadron later.
But I would suggest that most, and not very few again, will be.
But everyone will be granted the privileges of the resurrection and empowerment of a body that is no longer subject to carnal death, right?
At least after the second one, after the second death.
Because most people, it seems, or if not a good amount of people, will experience the second death as well.
That is also a theory though.
Well, it's a conclusion that you've come to.
I don't think a lot of people are going to make it in there proportionally.
But, you know, we have our differences on that.
Here's the thing, you're going to find out.
And the thing is, it's not only about, the second death is also because of their stubbornness.
Yeah, we know that some people go in there because of their stubbornness.
But what I'm saying is, if you take into account the thousand-year White Throne Judgment, like how much does humanity suck that most of us go in there still after that?
Oh no, but I'm mentioning those that have come before, the billions before.
Yeah, but those people are going to be resurrected for the White Throne Judgment.
Well, you don't even have to say White Throne Judgment, say the Final Judgment, which would be after that thousand-year period, before all things are restored.
Well, after the Millennial Kingdom, yes.
But then you also have to remember that that's another thousand-year period though.
So you can't re-educate humanity in an over-a-thousand-year period?
The ones that are alive, yeah, but the ones that are resurrected already, no, you don't have to re-educate them, because they're going to be going through a specific education process and endowment that is different than the rest that are born carnally.
Yeah, that's fine, but the ones that get resurrected are the rest of humanity that consist of probably over a hundred billion.
Yeah, probably.
It'll be a round-off number that's easy to understand, but it's in the billions, yeah.
Right, so I'm skeptical of the fact that you can't successfully re-educate most of them.
Well, that's you.
It's like you said, my theory, or me, but I'm not saying this is exactly how it's going to be, but I'm speaking out on these things to give people an idea of a certain order, and also what to expect to happen that's simply in Scripture.
Right.
How many exactly, but you can look at Scripture, and those that are given the ultimate privileges, and actually exempt from many of the other nasties that happen later as well, are very, very few in comparison.
There could be a million people in the first resurrection which is the most privileged.
We don't know, over the past 6,000 years, right?
Right.
Or it could be as little as just a few hundred thousand, or a few thousand, we don't know.
Because part of the first resurrection includes quite a few people that are still alive now, that are taken up immediately after the tribulation, including all of the patriarchs and quote-unquote beloved and set-apart ones from the past.
But if we look at what was given, let's say, in Kings, you want to take it loosely or lightly, there were 7,000 held roughly in every generation.
So there's 120 generations, right?
Right.
If you're looking at the Jubilee type, or 60 generations if you look at a great generation, which is 100 years, so 7,000 times 60, or 7,000 times 120, it's still not a lot.
It's in the hundreds of thousands, right?
Or millions, I'm sorry.
It would be in the low millions.
So you can look at these things.
There's a lot of, whoa, is that Sam the noise?
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, I believe so.
So the numbers are small and great.
And I'm suggesting that the second death is going to be a great number on there, a greater number than those that are not.
Okay.
I'm just going off intuition.
Intuition doesn't work anymore, sorry.
I mean.
Yeah.
Let me give you an idea.
This is advice especially for younger people.
I always question my intuition, but I also listen and heed to counterintuition.
You ever heard of something being counterintuitive?
It's like it kind of hits you and stops you, and you're like, whoa, I can't.
This needs to be looked at, you know, not lightly.
It needs to be put aside and looked at again before I even think about it or say I need more, right?
Something counterintuitive is like it's almost like it has shop value to it, right?
That's an interesting thing in itself.
Some good comedians use counterintuitiveness, and they flip it into intuitiveness, right?
That's the punchline, right?
So I would suggest that this thing called intuitiveness is one thing that's broadcast by the adversary.
You know, how many people can you go out right now and they find it intuitively a good thing to go to church?
Many.
All these things that we're sort of discussing on these sonic events, most of those things are counterintuitive to most people.
But some people see it, and like let's say timekeeping and all the other things that are brought up in Greek speak, and they're like, holy crap, you know, it's not counterintuitive, but it's just a shock.
But it is counterintuitive to most.
So this intuitive thing I found is one of the main baits that the adversary uses.
But, you know, then there's the education or the awareness of the individual makes a big difference as well.
You know, if you're – see, most people are not – let's give an example with the Bible.
If you – let's say KJV, the V is in there.
It means version.
Everyone knows it's KJV, meaning everyone who's familiar with it, they're going to see version part.
Or they say King James, but they know it's version.
Now, the people that are strictly familiar with the way it's used in society, they think it's a good thing and it's the ultimate.
But those – there's a group, a good enough group in society that knows whenever you hear the word version, it means hearsay.
And it's not to be trusted.
But they never do anything with it because it's not important to them.
So the people that know that the word version means not to be trusted will not find this information as counterintuitive.
As those that just accept it as being trusted, it doesn't matter.
They don't care if it's version or not, you see.
So there's different levels of intuition.
But that's one thing that I always question my own ability to be intuitive or counter – or I look at the things that seem to be counterintuitive a little bit more.
And I've found – this is not to be making a personal thing here.
But I've found that most of the things that people find to be intuitive on their own is actually just don't make any sense at all.
And this is not for you, Sam.
This is just in general.
I will say that I'm not trying to make stuff up in my head based on nothing.
I mean for example, you could say intuitively based on the text because we are just going off the text.
Cain didn't like Abel.
OK.
Does it give us a lot of exposition on that?
No.
But you can figure he didn't like him and he went after him.
I mean it's pretty clear even though they don't explicitly say.
Does it say Cain had Abel anywhere?
I don't think so.
No, it doesn't.
But I would differ on that.
I think he didn't like the reaction, the overall reaction that he got in comparison to his brother.
It's kind of like saying your brother gets all As and Bs and you only get Cs and Ds.
Mom liked you best.
Yeah, I have no real reason to dislike my brother.
But why are they always rubbing that he's better than I am in school grades?
Well, for that effort I'm going to get him.
But that has to be built up over a period of time because the way that you're describing it is kind of like a sitcom presentation.
Well, suddenly it just became like this and now I don't like him.
But there was a build up.
There was a build up.
Well, we don't know that because it doesn't tell us how many consecutive sacrifices.
No, we don't know that.
We know of two.
We know there were at least two because there was the first one that was rejected and then the second opportunity, right?
So we know that there was around two.
How much of a build up that is, I'm not too sure.
But I don't think there was a predisposition that he didn't like his brother from what I get from the text.
Well, it was interesting that they included those two.
You know, there must have been a reason.
And also why are we told about Cain and Abel's situation and not all the other people that were doing their own things?
Not true.
You see, so this is, again, a marked event to illustrate a point that is going to repeat again and again and again.
I mean, I bring it up to illustrate the intuition aspect.
I don't feel like it's unreasonable to say that he had a girl.
I mean, look at Jacob and Esau.
They like each other.
I mean, clearly, Jacob didn't think enough of his brother to not steal his birthright.
Right.
And he knew that his brother was going to come after him.
So he ran.
Neither of them were likable characters.
Neither one.
One, Esau was brash and just kind of guy that was just rough or whatever.
And Jacob was conniving and misrepresenting.
And also he had the assistance of his mother.
So just like Bruce said earlier, you were mom's favorite.
Who was mom's favorite?
Definitely not Esau.
That plays a lot in family.
It does.
Yeah.
She was Rebecca, wasn't it?
Yes.
Yeah.
She was playing favorites big time.
Do you see what's going on?
And you see those stories even in this day and age repeat itself, you know, where people are led astray by their parents or something.
Oh, yeah.
So in simple Greek-speak talk, and I'm saying it's Greek-speak, not because of the word, because of being used, guess what happened to Esau.
He got what?
Pranked, didn't he?
Yeah.
Didn't he get pranked?
Did he get pranked?
Yeah, I guess.
No, well, he was an idiot.
He gave it up on his own.
Well, yeah, he gave it up.
You know who got pranked is the father got pranked.
The father got pranked, yeah.
I think it didn't seem too bright, really.
Yeah, he even put on something to be furry, you know, and hairy.
And he couldn't see, so they pranked.
I mean, it was a prank all around, I'll tell you, because he got him.
He got pranked for a bowl of porridge, let's say.
Yeah.
He got him when he was a moment of weakness.
I remember from doing competitive athletic stuff, if you bonk, I don't know if you've ever heard of that term, you feel like you're going to die, not like a heart attack thing, but you have no energy to even move.
And you'll do anything for a Snickers bar.
Yep, you've expended yourself.
Yeah.
You'll do anything for just like a sip of Coca-Cola, just to give you an extra three minutes to get to, you know, the end.
Yeah, so when you're at that bonking point, if anyone's athletic, they'll know that pretty much all reason goes out the window, and that's the time if you're going to convince someone, you know, they'll sign over anything to you for a cookie, chocolate chip cookie, right?
Yeah.
So they got him at a moment of weakness too, so I don't know.
I would just say it's not good all around, man.
It's not good for anybody.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's nothing benevolent.
The best you're going to do, the best you're going to do is set yourself apart from the worst of the worst and just be with the worst.
And it keeps you out of the temptation.
So many things, character building.
Well, but hold on a second.
Well, I'm not going to say no, Bruce, but listen to this for a moment.
The creator puts temptation in front of you also.
He puts it in front of you, but he never does it without giving you a way out.
So whenever you feel like you're in a temptation situation, if it's being put in front of you by the creator, which usually it is, look for the way out.
And I mean from the self point of view and the selfish point of view as well, because he's going to give you that to satisfy.
But, no, what I meant by there's nothing good in it.
It's considered a test by him then.
Yeah, well, it's more than a test because he knows what you're going to do ultimately.
Well, I thought you said that he didn't know about what our free will would do, but would this not be a...
No, I never said that.
Oh, I thought so.
No, no, free will, I give the cruise ship analogy.
Right, I remember that.
Well, everyone on the cruise ship is going from point A to point B, but while you're on the cruise ship you have options on the cruise ship.
They're like little floating cities, right?
You can pretty much get anything on a cruise ship than you can in a well-developed small town.
Correct.
Now, when you're designing the cruise ship, you know through demographics and statistics how many people are going to be using the skeet game on deck, how many people are going to be at the theater.
Oh, okay, okay, right.
Yeah, so you design all of it to accommodate everyone.
So when you're doing free will, you're actually still being accommodated.
Right.
You could look at a cross-section of society.
You ever hear sometimes, you know, look how many lawyers are graduating in this society this year, how many doctors are graduating from society.
Oh, we have too many lawyers graduating this year, right?
Or we don't have enough doctors graduating this year.
We have a shortage of doctors.
So how do you determine you have too many of one or too little of another?
Right.
Because there is a structure there, you see.
So that structure is still in place.
Perhaps maybe I used the wrong word in temptation in the free will.
I guess what I was trying to allude to is the fact that he puts us there.
If we take that way out, it strengthens our position with who our love is for, our God.
Yeah, but he calls and then chooses, and here's another way to look at it.
Don't forget the cosmic censorship.
Right.
If you're really subject to the cosmic censorship, your options go out the window.
So your free will is, like, limited.
It's gone.
It's shot.
Yeah, I'll give you an example, and this might sound kind of narrow-focused and almost prejudicial in a demographic way, but go to a Walmart and spend a day at a Walmart, and you're trying to tell me that these people have any free will?
Well, they think they do, but I can look at your typical, this might sound arrogant as hell, Walmart shopper, and I could tell you everything about their life without them opening their mouth.
Yes.
That's how superficial they are.
Correct.
So, and I'm just a human.
Okay, okay.
Imagine what a God can see.
Right.
So even though, does this Walmart guy, typical Walmartian, have free will?
Well, of course he does, but are they as shallow as about as shallow could be as a human?
Right.
I mean, just look at your average, you want to spread it out, whatever, your average American that's into church, football, baseball, hot dogs, going to the doctor, and pension.
I mean, what kind of free will does that guy really have?
Does he have anyone telling him he can't do what he can do?
No.
But look at how shallow they are.
I mean, they're so censored.
You know what I mean?
Right.
You with me?
Yeah, I am.
I am.
So it's the free will, to me, I don't see it as ever being a question other than the influence for the elimination of options through cosmic censorship.
Okay.
The more you are subject to the censorship, the less free will you have.
Not because you really don't have the free will, or you're really being limited, because you're so censored you're too dumb to do anything.
Right.
I mean, dumb meaning you're just too far.
You're like a poster boy for Gustav Le Bon and the crowd.
Yeah.
Every day of your life you're thinking of what crowd group you're going to join, because you can't think about anything on your own.
This is the majority of society now.
Yeah.
So, I mean, what free will?
I mean, look at the society that you live in, even your own neighborhood.
What free will do these people have?
Yeah, they're locked in it.
Yeah, but if you ask them, do you have free will?
They say, yeah, I can do whatever I want, but what do you know about doing nothing?
Do you see what I mean?
Yeah, exactly.
The free will and the predestination, that needs to be sorted out, because that seems to be an esoteric religious argument that people have.
Yeah, I can see that.
And it doesn't make any sense unless you consider that you're being influenced by an adversary.
He's broadcasting for you to do everything that's good, which is actually bad, and what you think is bad is actually good in most cases.
I'm not talking about putting knitting needles in your eyes as being good.
No, but I'm speaking morally and lawfully.
Correct.
And also you have censorship.
These people that discuss academically this predestination versus free will never discuss cosmic censorship, ever.
And they never discuss that this planet is being run by the adversary.
Yeah.
And they never discuss there's a time period that things need to be a certain way until all things are restored where the Creator is here again.
Never.
They're looking at it from like a pseudo-academic, pseudo-religious, pseudo-divine, quasi-whatever perspective that is just, again, superficial.
So think about it.
It's very, very simple.
Even what things are discussed as biblical secrets or biblical mysteries are not that at all either.
That's another level of censorship.
It's right there in front of you because it's disclosed by the prophets.
But you can't see it.
Look, I'll give you an example.
You know, still people talking about free energy and all this crap, right?
Didn't I send you a movie about a Joseph Newman machine?
Yes, you did.
And you know, I should put that up there for people to grab sometime in case they haven't been able to get that.
That's a heartbreaker.
Yeah, that's proven without a doubt that electricity doesn't work the way that we're told.
And when you properly rotate and properly configure a coil and a magnetic element, that you can give off enough excess spikes to charge a battery system that will perpetually run it.
Not perpetually.
It's not perpetual because if the batteries go fault, not run out, right?
But you can set up a Newman machine, especially if it's large, and it will run.
If you've got, let's say, a 3,000-square-foot warehouse, and you put about 10 of these in there, like the two-ton ones, you could run an entire city perpetually, and the batteries will never run out.
They'll run down, and then you cycle them.
Look at the fact that the output of it, you could take and you could rectify and bring its charge up.
Also many possibilities on that.
The way to do it is you go to any power station right now that either uses nuclear to make steam to turn the turbine, or a dam uses water to turn the turbine, or coal fire to make steam, or oil or gas to make steam.
Now you just disconnect the turbine side, and you attach the Newman machine directly to what they call the generator.
Right, exactly.
And it'll never run down.
It'll never stop.
Well, you need to maintain things.
Yeah, well, this is true.
The bearings will wear out.
You'll have to be able to change the bearings.
But now there's bearing technology that is good for 20 years.
So these things are simple.
And you still have idiots all over, where's the free energy?
Oh, man, this has been out for 35 years.
Right under your nose.
Yeah.
Oh, and there's a lot of them out there.
And it's like you said one time, the ones that do know.
But they're not most of them.
If you go online and research them, very few of them are over unity because they're not building it right.
Right, right.
They're not building it well.
I mean, I put out a lot of things.
They're like, Greg, it doesn't work.
I said, well, let me see what you did.
And they didn't do it the way I told them.
I said, well, you've got to copy it exactly how you know it works and then modify it later.
Right.
So, you know, I mean, like there was I know a guy up in Montana, and he spends $100,000 a month irrigation of crops.
And the $100,000 is for diesel and the power company.
He's got three phase, you know, for the pumps, for the water.
Sure, right.
And I'm saying, well, for about $100,000, I'll put a machine there that will turn the pumps and it will be off the grid.
And you'll never, oh, no, I don't think I want to do that.
You know, I get a tax break, you know.
Yeah.
I mean, stupid.
This is like ridiculous, you know.
God.
That's why I'm like, nah, you guys are on your own.
Yeah.
And the new machine doesn't have to be built the way it's shown.
But you need to build a few of them that way to learn the principle.
And this is, I'll tell you, where everybody goes wrong.
And they try to copy them.
And they don't follow the instructions on the commutator.
You know, the commutator has a phase reversal and a dead short.
And most people see where it goes into shorting mode.
And they say, oh, that's no good.
And they reduce that.
And they rectify it.
I say, no, you need a dead short.
Right.
A dead short puts a field.
Have you ever run one of those machines in a room that has vacuum tube lamps like fluorescent lights or anything like that?
They're flickering constantly.
Sure.
Yeah, it interferes.
It puts out a field.
Well, the FCC, it will not.
Here's the interesting thing about it.
You know, the FC, when you put an electronic device, the FC has to be passed by UL laboratories.
It doesn't put out noise.
But the irony of it is.
Right, spurious radiation.
But, you know, Wi-Fi, that's all Wi-Fi is.
Yeah.
That's the irony of it, right?
Yeah, yeah.
You know, there's no Wi-Fi that will pass that, right?
Obviously.
Correct.
So they have to stay within their tolerance of their band.
Yeah, but the band itself is spurious radiation.
Correct.
Bandwidth that's bad.
And I think you can't splash frequency-wise onto another adjoining frequencies.
So your ratio of output has to be long.
Right, exactly.
They sell rights to the difference.
That's why the Bluetooth changes.
You've got the old one and the new one.
Right.
And when they change the rights, they say, well, the old devices have to be destroyed.
You can't buy them in a pawn shop or some shit like that.
Remember?
Right, right.
But the interesting thing about the Newman machine, the spurious radiation, if you build what's called a Faraday cage, and it's not grounded, right, but, you know, if you basically put a pseudo-ground around it, you could capture even more energy off of that.
Correct.
Yes.
Yeah.
Again.
As long as it's floating.
Right.
Yep.
So, I mean, there's stuff we do with cars, stuff we do with water, and it's like, man, you know, years ago when I was really naive, I was like, oh, man, this is great.
The whole world, we're going to change the entire world economy.
I never really said that, but I'm just saying I've been told this process will change the entire world economy the way it deals with water.
I said, I doubt it, but let's do it anyway.
Right.
What happened went away.
Nobody wants it.
I'm telling you, this is a ridiculous society.
Yeah.
No.
So let's go back to the free energy with the Newman machine.
How many people are looking, how many lectures and people, you know, movies.
They even did a movie, that idiot.
I spoke to him.
I had him on the Skype contact.
The guy, he's the heir of a fortune, and he did a movie called, about six, seven years ago, about looking for free energy devices.
He invested, like, millions of his own money to put out.
Oh, wow.
Charged or something.
What's the movie?
I was frequently speaking.
Someone put me in touch with him and I had hours and hours of conversations with him, and he doesn't get it, you know.
Oh, anyway, he's a descendant of the Palmolive or some Soproctor and Gamble.
Oh, Forrest Gamble, Forrest Gamble, whatever.
Brilliant.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We'll get out there.
We'll look at it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, it probably gets more interest talking about it than actually doing it.
Yeah, yeah.
Another one of my…
It's ridiculous.
This is ridiculous.
The only solution is violent destruction.
Not just destruction.
It has to be violent so they feel it, you know.
They remember it.
The entire society.
The faster there's a…
I remember reading something from the 1930s.
Who was it?
It was a guy who's…
Some notes of someone doing some biblical study, and he says, oh, man, the faster this society ends, the better.
And he wrote this in like 1938.
Hmm.
And then back then they didn't have transgender and all the toxic chemicals and food.
Right.
And all the unlawful money and unlawful this and all the attorneys everywhere running the show.
And you see?
Mm-hmm.
They didn't have Jerry Falwell back then.
No.
No, they didn't.
Or Ernest Angley.
The other guy.
Or all these other guys.
Whatever.
I loved him.
He was a little short one that went around smacking people in the forehead and saying, Jesus, you know.
Oh, yeah.
But here's the interesting thing.
The interesting thing about anything is that it…
Like I said, ever since I've been speaking publicly, most of the retort and response that I get is about scriptural stuff.
But that's all well and good.
But do you know how to eat?
No.
Do you know how to heal the body from a wound?
Do you know how to apply certain mechanical things?
No.
There's a topic for you.
That's very important as well.
Lymphatic system.
Lymphatic healing.
I had somebody ask me to make sure to ask you next time I got you on the air about lymphatic healing techniques, healing, better health.
I guess that would be the general crux of the question.
There's two levels to that.
One is if you have a lemon of a body, which most people do, believe it or not, something that's going to get you.
That is from a divine cut.
You were cut from that, right?
Right.
You were cut out to suffer health problems.
There's the other side also that requires the free will part to take action.
It's pretty clear.
You know how we said get deeply into lawful and unlawful?
Right.
Let's do that very quickly.
Okay.
What makes lawful, not only that it comes from your God, is that it actually is based on something, substance-based or it can be technically accessed.
You can just communicate it to someone else and they get it.
Right.
When they tell you about calories in food, how can that be logical when you don't poop charcoal briquettes because in order to determine the calories, you burn the thing until it stops.
If you have an experiment to determine calories and the thing is still burning, do they say stop right there or do they let the whole thing burn out and get the full caloric measurement until it's carbonized, right?
Right.
If you're eating food, do you know anyone who eats food that poops carbon?
Not a one.
Pure carbon.
How can it apply to food?
Right.
It's unlawful to say that calories apply to food when you eat it.
It applies to food in a laboratory but people are applying it to themselves.
Right.
That's unlawful.
Okay.
How can you put your feet in water and hands in water and it softens the membrane and it shrivels up and you think you have blood pressure or pressure inside the system?
Right.
You have a vacuum.
When you take a slab of meat with a bone in it, put it in a bag and put a vacuum on it, does it shrivel up or does it expand?
It shrivels up, yeah.
Just like your fingers.
Right now, if you do an internet search, why do fingers and toes shrivel up in water?
They tell you.
The scientific website says no one knows why that happens.
Completely unlawful.
Yeah.
What happens from a lawful perspective is if you receive an injury, even a cut, you ever notice over a certain period of time, whether it's minutes or days or hours, that it starts to swell up?
Right.
A lot of times when you get a cut and you get a local swelling, they say, well, it's infecting, right?
No, it's not.
There's no infection there.
The reason why you have swelling is to close off the area.
It's compressing.
Like a patch on the top.
Yeah, like a compression internally.
Right, to create compression.
The tissue is hard and you'll notice that if there's an opening in the skin, it starts to close or curl away and then move downwards and swell even more.
If you understand that lawfully, you're under a vacuum, a slight vacuum, because even the ancients can determine what a vacuum was.
They had flexible membranes.
They could expand and contract using positive and negative pressure.
Right.
If you know that, for example, when you have a pressure breach, whether it's high pressure or low pressure, if you do any gardening and there's a hole in the garden hose and you don't want to afford another one or the hardware store is closed, what do you do?
You go get a roll of tape and you start wrapping it around the hole where the water is leaking or the pipe is leaking.
If you don't do it tight enough, it still drips, but not as bad, right?
Right.
Apparently, there is how firm the wrapping and the dressing is that matters, you see, even with a hose or a pipe, right?
Okay, so the same with the human body.
If you are under a slight vacuum, it's not an extreme vacuum, you need to wrap it as tight as you can humanly do it without causing destruction somewhere else, down further down the limb, because you understand that the body, the fluid circulates through the body to the center and then back out.
So if you make a wrapping too tight, that's too far away from the heart or the lungs.
See, they always tell you that it's the heart circulating the fluid.
What about the lymphatic?
It's very indirect, right?
So if you have a joint or a cut or a bruise, you need to wrap it as tight as humanly possible without, you know, not to the point where it's going to like a tourniquet, but to the point where it's comfortable.
If you know you're in a position to loosen it in 5 or 10 or 15 minutes and then put it back on, make it that tight.
But if you know you have to put it on tight and you can't address it for the rest of the day, don't put it on as tight.
See?
Okay.
Let's say you get a cut on the finger and you've got nothing to do and you can just, nothing else more important to do, and you can just mind it for the next half a day.
Make it super tight for 5 or 10 minutes.
Loosen it a little bit.
Don't take it off.
Just loosen it.
Let the circulation, you know, the finger turns purple or blue.
And then make it tight, but not as tight.
And subsequently, after 2 or 3 wrappings of that, make it firm to where it doesn't remain, you know, it doesn't cut off circulation and the finger goes numb or turns blue or pink or whatever, or black even to an extreme.
Right?
So, but if you're, let's say, doing something and you need to address it just once, don't make it as firm as you can and leave it on there.
You know you're not going to be able to loosen it in 5 or 10 or 15 minutes.
Don't make it super tight, but don't make it just topical either.
You should wrap it pretty firmly.
One thing that I tell people to do, if it's on the finger, start, definitely wrap where the cut or the bruise is and then start making it tight from the tip of the finger back towards the heart so you're not trapping fluid.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, depending on how tight you make it is when you can address the dressing again to redo it, to let it out.
Now, if you're doing this from a therapeutic point of view, let's say you're working in an emergency room or a surgeon, obviously you need to do the best, so you would have someone after surgery and after a procedure make it very tight, and then they would loosen it slightly.
You would have a type of bandage that you can do that, right?
You have Velcro now in various strapping forms and things.
You can do something with elastic cords with loops, right?
Right.
I have simple designs and things that I used to implement and things I can't implement, but I find the best thing to use is paper towel and electrical tape because electrical tape is pretty flexible.
You could really stretch it if you pull on it, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And it's cheap, and it's easy to stick in a tool bag or in a drawer somewhere, in a glove box, in a book bag, in a purse.
When I meet people, if I know someone for more than a year or two, after a while they always end up having a roll of electrical tape in the kitchen drawer, in the car, bedroom, and paper towels or toilet paper or anything.
You don't want to put the tape on directly on the skin.
Mm-hmm.
Because it will pull it, as you'll do the opposite, as you undo it, the tape pulls the skin open.
Right.
So that's the essentials of addressing.
It's very simple.
The lymphatic system is very simple, but it's almost too simple.
They used to discount ancient Greek medicine because they would just translate some of the writings as the Greeks said, the fluid moves through the body like a wave in the water.
And they're like, oh, this is bullshit because we know there are blood vessels that moves the blood.
They weren't talking about the blood.
They were speaking of the lymphatic system.
Right.
Oh.
So you have nodes and glands throughout the body, and it's very slow moving.
It's obviously going to be better in athletic people in most cases, unless they're predestined to not have it.
Predisposed, yeah.
Predisposed, yes.
And there's sort of like a pseudo-therapeutic stuff about using a trampoline.
Yeah.
I read about that, yeah.
Some people find it to be good.
I don't personally.
I don't do it.
I would suggest that deep breathing and learning how to breathe and avoid locking out your joints would be the best way.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the opposite of plumbing.
A plumber would tell you the more bends you have, the less the flow.
You want a straight run.
Right.
The body's the opposite.
You know how people stand all day and they have their knees locked?
Obviously, how else are you going to stand?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, that cuts off the flow.
In Tai Chi or Qigong, certain Asian practices.
Qigong, yeah, I remember that.
In Pankratio, in the European ones in the Middle East, their poses were always with a slight bend in the joint.
Now, if someone is standing most of the time, you have to train yourself to stand with a slight bend in the joint.
Don't stack your skeleton.
In other words, don't.
Right, right.
Bend the knee slightly and you feel like it's going to start burning your quads after a while and your leg muscles because you're not used to that.
Well, that is actually allowing the lymphatic fluid to move.
Another thing you can do is lay down on the couch, put your feet up on the back, higher than your head.
Right.
Lay down flat on the – near a bed or a couch and put your – bend your knees and put your feet up higher, elevation.
There is something called a declination board.
You strap yourself to it or whatever and you do a decline.
Yeah, you're upside down kind of.
Right.
Some people, when they hang upside down, their face turns flush and they feel like their head is going to explode like a pressurized balloon or something.
That's lymphatic, not blood.
You see?
Interesting.
A salt bath, temperature differences when you're relaxed.
If you're relaxed and you have a room temperature bath or slightly warm, make it hot and then cool it down in a bath when you're relaxed.
It's interesting.
I found that the most therapeutic lymphatic movements when you're doing lymphatic therapy happen when you are in a relaxed state, not jumping on a trampoline or what have you.
The other way obviously that you're going to get a lot of lymphatic movement is strictly by movement, which is calisthenic exercises, not necessarily running and jogging, but it's usually the movement of the arms.
Getting out and walking, for God's sakes.
A lot of people don't do that anymore.
But if you walk, swing your arms.
Have you ever seen professional walkers, how they bend the elbows and swing the arms?
Yep.
Like that.
For example, you ever notice how orchestral conductors are very long-lived or lived?
Go look up the longevity of orchestral conductors.
They usually go above 90.
You ever see how they move their arms?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Traffic cops in Italy are very long-lived, even though they're breathing all the pollution.
I tell you, the Tai Chi is nice, too.
Tai Chi and Qi Gong are the best.
Tai Chi would be the best to do, where they focus on the Qi.
The Qi is interlocked.
The life force is interlocked with the lymph fluid.
Just like it is with the blood, but the life is in the blood, the scripture tells us.
Meaning, from a divine point of view, but from a health...
And addressing the lymphatic system, that is like water.
You know, like the tear duct, and when you pop a blister and all that.
That's all lymphatic fluid, right?
Okay.
And the other thing to consider, it's in a gel state in the body.
It's not like liquid when it pours out of the body.
That's interesting.
Once it loses its vacuum state, it goes into a liquid form, where it's in a gel form when it's in the body.
All the water is in a gel form.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
And I've given the...
When you were young, do you remember drinking a lot of water and jumping up and down and figuring jiggling in your stomach?
Yeah, very young.
That only happens for a minute or two, and then it doesn't do it anymore.
Then it's gone.
It's not because it went down the tube like a drain.
It's because it went into a gel state.
Hmm.
You're typing, Sam, really loud.
I'm sorry.
So, the problem with...
I shouldn't say a problem is not a problem, but the lymphatic system, there's not much on it on the rectangle.
Yeah.
But there seems like there is.
Look at everything, but with discernment.
There's something like Shaul or Paul.
I never suggest anyone read the New Testament anyway because it's such a hot mess.
The worst thing you could do is read the writings of Paul.
But Paul talks about things, certain things that people misinterpret.
And if you look at the meaning, it says, because don't do these things because those that are with you lack discernment.
You know, Sam, like where he says about eating meat sacrificed to idols?
Yeah.
Right?
That's an issue of discernment.
Hmm.
You see?
Because meat is meat.
I'll give you an example, the discernment aspect.
I had someone come out and visit me here in the Southwest, and he was into what I was saying years ago.
And I said, listen, it's what they call Woden's Day on the Pope's work schedule in this place called Govinda's.
They have a Vedic buffet, you know, all you can eat.
It's really excellent food, all Vedic.
There's no animal.
It's very well prepared.
And we go over there, and he didn't want to go in there because it turned out it was in a Hindi temple.
But it wasn't in the temple itself.
It was an annex building next to it.
And I'm like, I don't care.
I mean, I'm not going in there to be a Hindi or Hindu.
It's not in their temple.
It's beside it.
Oh, man, I don't know.
I don't want to deal with that pagan stuff.
I was like, all right, whatever.
But, you know, I go in there, and I sit down in a meeting, and they got this one of these morons.
The monks, you know, they're wearing orange, and their head is shaved.
And they've got all these little statuettes all over.
And he's explaining to the patrons, you know, this god does this, and this god does that.
And he's pointing at the statue.
But all the stupid white people are like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It comes up to me, and I let him say it.
I said, you know what?
My god made the wood that you made your god out of.
I'm not offended by these morons, but most of these people are.
I mean, the people, you know, they come out of this Judeo-Christian ethic, right?
And they don't understand.
You see?
Right.
But I won't, if I can avoid going into a hospital, if I can avoid going into a church.
Because these, you know, dead, I don't want to be around dead bodies.
I don't want to be around, you know, a sex temple that's demonic, you know, at a church or something.
I know it sounds a little extreme, but wait until you figure it out, folks, later.
You know, those things are, to me, are pretty extreme.
Because they've also hijacked the biblical text.
When you go to these Hindi idiots, they don't claim to be anything near the biblical text.
They're just a bunch of, you know, elemental morons.
You know what I mean?
It's like, I view them like the hobbits in whatever.
Who's the guy who wrote all that crap?
You know, it's just like some...
Tolkien.
Tolkien, yeah.
They're like leprechauns, man, you know?
But they haven't hijacked, they're not telling you anything about the Ten Commandments and all this and that.
They're misrepresenting all this other stuff.
They don't even know, you know, which way is up.
But neither, you know, you see, their level of evil comes from a more elemental side.
They're just running around like a bunch of idiots.
Where, on the other hand, the Judeo-Christian ethic, they've hijacked something that beckons comprehension, albeit it's outside of the time right now, even still, to a certain point, and the cosmic censorship.
But they should have never messed with that.
You see what I mean?
Right.
It's too high-powered.
And they don't know it.
And that I find to be totally repugnant.
And again, that's a personal thing, you know?
But no, see, I'll still go to like a church party outside if they're offering me something for my benefit.
But I won't go into their sanctuary at all.
I find that's...
Ugh, you know?
I find that to be repugnant.
Or a synagogue into their sanctuary.
Or a mosque.
But if they're having a fair outside or whatever, where they've got falafels and whatever, that's well-prepared, I'll go.
You know?
I'm not going to go into any sanctuaries.
Or I won't go to the morgue.
If I can avoid...
Hospitals are another repugnant thing.
Because from the door where you walk in, that's a bank.
Right there.
Just like a bank.
All the information they're taking is being monetized.
You know?
That's another horrible place.
But anyway, it's really sad.
This is the planet of morons.
And, you know, make the best of it.
I'm going to take a break for a minute or two.
You guys can take on a conversation or something.
Okay.
Well, Sam, what you got?
I'm about out of steam because it's like 6 a.m. here.
Oh, my.
Yeah, we did just blow out two hours just like that again.
Yeah.
My goodness.
Yeah, it goes by quick.
Learned a lot, though.
I think the subject on the Codex was very interesting.
And the books, what was left in.
It always makes the body wonder what was the ultimate purpose of all that.
You know, those little questions.
And my constant question myself is, is this truly the real thing?
You know, just comparing our interlinears one day.
I had about five or six of them up and running.
And just verse by verse, I'd go through on certain areas.
And it was amazing.
Well, you can look at it.
You can look at it, Bruce.
If it's the real thing, it's very simple.
Let's look at the level of claims that are being put there that are unrebutted.
No one else is making a claim.
And also, you know, Scripture tells you itself how it's the real thing, and nothing else comes close to it.
Do you know how it does that?
How does it do that?
Right.
It tells you, but how do you prove it?
Through prophecy.
True, true.
That's the only way you can prove it, is through prophecy.
Because all the revelation is finished.
There ain't going to be no Elijah coming down and setting rocks on fire and whatever, and you still won't believe it.
It will be later on, there's going to be interesting stuff, but you're going to be under great delusion.
The other thing is about the codices and all that.
Yes, when I was early in studying, this is not to discount what Sam is talking about, do you remember the scene in Men in Black, the first movie, when Will Smith decides to go with Kay, and they're going down the elevator, and he says, well, just I want to let you know, I don't want there to be no son here, or no boy, or this or that.
I just want you to know that you picked me, and you recognize the skills.
And then right before the door opens, Kay says, from now on, your skills mean absolutely dick.
Right?
Yeah.
Because no matter how accurate the codex is, or inaccurate, let's say it was pristine, do you understand what's in there?
And the answer to that is no with a capital O, so it doesn't matter.
Yes, if you have the propensity to gain understanding with objectivity, of course you should have the right stuff.
But there are so few people that have that ability to objectify, and to cut through the stuff, and see that it is strictly a message to be comprehended, that right now it still doesn't matter if you have it or not.
That makes sense.
Well, I get emails and messages, I'll say this for the hundredth time in six months, which interlinear is best, Greek?
Which Bible is best?
Which one do you read?
It doesn't matter.
If you don't understand it.
If you don't get the information out of it, it doesn't matter.
I learned this early on when I started studying.
I said, oh, I'm going to learn about scripture, and that's going to be easy.
I just have to find some Bible experts.
They've been doing it for 50 years.
That will be easy.
They've been studying it for 50 years, and they don't understand it.
They could memorize and tell you verse and where something is, and word for word or whatever, but they can't put it together.
Okay, yeah.
So it doesn't matter again.
But does it matter?
Yes, of course it matters.
Good ingredients.
We have a thing here.
It was a pizza company.
Good ingredients make better pizza, right?
Right, yeah.
Of course.
But if you don't even know what a pizza is at all, well, forget it.
It wouldn't make any sense.
Yeah, and for most people that I still see around me, don't understand anything out of it at all.
In context.
Yeah, no, that's understandable.
But as usual, you're talking about society as a whole.
And, you know, personally, not that it necessarily has to matter to the audience.
You know, I could care less about them.
I care about myself.
Well, because, well, of course, however, you need to put on your own oxygen mask first before you help someone else, right?
But if it's already been established that they're unrehabilitatable, then why even bother thinking about putting their mask on at all?
So that's another aspect to it.
But I would suggest that it's so bad right now that the bell curve is – if you objectify who is the cream of the crop of intelligentsia, academia, and those that are aware, I'm telling you, you can't get any lower than that.
And the majority of the people are rotting on the ground.
They're not even worth considering at all.
And if you don't think that's true, look at how your leaders are treating you.
Do you think the leaders of governments and corporations and whatever are treating people like crap because they're just doing it and the gods have nothing to do with it?
No, it's the other way around.
The gods are making them do that.
So the best of the best in society is the low-hanging fruit, ready to touch the ground and be eaten by worms.
The majority of society is just rotten fruit on the ground.
Or they're called downers.
When you're a farmer and you wake up and the animal's dead, you're not supposed to put it in the food chain.
So that's why I'm saying you don't want to really know the truth to a certain degree about humanity at this point.
It's much, much, much worse than you can imagine.
That's what I'm saying.
The miracle for me is that no one has come through your window at night to eat your liver.
That's a miracle.
If you wake up tomorrow, that's a miracle.
And I'm not talking about dying in sleep or whatever from a heart attack or whatever, failure for the soul to continue.
I'm speaking about if you go to sleep tonight anywhere in the world and you wake up tomorrow intact, that is a small miracle if you understand the forces behind humanity right now.
And people are taking that for granted.
I'm not saying be paranoid and whatever.
I'm just saying that's the reality, whether you perceive it or not.
It's better that you don't perceive it.
You went on a mini sort of diatribe against the Hindus and such.
In the past, maybe like five, six years ago, you would mention on round tables and such that the holy writs are actually in agreement, the ones from the major religions.
So either you have a situation where all those writs, in order for them to be in agreement, are coming from benevolent forces, the writs themselves, not the religions, or it is that you have, as is widely propagated, malevolent entities behind the religions that are just pranking everybody.
So which is it?
No, it's very simple.
Whenever I say all the writs are the same, it's for two reasons, and whether I underscore it or emphasize it, maybe I haven't as much as I have been recently.
The reason why all the writs are very similar is because we all came from the same place.
So the legends and traditions and what was spoken through people is the same, because obviously they came from the same location, same place, post-flood, right?
The other reason why they're all the same is because you have a major axial period that happened around the 6th or 7th century B.C. that's earmarked in the Book of Jeremiah to put a Babylonian system in place.
The other reason why they're all the same is because of the great communication between the culture.
The only thing that makes the scripture different is its level of quality.
So when you're reading anything that's considered a holy writ that has to do with the gods, the scripture is the only one that's directly inspired.
Okay, but the ratio of agreement is not 1 to 1 between all of them.
It's probably not even 2 to 1.
Well, the ratio of agreement is where do you want to find things that are in agreement.
In other words, you're going to find more agreement than less agreement.
Like, if you look at most of the stuff that people say about the writs, other than, let's say, the Hindi or whatever, what the people are saying, just like the Buddhists are saying, you won't find in their writs.
It's folklore.
Just like the Christians, when they say, you die, you go to heaven or hell, you won't find that in the writ.
Right, but let's put the religions aside.
So even though there are jokes in the religion, if you look at the writs, for example, in the Hindi writ, it states that all men die, meaning mankind, and then you're brought back and be judged on your works.
That's in agreement with scripture.
The Koran mentions a day of judgment.
Okay, but these are such tiny little verses, and then the other 99%.
But the eschatology of it is the same.
Look, if you have a bus, a plane, and a train, and a car, all going from, let's say, one city to the other, they're all going to the same place.
Well, you're not going to get there the same way.
One is a train, one is a bus, one is a plane, one is a car.
But you're all going to end up at the same place eschatologically, right?
Meaning the meaning of all end things.
Okay, so in broad strokes, they agree with each other.
But on the minutia, they're not there.
Well, no, they're not.
Because even if you look at, for example, what's been done with how the biblical text by itself has been brought down through the ages, let's say, or age is not the same.
Okay.
Just within one text itself.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have had the conversation about the codexes or look at the interlinears or look how this is translated and this is not this way.
So, you know, even within it.
But where all things come from and how things are going to be and how things are all the same, absolutely, without a slight chance of deviation from that.
The deviations happen on the focus.
Like, for example, the level you're going to get more of minor gods and folklore of minor gods in the other texts, right?
In the Hindu texts, right?
But the thing is the same.
You know, they can take animal form and human form and all this and mixture of forms because that's what they do.
They're gods, you know, and you're not to mess with them.
And if you mess with them, well, here's a couple of things, you know, that happened to some people that did.
And you'll notice that in all cases they deal with people of wealth, prominence, or princely ship or principality.
So they're all very similar, very much.
And it's not just broad stroke because if they're all starting at the same place and going to the same place, they're all on the same thing.
Now, obviously, the scientists, and this is another thing that's interesting, and I haven't said this, but maybe I'll paraphrase it.
Scientism itself is a religion, just like psychology, all this stuff.
What's interesting, what most people don't understand, or, you know, unless you have a family member or a spouse or a friend that's a professional scientist.
Now, I don't mean an academic that works in academia, but one that actually performs works.
Whether it's themselves or others, there's always Biblical references that are considered.
They always go back to the Bible to see if what they're working on developing is in the Bible because that is viewed as a head start or it's viewed as something that is way advanced later.
You get it?
So one thing that I haven't discussed is how there's going to be a reckoning between man's science and Biblical science, because right now the Biblical science is still too far ahead of what man can, well, has allowed himself to perceive.
But one thing I wanted to bring up, just from being here in the American Southwest and being around these types for certain types, they're very secular almost to the point where they profess atheism or evolution, but they do know Biblical references regarding the subject matter.
Isn't that interesting?
But they won't go to the Koran or Rig Veda or Mahabharata.
Given that scientism is a religion, is that currently being governed by the goddess religion?
Yeah, of course.
When you look at the mixing up of the genders, that's one of the main things, and gender bending, that's one of the main things that she does.
Does science get involved with that?
Of course.
Chemists, right?
When I started looking at the goddess religion, there were coincidental articles where there was some processing plant near a river and it dropped chemicals in the river and they found that the fish, just a month later downriver, flipped, changed gender.
It only took a month.
Yeah, I've seen that.
And it was interesting, I was explaining this to someone around that time and an article popped up as if it was a sign to me like, you're on the right track, that the goddess religion is with science and it's with the legal system.
Have you ever heard of marriage rights being granted to same...
Who does that?
It's the legal system, isn't it?
Right, but it's overtly displayed in the legal system because of the iconography of the Justicia thing.
I don't see that in science per se.
Where's the Justicia statue in science?
Have you ever heard of Electron?
Electron comes from Electra, doesn't it?
Do you know about the Electra complex?
Yeah.
In mythology.
They're always borrowing all of these terms from various mythological stuff.
Why can't they...
I'm not saying be secular, but if you profess being secular, why don't you do what you say and say what you do?
If you ever look at evolution, if you ever read books on evolution, it's a statistician's nightmare because every other word is if.
You ever notice that?
What if a certain chemical emerged that created a genetic change, and then if this genetic change came...
Do you ever read that stuff?
It's a statistician's nightmare.
It's like, wait, okay, so here we have a one in a quadrillion possibility, and then it actually takes place, like one out of a trillion trillion or a thousand trillion, and here's another one, another thousand trillion out of a trillion chance happening.
What are these guys talking about?
So the chances of any of this evolution stuff, when you look at it statistically, would be a trillion times a trillion times a trillion chance of it happening.
That's how slim it is.
That's why I mean it's a statistician's nightmare, evolution.
And the other thing that it is is they're always using terms like design and create in evolution.
So guess where evolution is stemming from also?
Don't you know that in ancient Egyptian folklore and culture, the pharaoh and other priests used to tell the public that you evolved from slime out of the Nile?
And the pharaoh is your god?
He's the one that made you put your intelligence and all that together?
I mean, what do you think that was?
So anyway, it's quite interesting.
But what's more interesting is there's a dichotomy here,
a diametric opposition perhaps to a diametric aspect to it,
is that as we go into the future and Scripture is being validated,
mankind is going to get to a point where even though he has all this validation and education
about verifying and validating the historic biblical history
and all these other things that exist and are mentioned in Scripture,
he's going to drift away and do things that have never been done in the abominations category.
So it seems like, it's kind of like, this is a metaphor, have you ever heard of the people that are supposed to uphold law and order are the ones that are breaking it the most?
Yeah.
So it seems like the more the people become educated or learn about what's true and correct, they're going to veer off and do what's the absolute worst.
Think about that.
Now, is that Scripture what I just said?
Yeah, it is.
Again.
So violent destruction on the planetary level is looking pretty necessary, isn't it?
Kill them with fire.
Yeah, fire.
Well, it's going to be nature.
Because you know who's really chomping at the bit to unleash whoop-ass on these people on this planet?
It's nature itself.
And the nature in the cosmos as well.
Other than the sinkholes around the Dead Sea, do we see any other evidence of nature being passive-aggressive?
Earthquakes.
Yeah, but you're going to get them in more frequency.
And also space weather, space objects, you're going to get more frequency.
It's going to be commonplace.
So when the two big ones, possibly a third one hit, it's going to be, eh, two billion dead, it's okay, we'll clean it up, we'll be all right.
Where if it happened now, it would pretty much shut down society for a hundred years.
You're going to look at just nature in general rebelling.
The animal attacks are going to be interesting.
A proliferation of species of animals, known species, on levels that we've never seen before.
Non-friendly to mankind.
It was funny, one of the years ago, I would be up with Seth Michael doing a thing on the radio, and I said, well, look for animal attacks.
And it's funny, there was like four articles about a boy walking to school, and a bunch of coyotes come out of nowhere and attack him, right?
So, yeah, nature is just really not having it, I should say.
Nature, when I mean nature, I mean weather as well.
Weather animals, fauna and flora.
But here's the other aspect to it.
You're already in a veritable Garden of Eden compared to the past, right now.
Even with all these little idiots screaming about disaster.
I think there was an article about 15,000 scientists sounding off, warning mankind.
No, no, I think those 15,000 scientists need to be warned.
And they need to be done away with, however you want to do it.
Put them in a zoo, or whatever, or put them on an island by themselves, because they're part of the major problem.
Those scientists are the ones that are telling you that calories affect human food, and blood pressure, and vaccines, and all those little nasty chemicals you see in the food, right?
Those are the guys that are telling you weather is thermodynamic, right, as a cause.
Maybe those guys should be put away, those 15,000 scientists.
Put them on an island or something, or get them out of your society.
That would be a very good start, because at least at that point, you have a void of these morons.
And you can at least say, well, we have a void, and the people coming in might have a chance to have some objectivity.
I wouldn't suggest that they would, but the chance is at least there.
If you have these idiots in position that they are now, you have no chance, you see, of any information.
But that's just a personal comment.
But you can't get rid of them without getting rid of millions of attorneys, and doctors, and professors.
So the situation is just very, very, very bad.
But you have air to breathe.
There's plants that are still growing for vegetation.
There's still availability of relatively clean water, even though it's energetically toxic.
So things are really not that bad from one side.
But from a spiritual side, yeah, they're bad and getting worse.
But gradual.
But you're going to be going into a society that is going to be nearly perfect, perceivably, in the near future.
Yeah.
At least the coming society will give us good stuff, consumerism-wise.
It will be.
Well, it will be beyond consumerism.
It will be attitude also.
Because remember, the validation of all of these ancient things is going to bring rest.
And a lot of careers will be lost, by the way, obviously, at the same time.
But there's always weeds to be picked on farms.
McDonald's or whatever.
But the leadership is what is going to drive the crowd.
The future society is the ultimate Gustave Le Bon in the crowd.
The whole crowd will fall for it.
And I always tell people, just to keep them on their toes, and so will you.
You know, Bruce and Sam and all the listeners, they're going to fall for this deception that's coming.
I always tell everyone, you're going to fall for it.
Why?
Why do I say that with such confidence?
Well, because the Ritz said that even the very most set-apart ones would almost fall for it.
Yeah, so say almost.
Yeah, almost, right?
It doesn't say that they would fall for it.
So are you very set-apart?
Well, like I think you said before, you better know the future.
And if you don't, you better know somebody who does.
So I think I know somebody who does.
But here's the thing.
There's an emotional aspect to this, and you know that there's something called emotional override default in humans, right?
You ever hear about, don't go talk to him, he's a little upset right now.
Wait till he's not so upset, then talk to him.
You hear stuff like that in society all the time, right?
Sure.
Well, the opposite is true.
If you're really happy or into something, you're not going to change someone's perspective either.
So if they're too happy or too sad, it's not a good time.
If you're too early, it's not a good time.
If you're too late, it's not a good time.
Somewhere in between, right?
Right.
Well, we chewed up two and a half hours just like that again, Greek.
All right, let's call it a day or night or wherever you are, and that's enough for now, I think.
Yeah, we did a pretty good job again.
Yeah, I hope something got out a little bit more.
You definitely came across with a lot of material.
Yeah, you know what?
I've heard it all before, though.
You have.
Some of us haven't.
If you haven't, you might want to listen to it again or not.
Okay, let's just call it right here.
Let's not burn up anymore.
Okay, you folks be well.
Good night now.
Bye bye.