More than a lifetime to study or pursue so there's no reason to really pursue
this these sonic events that much especially because there's no support
for it I mean I say no I mean you know even when you go outside and someone
asks you is it windy you're like no the wind is still moving at like two miles
per hour you know right right so there's no support so I'm just kind of like
gonna figure out what else how to spend the rest of my days on this fucked up
planet or fucked up world and in the meantime you know whenever the
opportunity arouses arises come around and put out something that's fine you
know I think so yeah and that's pretty much the whole thing in a nutshell but
the thing is the lack of discernment is just incredible incredible meaning it's
not credible anymore because but but it is let me let me let me give you a
preface because it's the information age right so you're supposed to have a lot
of information but on the other hand when you were in the industrial age were
you in the industrial age no you're either a factory worker or you're bought
their crap right right when you were in the space age did you go to space no not
a bit all this bullshit stuff on TV right right so now you're in the
information age are you getting information yeah no it's all bullshit
you're still people are just uh I did an interview recently which may not get
aired because I kind of laid into the host in a way that they're not used to
politely and this is how do you want to finish off so get knuckle-dragger cream
you know because you drag your knuckles on the ground the whole life so you're
gonna need some cream right and the latest thing I usually say is why bother
you know whenever you do something just think why bother why should I do that
yeah exactly so but on a on a on the on a realistic side you know where people
can use stuff you know maybe we'll continue I just gave you some Greek
thoughts there yeah it looks right on the board Sam's back oh good Sam if you
want to pull them on in hmm he should just hit the green button and be right
on yep that would do her like that yeah hello again hey so maybe I'll recap for
Sam I don't think you got that did you Sam what I was saying I was all yeah
there's no desire for Greek speak so I'm but every so often we'll do these
there might be desire but there's no support there's a reason to do it but
the point is the lack of discernment and the is incredible meaning there's no
credibility you know like when you're in the industrial age you did you how
did the people participate in that while they're either slave like factory workers
or they bought the shitty products that they put out when you're in the space
age did you go to space no where do you see some bullshit agency stuff
Hollywood production your garbage I told you on the moon now you're in the
information age yeah right but you're all dumber than ever and dumb because
you lack the discernment it's kind of like if you don't know how to put a
bucket in water or fill a container it doesn't matter how much abundance of
fluid there is it's not going to happen so yeah the reason I wanted to do the
sonic event was how did I called it on the Skype how to think in 3d remember I
didn't put it down to Bruce but I did for you right so what I mean by 3d is the
three dimensions you know and it's not I don't mean like length width and height
I mean you have the audible you know linguistic communication which most
people fail miserably at communicating then you have the written and then you
have the visual illustrate illustrative which goes in between language because
you know how letters can be pictographic but you know if you show
something in just pictures anyone can get it like the universal symbols versus
a language if you can't read it you can't read it so that you got the verbal
you know the audio and then you know which could also be performance visual
kinesthetic the actual literal written and then you have the just pictures
showing stuff right like what I like about instructions now is when you open
them up I didn't bother reading I just look at the pictures right immediately
and the reason why you go for the pictures is because if it's important
they're going to make an illustration and if there's an illustration it means
that it's important and that's also a trap I call it image training you know
they train people with images both good and bad so you know a good image for
example would be if you're traveling anywhere in the world and you go to an
intersection and you see a red octagon with white writing even if you the
language is foreign to you there's a 99.9 if not a hundred percent chance
that is a what stop sign right so you have various things like that so no the
jagged line looks like a lightning bolt you know whatever is written if it's in
yellow and black and whatever is written underneath it means caution is probably
electrical shock warning right but they've pulled a lot over you know like
for example seals and bat if you could go and look up laws and code seals and
badges have no more effect right is since the 50s this is in the codes all
over the world but and but they still show that you know like here's your
badge you officer let me see your badge right who cares or a seal a court seal
where it doesn't mean anything they still ask for it doesn't have a court
seal so what I was done away with you see so as many aspects to that so I
wanted to talk about the 3d in that way it's like basically a talk about
communication how there is none so you guys hip to that any but anything you
guys on your minds you want to bring up no I'm good with what you're gonna go
with yes yes but I'm just wondering if it's more of if it's about touching on
three disparate concepts within thinking or if it's a methodology for
how to think of the most equal right both and you the only way you could do it is
by example like when a child like Jack Fresco says when you're teaching
children and they come with you as something and it's not as correct as you
know it's not like you what you had shown don't say it's just wrong it's
wrong and it doesn't tell anyone anything but if you tell them if you give them if
they ask you for what's quote-unquote grading or feedback if you evaluate it
based on a whole holy what they did correct and what they did incorrect now
you're telling them more you see but you know again in in these desperate times
usually that's why I say I talk at people I don't have no desire to have
conversations with anyone and what I'm always thinking is yeah I give people a
chance you know scripture says you know it's better to listen than to speak but
taking that you got to keep scripture in context when it you know in scripture
tells you it's better to listen and speak and be short on words that's not
talking about you dumbass pagans all over the world it's talking about people
that within a culture that is trying to be lawful right I always have to keep
that in context right mm-hmm so basically when I have discussions with
people I was like what the what could this person possibly say that makes any
sense and I'm gonna predict nothing and I'm not being pessimistic pessimistic or
optimistic I'm just saying and guess what I'm usually correct like you know
recently I've been I talked to a couple of hosts that do all that ridiculous
alternative media and I'm like you know these people should have their
microphones taken away but that's alright because it's the Internet
anybody can go on you know look at Craigslist right you know it's just so in
other words when you go look at I don't want to mention you know names like
Bocelli effect or Freeman TV or anything like that but you know that's
like going to Craigslist you know every you know or Alex Jones or Pete Cento all
the crap out there AFR or whatever all that crap is just somebody getting a
microphone having internet access that's why I always ask people you have
internet access because believe it or not some people do and don't I mean do
have the ability to and don't care about it anymore and that's actually a fairly
evolved being if you can proceed with your life without it you know what I
mean I mean involved meaning you've unfolded and passed it you know but
basically what's going on people have the misgiving well I should say this way
people have been led down this primrose path if you're old enough if you well
19th century they say that a lot means you're being fooled basically again just
to recap what did you get out of the industrial age nothing what did you get
out of the space age nothing maybe velcro bullshit right what did you get
out of the information age nothing you're not getting anything but this is
what you are getting this is why communication is important I'm going to
ease into the subject overall and we'll get into I'll give some scriptural
examples because the best way to do it is by example you know if you go take
tennis lessons you can do descriptions all you want but once you go out on the
court partner up and then try to implement that description then you're
getting you know now you're getting a handle on really what it is right we're
talking about but if you go back to the aspect of communication and being in the
information age and getting ready for what's coming let me just pose it this
way as a preface how many people have access to the Bible even someone going
to get his dick sucked at a hotel has a Gideon Bible right oops sorry that was
not family our talk is it anyway oh you're good all right they have access
to the Gideon Bible which is still you know King James and all that all right
so you bring up the Antichrist on major TV or movie every yes people in the
audience anywhere you go in the world really to raise their hand if they heard
of this Antichrist figure and most people will raise their hand right now if
most people ask who can give me some details about it very few people raise
their hands but whether everyone does or not is irrelevant the information is
available to everyone right mm-hmm okay so if you can sit down and literally
read and with comprehension what's in let's say regarding the entity let's say
the Antichrist or end times that means that there'll be enough people crying
foul when these things start to happen because most people think what they're
reading is quite obvious you get it so why would the gods hide this in plain
sight and have a whole bunch of people in the end when these things are
happening cry foul and kind of upset the plan a little bit because what you're
reading is not what you think you're reading and I'm not talking about some
stupid astro theology and this means this like purple means red and an
elephant is really a car type stupid shit that you hear out in the world right
I'm talking about getting real and this is where the thinking is really really
lacking now why is it why am I coming up because and saying it this this right
now is because when not now in the next few years and now really but in next few
years you're going to be entering into a realm oh yes where the mixture of two
realms the earthly realm that you're familiar with what's called laws of
nature animals plants air earth people societies cultures with more of an
overt effect of the gods meaning minor imps and demons under the under the
plan of the Most High affecting what's going on there's an old saying that you
know the way you one of the ways men gods deal with men is by making men mad
crazy ok so when you start seeing let's say some notions that you pick up in
scripture about what's coming you have to remember that there are entities
behind that that are going to make that happen right and pushing and provoking
nature but also the one of the purposes let's just dive into scripture for a
moment ok this is just to give an example because let's give the more
juicy stuff up front for example you know they have the Cecil B DeMille movie
a piece of shit movie with Charlton Heston and the Ten Commandments right
well when people read the Bible they say oh this is the part when the Red Sea was
parted and I saw that in the movies and they read it like as if it's just
cruising down the road eating a bowl of cereal you know I've seen people put
makeup on while they're driving or eating while they're driving a car let's say
conveying in a motorized wagon right engine-driven wagon they do all kinds of
shit that's how they read this stuff and by the way when someone says I read the
Bible they're lying and because I've told you before and everyone ever listen
anyone that picks up the Bible starts where Genesis they try to read a few
verses and they don't understand what's going on so they start skipping through
and they eventually when I say they're lying I mean that's 99% of the people
99.99999999 now they skip through the Genesis and they try flipping through
the book and they don't understand they're like oh shit I had there's no
way I'm gonna understand anything in here comprehend it even though I could
read the words so I'll just tell people I read it because the chances that
someone else understands it is very slim I see these jerk offs I assume all the
time and I hear of them oh I'm an atheist yeah I grew up in Catholic Church
I've read the Bible and I know the Bible and I'm that's why I'm an atheist and the guy says yeah
I read the Bible too.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
No, you didn't you see this is just stupidity that you see
So don't fall for that
No, there's very there's only a handful of people that have ever read the scriptures with comprehension that I've ever lived
forget about running into anyone that has
You see and then you have those that are on the brink of actually doing some
Revelatory work and bringing it publicly and they never do because there's no monetization
When I used to speak to people that worked with Ernest L Martin, I said well
Why are you using the Pope's work schedule and the term Christian and the crucifixion even though?
Oh, well, what you say?
Oh because you see well, you're saying Greek that divides people and We don't want to divide people and and no one will buy our materials.
Oh And that was like, oh, I'm out of here You know, I'm out of here.
Take your Ernest L Martin crap and go, you know, so You know, I mean and you see this all the time.
So now After that, I realized that there are a lot of good work has been done, but they're basically undigested pieces of corn in poop So then it was like do I feel like holding my nose and eating fecal matter, you know Sifting through fecal matter to get corn or do I need to do the work on my own?
Efficiently, well, unfortunately, it's a combination of both but lately I've just been doing it mostly on my own based on things that I've been used to finding out.
So back to the Piece of shit moving to call the Ten Commandments people read the scriptures.
Let's say when they get to Exodus 15 and They think they know what they're reading and when you read Exodus 15, I'm not going to read it You could read it on your own.
However, even the piece of shit King James Does tell you That they fell to the bottom Like a stone they fell to the bottom like lead now if they're already walking on the bottom of the Sea of Reeds How could they fall to the bottom when they're already on the bottom?
You know what?
I mean?
Right doesn't make any sense
You know, so little things like that
Very importantly there are scenes that are discussed but then the scene is never really discussed
Based on common how common the scene might be in everyday life or just something very unusual and
The actual sentiment behind it like I'm not going to quote anything here
But just to recall when Moses had spoken to the angel behind the bush that didn't burn remember
There's no burning bush, right?
It was an angel that gave off fire and his fire did not consume consume the bush, right?
There's no burning bush because if that angel was not there the bush would not be burning, right?
But anyway when he comes down after a while with Joshua and to see his wife Sam do you recall what happens an angel is sent an angel of Yahweh to kill Moses right and they're battling right?
Do you remember that one?
Yeah Yeah, well why it was why isn't that depicted or discussed and doesn't support his wife circumcised I Think their child or there's a circumcision that happens and she throws a foreskin at Moses and the angel.
Do you remember?
Yeah so Why are these things overlooked?
Do you know how many when you bring up the scene of Having a discussion and given orders by an angel whose fire does not consume the bush and after it's like boom all of a sudden They have to skip to Pharaoh Why why is that detail left out?
Because they're not reading the scriptures.
They're looking at the movie You see here's another point.
I don't need to get over the there's no crucifixion right because you guys are familiar with the verses that Pontius Pilate washes his hands and Returns the Christ back to the Judean authorities, right?
And there's a little bit of a controversy about that, but they do successively achieve a mosaic execution, right?
Mm-hmm, right Right, so I don't need to go into that and that's where the image training is That's why I keep saying why do they put this guy nailed to a cross wearing a long-haired freak wearing a diaper on a crucifix?
showed to you, which is a sclepius and Someone recently was talking about.
Oh, that's Mithra It's like no.
Well, no Mithra is different if you look up a sclepius, so there's actually another one I can't remember his name starts with an N It's an Egyptian Greek God of health and if you could look up the busts it looks just exactly like the JES Character that they show everyone today.
That's why when you ever hear in Christian circles, they always say God bless you
They use that term a lot
That is not a biblical term that is at all actually we don't even find that in Scripture those words put together
Elohim bless you or anything like that
My correct, you know if meditate on that you'll see that comes from the turn that from the cult of a sclepius
Because they're into health and all that and the gods, you know, so
Very very interesting so
Yeah, I popped a wiki into the chat about a sclepius
Okay, and there's another one starts with an N.
It was a there are actually several other minor ones that sprung up They kept springing up until the third or fourth century AD Constantly these health just like today when you're on the stupid rectangle aren't there is health gurus always popping up They're obsessed with it.
Okay, and and you ask them how the body works and they can't All right.
Let's go to another one.
For example You know when the Christ I don't like discussing New Testament stuff because just way out of league It's like discussing PhD nuclear physics or something as a metaphor in public It's just not a subject you discuss in public, but let's let's jump in there for a moment I believe it's in the book of Matthew.
It's recounted in Mark and other places as well When the Christ goes on a field trip and he's being followed And trolled by the Pharisees all the way up now.
Most people think it's Jerusalem because it says the Pharisees from Jerusalem He's all the way up like north of Galilee In like Caesarea area like up to where the old Naphtali and Dan Tribes would have been you know, like the northern part of Israel and The he's apparently revealed this is the first time he Affirms who he is to Shimon Shimon bar Jonah, which is Simon Peter, right?
He's made son of Jonah, right?
He says who do you say I am and he says you are the Christ is well No, man could have ever seen is you know gotten that information unless it was given to him, you know external input wink-wink, right?
and Then he says that on this rock Now we don't you know, we don't know most people think it's Peter, but it doesn't just on this rock Okay, what rock?
Why would he bring up a rock because the Ecclesia the church is the Ecclesia just means those that are called out Just a group of people is Where I will build My Ecclesia and the gates of hell will not prevail against it, right?
And that sounds really like romantic or it sounds like in a religious from religious
Religiosity point of view it sounds like a strong affirmation of good versus bad, you know
Oh like, you know, like Darth Vader won't prevail with a Death Star, you know kind of stuff like that
This is how people take it
But if you actually look that they had traveled up to the northern parts of Israel
right
Because prior to that there's discussion with the Pharisees which came from Jerusalem not in Jerusalem
But if you understand that that location that were the setting that they were in there is an actual pagan temple
Called the gates of hell.
It was to Zeus and to Bacchus and They had a little Theater in there as well, and it was carved in rock very impressive.
Are you guys familiar with this?
I'm not Why don't you either one of you Google in gates of hell or gate of hell temple, northern Israel And it's right by it's like What would be the old area of Dan or it would be?
Like north of Galilee what you called?
Copernicum Caesarea, that's where they were by the way.
They did at least a one day's journey boat journey But you put in okay, I got it Temple called the gate of hell, and it's to Bacchus and no it was to pan and to Zeus I believe It was it was a Greek slash Roman inspired Canaanites it was it was like modern Christian is everything mixed in right it was like Christmas Easter everything thrown in it's carved in the rock It's quite impressive.
There's some buildings and platforms up up against there.
I'm going off of memory Do you guys are you finding anything on the rectangle about that?
Yeah?
I got it right now I've got a couple of it a little bit of wiki And some reading material Right that was impressive looking piece of work though.
Holy smokes
Yes, that was like when Scientology first came out or the asked remember in the 70s and 80s a lot of people were talking about
Yes
Well it came out before that
but it was popular well during the time of the Christ this cult of Zeus and the cult of pan and the cult of
Bacchus and the cult of
Diana and the cult there was a major major
How many times you ever heard me through the years the first century especially the time of Christ in Israel?
There was a major resurgence of spirituality like just fads everywhere like look at how much the clothing changed between
The entire 19th century not very much, but look at how it changed between the 50s 60s 70s and 80s
You see what I mean like rapid change rapid fashion trends major trends
Okay, that was what was going on during the first century
During that time and they were north enough
and if you look at way if you were to peg that on a map the gate of hell or the gates of hell of
Hades really hadios
The pilon to an adios, I think it was what it was called in Greek
You would and if you read it in Greek by the way when you see pilon de adios, oh, that's a city
That's a place.
That's not a metaphor.
That's that's the beauty of being able to use the other languages, but
When you go and look at that area that is in the northern part of Israel
I would say it's north of the Sea of Galilee
Maybe half a day's walk from the sea northern coast of Sea of Galilee right up in the area of Dan
the ancient part
not too far from
Yeah, I believe also if you study in the text in the text
Then that the Christ is in the area of Sidon and Tyre also
Which would have been a date more than a day's walk?
If you go to Matthew I think it's like Matthew 14 or 18 or something like that in the middle of the book of Matthew that's recounted in other places He's up in the Lebanon.
This is when he meets the Canaanite woman, I believe also You see okay, so basically I don't okay I had to give a little more detail when when you hear something like yeah, you're you're the one I'm gonna build my group on Groupons, and I hear the place that discounts tickets and stuff.
No
The mob basically he's telling me when I create this mob
The this temple this religion will not prevail against it, you know what I mean
But it did it did prevail at the time see so that was one of the things that must have confused his followers
Because he said it would they wouldn't prevail but they but how many people read the gates of hell like oh that sounds like poetic and
An inflamed poetic metaphor there, you know, like oh the evil, you know, cuz gates of hell doesn't sound good or evil sounds evil
Okay, that's just like saying the evil will not prevail against it
Do you see what I'm do you see what I'm talking about thinking in 3d, right?
So would you read when you read scripture you see gates of hell is it like just you know Good and evil or some poetic use of metaphor or could there actually be a place called the gates of hell?
And if we actually look at the setting the chances are that he was standing in front of that area.
It's like 99 Percent that he was because it already says he was right in that area, right?
Mm-hmm.
So this is what I mean about thinking in 3d and that you don't allow yourself to be a slave to image training Yeah, because when you see something with her example, it says in the gates of hell will Not will not prevail against it.
You think that is Wow.
What a beautiful, you know rhetoric, you know or metaphor, you know
Words being used it makes me feel a certain way, but you don't stop and think and say well
Maybe that's because the gates of hell is an actual physical real thing
You see
Just like when you read in Exodus 15, well, you know, they sank to the bottom like a stone they sank to the bottom like lead
Well, duh, if they're already walking on the bottom and the waters fell on top of them
Why would that be an issue and why would it also be an issue that it was when the Sun came out that they made?
pursuit right Now what you see It's a good way of detecting things too because like in our own society white is black black is white and They would do the same thing in the book.
Yeah Yes, but don't fall for the flowery terms Like if I said to you we're gonna do this right and the gates of hell will not prevail against it You're like wow Greek.
Yeah, it sounds good Right heavy image Yeah, but you do did you did I didn't tell you the gates of hell was it was actually a real place yeah, yeah Well place based on a religion right of Zeus and Pan and Bacchus and No, Mithra yet in that.
Hmm.
Is it is it overt why this particular place was significant?
Yes, because it was the it was like the Esther Scientology of the 70s.
I remember in the 1970s In the 80s every other person I met that seemed well-educated pulled me over to the site Have you ever heard of Dianetics L.
Ron Hubbard?
I'm like no, but after a while.
I was like, yes You know, you're like the fifth person this month.
That's talking to me about they even had TV commercials on Dianetics Do you remember that Bruce?
No, no, nobody.
I remember the Scientology Increase it's called Dianetics was this book?
Yeah And then there was Yeah, there's Dianetics late at night in the 70s and 80s Dianetics get L.
Ron Hubbard's book You know, okay, it was way of getting it in your face.
You know, this was a promoted a heavily promoted thing going on at the time
But this was a time of great change which took you know a full generation to take place
Whenever you have these ages that go in two thousand year chunks, that's another thing
There's this this there's the actual timekeeping aspect of a thousand years and there's the actual cultural traditional aspect of
2,000 years and there's the generational change the small generation
Which is the physical one and then the great generations which could be 70 or 220 years old as we see with the Patriarchs
And then there's these major changes that happen, you know, but the law doesn't change it's just that
The you know
the the culture or what's allowed to to
to happen changes
The law just sits there what I mean by the law is like, you know, what's right and wrong, right?
That just sits there unknown Here's another example, you know, you ever noticed throughout Scripture the thing to do is to walk on water the Christ walked on water They walked on water crossing the Jordan they walked on water In Exodus, oh But here comes who's the greatest prophet according to the Christ John the Baptist Right, and what does he do now?
You're no longer walking on water now You're being dunked and submersing under the water.
You notice big change Big change how come nobody's talking about that?
Hmm what's the change that took place?
Throughout scripture.
It's the prominent thing when it comes to water is to walk on it Like it's like as if it's land and now all of a sudden the greatest prophet that comes according to Christ He puts you underwater hmm There's a whole bunch of stuff to discuss about that.
I'm still working on put it doing a presentation on that I haven't thought about that in years.
I started thinking about it a few weeks ago
So and this very significant
Scriptural references to that
but nonetheless
If you look at we gave a couple of scriptural examples here, there's a lot of examples that I've given recently
Regarding other aspects which are actually more important to the body
Like if you don't know how the body works, it does scripture doesn't matter
You're not gonna have an angel walking into the room and tell in reading it to you like a bedtime story
So if you're in a total physical wreck forget about scripture, you're probably not you know what I mean
You're probably gonna have to wait for the resurrection, right?
So I Give a lot of references where I bring up if anyone wants to bring up Go to the rectangle and put in cross-section of the intestines Epithelial cell or the lumina which is the general thing if you look at a close-up nothing get goes through that right at all You can see it's totally closed off the same with the alveoli and the lungs and all that, right?
It's completely sealed.
There's no absorption
It's all induction
right, so
So on one side you're being told absorption absorption absorption, but do you does anyone ever stop and think and say well
Where what are they discussing the intestines, you know, it's very easy for me to access what the intestines look like
Let me go look at that
And when they look at that how many people raise their hand and say shit man, nothing goes through that
That's totally that's like a steel belted radial tire.
Nothing goes through that How many people have done that That you've heard of none Right, you know why because it's the information age just like During the space age you say how many of y'all suckers have gone up into space?
How many of you how many people raise their hand?
none So it's the same metaphor as being dunked underwater as far as information Yeah, you could then you start doing like what I was explaining to someone recently It might have even been Sam recently as well.
But this I was a little stronger with this other Individual I was basically saying just go to Scripture and start putting together, you know when the term comes up and find out statistically where how it's being used So when you talk about the water What and what other ways is water, you know?
Like in during Noah's time, you know, what was on the water and everyone else and everything else went where?
underneath the water Right, and there are references to Noah's time right, there are references to Don't don't be concerned about harm to the body.
It's the harm to the spirit Right, right you come out of water, right the the water is a neuter thing.
It's a neutral thing You know in in Genesis it There's creation and then there's the remodeling but there's no mention There's mention of light being created and being good There's other things but there's no mention of water being made is there or there's no mention of the water being good or bad Is there in Genesis right at all?
So when when you see walking on top and going under now you go under it as a rite of passage now It's not the water that's important.
It's the motion and who and what is going over or under
right
Because it's not mentioned as being any aspect that's relevant to itself
like the light is being you know was made and it was good, which is
a
Another discussion, which I want to
Bring the future perhaps in private discuss light a little bit more because you know
If you don't have a physical body
You can't see light the way we do the gods don't see light like we do
Because they don't have a physical eye everything that you see and call light is because you have that wet juicy round eyeball
Unless you have a wet juicy round eyeball in your head
That's functioning as according to as we know eyeball should function.
You don't see light the way we discuss light So it's a completely different thing from that respect Now I'm not saying that the gods can't put themselves to have a round juicy eyeball that works or an angel But it's not what I'm talking about.
Of course, they can do that.
But this is not the light that we discuss
so
very other aspects
You know keep coming up in communication
Or lack thereof, I think the best way to I think we haven't been on very long
but I think I
The the metaphors I gave regarding the lack of communication and the lack of perception
Using scriptural references, especially to this crowd is I think it hits you between the between the eyes pretty good, right?
I Mean, I think food for thought for a lot of people.
I mean, there's also the aspect of
when you say that these are things that perhaps people are not considering as far as the obvious nature of of
how certain things in the biblical text are
Brought up and people prefer to allegorize or use them as poetic metaphor
There are a million things that could be considered at any one given
particular
Point in time
So the fact that people aren't able to pick up on what these things actually mean even just from an observational or common-sense
Perspective that has as much to do with how their perception is being steered as anything
It's not necessarily that somebody's a moron or that they're stupid
But if their perceptions being pushed in someone somewhere else, there's no hope for them in a certain way
Well, they're in a moronic state and they're in a stupid state
Yeah, it's very hard to really say someone is
Definitely a moron or stupid, you know, you might they might be in that state long enough that you no longer want to be around
that person
You get it
like
I'll just I'll say that I haven't said this before probably I'll say it once I've been around people
That I thought were in a moronic and stupid state and later on I see the
Wikipedia pages on them and I see them on high government position and high positions in industry.
I Know that doesn't mean much because we all know how things work, but you see what I mean So that doesn't mean that It doesn't mean other anything other than an observation also being moronic Dubbing someone as moronic or stupid in that state Is it possible to be in a moronic and stupid state from your young adolescence to the day you die?
I don't know of course So but that still doesn't make that person moronic and stupid at the resurrection does it?
You know, so well actually yes Some cases they are going to be making some very bad decisions based on lack of inquiry and lack of knowledge But still it is a condition.
It is not them but yeah, what what I see happening that Again, I you know in the end.
What did you get out of the industrial age or your forefathers?
What did you get out of the space age or your forefathers?
What are you getting out of the information age?
right So and then again, you're trained at your based on your culture You know does it bother you go to a society of headhunters?
You ask one of them one if they invite you over
Does it bother you they have five shrunken heads, and he says yes, it does as a matter of fact my brother has 20
It's their product of their culture look at what's going on here
In this it is firmly in place you know
Yeah, but that's not
What I'd like to discuss this thing on the topic is the 3d how to think in 3d
which is the literal you know the the symbology of the alpha of the the language that you are versed in or fluent in and
Then you have the the vocal part.
You know radio music.
I think a lot of people are affected by songs and lyrics and
Just verbal communication, and then you have the pictography or the imagery the iconography
All right, and those three, that's what I mean how to think in 3d, and you always you have to go
you know three-way on that like
You bring up the intestines or you know we turn on the in the middle part linguistically is saying
Oh this buy this because it absorbs better
You need to detox to absorb you know better right clean yourself out the list other so you absorb better
okay, then you have the pictography where you go look at the
Anatomical drawing a detailed anatomical drawing and you see there's no physical way anything can physically be absorbed and then you actually go
To anything in and you know what they write in the medical anatomy books about the intestines absorbing
They give you a list of all the various
Cell names and areas of the intestine that they've identified
You know using whatever language, and then they say therefore the intestines must absorb in the anatomy
But you look at what they're showing you that it must be absorbing and it's physically impossible that anything goes through there as a matter of fact
many older cultures absolutely rely on no absorption on these organs in order for them to use the
These organs as water carrying and liquid carrying vessels they actually rely on their lack of porosity
you see
To be water carrying vessels some cultures.
You know like you know soccer balls and football those things originally made from organs, right they use Water gliders and things water bladders.
Yes.
Thank you.
Okay, so they actually rely on those things to not be
You see permeable
So you have the three aspects the middle aspect is absorption you hear that all the time
Then the primary written would be the anatomical books
They they list the description of the of the features of the organ
But and then they tell you because of all these features it must absorb
All right, and then you go to the pictorial and you see that it's physically impossible
All right, and the same thing with with
By the way has anyone?
I'm not good You do it on your own time does anyone within let's see earshot have an unabridged King James Bible or an unabridged Bible, you know what?
I mean by unabridged It's it's like a larger book and it has the full introduction in it before it gets to the book I think I do and I think it's in a box stored away somewhere good But if has anyone right?
this is a rhetorical question read the introduction to the King James Bible or any Bible you have the introduction and Usually some abridged versions have them.
That's why they call it a bridge by the way The reason why you're reading it the way you're reading it, right and I years ago I told someone I said go read the interest Oh, yeah, I have it right here.
It's about eight pages long You know the the introduction to the King James Bible how they kick why you know, why it's called King James, but the premise.
Yeah And after you read that do you still want to read that no, there's no way yeah, they're telling you what they're doing Even the Somewhere used to be on their website the scriptures the guys that publish out of South Africa they even At some points made exceptions.
Yeah, we're trying to be as close as possible
But for you know printing and my whatever they say monetary, but you know for reasons we have to retain this particular format
You know, it's which is King James, you know
so
They have a slightly different
Arrangement they've pretty much put most of the books in the right order except for Daniel
but nonetheless
the discussing the 3d
Aspect is going to make some people spend more energy on
How they interact with themselves and others and yes, you do interact with yourself
But he'd give you an example because you have a conscious.
I'm presuming most people have a conscious a conscious You're in this physical container this physical body.
It's very lonely.
I was actually The metaphor was done about this recently, it's very very lonely To be in the body that you are because you know, let's show around people who are telepathic and even then it's not a full-on stream Even with the gods, it's not a full-on stream Right.
I mean there are individuals that I'm sure have had a full-on scream aka the Christ right Imagine being born with full knowledge, you know when it was time, right?
So
But to go to the point where we consider ourselves
It's extremely lonely like people who cannot let's say people who are functionally literate and sound like they're educated
But who cannot communicate well are very lonely people
All right
One of the things about having a best mate or best friend or a wife or a husband or something is being able you don't
Say share your soul with them, you know and being you know, even then if you don't communicate, well, you're still gonna feel alone
And they'll bury his ideas off, you know, yes and communicate just the hardcore communication
Now which means just you know, my thought to your mind and your thoughts to my mind
right
so
The human body the way we're made with the self-contained consciousness is a very lonely place
Very very lonely to be in
So once we know we get used to it being alone within ourselves in our minds, right and
The spirit, you know being in the container is you know, and unless it's expressed
You're you're pretty much you remains with you
The lack of communication I think goes hand in hand with the lack of perception and vice versa and discernment
right
So but here's the thing again
No matter how much talk of industry there is back in the day
all you saw was the skies being polluted this nasty smell in the air a
Lot of cheap goods being available and a lot of people bitching and whining about they don't like their work
So what'd you get out of it?
Then there's all this space-age talk from when did you say the space-age started Bruce for sure in the early 60s?
Yeah, the 70s.
Yeah, right in the 50s.
They're already hitting everybody with it They were preparing all the Russians and Sputnik and all that Then yeah, then you had the introduction yeah a few little test runs There's a YouTube video of a woman in 1960 or 61 Riyadh burning up entering into the atmosphere from a Russian cosmonaut She's a woman and a guy a bunch of guys ham operators in Italy recorded it She's talking about that.
She's been yeah, so the So But what did you get out of the space program?
Nothing?
We got Velcro Yeah, you know nothing basically.
Yeah, what are you getting out of the information is what I'm saying nothing Many times I've said the Internet or all this communication stuff is a beta test, right?
It's a mic test until later on so it's part of one of the devices things are going to be used to unite mankind You know with audio and video But you know here's an example like recently I was looking at a few things and this popped up at me about internet privacy and Like recently a couple got upset about Amazon Alexa because it recorded and send a conversation, right?
I saw that on the home page And you know, it's really stupid like if you somewhat doesn't invent a guy speak to does design work well, but he says I got this Alexa says some stupid-ass nigga technology and And and I said if you sent me one of those things I'd Wouldn't even open it will go right to the curve.
Anybody watch the boondocks, by the way No, no, that's Alex McGruder.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's where I got it from but the the nigga technology, but
Just means if you can't connect the printer to it, but now anything goes by printer because of Wi-Fi, but here's the interesting point
If you look at all these privacy and anti privacy statements
What these companies say is your privacy is very important to us now most people they're not they're telling you the truth
Most people take it in a sympathetic point of view that you know, oh that means they're not going to invade it
No when these companies tell you they're your privacy is very important to us
That's because they're harvesting it and monetizing it and the more private it is the more monetization they get you see
They're actually telling you the truth
But most people don't take it that way
Most people say oh, they said my my privacy is important to them.
It means they're protecting it.
No, they never said they're protecting Right Get it Yeah Yeah, if you ask a thief right before he breaks Into your house, he'll tell you your door locks are very important to me of course Right, right Yeah, like a rapist, you know, your ass is real important to me, right Anyway, you see my point.
Yeah in front of you.
I was like, oh man
Now I think giving examples of discernment on that is important as well, but I would suggest that
If you take one aspect of it alone, it could be of overbearing aspect like for example
I've like the crucifix the whole, you know guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper the long-haired guy know that
Okay, I've spoken to people that has studied scripture all their lives and when I brought that up, they're like, huh?
What what?
And I'm like, yeah, go let's go over it again You see because for them that image overpowered their ability to discern what was happening What was written?
I Mean doesn't it say that the Christ would lived and died according to what?
the laws of Moses Isn't there a verse that says that or am I imagining it?
but anyway
So there's another that's a direct
Right
So the idea is that between the pictorial the linguistic and the
The oral things should harmonize in a way that if they don't
Check well cross-referencing all three
Now when all three are easily in concordant, you know across the board you you got some good information
validation verification
but when it's not concordant like when they show you the guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper and then you read scripture and
then you
See what people are talking about
Well, the image and what people are talking about is very strong seems concrete when you read the text
That's also very concrete, but it somehow has taken the backseat
Just like that an example with that would be the gates of hell should not prevail
Prevail against it because when you're giving a good versus bad scenario and you say well
The gates of hell will not prevail against it.
That sounds like some really well chosen words for some rhetoric right or rhetorical statement something that go should you know be something that will imply a Sympathetic response to don't be afraid of the evil, right?
You see so you so how much do you?
You know, it's just it's just like people so what version what do you read Greek was it?
I read all of them I got to know all of them You got to know all of it, sorry You know, I mean how many times have we brought up?
Well, what do we read?
Will you read which one do we which interlinear which version which by all of it?
Why?
Let's say you only know the interlinear or the Hebrew and the Greek How are you gonna have a conversation with someone who is genuinely willing to expand their reference?
That only knows the King James as a reference.
How are you gonna have a conversation?
Very difficult, and if you just know the King James you cannot discuss Anything with someone who knows the interlinear or all the mistakes were made in the versions, right?
So yeah, unfortunately you have to do all of it The scam is is large because it's an adversarial See most people think evil is this coming in destroying?
Yeah, that that's to me.
That's not more.
That's not evil I was trying to tell someone in an interview saying all Greeks gonna talk about the failure.
I'm like no Talking about the cleanup You know when you see the destruction that you read about in Scripture that is not the failure That is the cleanup point because it if it had not failed it would need to be cleaned up.
You see what I mean?
right
The failure of what the failure of morality the failure of law the failure of good
the failure of you know good intent and
Then the cleanup crew comes in because your people are given chances
To you know restore that quote-unquote sin which means missing the mark or failure
And if not, then you have the overt cleanup crew
So
so the aspect about the 3d the combination of all three is
heard someone say he's trying to make a
Saying like what the public knows is not true, and what is true the public does not know
Right so what is truth the public does not know and what the public thinks is true is not true at all
Now that's a really good thing to lean on
I think I've given here's another one where I use the 3d
Communication perception when I go into the shops into commerce
You know I need a particularly knuckle-dragging lotion for someone right and I go to the health food store
And I say what do you have knuckle-dragging lotion?
She goes yes, so well He's got four five six ten of them series which one is the best because this is the one that everybody buys and immediately I say well, that's the one that I don't want And she goes why I said well having you met what you call everybody your average customer How the hell would they you see what I mean?
So that's a really good thing to lean on Very often you see in marketing and Bruce in America.
You'll see this is our mother this sold you know 10 million sold Wow You're right.
That's why you get right to
No, that's why you should never buy one
No not on that merit alone, but be cautious not I mean outward you know fatalistic rejection
right
so
But yeah be considerate of that
So why am I why did I call for to do a stream on this now is because you're coming up on a time
Here, especially the midpoint which would be the 2021
Time period is summer where there is going to be more of an overt spiritual like this shit shouldn't be happening
You know what I mean?
Okay, it's bad shit.
That's gonna be normal like you know animal attacks natural disasters Diseases wars people acting unusually those things always seem to be around but through their frequency is going to be in an odd way Well you in other words.
Can you perceive?
The answer is yes of course you're asking can you perceive like when bad things happen or strange events
But can you excuse me can you perceive that they're so strange as it excuse me and so out of the norm
That it's it's if you had the right glasses you can actually see an entity coming and forming it to be so I mean overtly
You know there's an entity behind everything, but it's going to come to a more overt point
Where the reason why it'll be like that is so you're willing to accept what comes after that when the you know after the?
2025 period comes around
so be cautious of how these things are described and
The way they're going to be talked about and the way they're going to be shown is going to be different what it was written about it
The paranormal you know which is that's an interesting term right yeah, that's what I'm talking about
You know so oh
Other examples are
Anything you see in film or television or university school all that that is an example of that the vagueness
That's taken as as writ
How many times you seen on TV authority say that this guy blah blah blah okay?
Well hold on hold on or?
You know Korea said hold on how the hell can Korea talk?
What are you talking about?
Can I meet mr..
Korea you know?
What authorities what are you talking about?
That's already been going on for a very long time and everyone has settled into it When you hear stuff like that?
Oh, that's like tons of shit is B.
That's pure propaganda How many times you heard says the Russia said that the president Putin whatever will be doing this okay?
Ho ho hold on hold on that's pure propaganda See a court document the state of Illinois state of Massachusetts United States a fictional versus a you know plain Defendant pure fix that's attorneys getting or we can't do that.
It's completely illegal.
Also.
That's called a fictional plaintiff And that's happening up by the millions every day easily easily yes Can't fictional plaintiff is illegal and unlawful go look it up It's passing through so in other words Yeah, the mop-up is the only thing that could fix it Which is an oxymoron because if it has to be mopped up, or you know completely demolished.
It's not fixing it right well The miners talk about that either fix it or blow it up That's what they say the miners right, and I'm not joking you know once Yeah, like if they have a crowbar In a crowbar which dynamite they put it you know if they know the next demolition charge is gonna go off They just pile the stuff there, so it'll just turn to dust anyway.
You know they don't have to haul it off, right?
Yeah, yeah So should I keep going I don't have anything else really in mind.
It was just to bring up the
Unless you guys have any questions or any questions in chat
I'm outside right now just came inside to make myself a little more Java having a smoke
but
regarding the the combination of the literal description
explanation literal works Ritz
Versus what people are saying and you hear and versus pictures illustrations diagrams
You know like like a blueprint is a combination of both, but but both written and pictorial
But primarily pictorial right a blueprint
Yeah
So to discern all of that now the other thing you're going to hear especially talking to some hosts recently is the level of
Subjectivity is just so ridiculous like I was recently on with Chuck, and he got so subjective
This is not I mean, I like Chuck.
He's done a lot of good work me But so many times I wanted to say all right, so you don't like that so do you like ice cream?
You know do you like TV?
You know it's like wow man.
You know the subject and anywhere you go.
I've actually seen various professionals recently medical and Totally subjective again.
Well.
I don't really like this.
I think I'm gonna just prescribe that I'm like whoa whoa whoa What do you mean?
You don't like it?
And people just sit there, okay?
like whoa This subject subjectivity is just it's just rotten to the core you know opinions the Opinions are like assholes.
They say but only assholes go on opinions alone You know the Supreme Court.
What do they give?
What are the judges give they do they talk about verdicts in law?
No, no opinions opinions.
Yeah
So yeah, that is a very strong fate a chronic disease terminal disease is opinion
very very bad from any point of view I
Want to get all the people that are based off on opinions put them on a boat put a big hole in the boat and
Then ask them what their opinion is
Well, it's like this psychological stench has been on us so long
It's it's you're almost acclimated to it
Quite well the headhunters great, so
We got nothing left left to it to do except for just express it in different ways
The subjectivity would be a fine example I
Know it's been a while.
Oh go ahead good
No, I say you said subjectivity, but you might want to be subjective with certain things like scripture
Come into it with a subjective notion that you can't take anything that's being said there for granted
You're gonna literally have to bring up everything
So that's a subjective point of view by looking at everything in there
I think I gave a couple of examples or one strong one tonight with the gates very very fine example.
Yes Yes, I Gotta personally say I glossed right over that one Mm-hmm You took it as a literal sympathy literal visual clue You know It's kind of like the pep talk in Star Wars before they go to fight the Darth Vader, right?
Right, that's how you tell the coach at the basketball game or right, right, you know It's made you feel good inside, but you did and then you kept going Okay, great, right it provided just a smidge of curiosity Yeah, what are the gates of hell no not enough to act on it.
No, not enough.
No, but now Well, how much you know that's again people ask what are you really all of it Everything that's out there But obviously when you discern something as being garbage and validate it and verify it to be such Do you dwell on it more than something that has a greater value?
No, just but you still have to be familiar with it You got to give it equal representation in search in a qualitative form and in the Time you you spend on it should be Reflect the quality right exactly or quality more quality more quantity.
It's a friend look less lower quality
I
Still have discussions frequently not much about the historicity of Genesis, you know
The scriptures is very his even, you know, there's a lot of historicity, you know
In other words the stuff in the beginning of the book takes precedent in time before the stuff at the end of the book
You know when you when you look at what's been ensued about who has penned
Chronicles Joshua Kings and all that which all happened
Over a thousand years after or five hundred years.
Let's you know thousand to five hundred years later really five hundred years later done by the courts of Samuel and Eli mostly Samuel Had put all that together because you can when you read the book of Joshua and study it you could see that's done in narrator It's it's second.
It's you know second person.
Yeah second person.
Yeah, and
And their quotes in there as well
Like for example
one of the time
Timely quotes and there's a basher the book of upright when that was that was penned around the time when these were compiled
But even they have historicity
Right, so how can you have man-created male and female and their job is to in Genesis the sixth day
Their their task is
They're out on the they're out on the earth
is to
Multiply and be fruitful multiply right like they say in the Old English
Then there's the Sabbath and
Then there's another after the Sabbath after the Sabbath.
They're in the garden now, which is not on the earth Let's say or not the earth at large And they're not created Adam is not created.
He's formed By himself and his job is not to be fruitful and multiply his job is to what?
Prune the lawn.
Yeah I was gonna always ask you I remember you talking on that before and But there's no other mention of them whatsoever.
And so would they be like to control a controlled study versus
us
Yes
The control and also maybe they in Scripture you'll after a while
One of the things you make note to self is the lower the less character
You're considered to be like the more evil the less mention you get
Right hmm like you'll see in Genesis when the generations you'll see all these sons is that they were wicked, you know, they're not mentioned
real
So the less the gods like you the less they mention you in the writ
But you know overall you have to understand also and this is I've looked at it from my
systemic point of view
But the way the scriptures are compiled there that yes, they do communicate history law prophecy all this other stuff
but they themselves each word in each space between the word and the and the layout of all the words is is
input
In other words, it's a program it's all the bytes and bits to to put into the right hardware or the right
You know configuration or something to animate
You see right, right
Yeah
In other words the words are aligned and everything is set up the way it is because it has more use than just being writ
So
But the historicity of things when you when you look at the historicity of Scripture
Even what you call the New Testament in the very end it falls apart
The very so do you look do you feel that there there is you know, how you always said that there's always a primer for the
code
Mm-hmm.
Do you feel that there's a primer for that?
Yes what you just meant?
Yeah that I will not discuss publicly But I'll give hints for it.
Okay.
All right, it's in the it's in this it's in the Psalms and it's in my goodness All right And now when I say it's in the Psalms That's that should light like you said Oh my goodness, because you know how many things are in the Psalms that are just deftly profound that everyone seems to ignore Not everyone.
Well, yeah, I kind of took it a different way.
I was like, well how ironic you know
Yeah, it's also in Exodus because Exodus was the only time that we had
that much
Interference from the gods
angels gods, you know minor angels cherub
interacting with
People we're talking about a time of 40 years consistently on a daily
You won't find any other time other than what was going on in the the earlier part of Genesis that
The angels
Major and minor were dealing with mankind on a daily basis for 40 years.
Are you with me on that Sam?
Yeah from your recall Yeah, so there was a time in history that 40 years where?
the gods were interacting with millions of people and their leaders and
To the point where they got used to it and there were they did and they were still negligent
right
so
Right
Yeah
But the reason why I say the primer is in Exodus is because at that time
There's at least three or four maybe seven instances I should say
But I know three or four off the top of my head
I could tell you where Moses was directly given orders to do something
Because Yahweh was sending his angel to show him something or to train someone else
Are you with me on that Sam or you remember that?
Yeah.
Yeah, Bruce.
Yep.
Very direct.
He's like listen Moses Okay.
All right.
You got a chill because I'm sending you my My head angel he's gonna show you ABC and D or you got to gather these 70 elders or you got to bring me this guy and I'm gonna show him how to build this and You see Mm-hmm.
So with that heavy interaction
The mode the modus operandi of of things being done a very very very specific way
Yes, not just how they are, you know replicas in heaven, but they were done very specifically, you know
Just like when you send code over the wire, you know, it has to be very specific
Right, and then it's in the Psalms
And now in the Psalms mostly the Davidic Psalms where David the psalmist in this case
was prophesying
Certain aspects of artifacts that were in
Construction during the time of Exodus, right?
And that's your primer
and and the other aspect is
the the
Software engineer would be the Christ
Right, so you have to also the the primer is in what the Christ had said also
All right, but without the Psalms and without what Moses had done the just reading the Christ
You won't get it because even after his resurrection
He was walking with some of his disciples and apostles and they said if you want to know about
Who I am you have to know what Moses?
The Psalms and the prophets not you got to form this new religion with Santa Claus
right or biblical scholar
Bullshit they've been putting in front of you for 2,000 years
Now the the concept here's another thing about the 3d thinking
You know, there was at least several periods in the Old Testament
say thousand-year swaths of time where nothing was going on and people were just
stupid like between let's say Adam and the flood and
After the flood to the Exodus, we're looking at almost 2,000 years a
Little bit under 2,000 years
Basically nothing going on except for Abraham and right
Marie, okay
So is it so or you know thousand-year swaths of so is it so inconceivable to say that?
From the first century till now nothing is going on
Is it so inconceivable to show that as another example of a large swath of just you know
Stupid human stupidity being employed as the norm
No, very reasonable to say that
Hmm
Past 2,000 years have been a waste of time for humanity, but not for the gods because obviously
You have to go through this time
All you need I think of the last sonic event
I said all you need to keep these idiots going is fire and genitalia and both things require rubbing, right?
sometimes right You see my point.
It's right.
I mean, yes, I do break it down from heuristics, you know, if you take away genitalia That's it.
And if you take away fire, that's it, right?
Yeah, imagine no ability to make fire Now, what are you gonna make metals?
You're gonna make plastics.
You're gonna make computers.
You're gonna make food.
No You're gonna have agriculture Nope That you know, the Greeks were spot-on with Prometheus one of the Titans taking fire right giving it to man, yeah so He was a Titan but nonetheless Comparative I would say this is like comparative Communication ability, you know, you know how they well, here's another aspect to it.
I believe Half of what you see and none of what you hear or was something like along those lines so hmm All right, so we're at a point now.
We're Not we were at a point well things are gonna start to get kind of bizarre But Greek they've always been bizarre Yes But bizarre from a paranormal point of view that people do not recognize because when you say paranormal again People's minds go to what they've been shown through, you know are the arts, you know film Superstition and scripture has nothing to do with that, right?
I'm talking from a scriptural point of view and also couple that with the notion how many people have access to what's called the scriptural narrative and to identify the end times and If so many people can actually identify it when it happens, how many wouldn't they call foul?
Right, right
But they're not because they don't comprehend it now to say that it's incomprehensible is slapping the face of the gods
Because that's telling them that the God state they want to communicate with us and their and their communication is futile because we can't understand it
so you have scumbag preachers and ministers and
You know quote-unquote religious type says no one can understand it.
They're basically saying I don't really need it because I got your Attention and you're supporting me, you know so Well, that's pretty much in the crux.
You can go into more detail.
I I didn't take write any notes I do have notes on this subject somewhere Like about image training on how that's been used on people.
There's nothing wrong with using images communications You know very often.
I test I don't test the gods and how I'm being protected But I test the consciousness of men when I see these vets and they bring up.
I'll bring up deliberately side
What do you call it when you come from the side laterally or tangentially bring up the flag and then
Deliberately disrespect it and say that it's just a cloth like any other I could use it to wash my car or polish my shoes
right
And they freeze when I say that because they don't know whether because they've been trained like a dog
To bite when Nate when that you know disrespecting the flag, right, right
You know what?
I mean, but yeah, that's a that's a foot now when you look at national flags the way they're being used
Those are the origin of those were they were Admiral, you know Fort and
maritime
Communication devices even you know, there's actually the flag Corps in the Navy or whatever
Using the right term when two ships were passing they would raise and lower different types of flags and banners to communicate right colors
Geometric patterns.
Mm-hmm, right.
They don't do that anymore I think there was I had a book on that a while when I was they put on their cars ago Yes, so it's just to communicate and now it's turned into this religious relic like a rabbit's foot and you know Like the rabbits, but if it's so lucky the rabbit had four Right what happened to him he had four of them what happened to him, right?
And so anyway
The image training aspect can be good, you know, obviously
Image training is when you recognize the alphabet
But the bad thing about it is that's all you need people feel that's all they need to achieve
To sound off words to go into the audible, you know the but they don't
Comprehend what words mean the hence the etymological references that I've been bringing up for over a decade
Which I'm glad to see there's a little bit more trending of that going on
I go around sometimes and see what's going on on the internet and I see them
Them whoever them is the great unwashed reaching towards etymology where but you know in the past that was
Foreign it was not a thought
so I would suggest that
Even now
You know a small attempt to see what things really mean is it's a little too late, you know too little too late as they say
But the recognition of images going back to that is basically what the alphabet is, right?
So or when you're doing electronics, you know, what is a resistor?
What is a capacitor right?
The ground is a little squiggly line, right Capacitor is a long line and a shorter line Parallel to it, you know, I lose everybody you guys still there.
No, no, it's just listening Yeah, so here's the other thing, you know This is from an eschatological or let's say from a scriptural point of view Is there any anybody pick up on anything that's going to be coming prophetically where imagery or iconography is going to be used?
Or is it going to be you know, totally cognitive mental, you know You know, in other words, I'm asking that as a rhetorical question to focus on that.
In other words You read in Scripture During the time of Kings was a Jeroboam or someone else he set up they set up golden calves again Remember was it Kings or Chronicles the bad kings of Israel?
They got into making golden calves, right?
Yeah It states that they actually made golden calves to worship Okay, so, you know right there it's showing you.
Well, yeah, you know if you were there, guess what?
You would see a golden calf, you know an iconography.
We'll just you know, cast gold Are we are we looking out for anything specific in the near future or you know all the way to the end?
You know think about that or is it going to be more spiritual and basically, you know, very general
Impression made on mankind through aspects, you know of the earth and the sky
You know, these are things to you know, discern and try to pull out
Because right now as it is the language is changing radically from computer talk
All right
the advent of computers
Is changing the language
So what is there to watch up and here's the thing people are so moronic for all these years
They still haven't realized that they're being ruled by the goddess religion when it comes to law
They're still asking for justice this that and the other they don't know what it means.
They think it's good hmm All right, I just went in front of the chat there's eight people Wow, that's like twice as many as I would think would comprehend what we're saying and I see We got seven hell.
Okay Seven yeah, and we got seven on the stream at the moment and it's fine.
Yeah Okay, that's again twice as many as I think could comprehend what we're talking about but this mobbery, uh-huh Was Vandy's in there?
hmm So basically Does it sound like you there's a lot there's a lot of work to do Yeah In anything that you're doing it, you know, it's gonna require some time, you know years ago It took an hour to make supper now anything more than 15 minutes is considered a grind and a chore right for most people But then again, what does anyone ever?
as a regiment or routine Ever had to go to the what they call the gym to work out with weights or machines Do you remember the first first time you went or the first few times you went to the gym?
And then you recall Yeah, if you recall going there frequently after a year, how did it feel very different what you did after?
Performing at the gym for a year You know was nothing compared to the first day I mean the first day that you were overcome by you know, what you did it was nothing a year later.
I should say Right.
It's no big deal Right, right So It's like a muscle the more you exercise it the stronger it gets and the your ability goes up So, how do you go through stuff really rapidly, you know is is the key and that's just a muscle, you know and discernment Yes, there are technical ways to read faster You can I don't know speed reading.
I don't I haven't found any system that I could recommend But think about it if you have to go through everything like I suggest again with the Bible versions Isn't it good to be able to read fast?
See, but then again the purpose of this sonic event was not about speed reading or memory or getting stronger Anything was just to be aware that the manipulations that are still taking place by various minor and major pundits On what's called the internet in a net?
the subjectivity they're still being ruled by really poor iconography and imagery and still being ruled by the urban myths and urban legends and street talk You know even in finance.
There's something called a street price, you know the market price, right?
and Also when you start checking up on what's been memorialized in texts and reference documents You'll find that there's a disparity between the three now very rarely is there Harmony between what is being shown in pictography?
Let's say what is being talked about and what's in the reference documents?
Now I'm just saying that because that's what I've discovered in any field So so is everybody with me on this?
Yes, yes.
Oh, yes A whole lot of things to think about that's for sure Yeah certain things That are finite, but yet are arduous like scripture scripture is very finite.
You can you know you can Take all the information put it on a hard drive.
You can hold it in your hand or hold a book, right?
But when you go through it, it seems like it's infinite because the way it's structured, you know, there's a lot to go through and
You have to you can't
It's
Like a mathematical equation which mathematics is just a communication
You can't overlook a variable or a function or an operation
Otherwise, you'll fall flat on your face when it comes to figuring out what's on the other side of the equal sign, right?
Right, and you can't get what the other side of the equal sign if you miss a function a number or an operation So yeah, you're starting over One thing I brought up in chat in the book of numbers There's the mention of the book of wars of Yahweh.
I dropped it in chat in a few weeks ago Yes, I do remember By the way, this is fair game to anyone and whatever when when they tell me They've read a book and I'm like, yes, so, you know, and so as I just finished the book of Genesis, yeah, so You know, well, I just read Revelation.
Yeah, so And the way I do that is by saying well, I'll pull out something that I know they missed which is most of it You know, that's why someone recently put I just read the book of Numbers.
I was like, yeah So well, did you remember the part where it said and isn't it written in the book of the wars of Yahweh?
How many people are discussing?
Where is the book of the wars of Yahweh?
It's mentioned in the book of Numbers none I mean, there's a couple of things on the rectangle, right?
It's missing Yeah, I don't know how much can be said about a missing book.
No, that's right But how come not much is being said about it being missing?
Well, that wasn't query.
It's actually to take the thing seriously
Yeah
Yeah, exactly
very often I brought up the analogy of the you know after Moses spoke to the
Fiery angel behind the bush that didn't burn he comes down and is you know, and there's a really potentially tragic and fatal scene and
And you know bloody, you know, I think his wife says this is your bloody, you know, whatever self
And no one talks about that
You know, it's like wow, you know, here's this God
The chief God wants him to do stuff and then tries to kill him.
Don't believe me go read it But somehow it's overlooked and somehow it's not discussed why why would a God task someone and Suggest protection.
I think more than suggest.
He said he would and then Try to kill him on The spot or not on the spot, but you know later on what's going on here?
Yeah, there's just more one book There's about 40 or 50 books that are mentioned in Scripture that are missing And when I say 40 or 50 books that are missing It's when you I believe say maybe you might want to help me on this.
Is it Chronicles or Kings whenever a King is mentioned or a battle or some change Doesn't it state isn't it written in the annals of the book?
You know the wars of this King or the books of this King or the Chronicles of this, right?
You're familiar with that.
Where are those books?
Well, are they missing as in missing destroyed?
You know, or are they missing?
You know from the surface right surface dwelling earth inhabitants don't have them and what's the reason for writing something in a book?
Now there's many reasons, but the main reason is for posterity so others can see it who have not been there
Right, so, you know you can
But also those books are being used against people like recently I got into the habit of watching late-night TV the Star Trek
Right just it's this perfect escape
I mean, you know, you don't want to take drugs to escape because it could be painful if your mind is clear, you know
So you just put on something that you grew up with makes you feel like, you know, you're watching some theater
And there was an advertisement recently some psychic woman is coming to town
To tell people about their dead loved ones, right?
And do you know how that trick works?
Have you heard there used to be a TV show based on this by the way?
This guy used to sit there in the audience and People would raise their hand and pick them and tell them that you had someone that died and they're okay And they want me to tell you this and this is that and they'd be very specific.
Do you know how they pull that off?
I've seen some people just ask, you know generic questions.
No Yes, there was the answer wireless headsets, wasn't it?
Nope, very specific before you go and sit in the audience They have you do a sign in in a guest book and then once everyone's assembled They also take your picture.
They have a video camera
No one on stage the people that are on stage are behind, you know in a green room type such setting
So now they get everybody to sign in and they know what you look like and they have the audience wait
They entertain for about an hour and during that hour
They start looking up everybody who signed in and they see if there are any recent deaths on public records and who they were
So the the guy on stage the psychic only picks the people that he's familiar with
So a lot of you know, he'll skip around and he'll only pick the ones that he knows
He's got the scoop on with the wireless headset also
to get information
that would make
But if you go to a small one of these groups and you refuse to sign the book no matter you no matter how much
If no one is raising your hand and you're the only one they will not call on you because you didn't sign the guestbook
So be careful when you go to sign guestbooks not now and you know now it's different now they could lift off
Information off your phone.
There's technology you can buy
It's very very expensive that you could lift off, you know information off of people's devices without them knowing it at all
I'm not talking about logging on to a Wi-Fi at a cafe either
right
So
That's how they do it using a book
Guestbook very simple
See how books are being used
So
Yeah, the 3d thought which is you know, what is spoken what is illustrated and what is written literally within the language that you
subscribe to or fluent in or recognize
Now, you know, here's someone who understands how to read the Roman letters from a through Z the Roman alphabet, you know
Well French Portuguese Spanish
English
German is written in the in those right?
I mean, there's some German characters looks like a Greek V B, you know, but you can read let's say you're just educated in English.
You could read the Italian newspaper You could read the Spanish newspaper.
You could read the Portuguese newspaper, right?
But you do comprehend it know because the way the letters are strung together are different Think about it right Same letters as in English, but the one when the letters are strung together differently now all of a sudden it falls apart It shows you how subtle the What can be communicated with the written word is right?
Images are much more powerful, you know the badge
No, if you're trained that a badge, you know, one of those metallic shiny things on a uniform or someone presents
No matter what culture even if you you grew up in a village
And then travel the world no matter where you went if someone presented that you were already trained
To what that means right or a stop sign being a red octagon or a red circle at an intersection
You've already been trained
You see
so the level of training at this point has
several layers of
degradation from cosmic centership
deliberate social engineering
deliberate dumbing up
When you combine all that it's one hell of a cocktail when you look at
Information age you got to be joking
You've got to be
kidding
You're getting as much out of the information age as the people did out of the space age and the people did out of the
Industrial age, what do you get out of the industrial age?
Let's see Do you guys remember the Superfund cleanup Bruce maybe here in America where they they made so there was lots of them toxic Yep, there were lots of them.
They're still going on Utah Yeah, where they would do toxic dumping which is really nothing toxic But what happens is when you do certain processes in industry where you refine certain compounds and elements So much that they become toxic and then they're dumped in that state without being neutralized or encapsulated.
Yeah So I think they changed it to brownfields later on Perhaps.
Yeah, I've never heard of Mm-hmm.
So it was a big deal in the 70s I think with car with the EPA came around the 70s and they started trying to figure out how they're gonna scam everyone out of That but okay.
So what'd you get out of industry is you know, what's synonymous with industry?
And I mean this clearly is industrial pollution planned obsolescence right a caste system You know what?
I mean like middle-class that's you know Yeah, it'll say we don't have you have a caste system in the Western world You ever heard of middle-class upper-class right rich and it's right in your face, you know, it's slavery.
Yeah
It's worse than slavery now because at least the slaves knew knew that they were under bond
You know, you know if you're watching the old movies, especially Romeo, I'm a bonded
I'm a bondsman me or bonded men mean them
You know, I have a contract that I have to be as man slave for seven years like in Scripture
Yeah, after that I have a chance to you know, break away or be bought or sold or redeem myself
But these people now these slaves now they're spirit, you know, they have no idea
They're too patriotic to realize their slave.
They're too diseased You know you just wave a flag and create an enemy and Tell them that they should bow down to this goddess religion called justice.
Just keep asking for justice.
You'll be fine There's no chance There's no chance at all Is it the old metaphor snowballs chance in hell that these people are ever going to get out of it on their own?
That's why in Scripture if this is not interrupted it stated that there'll be no life Left it doesn't say man's life me all life So They're already Past the level of you know insane or unsane or whatever Already past that point long time ago So you so again, what'd you get out of the industrial, you know?
What do you the same stuff the okay the effects on the ecology of the industrial aspect and the space?
Age and all that is the same effect you're getting With the information age, you know, but it's a different level of toxicity more of an auric or spiritual stench, right?
Which I remember when you were doing a little chat about space in the smell of space Yes smells like burned flesh.
It's like burnt flesh Yes, that's that's interesting because the gods were doing a sacrifice and if you read in the Let's say numbers Deuteronomy especially a lot of times in Deuteronomy That smell was a savory sweet savory odor.
They enjoyed it.
Mm-hmm Well, they didn't and there was other astronauts that even said that there was like a smell of Was it brandy or something like that?
It was sweet Like metal and in a sweet metal kind of smell Yeah, very interesting From a former AT&T, you know, you say I Spoke to an AT&T engineer most people that when you say AT&T engineer, they don't associate it with space But you know 90% if not more than that of the domestic Let's say American satellites were put up and maintained by guess who right?
Yeah You told me that it was very strong ozone and very foul smell and the reason I met him Let's say over 25 years ago, he's in his 90s at the time because he was into antique clock restoration and One day someone said go pick up this old grandfather clock from the 1700s and bring it over to you know Such-and-such so I show up to the house and guys on the phone.
He says it's just right there Help yourself.
So he was on the phone for like 45 minutes and I'm waiting there and he comes down and he's like I told you you just help yourself.
I'm like, well, where the hell is the grandfather clock?
And he says we see those five Five gallon buckets.
It's in there and I'm like really These buckets here are the clock.
He's like, yeah, I was like, okay.
Gotcha.
You just that's all you have to say Wow There's a little subjective personal experience And then this old man had a lot of time on his hands and I was willing to listen, you know about that specific stuff What was going on up there?
another guy I
Did a project here in the southwest
Retired he said my father this guy was already old and he says my dad's here and his dad worked with the OSS
He had some interesting stories to tell also
So
Okay, so there you go information age is crap and if you don't believe it you're not paying attention
But here's the interesting thing
The
Understanding it from a prophetic point of view at any time by the way is efficient, right?
You know the time that you're living in
Give you know example that I always give is let's say you're in Europe in World War two and you have some evangelistic
Whatever idiot telling you well, this is the book of Revelation the apocalypse happening right now and you're in Europe with all the bombs falling
You know, let's say in a city or something it sounds very convincing doesn't it
But if you really know scripture, you know, it's not time yet
For sure, you see no matter what is happening, right?
So from a small prophetic point of view what you will see is I think I've been
You know with all the quote-unquote Jew bashing that's been going on
I don't like to talk much about Israel unless it's necessary to
Because the public at large, you know is too moronic to objectify what I'm trying to say
But this is the time right now by the way that just started and I again with Ocelli when I was doing Ocelli in the Greek
In 2015, I said 2018 this spring.
No, it's always like oh, no, I think it's 2017 I'm like, what are you basing it on?
He got quiet because he's you know, just like normal humans, you know
Doesn't know what's going on and you know has been livening up a bit over there
You know, yeah, and you can't and you can't be yeah, you can't be accurate without accurate information
So your opinion has to come through this is not that what I'm suggesting here
about the importance of 2018 in the spring is what I'm also been suggesting through the years is
Spring is planting summer is growth fall is harvest winter slow down time, right?
Back to Israel what's going to be happening in the 2018-2019?
You know spring summer fall
2019 spring summer fall
2020 spring summer fall
2021 spring summer is
Israel being played to the point where its very existence might be threatened
Right, and you know how I was saying earlier be aware of supernatural paranormal and all that and they're being a very strong
supernatural assistance
But also keep that to preserve it but also keep that coinciding with a consecutive
format of judges repeating as prime ministers
After this prime minister and possibly after the next one is going to be the position of Samson is a good position
There's a good
strong
Indications that I see in terms of the overall timing that the next prime minister will be more in the position of Samson and during
the time of Samson
Israel was subjugated
to the Philistines and the only way
Modern Israel could be subjugated to the modern Palestinians is not by the Palestinians, but by world
Opinion world sentiment against it you see
And of course local squirmishes, you know, what's odd about that?
Is that?
Right now Israel doesn't listen to any of them anybody out there
No, so that's is that in itself is going to be a turnaround
But you but here's the thing
Let me just put it this way and I'm gonna try to be as neutral and neuter and objective as possible
You were in Israel in that place in that this time right now you wouldn't either
I think I gave an example if you speak to people in Israel that are interacting with their neighbors
especially the Palestinians the thing that's usually being said is
When you do you live next to the Palestinians in Israeli speaking, let's say
If you try to remain neutral they try you give an inch they want to take a mile or a yard
Right if you interact with them, they always try to take advantage
But the moment you try to defend yourself, they cry foul that you're killing them
Right, right
Right, and this has been going on for a very long time
So this harshness that you see right now is a reciprocal harshness
Not because Israel should be doing it or the palace.
It's just the way it is again.
Go back to the Star Trek analogy you have the humans you have the Klingons and the Romulans, right?
Like the Klingons to them.
It's the most horrible thing is to die of old age.
They have to die in battle
That's their culture
Right, right the way you punish a Klingon is by putting him in an old age home
You see he has to die in battle and as they get older they want to go into battle and die in battle
So they're remembered honorably
Now take that and transfer it over whether it's the headhunter mentality or whatever
To the mentality that they have in that part of the world, which is very ignorant on both sides
I mean you want to take the ignorance of what quote-unquote in Israeli?
They don't even know anything in their own book All right, what I mean, you know, let's say, you know the scriptures very little it's not anything Put it this way.
I've never met even a rabbi that knows the scriptures Even though they open the book of Isaiah every week and Read out of it, you know, it's part of their kadasha.
Whatever prayer morning prayer after a prayer, right?
Yeah, they don't know the book in its entirety very few and the ones that do usually There probably have been rabbis that knew the scriptures, but they cease to exist as rabbis They got out of it.
Unless they just so evil
They decide to go back in and you know, you know because it's their rather prosper because the more scripture
You know the more manipulative you can be to these to these congregations because you know seem invulnerable
Same with the Christians or any religion if you actually say the similarities are just
exact
Preacher rabbi same thing
because the more
You know scripture you become so advanced in thought form that it seems like anybody with any question
That comes to you can answer it.
You're almost invincible
mentally, right
So they they tend to gain a lot of power that way but for the wrong reason
So we're talking about a very bad condition there
It's basically going to be focused around Israel for the next three and a half years or four years
I'd say three years three to four years, you know center it around that time
but by around the time of
2025 there will be no doubt in anyone's mind that there's a Middle East Union and a new you know
New kid on the block new world power functioning out of there and things are looking very optimistic
you see
So how is how is the entire mindset of the planet going to change?
Well, we'll see That's why they think a few sonic events ago or two sonic events ago I went through a very simple routine of looking up all the biblical cities Corresponding verses and yes, is that inclusive of conquests of David and Kings that is the future map of Israel, right?
very grim If you present that as the next let's say three to seven years Very it makes a lot, you know There's a lot of it's a Chris some grim nature and stuff out of there because how are they going to be, you know?
Okay without getting into specifics.
Let's just do one big chunk
Lebanon is finished
right pretty much and
a third of Jordan is finished, you know, or a third of Jordan will be a
Quarter of Jordan will be under Israel and Lebanon is done forget about Lebanon
this will cease to exist as it does unless
It is completely under
Occupation, but they have a puppet government you see and they're still it still does exist as we know modern Lebanon, you know
But that needs to be viewed very carefully
As well, it is possible like, you know what the Korea's for example, those are all puppet governments, right since the 19th century
Don't think for a minute that Korea has had a Korean government since the 19th century
I mean, well, that sounds weird, you know, well, Germany Germany has not had a
Domestically run really, you know an autonomous government since the 1930s
Modern Germany don't think for a minute.
I don't know if you guys have ever communicated with anyone in Germany.
They Bring up politics.
They don't want to discuss it because like we haven't had a government 75 years Like what do you call Angela Merkel and all that going on?
That's not that's total abomination
Have you guys ever spoken anybody from Germany or anything like that not as of late I used to work with a lady but
She's gone back
Yeah, so there's that capacity that reason I brought that up because that capacity is a strong potential as well
So
But Lebanon, you know for I think Sam and I've just tried to discuss it on several sonic or one sonic event a while back
Well, if you're gonna get a broad brushstroke and run it across Lebanon that's Canaanite
Generally, you're like who are the Canaanites right?
Who are the Phoenicians?
Well, if you were just if you had to bury that axe real quick and just you know Move on to another subject yet yet one of those big 4-inch sass brushes, you know And you dip it in some red paint and you just brush right across Lebanon and write Canaanites on it.
You see That would be fairly accurate from a generalistic point of view Are you with me on that Sam?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, it works.
Yeah, it works, but it's not that simple but for you know General purposes.
Yeah So the Canaanites are done for So, I don't know we're talking about I don't know What what how what form of bizarre net a bizarro world do you want to get into and this is it from now on I've said this a decade ago get ready for bizarro world, right?
So but it's gonna seem normal But here's the other interesting thing and because the thing is about you know, how do you discern these things?
I've noticed I read it some people.
I haven't seen in a while recently about a week ago and They're pretty they can rationalize.
I mean more than more than most humans, you know
so they're in like the five three to five percent ability to rationalize and
They're you know wondering the end times came up in all disasters and all I said don't know remind you guys
All this doom and gloom this like, you know terminal doom and gloom, you know with the asteroids and the solar event and the massive
Oh, that is like the last week or last month or two
You know what I mean
It's not like you're gonna get hit by an asteroid and you got four years
so
Yeah, it's and for sure the shit isn't gonna hit the fan, you know to a point where not only the shit
It's the fan but the whole fan and the motor and the blades break off
That doesn't happen till like the last few weeks or months
Let's say I'm gonna give myself a little more room and I could tell you why really most the worst of it comes in one
Day, right?
How many times have you heard of the day of the Lord and right?
It's one day and that day that fateful day and this day and this day over and over and over, right?
Most of it the the major destruction comes in one day less than a 24-hour period
but for sure
the last three and a half years will be quote-unquote from a
Kafka esque and a Nietzsche esque and
Dante esque hell on earth
The last three and a half years for sure you see what I mean
hmm, and
That's still a good decade away plus
So there's no need to live in any kind of like oh shit, you know shit's gonna hit the fan.
No
It won't but here's the other thing about that last three and a half years
No matter how bad things are for those that know those that don't know where things are gonna still think things are getting better
They're on the upswing
It's only gonna be bad for those that know what what's going on and by that time
I think that's going to be whittled down to a small secretive group or a small select group that is, you know
Extracted from an immune from that, you know
But still conscious of it
So in other words the doom and gloom stuff is really a side on I don't talk about that much and I don't think about
It much because it's very little and it's going to happen very hard very fast at a very compressed time at the very very tail
end the interest in my purpose of speaking is
you've got a
Turnaround in the current society
Which is the modality from the industrial age of space age information age that there's still a big question mark over
everyone's head or what's coming and
My point is what's coming is these massive changes political geopolitical
economic military changes in the Middle East that the world will follow and fall into as
Being the next the start of a golden age on this planet and all of that is going to be a lie
But it's not going to be a propagandized lie.
It's going to try to be actuated It will be physical evidence of it coming together like world peace for a little while, you know prosperity so on and so forth and all that is going to be starting around 2025, so my point of speaking and Rationale publicly in a private is how the hell do you take a society in the current state of mind?
which is you know industrial, you know, you could say it's also a product of the Victorian Age, but with the With all the quote-unquote modernists and moral changes.
I think Victorian stuff has gone out the window.
Would you say so?
I
Still hear different remnants of it people wanting to decorate like that or some such well certain etiquette
Forms of education etiquette like if you go to a high-end restaurant what cuisine they're still using Victorian
Standards, right, you know the place settings and and the way things are done
but I think that's falling apart because for three years in a row Nobu or Noba and
Bunch of snotty ass 20 year olds are voted as the best restaurant in the world up in the
Whatever.
I'm like shit, man.
I wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't even do takeout and they're voting it, you know, so anyway I'm there.
I wouldn't even do take out from that's the best restaurant in the world.
So I mean already gone to pot there But I think they tour so you still industrial age and you're still and you're still Space age bullshit and you're still Information age that mindset which is still leaves nothing but a dark, you know, those black light light bulbs, right?
No question mark what the hell's happening next every year.
These idiots are still crying At least they're not crying the end of the world.
They were doing that more a few years ago
But how is the mentality going to change to a perfect society that they're all going to fall into I mean everyone
And including everyone I'm speaking to and listening to me now you are going to fall for the big deception
You know
so
You know, I mean, that's that's how strong it's going to be
So, how does it transition that is one hell of a you know punch to the head?
You know what?
I mean?
Yeah where you are now to everyone believing How wonderful it is and again you have to remember I'm gonna repeat myself many times again Everyone has access to this information and if enough people get handle on comprehending it They're gonna cry foul, but it doesn't state that they are It states that certain people will not go along with it and they'll be sought out and killed, right?
But I'm telling you all these things are going to be in secret Even I would suggest that even the rise of the Antichrist will be difficult to identify him specifically even after the mouth The malformations that he suffers to be possessed by Satan, right?
He loses the use of an arm and an eye Even then he will probably appear normal and if you were to suggest that maybe this guy had lost his eye and his arm and They'd be like holy shit.
That's a secret.
How did you know?
you see Because remember he's an Antichrist the Christ his identity was completely secret Completely secret.
He you didn't know who he was unless he wanted you to know who he was and it was either momentarily or whatever You see what I mean?
So what are the chances of this Antichrist also being secret in plain sight?
I'd say like, you know a hundred to one, you know, what say you?
Wow Where's the hint on that How many times do you have you heard those that claim to be of Judean and or not?
or the synagogue of Satan We think that's referring to See his identity he is of us Syrian descent But is he going to be introduced as as young as Syrian or is he going to be introduced as a young Judean?
Think about it That's food for thought.
I Mean it does say those so it's also plural.
It's not just one person.
Yeah He doesn't roll alone.
He's got a crew You were eat.
I don't know how deep he rolls, but we know he's got a false prophet or two, right?
hmm a council Could it be possible?
He's rolling with 12 or 13 Yes, it's very strong possibility, right?
Now we can't take a scientific approach to scripture no, we can't do that no no no way You know scientific meaning, you know using good methodology Analyzing the information coming up with theories and conclusions that are according to the information.
We can't do that That's not allowed you see because it's just based on faith and that alone, right?
you know, I'm being facetious but So, hmm, there you go Yeah, I May have to drop out just for sleep reasons Okay, I can do the same.
It's about a Quarter to seven here.
I'm having coffee and I'm I think I'm gonna make some ganache cake.
So While you're sleeping, I'll be making a delicious dessert Anything else No, I think I'm good boy.
That was uh, that's quite the amount of info And yeah, I know again, it's just one that's gonna be something to think over.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Oh
And this is just stuff I had I was just bouncing around in the head
I said I should just do a stream to get it off out of the head and talk about it
I'm planning on formulating this I have some notes
I have a clipboard with about seven or eight pages of notes on what I've discussed today, which I haven't referred to at all
But I just wanted to put it out
Yeah, I want to I just wanted to put it out to see what kind of reaction this gets because I think
Putting together, you know a more formula how Sam used to call in with questions.
Remember that Sam?
Whatever and bring up maybe a list of a dozen items and just going down them based on this track this type of traction You know like we had yeah, I think we're gay.
We're not spinning wheels.
We're not in the mud, right?
Right now with this thought look at what's been shown look at what's discussed look at what's written What do we discard?
Can it be harmonized?
You know the three aspects Well, you know what people discuss how it's being shown in illustration and what's being referenced what can be harmonized how it should be harmonized Believe it or not.
Most of the notes have nothing to do with scripture only a few items I mentioned the gates of hell.
I have a few things pinned in there from numbers in Genesis also, which I didn't bring up but
Each because each one of those really deserves a two-hour discussion on its own
But most of the stuff that I've written down has nothing to do with scripture from that set
But it has to do with the human body health
Financial stuff and other things which I think would be interesting to get into in detail show you how things work
I'm gonna certainly leave that at your leave and it does sound like a wealth of information
It is and believe it or not
I'm being lazy because most of these things that I've jotted down here are
things that I have brought up and asked her about in the past few months and
in private conversations, so it's it's
Nothing new, but I think it's new on this on this venue.
So Okay All right Yes, both you both you Sam and and yourself Okay, guys, take care.
Thanks you you also good night now Bye bang later