Yeah, there's a lot going on that You'll behoove anyone to just stop and say what is what is really going on here?
But when you you see the thing is you have to assess the entirety first That's why when it's very you know Some people get offended some don't some laugh some just sit back and say nothing when I say this is a planet completely filled with morons Well, what does that mean?
Well on a wholesale level that's very accurate extremely accurate, you know It's like the science fiction you go to this planet Well in this planet the people, you know, when you read sci-fi books, they explain what the people there are like not all you know It's just a general statement that holds fairly true So if you establish that this planet is full of morons.
Well, what kind of Individual society when the planet would they be moronic also?
Yes, they would and within that each society or each country if they're moronic Do you think they're going to engage in things in an intelligent rational objective way?
No Doesn't matter what it is, whether it's food nuclear physics astronomy religion Medicine legal society you see what I mean Mm-hmm, very simple to objectify, isn't it?
It doesn't mean you have to be stuck in that stupidity Yeah, I always like giving the metaphor of you ever see Photographs of people that were consider themselves to be fashion sensible in the 70s with the large polyester bell-bottoms wide lapels and all that You know, why did they do that?
I mean, can't you tell that that looks ugly?
The aesthetic is not appealing but everyone wore it why it's fashionable And now you see they were so proud to go get the Pierre Cardin or Kiana polyester shirt with a really wide lapel But if you show them photos now, they all laugh.
I'll put that away It looks terrible doesn't it but you didn't at the didn't think so at the time.
Did you?
So this fashion you call astrophysics or this fashion you call nuclear physics or religion or food Management our agriculture.
It's a fashion trend Yeah, and the only reason you're here is because your biological needs are met and that's the crux and the premise of humanity All all all in all really you're playing out a scheme that's been laid out by the gods Very simple and you know what?
That's a pretty hardcore truth.
That's really hard to get around You may not like it you may not agree with it, but that's the truth Ruth or Bruce see that was It's not hard to settle into where where do you get this?
3,000 a day People number killed by doctors.
Is that a stat that can be that's just yeah Well, you have million people a year divided by you know, okay.
Where's the million a year stat?
Oh
You're gonna have fun with that
You I
Would encourage and invite anyone to start looking up how many people die according to medical deaths
In the u.s. And you're gonna have to put it all together
You know how the shaky camera technology works the anti shake function
you know it takes very rapid averages and
The average is the definitive aspect and the it tries to shed the blurry stuff and that's the you know error correction
Is another way of saying it, right?
It's not going to be like a digital bit of information zero zeros or ones You're gonna have to do a lot of error correction.
You're gonna see numbers all over the place High and low but it's going to end up being around a million a year through medical negligence.
Yeah on a rough figure That's not actually if I told you it was roughly around three to five million a year.
That would sound really exaggerating It's kind of like but it's probably more closer to the truth When you consider, you know the what they're putting in foods and things And also a lot of the things that are considered natural deaths that are not Because you have the concept of allergies developing right?
But anyway
It's it's very similar to the figure the unemployment figures which are always doctored right if they
You know, they say well the unemployment went down or whatever or went up whatever it has
There's nothing to do whether who the hell knows if you got a job or a job
It's when you're inquiring with the government for unemployment benefits
There's one thing or when the benefits are cut off, you know, like the unemployment compensation wages and stuff
They when they cut off wages, they'll count that as someone who got a job even let's say they didn't or someone
applying for
Unemployment benefits as they from the government, you know to tap their credit line and they're still working
That can be done also, you know what I mean?
So these numbers are based on certain what it called metrics that are not accurate That's why you have to look at the number how many people are actually killed by meta.
Here's a simple way to start.
Are you ready?
Look at how many lawsuits are filed against doctors, you know for their practice.
Think about it Malpractice how many malpractice lawsuits are start there?
Right because that's just a small amount the majority of the people that are killed from bad Surgical practices or prescription medicines and stuff like that.
What would be the percentage of those families filing a lawsuit?
Small or large right?
You have to start looking at various metrics, right?
But by looking at it for a while, I found out it's roughly a million a year
Okay, and that was about looking at it for about ten years
Alright
But as far as the people and their lives
I think it's also been said that the reason why people live longer is mainly because of improved sanitation and not directly
The medical but can this cannot be shown
sure, like
sure
Wastewater treatment would be the main thing but at the same time
it goes back and forth the quality of the municipal water and the access to
Drinking water is going up and down also
But they're both going up and down but the meaning the sanitation removal is going up faster than the
You know people went from drinking tap water to bottled water which is worse in other ways
It's basically sanitation
Within the food supply as well
Even though the poison food
Right.
It's just that you know what I keep saying That's a testament for the robustness of the human composition or the human Constitution Humans are pretty tough.
You know, you get a lot of false.
Well, I shouldn't say false Non-qualified statements like for example in the past people only live to the age of 25 or to the age of 40 but when you go and you find where these numbers were gotten from it would have been let's say from Rome when they had a typhoid or a tuberculosis outbreak for 10 years You know what?
I mean?
So what happens is their census showed for 10 years?
the average people, you know the average
age of
Of a corp, you know
Someone who died was 25 to 30 and they grabbed that and they say see people back there
I live to 25 or 30, but they leave out the part that there was a tuberculosis epidemic in Rome
You know what I mean, you could look this up look up tuberculosis epidemic in ancient Rome or even like a hundred AD or 200
You'll see those a bunch of stuff
There were good record keepers or at least they hired enough Greeks to be a good record keepers.
You know, I mean On something completely different We're also seeing this thing with the Nile and the Delta that it seems to be suffering from selling a salinification Well, it's not the salinification.
Yeah the backflow of the sea saltwater.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's been going on for a long time 30 years, but is it is it true that that's being caused by the Earth spinning slower.
So the sea level rises.
Yeah, that could happen the Coriolis effect.
Yeah, I've been speaking about The earth and the planet rotation movements are fixed on to the Sun Right because of the vegetative layer Mm-hmm Well, did I lose you?
No, I'm here.
So it starts with the Sun then what does it did I lose you there?
I just changed location here.
So no, I'm fine Well, you look here's the thing if the sunlight diminishes the earth slows down and the Coriolis effect You know the spinning of the earth, right?
I mean, there's here's the thing that you know What I I do appreciate the I'm gonna bring this up, but you didn't mention it the flat earthers.
I'll bring it up.
I But I don't appreciate the people and what they're saying well, I don't know the people but what is being said is bears looking at but it can be dismissed very quickly because you can see that They're getting people that are you know?
Emotionally handicapped to promote it generally
And they're using it as a crutch because they feel bet you know when someone has a broken leg
They walk around with a crutch
So they walk around with the flat earther thing
But the the instinct the instance that there's a dynamic on questioning the you know
The general, you know such a big aspect of our reality that we're always told, you know
This these little fairy tales about how things are they're questioning that and that's good
But I'll tell you the earth is not flat and it's not a globe.
It's neither Get over it so What is it then Greek well, I think we've gotten into that to a certain degree It's a it's something that's been manufactured just like, you know, if you have a good telescope You can go out and look at how things are manufactured, you know, so is that Bruce still with us?
He showed you well, we wouldn't be on if he wasn't is there anything in chat Bruce?
Before sleep
Okay, cuz I'm going yeah, I'm moving from indoors to outdoors
here
Consistently out the wind is picking up a bit now
So I'm going to be it looks like someone is outside with a giant hand shaking all the trees
Which means that something is coming this way
so
Anything in chat Bruce or anything worth mentioning probably not
Bruce seems to be coming and going
There's about 19 or 20 listeners
in the
stream right now and
it's a rather silent in the
chat
Well, it's okay to be silent, um
I
Almost want to be so I'll tell you again.
It's not it sounds like a rat this week I spent a little bit too much time looking for stuff on YouTube and Google And it kind of hit me across the head like a club on how pathetic humanity still is or I mean has been or is and is going to be by the use of the media and I just tie it back to the modern art being ugly and Poetry and new authors also writing about crap.
I've had authors Send me books.
I want to read my book.
Let me know what I think and I'm like
Looks like you had an eight you were an English major
Because you just so formulaic all these people that write books, you know how they make try to paint a picture when they're writing be descriptive
It's just so formulaic and just rubbish, you know, it's it's like you ever see a paint-by-numbers, you know
Kind of painting, you know
Two-dimensional so I've been looking at
researching a few subjects and
Talk about it's I think it's worse than finding edible corn in poop
it's partially digested corn in a lot of poop and
And
again, not only are the hosts just laughable cringeworthy the guests have the impression that they offering some information and
The public at large is definitely
Appalling and what do I mean by the public at large is the comments?
the audience just appalling and I thought you know what I go out to the shops and out to the public if I'm gonna Go and interact with the public.
I'm like, oh, maybe it's because I mean, you know a medium-sized town or you know Just you know, whatever but no, it's it's everywhere.
It's humanity at large You know, this is objective now I'm trying to be objective.
It's not that I'm better or smarter or dumber or wiser or anything.
I'm just trying to objectify it You know from an engineering point of view, you know when you when let's say you're on a big ship and you have an engineer Whether he's a good engineer or not.
What makes him an engineer is that he has practice skills and training and being objective You know, whether you're a good mechanic or a poor mechanic.
You have to be able to objectify what you're looking at, right?
We're not talking about your personal and private skills or aptitudes.
We're talking about the general art
Of objectification and anything the public at large throughout the entire world is crap
complete crap and
Then you have a few of them that have either a casual or adamant response to being crap themselves
into projecting something through the media and
It's just
Sad just really really sad
That's why I keep stressing lately if you see I put in charge just try to put some food thing in there every day
Get some good food in you.
I Enjoy a good meal You know, oh Speaking of another thing that wasn't chat.
What's this thing?
You're saying?
Not just saying but maybe showing a bit but not really explaining that yes You is some kind of a thingy for his name was obliterated.
Mm-hmm.
It's an accurate.
Yes, you it goes back to an old old
Judean or priestly tradition about obliterating or blotting out someone's name
Which was not only in the Judean world or that aspect, but it's in the entire
Muslim world actually you'll find that even in the in the Egyptian records every
Far East or Near East culture had something about a class of people or person where a clinic class
But you were put into that class of those that were to be blotted out
Are you familiar with that concept that's sort of been lost in
in the Western world
Right
Whether it was political or religious, but in those days the the politically even today believe it or not
Every politic, you know the patron or matron deity, right?
You cannot have a political system without a god behind it it doesn't mean you go around and remind the the the plebeians, you know your followers if you're Political or whatever leader about that.
It's really, you know But it's always there.
So it's usually an offense to the god of the political system, you know Or their beliefs or their traditions or their position or what have you?
It's a very dishonorable position to be in there was a who's the Hosni Mubarak a president 30 30 plus year president Of Egypt when they did that Arab Spring and they threw him in jail now They got him in jail for like obstructing justice or something, right?
You know, they actually there was an article years ago about it
this is happening about me five or six years ago when was the big Arab Spring, right and
There was articles about they were starting to go into public records and remove his name and and you know
This is what they're doing there
you know like
In Western countries they find that to be you know, not necessarily, you know
They go back and delete his very existence you'll be even like they ever existed, you know through the history they go back and redact and
Change the history books and even the birth certificate gets eliminated, you know, just erasing them from existence, right?
This is not commonly done.
It's actually quote-unquote illegal.
There's statutes against it in Western countries to do that, right?
But in the East it's quite acceptable I'm not saying that they're gonna succeed in doing it But it was brought up as it would be had begun on a cultural level Right, right.
But how do we know that?
Yes, you is the part of that?
Hmm From an acronym Acronymistic way.
Yeah, but you can make anything in acronym.
I can make cat into an acronym for cold, you know apples and trees.
I Would say there's a loose prophecy behind it in up in Isaiah where his name will be blotted out sure, but yes, you isn't mentioned You can make anything to that who is he who when you read scripture who is it's about the gods, right?
It's not about you Sure.
Yes, but that's why it's so sparse in detail They don't need to know about your iPhones or your blacksmith down the road.
They don't care about that.
How do I know?
Well, they didn't know they're not talking about it.
No, that's fine.
But the yes you thing I mean that could be I can make anything into an acronym for his name will be blotted out Alright give give an example you can make anything on it to his name will be blotted out.
Go ahead.
I came on the spot But you know, give me a day Yeah, okay.
I don't know what to say to that.
I mean, I'm just showing you things that are coincidental here, so Yeah, I just want to know what it's based on though.
Like what's that based on?
Because yes you what it sounds like.
Uh-huh Okay Isu even in the in the The early King James there was no J is I they use the IES you for s right Which is Latin, you know, you put an s on the end of Latin words right to show of It's like the olive tog in Hebrew or towards When you say you Seuss in the early King James, it meant about East ooh, right?
Or of the one known as Isus in Latin, right?
So, oh, I don't want to go back this but here
Do a little bit or I was looking at some notes about the early
iconography and imagery of what they called the J es us or used to character and
I
Was I was going to drop a link in chat that Wikipedia does a fairly comprehensive, you know at a glance
put in
An image of J es us and a Wikipedia thing
They give about 20 examples of how they decided on what image to use and it was a few centuries later
You know, they had like all these different varieties and no one knew much about him and you know
Right.
Mm-hmm.
So when you it's really difficult to discuss The poignancy of is issue or yes you Really even the one in Scripture because how many times can you anyone say that Christianity is 0% biblical when it comes to the facts?
You know 0% And if it was 1% you'd have to grant it to be rational so But even the imagery of the J es us is another thing about the name it's so far removed from anything factual truthful or historical that now You can even abandon the yes you thing if you want with that just just the whole thing down the drain It's irrelevant but Why it's relevant.
Well, I find several places in Scripture where it talks about the blotting out of a name It's not you know, if you notice scripture reads a lot different than an army manual Which is the opposite of scripture which gives you you could find out how to tie shoelaces in an army manual What luster to put on you how to even make your bed, right?
They got manuals on everything So when you're reading scripture, you're gonna have to figure out that eventually The the narrative is so strong, but yet so sparse on detail.
It can't be taught.
It can't be about you Can't be Yeah it's about the gods and They're like, hey, let's go let's go tell these guys something down here while we're Well while we're putting them through this curing period.
What are we going to tell them?
All right
Well, obviously they're not my reading our minds
So we're gonna have to tell them how we think and how we view things and that's what you get when you get the Holy Ritz
Mm-hmm
That's why it's so easy to bust
The epoch some of the apocryphal if not all the apocryphal works as being bullshit
When you read a lot of the Gnostic stuff, you see the mindset changes, you know
Let's say this is the epistle of this guy or that or the in the Gnostic works like no it isn't
Completely different mindset how it's written
It's like, you know, you could see it's it's forced.
They didn't really comprehend the scriptures.
Oh Yeah, they don't you see the style is different and there's no The fact everything about it, you know, and you could see they're over embellishing trying to sound like it But it's not the you know, it doesn't have the effect on the mind Now obviously the weak spirit did people the the confused people the moronic Are so disgusted with the mainstream religion what's been put in front of them.
They look at the biblical text They don't understand anything past the word the They pick up the Gnostic stuff is how I like this this works for me, that's exactly right.
It was designed and written for you It's a sellable story.
It's an agreeable story to the common plebeian Disney is a master at that, you know Hollywood is a master at that Why does Hollywood whenever Hollywood puts out something historical?
Why is it always factually incorrect almost always factually incorrect?
Why?
Think about it Because if they put something correct out with the people would see it and they wouldn't understand what they were seeing You know that I get reminded with this constantly with chemical reactions I have this thing called a five-minute epoxy It's a two-part Liquid or gel and you mix it together in five minutes.
It gets really hard to like 1200 psi like hard as you know hardwood or not like it's like soft stone, right?
Supposedly now when you're reading the package and it tells you all the attributes of it How it's bondable and durable all that well the moment you start working with you're like wow look at this is gel It has no strength at all.
It's messy.
It's sticky.
It stinks, but you know when you're looking at the label of it oh It says oh, it's hard as a rock, and it's strong and all this well.
Yeah, eventually You see while you're working with it in its initial Combination it's nothing like and where I'm leading to with that is the What people are constantly being told is that they're wonderful.
They're intelligent they're their beings of light They're good They have to stick together all untrue.
It's their people are the exact opposite of that Ultimately, that's true.
Just like the epoxy Ultimately it will be more true, but right now.
It's they're the opposite.
They're not good.
They're not being of light.
They're dark They don't they're not intelligent.
They're quite stupid there you see my point
It's not it's and but that and that is terminal that condition just like when I'm mixing the two gels of epoxy
That's terminal meaning
It's not going to be this liquid sticky crap
Because I'm reading here the factual aspect of it after five minutes it will become this hard bonding bonding material
You see
But if you're looking at it without that temporal conditional
You know
Manifestation you'll say this is bullshit over here.
It says it's hard as rock, but look at the stinky gel You see what I mean, so you have to see the whole picture here, right?
Mm-hmm what we're being shown is there's a time period that humanity has to go through and
You can't show me anywhere in any ancient writ that speaks well of anyone
At all other than you know the Christ and a few others
Minimal so meanwhile what's going on is all the ancient wisdom says that people are basically crap ignorant dark evil
But what they're being told all the time is that they're
They're light.
They're good and They're wonderful, so which one is it well.
It's neither, and it's both right not right now And not right now not a hundred years ago.
They were good and not a thousand not three thousand years ago This is the part of the curing period.
I hope that that's like a very general message to give
That ultimately has to be ended up with don't take it personally
You know
And it's hard not to depend on where you are in the fortunately and unfortunately
It's hard not to yes, but fortunately and unfortunately your life is so short that you're not going to have to put up with it
for four or five hundred years you just put up with it for I
Don't know 60 70 80 and when and here's the good thing about it most people are so
Asleep their entire life from cradle to cradle to grave they never see any of the contrast they fall for it.
You know all the way That's why I keep the last time I think we spoke Is that there's no way that this could be a lesson those people's is a lesson you have to learn your lesson here You know you know I'm like what?
What about the ninety nine nine nine nine percent of the people that that are born and die clueless of everything?
What lesson did they learn to be clueless?
So that you know no
But I mean the sphere of the sphere of their awareness even though it doesn't extend into
Matters of say the true workings of things is still
Existent within their own subjective interpretation of their experiences
So their suffering is still valid to them and their confusion is still something that causes them distress
So on so when they wake up in the next right phase of things
They're still gonna have a basis to say well, we got screwed and we don't like you very much now because of that
I mean you have to have some kind of momentum that propels people into a state of
Acting and thinking that leads them into the lake of fire anyway, because how do you end up there?
Sure, well, I don't think you end up there.
I think you're put there
Yeah, but you're put there for a reason because yes you didn't act right
But you had a period of time
Because of the white throne judgment period to get your act together, and you still didn't right so presumably you're still mad
Right and apparently they're gonna be some people even when there's more awareness or if not complete awareness available to them
They still won't inquire in Zephaniah for example.
It's mentioned So it's a matter of inquiry Yeah, but there's not much here.
What are the basics then so ultimately what what everyone has in common for basic happiness is biological functions right Clean air clean food happy family happy self healthy, you know no pain, you know, no belly aches from fake food Or bad food or bad water, you know biological functions, right?
So when you prioritize that, you know, if you destroy the biological functions of someone they destroy them essentially right now
So the biological functions upping the quality is the immediate concern or you know to up the quality of being here right now
You know, here's an interesting thing that I discovered not recently
But I'd say maybe 15 years ago as I noticed when
The upper crust people the upper society
When they started losing their leisure ability to be I have a life of leisure and the quality of intake of food
That's when I realized
That
This is now we're in a time that there's equalization happening
You know what?
I mean?
Everyone is being considered the same, you know
Hmm
In other words when you run into rich people that eat crap food
Where they don't have to because they can afford
You know, they can afford to feed a million people if they wanted to and they're eating crap
You know, there's something wrong right I'm not saying that all through history
Wealthy people let's say whether it was lawful money or just credit.
I'm not saying that all of them ate well But when you start seeing it more consistently You're like, okay, there's an equalization going on here now You know now now it's no longer rich or poor white or black Christian or Muslim or Christian or Jew or Whatever, whatever, whatever what people want Republican or Democrat communist or fascist No matter what's up these separations.
These divisions are falling apart and the people are being equalized Yeah, I see that Yeah with a very Americanized persona as a thrust for them or westernized by way of America Well, look the movement in humanity Well, you went east right Adam and Eve, right?
And and let's say those that were before you went we don't know much about their movement, but they are sent east, right?
And
then they go west and
Then they go east
But each time they go east and west they go further west and east right and
This final movement West which developed the Western world here
Let's say across the Atlantic because
Europe is also known as the West is as far west as you could go before if you keep going west now you become east
again
So this pendulum swing now has reached its maximum and now it's going to swing
back to the east
but to the middle
You see like it was in the beginning that makes sense
any who
I'll probably
Attack one more thing and then I think I'm good for today's string
This thing
You kind of come across in the Bible quite often
loosely speaking the Bible
This idea of there having to be two witnesses to something.
So the bare minimum according to Various places whether it's Matthew or some places in the Old Testament You have this Proprietor hold on.
Hold on while you're saying that hold on.
There's an exception there To the two witnesses of something being said or performed Unless there's a prophet Because if you're a prophet you can you can be the only one saying it right?
What is your false prophet?
Well, you could well, you know, what's interesting I found out Read look quickly.
I mean not quickly look closely.
I found this out just by thinking about it of what I've studied, right?
It's interesting You know You have many prophets and they seem to be solo at the time and there are places that there There are many prophets are not named But it's almost always when a false prophet is shown.
He's shown surrounded by a group of other false prophets not always but almost There's like there's like they work they for they work in a group or a posse or something you see so It's interesting.
They yeah, but when you have remember this is you know from the biblical narrative too
Which is very sparse in very in detail, but I believe if there was let's say, you know, when you look at the major prophets
You won't see a false major prophet
You know, you don't see any of the false ones having a major prophet coming out and be because if there were they they would be
Brought up and debunked, you know script use how scripture does, right?
That's very interesting how you see that Pattern or somewhat of a pattern you see when you look in judges in other places in Kings You know, there were people were prophesying and there were hundreds sometimes, right?
But that's not the case whether I'm speaking about the major prophets You'll see major prop but you won't see any major false prophets even in the end time It's you will have the instead of Christ or the Antichrist with his false prophet there he's shown there it's shown as as The only time that you see a single false prophet come you see what I mean?
Yeah Where you know anyway, it's just stuff to meditate on because what it does is it shows that there's a you know How to illustrate what's going on, you know But anyway, I just derailed you on that.
Go ahead
Yeah, so I mean in general I'm just talking about the principle you have the
Obviously the Peter and the Cornelius thing where he gets the dream twice
You have certain things in Genesis like Pharaoh gets the dream twice before Joseph has to interpret it
Things like that and I think Job also sort of mentions on the side and like chapter 33 for God speaks once yes twice yet
man perceives it not
Sort of thing.
So this is sort of understood as a principle not just some Aspect of mosaic law or something like that.
It's generally understood beyond that because Job predates that And it's in the Psalms a few times.
So what I'm wondering is If you need to witnesses generally, where's the second witness to the text itself?
Where's the second witness to Scripture?
We don't even have the original we're dealing with copies.
Where's the Even if we had the original Well, let's just go let's look at that backwards There's a term a literal term for something that there are many copies of but no original was there's a term for that It's a literal term, right?
You know There are a lot of literal terms that they're kind of handy when you find them out because they describe a condition If anyone wants to look it up what it mean what it is There's a literal term for when you just have copies and no original that's called something.
Okay I remember coming across it several times That's what the scripture is.
But the other thing is we buy in its internal management When I just brought up you notice that the the the prophets tend to come out singularly Even with the example of Moses when Aaron and his sister try to kind of rock in there with him, you know And he's like no I get out of here.
I just need Moses, right?
and The other interesting aspect is, you know, I've mentioned this is an old saying by the way from Others have said as well that when you read scripture your it's the only thing you could read Where the author is always present right or his agents, right?
So if if when you're reading it if you if you're getting it if you under comprehending it And the author is always present.
Isn't that two witnesses again?
I mean
The
Aspect of it is very interesting
When you look at the two witnesses being mentioned
it's when something is being challenged or denied or need or claimed or to be proven and
Internally doesn't scripture say that you know, this is true because it's the only place you're gonna get what happens in the future accurately basically
That's how you know how you prove the truth right through prophecy
well
In scripture, he says you will know I am who I am because I'm the only one who could declare
The end from the beginning, right?
That feels like an amalgamation of different things that I said, I don't know if it's said like that.
Oh, yeah Yeah, you could look at it.
Basically the here look you we want to say the Greek says this it's fine.
I'll stand by it The way you prove scripture is true is the only place where you're going to get grade-a information which is in military intelligence You know the great intelligence by ABC, you know all the way down then at number denominations to the letters as well It's a grade-a information about what's going to happen.
There is no way you can give such peculiar detail right Without being true, you know without being true with you know, that level of truth being bestowed on the rest of it No, but here's the other interesting aspect.
You ready?
How many times have we found things added or omitted from scripture many times?
I'm talking about even foundational texts which are still copies right with no original But generally the message comes through Yeah, but I mean anybody can be meticulous.
There are grim wars that are like 5,000 pages, but
You need to show that those things can bear themselves out in reality
So yeah, yeah, right, okay, and they do
But the thing is again if you want to look at how short people's lives are you can have people running around for an entire
Generation shouting the end of the world and it doesn't come and they die and it doesn't matter
Because it was just a fad, right?
and The way they shout it is about The same way all every time that's why when I'm telling people what's coming What's the caveat that I always give and no one's gonna realize it Let me just bring this point because on from a back Back channel side.
We were gonna discuss some things that I don't like discussing for let's just say right loosely Which is you know certain books of prophecy, but from a back Even even go even further back from that Think about it if everyone has access to Poor versions or good versions or interlinear or whatever and it's quite clear about prophecy right How is the Antichrist or you know?
the instead of Christ gonna do all these things if everybody has a copy of a trans or You know a pretty much a pretty good synopsis with some things very highly detailed others not let's say How is he going to do what he's doing if everyone is aware of it?
And the people are so good How are they gonna let that happen?
They don't understand.
It'll be two things They either got the all the details wrong or when it happens.
It's going to be a secret But it'll happen it'll manifest anyway.
You see in other words.
It'll be a secret in plain sight, right?
And also the mindset will change Could you imagine what kind of a mindset humanity is going to be in?
That you will have You know billions of people dying literally overnight Billions with an s you know meaning two three More than 1 billion, and they'll be that's okay.
We'll get back on track, right?
What kind of a mindset requires that so instead of Yelling doom and gloom which you would be listened to and quite popular anytime in human history Discuss what kind of a mindset People are going through The mindset and how it's changed radically right or how it can be changed with axial period Which affects the whole world?
Okay, and there's no way that such a rapid change in the mindset can happen
If it's if your mind and your spirit and all your thoughts and memories are internal
What are they going to do go down and like imagine everyone is like one of these mechanical watches
They're going to go down and rewind every single one
Or is everyone's mind up in another realm longitudinal place where they could just do it remotely like on the network, right?
That's a on a cloud.
You know what I mean like a computer You might you might feel people are like.
Oh, I don't have I remember people Various industries they were so happy when the clouding the cloud stuff cloud computing came out because now they didn't have to invest In this hardware they just put it they just pay Let's say you know compensate a service to put it all on the clouds And they don't have to worry about the thing shutting down right mechanically You know what I mean?
So so but what if what if the people on the cloud side decide to shut you down your hardware is working perfectly But you what happens to the information?
nothing So all of your in order for these rapid mindsets and things to take place on with everyone seemingly Ninety nine point nine nine nine nine nine except for a very few.
There's no way you have much internalized It's all happening externally, and you're accessing it, and you're just so comfortable with it.
You don't think about it How many people do you think in the IT world?
industrialists or whatever schools where are gotten used to the cloud networking now and What if it gets shut down abruptly It hits them across the head doesn't it no matter what they do that.
There's nothing they could physically do in the room to access it right where the in contrary if they had their own hard drives and Something shuts down well all of a sudden they try to bring some text and get get it off the hard drive, right?
No, they they can do more with it
And I'm telling you these mind sets change so drastically because there is nothing in your head
That you're accessing everything from somewhere else
Right, but if it was really just if it was just as simple as making some kind of an adjustment or an edit in some cloud
and
people's
Sort of linear existences would be full of glitches
Because I like wait a minute that just came from nowhere because somebody flipped a switch on the other end it still has to be
Worked out in reality, but it is
No, no
But it is people's lives are full of glitches like for example how many inventors if you ask them how you thought about this and I tell
You was this accident happened, and I noticed right yeah, but that's a that's an aberration
Well not in terms of phenomena, but as far as a social phenomena that doesn't happen enough times for you to be able to
create a
Sample based data set across the entire human population those are specific people that need to get that to advance human society
There's not a lot of that what advancement if you're in a curing period what advancement
Oh, but it has to be advanced to the point where you can take them out.
I'm just talking about forward movement Not quality.
There's no forward move the only forward movement comes after the resurrection That's clear throughout scripture even job that you mentioned earlier.
Yeah, but you're talking about quality.
I'm just talking about Progression as far as time to a certain point Progression time you're being dummy loaded.
I mean in other words.
You know someone who runs two miles on a treadmill
They didn't go anywhere, but they expended the energy of two miles
basically your lifespan is 75 80 90 or a hundred and
You need to be given stuff to expend the that lifespan just dumb shit
Because it was probably better to do that than have you live four or five hundred years
You couldn't fit this number of people
In a 6,000 year time span it would it would have been ten times longer right five times longer eight times longer
no, but the the you can't show me anywhere that
from a
From a biological and chemical and physical perspective in any science that they have found a memory cell
Anywhere that has the actual memory they see things firing off and whatever but nothing and even when they implant memories
Why do you think it's so simple to use?
Psychotronics on people
Because they know it's all external
If you had anything internal that they couldn't psychotronics could only
Can only modify it slightly or obscure it
Now you have to also
understand that there's a complex relationship between the cloud you know where your memory and your your spirit functions on for information and
also, what your your senses
Perceive that go back, and you know affect your spirit right in your mind
They're all tied in so you have this rapid uploading and downloading constantly
I mean, that's what's really neat if you relax into the you know into scripture when you see in certain prophetic writings
How they're told to
Write something and tell the people it's a download
All right
Yeah, it's really interesting
You see it also
these these kinds of discussions and all this I get interesting because it depends on what the
What specialty people are interested in because when you start getting deeper and deeper into a subject?
If a particular person listening doesn't is not into that they don't benefit from the the time That you know of what they're listening to but if you are Usually making remarks and Comments and discussing things that are a general broad Mindset that anyone can grab and use because it has to do with you know a better biological life.
You know food clothing shelter or Something has to do with the senses Because even you know when you read scripture, that's the senses isn't it I mean yes, there's braille, and there's audio.
It's still senses
You see so basically
to have a useful sonic event
It's it's best to keep things as general as possible
But when when you hear that term is very general and not specific people brush it off as being low quality
What if you are general in discussion, but of high quality can that be beneficial and I would suggest
That is the best sonic event you know
Because because ultimately
when you get deeply deep into a subject and give a lot of facts or information on that you are narrowing it down into a
Particular field that someone may not have interest in and now that person tunes out
I'm just I'm just saying that not only about what we're doing here, but just this is a general
General view on community, you know open communications
And I'm what I've noticed this was again this past week was quite a lick a shock to me is
The general platform or the venue known as the internet is just rubbish right now not because it's rubbish
The people that are on it are pretty putting out rubbish
I don't know if they're rubbish, but if I notice how much rubbish does someone have to put out consistently before you say?
They're rubbish Is that a con is that a judgment or a condemnation?
You don't want to condemn, but you can definitely judge that if every time I go and look at what either a venue an Institution or an individual or an author or a writer or an artist musician puts out is rubbish Consistently, what do you do?
I mean you don't know them personally But they're definitely purveyors of garbage Anyway, yeah, it's it's pretty bad But it's not bad that things are going to be bad because of that.
It's only bad because you know That's just the way it's been I'm fine with it.
Yeah, it's it's even the most basic stuff.
There's there's still no I think we mentioned earlier
What about doing a website and just making a list of all the most obvious things that everyone I mean everyone
Everyone has missed
Real basic stuff
Let's put together a list of 50 or 100 things that if you quote-unquote
Do a browser search nothing comes up and it's right in front of you
And it could be explained to a six or seven year old with clarity
And there's just nothing.
What does that tell you right?
There's a very narrow mindset.
Oh, what does that tell you how many websites or web pages or whatever?
Are on the internet Thousands hundreds billions right billions.
That's it, right
Yeah, and and you you have a list of 40 50 or 100 things that are just obvious and you
You put them in a browser and nothing comes up
What does that tell you is is it an it's has nothing to do with quantity its quality now
and what do you think I was harping about when I said these hosts and guests and audience are idiots and across the board you
look the host is just
Looking to produce something like a you know junk food
You bring someone like Ronald McDonald on as a guest and the audience is just eat coprofaglia
shit eaters
Wow, I was like what the hell's going on.
Yeah, that's that's that's pretty much it Mm-hmm.
I think I'm good for today If you are That's fine, it seems like we come around every seven days like this, that's fine.
No, it's not tackling No, I don't know Bruce anything in chat.
Are you?
You know this Nothing at all.
I Already got one of the event up on the servers and I was just do you guys go in right?
We had a part one, well, I cut it into two parts Mm-hmm Okay for easy file transfer.
I see Yeah, this this one was not that poignant It was kind of like a little old over the place.
That's fine.
That's fun.
What I information So what that doesn't telephone books got a lot of information remember those things Remember the telephone of the telephone book they even still put them out.
I think they do.
Yeah, most people Give it to the recycling.
Oh I got a by the way a copy with no originals called a simulacra Simu la CRE.
Thank you.
Someone sent it to me a standalone complex is what it means simulacra a Simulacra is copies with no original Hmm, okay much.
Yeah, it's a literal term Yeah, it's a nice to use a literal terms like that.
And I realize you know people say well you professor It was called a professor so much.
I was like, you know, I'm just gonna Kick back on the grammar use common terms.
I'm not gonna work on elocution Maybe that'll get through to people better But literal there are a lot of literal terms that are very descriptive.
You're descriptive heard of something called a pathetic fallacy It's another literal term.
You know what that is.
I like that one.
Oh You guys still there?
Yeah Bruce have you heard of a literal term called that's a called a pathetic fallacy.
No, and I was just trying to picture it but Yeah, no, it's a literal term pathetic fallacy basically means when you Take inanimate objects and you give them emotional attributes like that's a very happy car Or that's a sad-looking house When you have inanimate objects described with emotional attributes, basically, let's just go to the let's go to the rectangle Actually, I got some emails here.
That's what we've got I got someone here requesting Chat and Another person requesting And another person, okay, that's all they are.
Yeah Link to the new chat.
Oh Yeah, you know there's been about so there's about 50 of you people out there past few days since we created the Relocated chat.
I've gotten about 50 requests So just want to throw that out publicly If you ever go in a chat and you see five or six or seven people Those are people that are I guess sitting in the back in the bus But there's a lot of people riding the bus more than that.
I guess that come through But oh I what I want to do is say let's go back to the what it called the warm rectangle with the pixels on it Is that a is that objective enough for you guys?
Yes.
Yes
Sure, I'm gonna put in it's a warm rectangle with pixels
Let's see if what they have a pathetic fallacy
The attribution of human feelings and responses to inanimate things or animals especially in art and literature there you go
The phrase pathetic fallacy is literally a term for attributing of human emotion and conduct to all aspects within nature
It's a kind of personification is poetic writing for example clouds seem sullen when leaves dance or when rocks are indifferent
No, okay.
Anyway, but there's Those those kinds of terms are very likable because it's shop talk, right?
when you study the What would you call the field of literacy or literature?
The mechanisms behind it there are shop talk ways to describe various forms of literature, right?
Okay
There's lots of terms like that like simulacra empathetic fallacy or whatever whatever
And I think that having a very basic approach to
to communicating it is
Even using the word nice is okay in the British sense
You know, you know why I say the British sense is because you know
Supposedly they have a better command of the English language than most other English-speaking countries
Supposedly yeah
And say they did they're supposed to and
They use the word nice in a certain way, which is not the foolish stupid senseless
etymological
So if you're ever wondering if I ever say nice, I typically try to follow it up with
Presented it is the British would say it or the English
Okay
Any other anything in chat or anything?
Otherwise, we're gonna just call what are you over to out?
No.
No, that's nothing in there Okay And we certainly want to thank the 20 folks that came aboard to listen tonight How cool?
It's a very good Lot of discussions, oh my goodness Where Yes, oh, yes, okay Why not, I mean exactly Exactly.
It's funny.
You know if you back in the early days when I just come out and I spoke publicly
Initially in person I was asked to speak on certain specific topics
And then when I found out about the rectangle you could call in and do audio sonic events or whatever
one of the things I always likes to preface is that no one is paying attention and
to butt into
Call into what
We lost you there Greek
Yeah, Greek is still there
Think you went too far out in the garden
Yeah, thank you Sam
Oh
Well, I
Guess that was well you've ending it
Yeah, it's just as well.
We did three hours.
Yeah, we did we did do that Well, I guess on that note there Sam you have yourself a great great night and be well, thank you likewise Okay Later, bye-bye