Greetings folks, here with the Greek, and in a little while, Sam, hopefully.
So how's things going, Greek?
Oh, they're going.
I just had a sip of coffee there.
Let's do another sonic.
Let's see where people are, or could be.
It seems to be the first day of the 12th month, I'm reckoning, tonight.
Now, has that always been like that, where the 12th moon is kind of iffy, as you put it?
Yeah, but this one is unusual, because each year is different.
This one is progressing quite clearly.
I saw it rise quite prominently and quite distinctly, unlike any other 12th moon I've ever seen.
So that's a first.
But as I see it now, it's about 30 degrees above horizon.
Well, let's say 45 above horizon.
It seems to be one of the smaller ones.
Catch it later.
Excuse me if you catch it later on in the night.
So I would suggest that typically the 12th is the smallest, or it tends to wax that way.
So we'll see.
Yeah, very interesting.
And the first will be last, and the last will be first.
It came like right at the beginning of the 30th day, or the 29th day, it just came right in pretty quick.
The winter months tend to do that.
Interesting.
Winter months tend to be shorter.
We have eclipses coming up, some type of partial, I believe, or some such.
Yeah.
Was that used in biblical references?
Not by itself.
OK.
Yeah, typically what you'll see in biblical references, they don't stand alone.
There's always a grouping of things that have to happen.
Well, not always, but most likely.
They happen in groupings.
That's why someone was telling me, oh, you know, we had recently in a conversation, he was saying, well, we recently had the biblical red moon.
And I'm like, no, he didn't.
What do you mean, we?
Who's what?
And what Bible are you talking about?
That's the crowd think, you know.
Right.
Because where they use that, the moon will be blood red.
Well, that's a partial.
Those are just some words taken out of context, because the whole context is the moon will be blood red and the sun will be black.
So if the moon is blood red and the sun turns black, well, now it's biblical or scriptural.
So it's just morons, you know.
Right.
But there's technical eclipses, you know, ones you may or may not see.
I go by every seven or 10 years what's going on.
There's roughly 16 of them in the past 10 years.
So it's no big deal.
In other words, it's not from a scriptural point of view.
Yeah, how many eclipses in the past 10 years?
More than a dozen.
Oh, yeah, easily.
Of all sorts.
Mm-hmm.
But this is for the ignorant to be impressed by those things, usually, you know.
Just like we discussed before in the media all around, whether alternative or mainstream, how many times was the world supposed to be destroyed already?
And how many times we're supposed to have financial collapses already and pandemics and government crackdowns?
Oh, God, yes.
Yeah, and survival.
Yeah, so this has been going on for a long time, but in recent memory, with this electronic stuff, it gets a little more intense.
You know, if you're watching it a little more, well, it should say easier to get caught up in the worries of the world, as they say.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
So anything going on in chat?
I'm just wondering if anything's been catching your attention lately that you might want to share.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, it's all about mindset, so you have to watch what you reckon.
Like I'm reckoning this is the beginning of another seven-year period starting this springtime.
And this is still – it's a mirror image of the last seven years, but not in the same content that we've – the items that we've seen in the last seven years.
Mirror image, meaning it's still the preparation phase.
In other words, there's a 14-year preparation phase of the Middle East Union, and seven years of that is up.
Now we're going to another seven-year phase of that, you know, double preparation period, right, which will lay us out to – Everything else is picking up over there lately, though, you know.
Right, and it won't – it's – and for the next three-and-a-half years – remember, seven goes three-and-a-half, where it'll be three, four, one, and then three.
So, you know, you're looking at around a lot of things changing now, starting this spring, in that part of the world, and also the whole world in terms of how we'll receive it.
But it'll go through to – what's three years?
2021, the fall, and then between 2021, the fall, to 2025, the spring and summer, there will be no doubt that there's going to be a Middle East Union formed.
Absolutely no doubt.
So, in other words – and it won't be a problem, right?
Right.
So, in other words, what changes have to happen to the mindset for people to accept that?
And not only a Middle East Union, but also a world power center.
Right.
So, what's going to happen?
And you kind of wonder about the methodologies being used in order to get – you know, you're talking mass among people.
Yeah, but they're dumb, or stupid, or morons, or whatever you want to say it.
So, it's pretty easy to look at a crowd of people in a football stadium.
Right, right.
Or, you know, how much does it take to get them to do something?
Yeah.
30,000 people.
Well, 20,000 average on a full stadium.
Yeah.
What does it take to get them agitated?
Put a guy in a different color uniform and throw a pigskin ball at them?
Throw a little foot at them, a little drink.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I mean, it's not that difficult.
Yeah, they're really – yeah, people are just – yeah.
That's never been an issue, by the way, ever.
In any society.
How do we get the people to do something?
That's never been a problem.
If you have the wherewithal, you can do it.
Even when I read the Holy Writs, and you just look at the mindset back, you've got to wonder what the hell is going through their heads, you know?
It's the same then, back then.
They were not very different.
Yeah.
Not much has changed.
Well, it will.
Yeah.
The perfect part about it is that it's – well, it's once you see that it's just so much going on for so many thousands of years, so many people have to come through.
The perfect part is, well, they do keep their situation pretty tight, the gods, meaning, you know, you're not going to break out of it.
You're going to have stupid people, and you're going to be in darkness for X amount of time, and then you break out when we decide the time is right, and it's fulfilled.
You know, the time that we set forth is fulfilled.
That's the perfect aspect of it.
There's a discipline to it, by the way, to understanding reality.
I just want to – let's go back to something in chat.
I was in chat earlier, and someone put a question in Anon.
I was glad they did, about things being absorbed and giving a reference of oils and salts and baths and things.
Right, right.
And, you know, when I see something like that, you know, it checks my naïveté, because I get naïve.
I'm like, oh, yeah, everybody knows by now that, you know, everything, the medical stuff and science is bullshit, and they've already got it.
Then I kind of look, and I see questions like that.
I'm like, wow, people still believe the propaganda.
So the first thing that I have to reach for is what?
An image or a photograph or a drawing.
You see the intestines, right?
That's pretty accurate, by the way.
Hello.
Hey, Sam.
You made it.
Yes.
Am I audible?
Cool.
So just to finish up the thought real quick is you just put up an image of something that's discernible or something that is accountable and verifiable, validatable of what you're asking and look at it and see what you see.
And I put up the image of a steel-belted radial tire, an intestine, and the skin, and there's no difference between the three things.
Right.
Well, obviously the skin and the intestine and a steel-belted car tire are different items, but there's no difference.
Just judging from the questions that he was throwing about the inductance, I think that's a toughie for a lot of people.
I'm into electronics.
You are.
And we can look at two coils together, isolation.
I think people find that just a little hard to wrap themselves around.
Now, are you acting as their attorney representing them?
No, I am not.
I'm just throwing it out there as a general.
So the fact – I know, but here, so let's just use it as a fact.
Let's use it as a fact that it is difficult for them.
You know what I have to say about that?
Too bad.
Okay.
You're going to have to learn the discipline, right, just a little bit.
Right.
And you don't have to learn it strictly from electronics.
It could be acoustics as well.
That's why I mentioned resonance and dissonance.
Resonance.
Also, you can completely do it within the biological sciences.
You don't even have to go into the inanimate objects.
Look at what certain animals eat and why you eat what you eat.
And look at how your body reacts to normal things, breathing, when you're washing.
You know, the animals that we're given to eat lawfully versus ones that, you know, there's a reason for that, you know.
Well, you know what the reason is?
I was having several conversations recently about it.
You know, there's people still that say, well, the law's done away with Greek.
And I'm like, oh, which law?
Traffic law?
Tax law?
The Hebraic rabbinic oral law?
Which one are you talking about?
Right.
They don't understand.
But the basic thing then is people wrestle with it.
Most people give lip service.
If you meet someone who talks their walk and walks their talk, it's very rare.
I've only met maybe one or two being on this planet for half a century plus a few years.
Now, people sound like they walk their talk or talk their walk or want to do things, but it's different from doing it.
The essential part of it is this.
A lot of lip service is given to the gods, all the gods, whether it's a minor demon all the way to the most high that people try to find out about.
And they try to bring in their human rationale, meaning what they see in society.
And basically the conversations I've had this past week with people asking about the law, and I've actually volunteered this a little bit also, I said, well, you know, you read Genesis 1, and he says he made the light and it was good, and he separated the water from the land and it was good, and he made this creature and it was good.
But when it gets to telling you – and you're fine with that, right?
But when it gets to telling you what's good to eat, no, you don't want that.
No, no.
See, that's not good now.
Right.
You get it?
That's why I say it's all right there in the first chapter of Genesis.
If you just watch how people handle that, you'll predict the rest.
Right, right.
Not through Genesis alone, but watch how people handle Genesis, the first, let's say, two or three chapters, and you're going to say, oh, this guy here, he says he's into it, but he's really not.
Watch.
Ten years later, you know, it's like, oh, yeah, still.
Or a year later, they drop it or whatever.
You could see the mindset because the essence of the mindset is this.
You know, when you see a baby fish, you know it's going to swim.
A baby bird, you know it's going to fly.
When you see a baby human, you know it's just seeking joy, isn't it?
Right.
You ever been around babies?
Yeah, you know, even when they poop on themselves, poop, you know, it doesn't really tickle you or whatever.
Even with severe diaper rash, they're still seeking joy, right?
Right.
So that doesn't change.
Just like the baby fish, you know, is going to swim and the baby bird is going to fly, the baby human is going to be an old human, and what are they still essentially wanting to do is what?
Seek joy, right?
So they don't understand that when the Most High says it's good, that's where you find your joy.
They look at both sides and say, well, humanistically it's been done differently here, or maybe it's up in question.
You see, so they don't know how to find joy in these things of the gods.
But that's another discussion.
It gets into the priestly function and the spiritual consultation aspect.
It gets into a deep aspect of what people call philosophy, almost philosophical.
You know, there's a conflict between man and the gods, in case you haven't noticed, right?
Right.
And that's also been – you can witness it.
An easy place to find it is in Jeremiah when, you know, they know the shit's about to go down, and they go to Jeremiah and say, oh, we acknowledge that you're truly a prophet of Yahweh.
We'll do anything you say.
What should we do?
And he tells them, well, don't go to Egypt.
Stay here.
Do this.
Oh, no, no, no, we don't like that.
No, we don't want to do that.
So five seconds, ten seconds, they're going to say, well, do anything you say.
And it's like, oh, no, no, we don't want to do that.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you see what's going on?
It's because they don't know where to find their joy.
They're always looking, thinking there's some joy somewhere to be found that they don't – if they just understand a little bit more, they'll find it, and they don't get it.
All right, with that said, Sam, how are you doing?
I'm doing okay.
Doing fine.
I've been missing from some episodes due to a combination of fatigue and professional commitments, but I hope to be able to maintain a flow of engagement as per usual as we move along.
All right, let's start moving it.
Move it, McMahon.
Move it.
I'm calling from my phone today, not my computer, but I'm audible, yes?
Yes.
Okay.
I hope that I won't cut out.
By the way, whenever you hear the word smartphone, that's a pathetic fallacy as a literal mechanism, right?
Because a phone can't be smart.
It's inanimate.
But anyway, so I think we brought up the definite what pathetic fallacies are.
All right, man, rock on.
Get it moving.
Get this road on the show.
Sure.
Well, for today, I can't say that I'll be as wide ranging.
I think the last time we jumped around to a bunch of different things.
But for the past week or so, I just kind of focused on one topic.
So I'll kind of go narrow on that and bring up some things and ask a few questions.
But there's this prophetic theme of certain nations being brought up that I'm looking at.
And I think that the nation of Edom is always quite interesting to explore, because there are some interesting things said about them.
And people don't really focus.
I guess the initial inclination for those with a casual interest in the text is to wonder what Edom even is and why it's important.
And at best, you kind of know that they're descendants of Esau, but you know, so what?
And so is Amalek, and they're in a different light.
Right.
I mean, theoretically, even today, you say Amalek to semi-religious, quote unquote, Jew, and he's like, where is he?
So I could go kill him.
But anyway, go ahead.
Yeah, I think that kind of thinking is the product of a widespread convention of downplaying the importance of the minor prophets, which are some of the more instructive books on prophecy.
But when you survey the teachings of the Old Testament, you'll find that Isaiah kind of summarizes judgment against the nations at the end of the age, and some other books also.
And it describes that there's going to be this big terminal battle in which Yahweh will be the victor.
Isaiah 34, I think, is…
And by the way, just to refresh people, when they hear what you just said, they think of Armageddon.
And there's no battle at Armageddon, by the way.
There's a gathering place.
The battle is at the place of decision, right?
Which is Jehoshaphat, right?
Yes.
But continue.
Yeah, the valley.
Yeah.
So there's…
When we say things, I can see the gears turning in people's heads where they are trying to associate what we're saying with what they know.
And folks, I just want to remind everyone, just everything you think you know with word associations, like Bible or Moses or Edom or Battle of this, forget it.
It has what you think you know means…
Remember that movie in Men in Black when Will Smith is being introduced for the first time?
Just remember, from now on, your knowledge and your stuff means jackdick or whatever from now on, right?
So I just want to bring up a point that the chances of anyone listening actually associating what we're saying with what they've learned out there being useful is very slim.
So I just wanted to throw that in there.
I know it sounds kind of cocky, arrogant, condescending, but that's not meant to be so.
So I just want to say from the beginning, very often most people will discover, especially if Sam and I are speaking and giving references, that it's quite contrary to what's out there, quote unquote, on the rectangle, what you've been taught at the Churchianity or even if you're an academic.
So anyway, I just want to continue.
Go ahead, Sam, about Edom.
Yes.
Yeah, everything that you say is as it is.
I kind of just plow on in spite of that because I can't accommodate that sort of thing, but the disclaimer is fine.
Yeah, and I don't think that mindset is going to be accommodated as the time comes, so it would behoove anyone to be prudent and start dismantling and reexamining what they think they know.
So, Isaiah 35, we'll talk about, sorry, 34, we'll talk about Yahweh has wrath against the nations and fury against their hosts and he will doom them and get them up to a slaughter.
But it's revealing that despite explicitly condemning the nations of the world as a whole, also called the heathen, depending on the version that you're reading, the only nation really that's mentioned by name in Isaiah 34 is Edom.
It's used as an umbrella term, which means that it's supposed to represent all of the gentle nations.
When my sword has been satiated in the heavens, behold, on Edom it shall descend, for I have doomed the people to judgment.
But he's talking about the whole world, though.
So we have an intersection, which can be a conundrum for some people of various nations that are at play here.
We're talking about the end of the age.
So on one hand you have the Antichrist and he's called an Assyrian.
The end time system is called Mystery Babylon.
The major city out of which that system is managed is correspondingly called Babylon.
But the entire gentile nations are amalgamated into Edom, meaning that the end time kingdom as a whole is in some way Edomite, which no one really addresses.
The thing is there, is it stylistically as Edom, or is it because they physically can't be all descendants of Edom or bloodline of Edom?
So it would be in a stylistic way, just like, for example, if you said England and the U.S. and Japan were Babylonian systems, that would be pretty accurate, even though they're not Babylonian.
So is it an Edomite type system?
Then the thing is, what do we know about the Edomites?
And the thing is, very little, but we do see them popping up quite often.
Isn't there another prophet that's a short one, a minor prophet that's dedicated the entire thing towards Edom as well, other than Isaiah?
Or is it just Isaiah?
Yeah, there are others.
There's one that I think is just dedicated completely towards just Edom.
Now, Edom, I would suggest is, what would you say generally?
I'm not in front of any reference material.
And what's interesting is when we do this together on the sonic events, it's just strictly what's, you know, in between the ears, you know, in the gray matter, whatever I'm receiving from, you know, external input.
I'm not looking at anything.
I'm not looking anything up, as we're not even in front of the computer.
I'm in the kitchen right now, just making some coffee.
But from memory, I would suggest that, correct me or confirm, Sam, Edom would be generally the Negev area, right, the northeastern part of the Negev, like southern part below, just below the Dead Sea.
And borders, yeah, borders could extend east and west indefinitely, depending on their ability of conquest at the time.
And who would be there now?
We don't know.
It's a bunch of stray Jordanian enclaves, right, and basically Israeli farmers mixed in with some Egyptians.
I know they coexist, right?
Is that what's going on there right now, I think?
Yeah, that's the last time I checked.
Yeah.
So just to start placing the matter, you know, the substance behind what we're talking about, that's okay.
So, yes, looking at the meaning, we can start by, I guess, looking at the meaning of the names.
Sort of etymology tends to be a good basis for starting, based on Genesis 25.
It's usually taken to mean red, because Esau says to Jacob, please feed me with that red stew you have, because I'm weary.
That is why his name is called Edom.
I can't argue with that.
But Adam, yeah, it's like Adam and Adamite also.
Adamite is also used sometimes when you read the earth in King James.
You look at it.
It's not Adetz or Eretz.
It's Adamite or Edomite, which also means they've used – so they've used it with Adam, the Edomites, and also the earth, the soil, meaning soil or dirt.
There does seem to be some kind of a parallelism between these words, Adam for mankind, Adome or whatever, for red, Odum or Odum for redness or redstone.
And then you have Edom or Edom.
Like you said, the word Adam and red are spelled the same in some places, Adam and earth are spelled the same in some places.
In a plural sense.
Yeah, Aleph, you have the Aleph, the doll, and the Mem, and then you have variations of that, different good pointings for pronunciation.
Edom is spelled a little differently.
There's a Vav in there, so it's more letters.
I've seen some places, and you just mentioned it, that Adam actually means – if you want to look at what it actually means, it's made out of the earth, or more specifically, made out of the red earth.
And Edomites have meant something like red people.
So there's an intermingling of meanings here that you have to understand how the language works to sort of get to the bottom of it.
And the support for that sort of explication is the interconnection between Acts and Amos.
There's a quote in Acts that they're talking about the book of Amos, and the quote is, So here, once again, we see Edom being equated with the Gentile nations, which is consistent with Obadiah and Isaiah.
But then the Greek New Testament, they do something weird, and I don't know if it's because it's just the Greek.
Oh, no, really?
Did they do something weird in the Greek New – oh, no, I'm just joking.
Go ahead.
It could be.
I don't know if it's just that, but it's suspect.
So in Acts 15, James is talking, the one they call James, and he quotes from that Amos.
And the words of the prophets agree with this as it is written, So Acts changes Edom to mankind, which is closer to the Adam.
Yeah, it would be that, Adam, yeah.
So, but the word for – Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, but the word for mankind in Greek is anthropon, which is sort of corporate mankind.
Right.
And I think the Septuagint version for Amos also says anthropon, for Amos 9, instead of saying Edom.
So for whatever reason, the Greek documents, whether it's the Septuagint or the New Testament, don't want to read that as Edom.
Well, also, you have to remember, when you say the Septuagint, there's really two parts of it.
The part that is the formal Septuagint was just the first five books of Moses.
The rest of it was done hundreds of years later and almost at the tail end of when the first century, right, you see.
So the Septuagint, in a classical sense, is just the first five books of Moses.
And then the rest of it was done much later.
I just wanted to throw that in there.
So it would make more sense as the Greek got more contemporary that you could see the definitions change.
So I just want to throw that little, I guess that's trivia, isn't it?
Biblical trivia.
So, yeah, it's good to have.
I knew it in a cursory sense, but I haven't really thought about that.
So, yeah, the Leningrad Codex obviously shows it differently.
And that is the standard Masoretic hand down from the times.
I don't really know why they do that because, like I said, the spelling for Edom is different.
It has evolved in it.
I don't know why they can't see the difference and they're forcing it to be mankind.
But either way, I'd go with what's there.
They have rules.
They have rules when they do these translations, let's say.
They're being, you know, they have officers and overlords over the scribes, which are the labor.
And, you know what I mean?
So, yeah.
In other words, changes will be made to fit the preconception of the day.
Sure.
You know.
But nonetheless, the point here of this conversation tonight is why is there such an emphasis on Edom and how can that be resolved in terms of the coming times, right?
That's how I think about it.
I haven't given it much thought because I see it as a pattern to be watched in a developmental way, meaning if we look at the two things when you hear of a people, essentially.
The first thing is geographical, right?
And I think I've mentioned this before.
When you read Israel, for example, or Babylon or Cush or whatever in the Bible, it doesn't matter who lives there.
It's speaking geographically and the people there, right?
So if you read in Scripture something's going to happen in Egypt and you say, well, it's all Chinese now.
It doesn't matter.
It's still Egypt.
It's geographical first, right?
And that's what I've noticed in Scripture.
And I'm not saying this in a dogmatic way.
Well, the Greek says it's like this means it's like that, right?
No, no, not at all.
I have noticed a pattern that it considers the geographical part first.
For a long time I've always been saying, for years now, the problems of mankind and his environment are a result of how mankind deals with each other.
In other words, if you have an unlawful society, when people are dealing with each other unlawfully, the earth starts to fight against you, you know, with famine, drought, too much rain, you know, all this other stuff.
So man has an interconnectedness with the earth, not like the New Agers are saying, but the earth is used to resolve, I would say, punishment on mankind.
You know, the better mankind is more lawful, the better the earth is and vice versa.
So we can't leave the earth aspect out of it.
As a matter of fact, there are a lot of verses that are directed specifically towards the earth's behavior, towards man, right, and things that will happen to the earth.
So it sounds kind of New Agey to most people, but, you know, hey, I'm not making this up.
So that's why another reason just to back up why I say when you read Edom, it's geographical.
But essentially, when you see how it's being used in many tenses, past, present and future, it's definitely what the people are doing, because the whole world is not in that geographical region.
So now we have to break out of that and see what kind of an influence or fashion or status they create that the world, let's say, falls into their category.
So the first thing I want to look at is geographically.
I think we covered that.
I mean, there's not much more we can do other than getting into geology, basically saying what part of the world it is right now, what it's always been and who's there now and who's been there before.
We can get into the history of it briefly.
There were basically nomadic people.
And if you do some research on the Edomites, you might find that at one point they all left and went up to the northwest.
Right.
And it was pretty much empty.
And then, you know, so there's all these migrations in that area.
And again, geographically, if we go there now, I mean, I think they're trying to do some desalination there, you know, and bring water from Egypt and some agriculture.
And it's a mixed bag of Israelis and people from Jordan and Egypt.
And other than that, nothing to see here.
Move along.
So how does that transfer into the paradigm that we read about in scripture?
And that's a big question mark.
And I think it can be investigated.
I think in the next few years we'll see a lot of development there.
Like I just kind of threw something in there.
If you want to research, there's a huge venture.
It's been on the books for half a decade now about creating desalinization, not one plant but many plants and systems to provide the Middle East with fresh water that goes through there.
I don't know if anyone's aware of that.
And since I used to work with water, I had my finger on that for a short while.
I think it's still in progress, but it's in the billions, you know, kind of thing.
It's nothing small.
So other than what we've just mentioned, I would say there's some kind of a development to watch out for in that area geographically.
And then there's, of course, the people.
Do you think we've covered the geographic enough, Sam?
Do you want to – anything else you want to – before we move on?
I don't want to touch on the geographics too much.
I mean, I'll get into one thing later.
But regarding the Earth, I mean, the reason why it would sound new agey, what you said, is because, you know, and I brought this up, there's always going to be this disconnect because you're not seeing the manifestations take place in front of your eyes.
Maybe I can point to, you know, the – what's it called?
The sinkholes in the Dead Sea area.
That's an anomaly.
Or I can point to certain odd things going on in tropical regions as far as I don't really understand this.
But you can't really – you don't see in real time the Earth doing anything significant to cause a blowback against mankind on a wholesale level.
You know, they're able to build their largely Western civilizations and expand that influence throughout the world.
And it doesn't seem as if there's any hiccups in that.
So it remains a largely esoteric concept that the Earth is alive and has sentience.
Oh, yeah.
And it's getting better, Billy.
And its environment is getting better amidst all the cries of global warming and environmental calamity by the academia – academics and academia maniacs or whatever you want to call them.
The Earth is in pretty good state because it's part of the setup, right?
And what I meant by the Earth, if you read in many ancient writs when people – a group of people, even if you read in – I think it was in Exodus or Joshua, Book of Joshua.
A family withheld some things that should have been destroyed or left, and the ground opened up and swallowed them right there, right?
The Earth swallowed up.
Oh, yeah.
No, of course it did it on the command, but there are rules there.
Like, for example, the main reason why the inhabitants in Canaan and all that other area were – what do you call it when you kick someone off – when you kick a renter out, when someone's renting and you – anyway, Bruce, help me out with that.
They were expelled.
Evicted.
Yeah, they were expelled.
Evicted, yes.
Thank you.
That sounds a little harder.
Evicted, yeah.
They were evicted because of their transgressions on the land, right?
And then when the Babylonians came in, because the way they acted, it was – now that you're gone off of Israel to the Israelites, the land can enjoy its Sabbaths, right?
You see, that's also thrown in there, so there's a contract there.
But whether it's direct or indirect, there's a lot of evidence of that, is the Earth being handled as a sentient being when it comes to what to do and what not to do.
But as you see, if you go – when you go towards the – right before the mop-up crew comes, the Earth is cut loose to do what it – it rolls, it's on its axis.
It shakes to the point where the islands are covered and the mountains – it's finally said, okay, go ahead, and the whole planet – of course, on his command.
And it's always on his command, just as the most malevolent spirits are on his command as well, until to a certain point where he cuts them loose.
And concerning this aspect of the geography, I mean, yes, this is interesting because you have countries being tied down to geography separate of the people.
And to me, what that points to is sort of – it reinforces the idea of, as you've said, Scripture is about the gods.
So there's an Elohim aspect here where he – when certain nations are addressed, obviously he's not talking to rocks or the Earth.
You have these places that are tied to certain Elohim that either control the area or have a certain type of jurisdiction.
And maybe they can be expelled or evicted or – but then the jurisdiction gets transferred to whoever has displaced them.
So when he says, Edom, I'm going to do X, Y, and Z, he could just as easily be talking to a particular entity called Edom.
Right.
The entity that's responsible for Edom.
He's not talking to the human beings.
Like the prince, it would be – it wouldn't be right to say it is the prince of Edom, just like you say the prince of Persia and Daniel.
But it wouldn't be a wild speculation to think that way.
It would be actually fairly accurate as well, by inference.
Yeah, because he's never talking really to the people, unless it's Israel.
And then he's talking to usually their leader.
Because the people never seem to know what's going on.
That's right.
And that's always been a conundrum to many.
Yeah, even in – But they don't know anything.
Right.
Like the destroying angel that David was watching, you know.
Like 1950s sci-fi, you know, the little spaceship with the little green aliens come out and what's the first thing they tell the guy mowing his lawn?
Take me to your leader, right?
Yeah, it's an unwritten directive.
So, yeah, I mean that's why I think I'm probably one of the only people on the internet that come out and just call everyone a blatant moron.
Why not?
It's fairly accurate.
But anyway, go ahead.
Sure.
You need protection to do that though.
Some people don't have it.
So to conclude on that point, the final world empire will in some way heavily feature the influence of Edom, which in some way represents all of mankind.
So to specifically look at who are the Edomites and what, you know, the subtleties are of their influence.
I mean, the Judeans in the first century, they knew of the Isaiah 35 prophecies against Edom because they obviously had the Tanakh and they'd read it in the synagogues where the leadership would.
They knew where the land of Edom was, but they were banking on the Messiah coming in the first century.
They didn't think that the geographical location of Edom was significant because at the time, Edom was not a significant power.
And in Isaiah, it says that they will be and that the nations will be represented by them.
So the Jews, the Judeans at that time, they identified Rome as symbolizing Edom.
And anyone can see from non-biblical literature of the first, about the first century, that Rome was considered to be Edom.
They called the Romans Edomites and even Herod, that was the sort of government put there by the Romans, he was an Edomite himself.
Yeah, that's not far-fetched because there was an exchange policy in society, you know, like the Philistines were probably Minoan.
I think the scripture actually refers to that loosely.
I can't confirm or deny, but yeah, I've seen that.
I'm still looking at it.
You know, or Greek, you know, but the Minoans are not Greek.
There was a Mycenaeans and the Minoans.
It's like saying Italian and Portuguese.
I mean, they're considered.
And just like, you know, Alexander the Great, was he really Greek or was he Macedonian?
And, you know, Macedonia exists today.
It's not part of Greece.
It's disputed.
But do they speak Greek?
No.
You could say, and some people think they do, but he's Macedonian.
He would say Alexander is Greek.
Yeah, it's Macedonian, right.
But he spread Hellenism in a way that, you know, very similar to an American army today going somewhere and they'd say, well, he's bringing English.
The Americans are bringing English stuff.
Well, they are.
Right.
But are they English?
No.
It was basically he was supplanting, well, just moving around the Hellenism in a way that had never done before.
And also it was in a state that it had never been because prior to that, if you look at the Minoans and the Mycenaeans, their language was a pictographic where you had a picture, did an entire word.
You had a thousand, two thousand.
So, you know, you had linear A for the Minoans and linear B language for the Mycenaeans.
Right.
And if you're.
Yeah, actually, it's it can be if they don't have a Rosetta stone, let's say, but it can be with more archaeology.
That's why I think I've stated before what's the most precious or most valuable find an archaeologist can find.
It's something that has what on it, writing on it.
So and if you anyone who is not a diversion, but just if you want to go through an acid trip, especially if you're into what's called modern art, look up Kiklodik art, C Y C L A D I C, Kiklodik with a C or a K, Kiklodik art.
And the sculpture looks the same.
They're finding, you know, it's been found for a long time now, but it rivals any modern sculpture that you've ever seen.
And this is, you know, we're talking twenty five hundred B.C. Right.
Two thousand.
I'm sorry.
Two thousand B.C. A thousand B.C. to two thousand B.C. So going back to what were we talking about?
Sorry, the Edomites.
Going back to the Edomites and the Romans, the connection there.
I wouldn't say that the lines are blurry.
It's just they are seemingly on the surface, because we if you delve in very much like tuning a fine watch, you'll see the connections.
But I'm not aware of any major connection.
I would say that they are.
I'm just saying the Judeans said that that was their propaganda thing.
That was their brainwashing because they couldn't rationalize.
Well, how are the Edomites relevant?
Well, because Edom is an irrelevant country.
Oh, so the Romans are Edom.
Yeah, but I don't see.
No, I don't see them as actually being descendants of Edom.
I don't see.
No, I see the more of the European stock that stayed there from the Mycenaean Minoan mix and post Exodus.
And there were actually a penal colony started from the Greek sort of civilization.
But I would suggest that throwing about Edom in many different ways has a value in it, because it is being thrown around in many different ways in the end as being very significant.
And developmentally, we don't see any of it, you know, how it could be.
Even even look, even just a parallel with the Edom being so significant in the end.
Let's say another thing to look at is Babylon.
Right.
And if you look at Babylon, what's there?
I mean, what, 5000 people live there and they're growing palm trees.
What's going on?
Nothing right now.
Right.
And it's south of Baghdad.
So not in we say Babylon people, you know, it's the spiritual side to it, which I think is much detail is given in the book of Zacharias.
Right.
So we still have going to see a lot of development there.
So, by the way, there is a real estate firm that's trying to raise billions to rebuild Babylon right now.
They're Saudi or UAE real estate firm.
So anyway, back to Edom.
Yes.
So, like I said before, they mean the word loosely means red people based on Genesis 25.
Anyway, it doesn't mean that they have a red complexion, complexion, complexion necessarily.
But I've read any more than Adam would have.
But I've read that it could mean red haired, which I guess is plausible.
I mean, red hair is such a visually unique marker that it would plausibly have been incorporated into the name of any people.
I also know that archaeologists in Egypt have uncovered what looks like the city of Alvarez or what they call the city of Alvarez, which has some compelling evidence for being where the Israelites lived before the Exodus.
And inside a tomb, they found the remains of a statue of a red haired, fair skin, Canaanite figure that is said to be Joseph, based on the prestigious burial location, the non-Egyptian ethnicity, which is clear in the statue and the multicolored coat depiction.
There's also documentaries that have been made on that.
And, you know, I looked at them and I was like, OK, that's believable.
But obviously, I'm not there to know what's solid and what's not.
But it looks plausible.
The Danites I've read also probably had red hair.
So what's involved?
There's also the sense of does red mean, you know, something carnal or fleshy?
Or is it part of some duality between Esau and Jacob, since one of them was chosen to be loved and the other chosen to be hated?
I haven't explored that too much, but it's not a complete throwaway material.
Yeah, I would stick with the etymology.
That's always safe because that doesn't change.
You know what I mean?
And then there's etymology.
There's what you can discern from the scripture.
And then there's archaeology.
And then, of course, you have to understand the time that you're living in.
And hopefully there'll be some shovels hitting the ground, you know, and finding more things, which there are every day.
And it's pissing off, by the way, a lot of the archaeologists that if you do follow archaeology on a daily basis, a lot of archaeologists, you get a sense in their writing style that they're not very happy that they're finding things to confirm, quote-unquote, biblical myths.
They're not happy about that.
So.
Yeah.
As far as the geography goes, like we've said, Edom is south of Israel.
At one point, it did border the Red Sea.
And the name the Red Sea is derived from the Greek Erythraean Sea, which third century Greek writers say was named after some king.
But that's questionable.
It feels like a throwaway explanation.
Was it named after Edom?
I don't know.
It could be, but I won't insist on it.
It would be a good coincidence just to think of it that way.
Yeah.
Nonetheless, it was at one point the Greek name for the entire Indian Ocean, not just the small part of it today called the Red Sea.
We know the Greek literature, the Greco-Roman navigation books and things like that.
So Edom would have been important because it allowed it would have allowed people who lived in that region to go into mercantile enterprises and trading and commerce.
And I think it's safe to say that they would have done that because ancient people usually had a habit of playing to their strengths when it came to geography and natural resources.
Not like, you know, today where Africa has tons of minerals and favorable climate, but they don't really make much for their indigenous populations.
They just get it taken by other countries.
Cultural thing.
Also, their culture doesn't like doing things a certain way.
And when they don't budge, then they get they lose it anyway, underhandedly.
So, yeah, kind of like the opposite of that would be like the black market in the Western culture.
You know, they have no interest in legalizing, quote unquote, drugs because the people that are in control of the laws are making too much money on the black market.
So there's an aspect of not capitalizing, quote unquote.
I don't like using that word because, you know, I've defined it before as capitalism being when you're done using something, you destroy it so no one else can use it.
Capitalizing on what's on the African continent would change commodity prices.
So, you know, for example, in Arizona, there's enough one copper mine has enough copper to supply the entire world supply for the next 400 years at the current demand of production.
Right.
So what what happened when that was discovered is the largest copper find in history ever.
All the big copper mining companies purchased a share in it and shut it down.
So now you have stable copper prices.
Right.
So anyway.
Yeah.
But the people that are you know, they were they were relating like, you know, for example, what you'll find in the near future.
If you do history as Afghanistan was a supplier of a lot of the precious metals and stones to the ancient world, you know, then look how far away Afghanistan, modern day Afghanistan is from Rome or Greece or even the Levant.
Right.
It's not like a week's journey.
It's a six month's journey round trip.
Right.
If you're hauling stuff, even if you're hauling ass, you might be able to do it in three or four.
So like, you know, a lot of the tin and the bronze ingredients, lapis lazuli, diamond.
Yeah.
So.
And if indeed the Edomites had a sea named after them, they would have been very interested in productive mercantilism and commerce.
So I do think that that would have been a natural thing there.
Yeah.
But who are the where are they?
And the thing is, when were they at their peak?
When when did they did they have an arch in their dominance?
You know, when what were they doing, when and how and what was what befell them?
You know, that's an interesting thing.
So from a from an end times perspective, one would say because of the significance, you know, the paradigm that's put on them, you know, like what?
Just like Edom, you know, what will happen to Edom, for example, is being significant development.
There has to be a lot of development in that area or amongst the identity of those people.
And, you know, by the way, when you read scripture, just because it's something blatant doesn't mean that it's going to be known.
Like an example is the is the Christ or people sometimes want to use the Christ because, you know, speaking English, people use Messiah, Mashiach, right?
And there's an Arabic word for him as well.
But basically, the Christ, there's so many prophecies of when he would show up on the earth and his character and all that.
But how many people knew the prophecies well enough to pinpoint when he would be born and where and how and all that?
Very few, only a handful, other than the descendants of Abraham, the Magi that came from the east.
And maybe there was an old man and an old woman that met his earthly parents when he was circumcised that prophesied to her.
Remember?
So, so very few people.
So another example to think about is, you know, when you say, you know, there's a lot of biblical terms that are kicked around like apocalyptic, which doesn't mean what people think.
It just means to reveal.
But when you say apocalyptic, it means disastrous.
No, not really.
And also Armageddon, you know, there's no, you see, all these things are misnomer.
They're not really understood.
And another one is Antichrist, right?
There's a lot of information on identifying the Antichrist in there.
So if it's, if the information is so free everywhere, anyone can access it, right?
Even if you go to a cheap hotel room, you open the drawer, what's there?
A Gideon Bible, right?
So, or on the rectangle, how many people do you think are actually going to be able to identify the Antichrist when he comes into power using biblical references?
Almost none, very few.
It sounds kind of asinine to say that, but I assure you it's true.
Right?
So, otherwise it won't happen, right?
Otherwise, you know, if so many million people that know, if you put all seven and a half billion people, let's say, in a big room and said, whoever heard of the Antichrist, raise your hand.
How many of the seven and a half, whatever corresponding languages, let's say you spoke in tongues, which means you spoke in every language.
How many people in the seven and a half billion people in that one room would raise their hand and said they heard of the Antichrist type figure?
About half?
Three quarters?
Right?
At least.
Now, it would be conservative to say four or five billion people out of the seven and a half billion would raise their hand, I've heard of it.
So, how is it going to take place if they've heard of it and know so much about the Antichrist?
It's not, they don't know Jack, you see.
So, when you bring up something like Edom and we don't see it, it's probably something that we don't, it will not ever be seen as such.
You have to know it.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I will say, I mean, I have yet to compile all the evidence, but what I've looked into points to the fact that, and you sort of mentioned it.
I mean, these things can be known.
I don't think that it's hidden.
Well, I guess it's hidden from a cosmic perspective, but it's also right in front of you.
And unless the line of thought that I'm going down is completely wrong, I mean, because I've looked into it now, it's obvious, but the information is there.
You mean regarding the Edomites' significance?
Yeah, because I mean, their influence is not, is clearly has not come from that region, or at least their influence has not extended into modern times.
It would have been, you know, ancient.
And what they have become powerful in has been under a different form, under a different name.
That we use, right.
But the gods don't use it.
The gods probably retain the Edom for them.
For example, isn't there a verse somewhere where the Edomites try to make it up to the heavens, and he throws them back down to the earth?
Or am I mistaken on that?
I haven't come across that one.
There is a verse that says that they have places in the rocks that they like to hide, and they think that they're so smart, and so he's going to bring them down.
Hmm.
There's a verse somewhere regarding a group of people that try to make it out into the heavens, meaning, you know, past the first heaven, right, into space.
And he throws them back down to the earth.
Anyway, that's, maybe I'm just getting a mixed signal there.
But I might, when I go, I'm going to go into the office here in a moment.
I'm just doing some chores, believe it or not, and muting.
Hopefully that's not interrupting the conversation.
And I'm fully aware of what you're saying.
So I'm still present.
I'm just multitasking, like walking and chewing gum kind of thing, right?
That's fine.
From what I've looked into, points to that the people who first established and inhabited the city of Tyre, which is known for its mercantile and commercial enterprises, were people that came from the Dead Sea region, where Edom was located.
As you mentioned, they moved to the northwest.
And these are the same people that later became called the Phoenicians.
So we need to address the Phoenicians.
These are the most ambiguous ancient people who have ever come across, even more confusing than separating Babylonians from Chaldeans.
One minute they're called Canaanite, the next minute they're Phoenician.
Then you find out that the word Phoenician is just a name given to them by the Greeks, so it's not an indigenous or ethnic name.
By calling Native Americans Indians, it doesn't explain anything about them or where they came from.
And even Wikipedia says the name does not correspond exactly to a cultural identity of the Phoenicians themselves.
Their civilization was organized in city-states similar to those of ancient Greece, and each city-state was politically independent, and it's uncertain to what extent the Phoenicians viewed themselves as a single nationality.
So the scholars aren't giving us anything.
Well, you know they were in between what I call the Hatti, or the Hittites, and the Egyptians and the Babylonians.
In other words, that was a well-trodden area, right?
So would you say it was full of emigres?
And whatever was developed was somewhat based on that concept of emigres, you know, people that have immigrated, or like a very highly trodden area.
So getting a handle on them, they can't even get a handle on them today.
Look geographically where it is, right?
Lebanon, right?
And politically, they're a mess.
You know, I mean, they're so, for example, let's just look from a, when I say developmental, meaning what's happening now and is going to be happening in the near future and distant future, meaning a decade or so.
They're very tightly knit with the Persians or the Iranians, right?
Politically.
And when you start looking at a lot of these current political ties, it would be a very good speculation to say that these are not recent developments.
These are ties that go back as far back as you want to go.
So that's another thing to be considered.
Yeah.
The fact that they would have migrated into the area does feel like the most compelling thing because you can't, they don't seem indigenous to the place because if they were, they'd be a better history on them.
And they wouldn't be all these different names.
Right.
Well, what it would have scripturally we have, there's several groups there.
You have the Tyrians, you have the Sidonians.
Right.
As a city-state nomenclature.
Yeah.
You have the, I forget the name, Sephardis or whatever.
There's a bunch of different cities in that area that are sort of independent of each other, but they share some kind of a culture base or ethnic base.
So the name Phoenicians, I mean, I kind of have to look at that, where it comes from, because it's the predominant nomenclature.
I don't know why it's taken root the way it has.
So originally it appears in Greek literature by people like Homer, and most scholars say the term is a Greek appellation, and we kind of try to find an explanation for it in the Greek language as a result.
And by the way, Homer is not to be discounted in any way.
I just want to bring that up as a background.
If you have a background, not necessarily what Homer, but you can access what Homer wrote, because his works have still not been really directly translated.
But the mindset of the people, you know, if you read the Iliad and the Odyssey and other ancient, or what they call ancient Greek writings, the classics, you know, that was pre-King David or around that time, you get the mindset of that age.
So it's not complete fantasy to read Homer.
So, you know, if you mention like Troy, which is a big deal, when you bring up Homer, that would be the Hatti, the Hittites, wouldn't it?
You know, in that area, you know, but obviously far west, where the Hatti were more towards the east, you know, inland, right?
But that doesn't render any specific identity for the Phoenicians.
Because the city-state concept also rules.
Like if you say Athens and Sparta, now you say, oh, that's all Greek, right?
No, it was a big deal to be Athenian or to be Spartan.
It was a very big deal.
Just like, well, an example today would be Austrian and German.
Never call an Austrian a German.
You know, very different.
So anyway.
You'll be able to confirm or deny or expound upon what the Greek etymology is here, because obviously it's a Greek thing.
But there are some legitimate readings.
I mean, if you want to look at the etymology of the word Phoenicians, and there are some questionable ones.
So let's just get the question of one out the way.
It says some say that the Greek Phoenices, I don't know if I'm pronouncing it right, but people get the idea.
Phoenices, which they want to insist that this means purple people.
And they're referring to the major export from the region, which was a cloth dyed Tyrian purple that was extracted from a mollusk.
But then when you look up Tyrian people, Tyrian purple, just that color on Wikipedia, they say, also known as Tyrian red.
So is it red or is it purple?
It's neither.
They'll also say the mythical bird, the phoenix, also carries the same name.
I've never seen any purple phoenix renditions, though.
Or phoenikos, or phoenikos is where you get phonic, and phoenikosmo, phoenikisto in Greek means murderer.
So, I mean, that's like the difference between those definitions that we just gave, is the difference between red and purple.
By the way, when you put red, for anyone that's into color, when you put red and purple together, that is very vibrant, very energetic to look at.
More than any other two colors I can imagine.
But the color aspect, and the people aspect, and the culture aspect, and the history that we have, I'd say is pretty piss poor.
Whether it's the Phoenicians or the Edomites, or a lot of these roundabout things that are still yet to develop.
But as far as purple, I mean, I'm not denying that they exported purple dye.
But if we're sticking with the Edomite sort of thing, I don't, I mean, purple dye, okay, whatever.
But I don't feel like it's a, I'm not really resonating with that.
Alternatively, you have the word phoenix, that would be derived from phoenios, as you said, meaning blood red, which could possibly be related to phonos, for murder.
Concerning the discrepancy between red and purple, once again, Wikipedia says, it is difficult to ascertain which meaning came first.
So, once again, I wouldn't lean on that too much.
On the other hand, you have this deceased Dutch professor, he died recently, a few years ago.
Professor of Indo-European languages, Robert Beeks, who suggested a pre-Greek origin of the word, which would be the Mycenaean phoenikio, possibly borrowed from the Egyptian feneku, which means Asiatics or Semites, specifically from the region of Israel and Syria.
And that would delineate a clearer etymology than just saying, purple dye, or something, which sounds stupid.
Well, they're also port city, they're port people, and very, very international, right?
It would be like, that's actually, geographically, would be considered even grander than the French Riviera is today, from ancient times, right?
It was much grander, you know, French Riviera can't hold a light to it.
And that's another thing that we're supposed to look at developmentally, for the cities of Sudan and Tyre, Sudan and Sor, to be very wealthy.
And if it's the geographic area, or is it Edomites again, you know?
Or are we going to have to delve into the developmental aspects of the geography of Edom, which is south of the Dead Sea, let's say.
Now, one thing to consider, in the future, there's a roadway, a pathway, or a highway, it's written between Egypt, Assyria, and what is it, Egypt and Assyria, right?
And Babylon, isn't it?
One of the prophecies?
Now, if you're going to go to Egypt on land, you would probably, from the northern parts of Assyria, let's say, you're probably going to make it look like a leftward pointing L.
You're going to drop down below the Dead Sea and then, you know, cut a right, you know, if you're looking at a forward or left towards Egypt, right?
Through Egypt.
Because you've cleared the mountain ranges down there as well.
People are not familiar, there's a mountain range west of the Jordan River from the Dead Sea going all the way up almost, right?
Along the Levant.
You know, the Seven Hills.
Yeah, all the way up to Megiddo and the Valley of Yehoshaphat, all the way down, you know, towards the Dead Sea, the Jordan Valley, let's say.
So, but when you go below, south of the Dead Sea there, it's, you know, towards Assyria, which is mountainous, again, to a certain point, until you get to the plains, right?
Of Nineveh.
So that's an interesting aspect of the prophecy.
But that's interesting, we've made the center of the conversation around Edom, simply because, developmentally, I don't see much yet.
And historically, it's very loose.
You know, if you said, even when you bring up the point of the Antichrist being an Assyrian, that's something you could put your finger on pretty easily.
Just go look up Assyrians right now.
They're very, very proud people, and they stick out like a sore thumb, wherever they are.
Not because they're a sore, you know, but I mean, they're going to form a very strong community sense.
You know, they have, even if you put 5,000 Assyrians in a city or a town, they're going to form an Assyrian center, and you know that they're there.
Right?
So where are the Edomites?
Well, the same with the quote-unquote, Judeans.
You drop 5,000 quote-unquote, you know, modern-day Judeans or Israelites in this town or city, you're going to see a synagogue and a jai, which they call the Jewish community center, spring up.
Right?
Where's the Edomite community center?
I don't see one.
Right.
Yeah, I mean, I'm looking at their influence really as extending through the Phoenicians.
And I can't see any other, any other saying that they're a major people group other than through that.
And obviously, the Phoenician doesn't mean anything.
It's like Native Indians.
It's just a Native thing.
It's a Hellenistic term, it's safe to say.
Yeah.
And here's the thing.
If you want to comment on man's society for the past 2,500 years or 3,000 years even, it's safe to use Hellenistic basis as a commentary.
But when you want to get down to the nitty-gritty, it's rubbish, Hellenism.
I'm sorry.
Even though I go by the moniker of the Greek, it hasn't served anyone well, and it's not that great.
It's basically synchronistic bullshit.
You know, take a little from here, take a little from there, put it all together, and you got something good.
It doesn't work that way.
And I'm not taking a rabbinical stance, but the way you make a rabbi go limp is bring up anything Hellenistic.
They hate it, right?
So I'm not on that stance at all, but I'm saying that if you could wash Hellenism out of something, you'll get down to the truth of the matter much quicker.
You know what I mean?
So to wrap up on the etymology thing, as far as the name, so the land of Phoenicia was also natively, if we put aside the Hellenism as we've said, natively it was known as Kananum, or something of that nature, Kananai.
Kananum, or Kananum.
Well, yeah, Canaan.
And the people were known as Canaan.
And we know this because of the Armada tablets of the 14th century BC.
There's clear records where people call them this before the Phoenician rubbish becomes sort of amalgamated into their identity.
So we have a lot of points.
We have a lot of things that point to a Canaanite origin, meaning Dead Sea region.
We have correspondence.
We have the etymology as far as the Egyptian pheniku, meaning Asiatics or Semites, and that possibly then influencing the Mycenaean language.
But one final thing to say about the name Phoenician, which you kind of did mention in passing before, which I don't think is insignificant.
When we examine the name in light of its transcriptions into Latin languages, we realize that there's something to be looked at, despite languages like French or German that have changed the first syllable from Pho to a Fe.
I don't speak French yet, but like Phoenician, French would say something similar to that.
The pronunciation of Greek and Latin is still Pho, the Latin being something like Phonices and the Greek Phoenix or whatever it is.
But the Pho syllable stays there.
So we get words which point to something similar in an anglicized pronunciation as the phoneticians, namely a derivation from the Greek word phone, as you said, which means sound or the human voice.
Anybody who does even a cursory study of the Phoenicians will find that they're considered as being the inventors of the first alphabet or the first phonetic script.
Right, that they standardized.
Yes.
Well, Byblos was in that area.
The book manufacturers or the text manufacturers for hundreds of years, the best tech, just like Swiss, they're known for watches.
Wasn't the Byblos in what we'd call Phoenician proper, you know, I would say.
But they were standardizing things, yeah.
And they were spreading it through their trading and mercantile enterprises.
Right.
Port, vibrant ports, yeah.
But also, weren't they rivals with the Egyptians, you know, back and forth, a lot of treachery with the Egyptians?
And also, weren't they loosely referred to as sea people that conquered, came and conquered, and they moved around?
The sea people is always going to be an object of controversy because nobody can really nail down where they came from.
Egyptian references.
Yeah, they're always going to push down Jesus' word and his mural or whatever it is, the wall painting of the sea people coming to invade.
But there's so much that has to be unpacked there because the archaeologists, some of them are just blatantly lying and making things up.
Yeah.
You can't trust Egyptian stuff, yeah.
Yeah, they'll say it's the Philistines and then you look into it and then it's not the Philistines and it's some Aegean people.
I can't comment, but I've seen enough to know that they're not telling the truth on a lot of things.
No, it's interesting if you study stuff that's been written up until the 19th century, they always say you can't trust anything Egyptian, whether it even comes out from their scholarship or whatever you find there.
It's been twisted and turned and covered.
There's almost a shame about anything Egyptian in real academia.
But when academics were more serious about making real discoveries and knowledgeable discoveries, they found that looking at Egyptian stuff was a task because you had to go through all the lies first and all the misdirection.
Organized chaos, I should say.
And the pharaohs lie.
They make themselves look good and they put other things down in their records.
But that's the culture.
Well, I guess it's strong in the Egyptian culture, also erasing what they didn't like, no matter how significant it was.
If it wasn't in favor, all memory of it was erased, which in modern Western parlance or concept is considered illegal.
You could bring up someone like Charles Manson or whatever.
It's an unpopular figure in the Western world.
And if you were to suggest that his birth certificate and his entire identity in every newspaper article, everything ever written or referenced him is completely erased from memory, there would be an outrage towards that, wouldn't there?
No matter how infamous the character is.
But this was common back then.
It's a different mindset.
I keep repeating that.
And I don't get much commentary on that.
But it's very hard for the Westerners, modern people, to understand that entire aspects of history and whatever you want to say, text or inscription, was completely wiped out simply because it fell out of favor.
And I mean completely wiped out.
Most people today cannot imagine that.
And this was common, especially with the Egyptians.
So to wrap up on the alphabet bit, the first alphabet would have consisted of novelty for whatever forerunners to the Greeks that the Phoenicians came into contact with, whether the Mycenaeans or the Pelasgians, which predated the Greeks.
But we've already seen that the Phoenicians were likely Edomite descendants, and they were descendants, obviously, from the twin brother of Jacob, also named Israel.
So how would their writing script differ from the Israelite writing script?
It wouldn't have really.
So maybe due to whatever pagan nations Esau married into, he married foreign wives.
Well, by the way, just a little interjection or interruption.
If you look at what they're putting in front through standard history as Phoenician writing, what does it look like?
Cuneiform.
I'm going from memory now.
Right?
So what was the standard writing?
You know, and actually, you know, it's still taught in standard lessons of that, that the Cuneiform, you know, was rotated and developed more firm geometry to form the letters that we see in things today.
And, you know, alphabets are written language today.
So that's the other thing that that Cuneiform type adaptation of 22 letters was every you know how people.
Yeah.
Well, it was limited because to promote literacy as well.
But anyway.
When I look at the Phoenician stuff, I mean, at least online, I'm seeing something that's akin to the Paleo Hebrew script.
I mean, when you say Cuneiform, what comes to mind is like what the Hittites used.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Just the cross hatchings and all that.
It looks like an inverted braille almost.
No, no.
Paleo Hebrew, I would suggest.
Yeah.
But the Cuneiform was a type set.
But also, if you understand the how technology affects language, just like with computers, you know, now, LOL and IMAO.
Half the time people send me these text things.
I don't even know what they mean.
Oh, yeah, whatever, man, you know.
But, I mean, I know what LOL is, I think.
But you see how the technology affects the language as well.
But I don't know.
The thing is, how do we drive the identity point of who the Edomites are at this point?
As we stand right now, it's up in the air other than the genealogies and the geography.
You know what I mean by genealogy is what we get out of scripture, right, and also if you study the traditions of the people.
Believe it or not, the purpose of tradition, by the way, folks, is based on oral tradition, which is based on what?
Preserving the culture through history.
So all that needs to be looked at.
But, you know, I harp on tradition a lot because what they've done is twisted, taken ancient human sacrifices and twisted into a modern celebration.
And the people are ignorant of it.
I don't mean it in that sense.
I just mean that we need to look at the traditions of the people, what the people say also.
You know, like when you study Noah's Ark, for example, if you read writings, you know, the 4th century BC up until the 1st century BC, people are like, yeah, we know what Noah's Ark is.
We got wood from it.
You know, we chop it up and make little talismans and good luck charms out of it.
You know, and you see that all over the middle, you know, that whole area for, you know, going back to the 5th century, 4th century BC.
But now you try to find Noah's Ark.
There's nothing left.
Right.
But you look at the tradition.
Oh, yeah.
We could take trips up there and we chop pieces of it off and bring it back.
So do we ignore that completely?
Or are these people just making it up that they go and find Noah's Ark and chop pieces off?
No, it needs to be considered seriously.
You see?
Yeah.
So what traditions and what kind of oral, you know, what are we hearing about the Edomites and also in other languages?
What were they called?
You know, like the Minoans were not known as the Minoans to the Babylonians or known as the Keftari.
Right.
So.
Yeah, I think two or three different names I've come across.
But, yeah, the Edomites, I mean, I'll touch on it in a sec, but I think that their relevance really was prominent at an ancient point.
And at some point it got sort of either migrated or cut off because by the time we get to, I don't know, David-ish, Solomon-ish, there's not really much to say as far as the region.
Right.
And Solomon's really dealing with the Tyrians at that point.
So and we know that those are Edomites.
Well, it also does say that Solomon extended his sovereignty to the Negev.
Right.
I'm just paraphrasing the verse.
And sovereignty means that you're able to enforce your laws.
Right.
And the Negev would be the Edomites or that land of Edom.
Well, technically, it's a general term, but it encroaches on that area enough to say that.
Yeah.
We don't know much about the Edomites.
But what if we go back, like I was saying earlier, tradition and genealogy, you know, from Noah and on.
Right.
We see them descendants of Esau, who was many nations to come out of.
And Edom being one of them.
And their significance.
Let's not go too far from the Solomon thing, because the Solomon thing is a bit interesting.
As far as the Israelite connection goes, we know that he worked with the people of Tyre to build the temple.
Right.
Lebanon cedars.
Yeah.
But not just manual labor.
That was, I think, secondary.
Primarily, it was the architectural skills capable of showing.
Sure.
The craftsmanship, the stone, the wood.
Yeah.
The metals.
So it would seem that the Tyrians also, they get confused with the Israelites in secular history.
Obviously, the ancient people knew the difference.
But some of the Israelite tribes, especially from Dan and maybe Nathalie, they intermingled with the Tyrians.
Yeah.
And I've seen that.
I've heard that the Phoenicians in some way recognized Yahweh as one of their gods, though perhaps not as the most high, which might parallel what the Assyrians had going on.
But even today, historians try to identify where the northern ten tribes went after the Assyrian captivity.
And it seems as if they confuse the movements of the Edomites and the Phoenicians with the Israelites because of the similar Canaanite culture base, which is why you get these alternative historians talking about the Caucasians, white people in Europe are original Israelites, and so are the Americans.
Well, I would suggest that most of the Israelites went east.
And all the way to, if you study what they call the New Testament, all the quote unquote disciples and apostles went east.
Only one went west, essentially, which was Paul.
But everybody always went east.
Black Sea, all the way to India, Persia.
I don't know if Peter went to India.
I know he focused on Asia Minor.
Yeah, well, north and east, yeah.
There's some interesting stuff I have to look at again about his name showing up.
Well, not Peter, but, you know, really east, I mean, way east of what's known as modern Persia.
So, but nonetheless, back to the Edomites and mixing in with the ten tribes of Israel.
The Tyrians and the Sidonians were known for doing that, and we know that based on 2 Chronicles 2, that the Israelites intermarried with the Phoenicians.
Because the king of Tyre sends a letter to Solomon about building the temple, and he says, now I'm going to send a skilled man endowed with understanding, Huramavi, the son of a Danite woman and a Tyrian father who knows how to work in gold, silver, bronze, and blah, blah, blah.
So the obvious implication is that some members of the tribe of Dan had migrated northward into Tyre and Sidon and intermarried with the Phoenicians.
And, you know, on a cursory note, when Moses gives his prophecy of the 12 tribes, he says, Don or Dan as a lion's cub will leap from Bashan.
And Bashan was located northeast of Israel in ancient Lebanon.
We know that the tribe of Dan relocated there from near the coast where they originally were because they weren't happy with their lot, and they settled into the northernmost part of the kingdom near Naphtali.
Specifically, they conquered the Sidonian city called Laish.
So later to see them marrying the Tyrians, that doesn't seem surprising at all.
Well, it doesn't seem surprising that they're breaking the first commandment written on the stones, but right, what's the first commandment?
Right.
Written on the stone, not the regular Ten Commandments that people are told in Sunday school and government movies.
The first commandment is don't go into covenant with the pagans.
Right.
Written on the stones.
We're talking about Exodus 34.
But, I mean, there's always fishy stuff going on with Dan.
They kind of do their own thing.
Yeah, they're not in...
I guess it was a Danite.
Well, legend has it they were the explorers, right?
If anyone were to go out as far away as in ancient times from where everyone else was, you know, the tribes, they would be the Danites.
You know, most far-reaching.
Like an explorer, the explorer class of people.
Both on foot and seafaring.
But how does that tie into the Edomites?
Would you say that when it says Edom, it's mentioning Dan?
I mean, I know you didn't say this, but I'm just stretching it.
I don't think so.
I think when it means Edom, it means Edom.
I know, I'm not either.
I'm just saying there's a lot of mixing going on and there's a lot of fuzz and fog when it comes to the, you know, how do you nail these guys down?
And I don't mean figuratively.
I mean just figuratively, but how do you identify them?
No, I'm just sort of going into the various lines of thought that sort of hyperlink from the core aspect of who are they.
But then you kind of have to look at everything.
You have to look at the Phoenicians.
You have to look at how they are confused with the Israelites in some way because of the movements.
And then you can look at the migration patterns.
And I'll sort of get to that later.
But as far as who they are, I know you keep harping, who are they?
I don't know who they are, but I don't see them as being…
Well, what's the easiest way to figure out who they are is through their behavior as described in Scripture, right?
Mm-hmm.
So it requires a study.
They have a, yeah, I don't want to break my line of thought, but I know that they have a covenant of sorts with Israel.
Israel, Yahweh tells the Israelites at some point in Deuteronomy, do not despise any Edomites because that's your brother.
They have some loose form of covenant, which is actually mentioned, I think, in Ezekiel, that they're supposed to take care of each other.
And Edom consistently breaks this covenant and joins with their enemies to fight against them.
Like Psalm 83 as well.
Yeah.
And this is not looked upon positively by Yahweh, and so he has beef with them because of that.
But like with the Babylonian captivity, they helped with that.
I think they helped with the Assyrian captivity also, though I'm not 100 percent sure.
So, you know, we do get a glimpse of the character.
But even what I'm talking about here feels a little bit myopic because, like I said, it's about the Elohim.
There's a specific Edomite entity that has some kind of a nature to him.
So for me to stare too much at what the people are doing doesn't really tell me much.
No, you always look at the gods first because they're going to direct the people.
Right.
And vice versa.
But just to wrap up with the intermingling bit, as far as the Danites and the Phoenicians or the foreign nations, what I thought was interesting that I came across is that the Danites could provide a connection between Israelite and Greece, which for me would explain, or the forerunners to Greece, which would explain how Greece came to be inhabited by Caucasians.
Because all the ancient drawings of Minoans and Mycenaeans, as well as the writings of Herodotus, show dark skinned people living in the Aegean.
So that has to somehow flip into the Hellenization that we know of today.
And Josephus writes about the Spartan Greeks having a close affinity to the Judeans in Antiquity of the Jews, I think is Volume 13.
And even going away from that, if you don't like Josephus, we can look at the Book of Maccabees, which quotes very significantly.
It says, The king Arius of the Spartans wrote a letter to the high priest of the Jews on Ananias' greetings.
It has been discovered in a written record that the Spartans and the Jews are relatives and are both of the family of Abraham.
Since we have learned this, please let us know how you are.
And it's a sort of diplomatic correspondence.
Now you can say that the Maccabees is in canon, blah, blah, blah.
No, it's fine.
You look at everything I just mentioned earlier.
Look at traditions as well, because they're supposed to retain history.
Even fiction retains history, right?
Look at what Hollywood does.
Go ahead, the Spartan connection.
I've heard of it before.
I haven't delved into it, though.
I can't vet it, but there is a newspaper site that you know of and some people know of, Haaretz.
He has an article reporting that new archaeological evidence found at the Tell el-Kadi site, which they're saying is the biblical city of Dan, shows compelling Aegean influences in that area in the form of weapons, pottery, figurines and ritual items.
So where would those things have come from unless the Danites were in some way in contact with the Aegeans, which would explain how the Spartans developed as per the Book of Maccabees and things like this.
The timing lines up.
It would be late Spartan because they were wiped out by the Athenians, weren't they?
Yes, I do believe so.
And we know also from Judges chapter 5 in the Song of Deborah that the Danites were sea-parting people because he says in Judges 5, why did the Danites remain in their ships when there was this war going on with the King of Hazel?
So the association with the Phoenicians who are also sea-parting people, that does make sense.
Well, does it make sense that they're thoroughly mixed with the Edomites?
Or no, the Edomites are still Edomites.
Well, the Edomites, like we said, the names sometimes obscure things, but if the Edomites as a people migrate out of the region, which we have reason to believe that they do, and settle in some other point, then the Phoenicians are Edomites.
So I'm using the word Phoenicians, but you might as well exchange that with Edomite.
But let's go back to the beginning of the conversation.
When we say Edom, where do we look on the map?
You see?
We look at Jordan.
Yeah, all the way south.
But they're not doing anything there.
No, I know, I know.
It's fine.
Just like there's nothing going on in Babylon.
Yeah.
And nothing going on in Assyria.
So the influence has to be, I'm guessing, what I'm saying has to be Phoenician.
Because what other world influence are they having outside of that?
Right?
So if the Phoenicians are of Edomite origin, and they intermarry with the Israelites, and they spread their writing script around the world, and they're famous mercantile people, that validates their place in the prophetic texts.
Because if you just look at Edom, they're not doing anything.
Well, then in the prophetic texts where Sidon and Torah brought up, Tyre and Sidon, right?
Are they the Edomites?
No, I guess not.
I mean, that's also going to be a problem.
It is, yeah.
There's a lot of developmental, there's lacking of development.
I mean, we do have, okay, when we read the scripture regarding the Edomites and all these other things, we, etymologically, we want to look at an interlinear, we want to know what these words really mean.
We want to know the geography, and we want to know the history.
Scripture and, you know, secular of the age.
By the way, secular means of the age, right?
What's in vogue today.
So we want to look at all those things, but also we want to look at what state of development that area is for it being significant now.
And I would say very little of it is.
So let's just float around a little bit.
You know, if you listen to any Greek-speak, I hammer prophecy, things to come more than things that happened.
And most of the time when I do hammer the past, it's to give clarity on what's going on right now.
What people are involved in, you know, not to walk away and say, oh, this guy's too pedantic.
What is he, you think he's some kind of historian?
No.
I like to bring forward from the past a comparative analysis or study of what why and what people are doing now to understand what and why they're doing, what's going on today, and also what's coming in the future.
That's where I find my emphasis and what I like to underscore as, you know, the narrative that I put forward, right?
So if you're if I think you've illustrated, if you go back and look at, you know, can we identify the Edomites?
And now we're sort of wondering about the Phoenicians.
Either way, there's there's very little development that I can speak of in the current day and also how they're going to develop in the future.
You know, to to, you know, based on, you know, the Greek speak narrative, you know, I still don't know.
Yeah.
Like who are the Edomites today?
Kind of difficult, you know, but you can take that almost with any route.
The only people here.
Here's something interesting.
The only people that I'm sure of to a high degree of who I know who they are, are the Assyrians and the Persians and the Greeks.
All right.
And let's say a 50 50 of Israelites.
You get where I'm going with this, that we know pretty well.
In other words, there's a there hasn't been a chain of title disturbance.
You know what I mean?
If you go if you go identify the Assyrians today, they'll show you a chain of title as far back as you want to go.
And they'll even they they even look today the same that they did on the pottery and the images that they carved 3000 years ago or two.
You know what I mean?
So there's only a small group of people that we can definitively definitely I should say advertises being surely identifiable.
And if we just go to Israel today, who's really an Israelite?
I'd say 50 percent of the time you're going to be wondering, is that 50 percent that you're you know what I mean?
More than 50.
Yeah.
But I'm being I'm giving a leeway here that is very generous, I should say.
You know.
Yeah.
In other words, less than 50 percent of the people there can say you would say this.
This is most likely an Israelite going back, you know, that we read about as formally being an Israelite.
See, so there's there's a lot of this gray area that what makes the times that are coming the next three and a half years, next seven years.
A time of not only exploring the information and getting a finger on what these things mean and who these people are.
And more than that is going to be a big blast of information and a big blast.
This is a time of discovery.
It's quite exciting if you really want to know more about these things.
This is the time period right now.
So it's almost like we're having this conversation a couple of years too soon.
You know, which is I'm not saying it's out of place or out of time.
I'm just saying that it's again, I'm going to use the term I've used it over a dozen times.
Developmentally, I don't see much going on.
And also scripture, scripture hasn't defined them in any any other way other than just bringing in this about the Edomites and that about the Edomites.
Right.
We're not getting we don't have a lot of information about them.
So how do we identify them as things start to unfold and evolve?
Which means the same thing to unravel.
How do we start?
You know, we have to be aware of it, you know.
Yeah, I mean, if you're like the like I was saying about the alternative historians, they'll say that all the Israelites migrated into Western Europe.
But if they're just confusing the 10 tribes with the movements of the Phoenicians that may have migrated into that area and you want to say that, well, OK, then the Phoenicians became the Western Europeans and the white people of today who largely run the world system.
And those are the Edomites.
And that's why it's a world system, blah, blah, blah.
Capitalism.
Well, it's there, but at the same time, you have to you have to address what's legitimate.
Yeah.
You'll see that there's a blur in the line of, you know, people, you know, I remember back in the day with Ocelli, we started doing stuff.
And a lot of comments that a lot, meaning like a three, five, 10 comments within a few weeks was, oh, I'm so glad you guys are not Jew bashers or bashing the Jews or blaming everything on the Jews.
I'm like, what?
What are you talking?
I noticed at that time there was a very anti, quote, unquote, Jewish sentiment a couple of years ago.
Right.
And that's why I brought up the point about maybe less than 50 percent of people in Israel are, quote, unquote, bona fide Israelites.
You know, when you bring up the concept loosely of who's a Jew, I mean, it's not it's not even a people ultimately.
So the Edomites are a people.
And right.
We're looking for them.
They're descendants of Esau.
And we know that when we I've been hitting the Greek speak narrative.
Scripture is about the gods to the gods and that we just happen to get it through the prophets.
Right.
That's why it's a very I shouldn't say difficult document to comprehend.
But once you understand that it's for the gods, written by the gods, and it happens to be a message to us.
Yeah, it's going to be difficult, but it's not difficult once you have that mindset.
So why aren't they giving us information about it anymore?
You know, but either way, identifying.
I think whenever you're looking at any information regarding any subject, you want identifiers.
It's sorting, sorting things out.
And so, in other words, if we were to end the call now, I would say, can we sort out the Edomites right now?
No, only through speculation.
Right.
Yeah.
And I would say, like you mentioned, the last thing you said was about the mercantilism and the business people.
You know, people still harp on, quote unquote, the again, the Zionists, what they control, the banking, the Hollywood, many, many industries, a lot of legal, medical, you know, all around.
How much of that is Edom really?
Right.
Because, I mean, Tyre is obviously the system that gets implemented towards the end on a Babylonian tip as far as the merchants.
Well, it's Tyre, Jerusalem and Babylon are the three home bases, I should say.
Right.
And Jerusalem, by the way, is it would probably be one of the best places to eventually find more history on the Edomites, because guess what?
If you're going from the Negev or south of the Dead Sea, south of the Jordan area there, where Edom is geographically to the northwest, guess where you're going to be going through?
Most likely from a cosmopolitan, economic and religious reasons.
You're going to be going through Jerusalem, aren't you?
Most likely.
So here's another thing to say, and this is more than speculative.
If Jerusalem was turned inside out like a sock, you know, in other words, there was not one square meter of Jerusalem that was not excavated or finding anything archaeological.
We wouldn't know much about these things.
I think one of the keys to discovering more about even the Edomites is turning Jerusalem inside out.
Literally, I mean, excavating all of it from an archaeological point of view, you know, responsibly, right?
Which may not be in the future.
Yeah, it's happening.
The problem is the academics...
Watch this, by the way, folks.
You're going to start to see negative influence in the writing style or the narrative of the archaeological, worldwide archaeological community at large, because they're going to be making more and more discoveries on a daily basis that are going to be confirming biblical records.
And they don't like that.
So, there was a recent article, by the way, about something being carbon dated near the Temple or the Gihon Spring, by the way, and it shows that the tower was, according to carbon dating, much later than King David, right?
And that makes total sense, and they think, well, the biblical narrative is wrong, because it's several hundred years after, or a couple of hundred years after the tower is supposed to be built.
And I said, that's not off, because during the Hasmonean, or after the time of Isaiah, let's say, wasn't the Temple desecrated and they removed it down to the bedrock, stone by stone, to consecrate and then put it all back together?
Right?
But they just happened to miss that part in scripture, and historically.
Are we still on?
Yeah, I'm here.
Yeah, so, you know, on its face, if you look at the recent discoveries of the Gihon, and that's how you did carbon dating, and it's hundreds of years after, supposedly, Solomon built it.
No, it's accurate, because it was completely dismantled and rebuilt again.
So, after that point, you know.
So it lines up, but they just happened to omit that part of scripture.
So, I mean, you have to be able to sift through that.
But I think when I say archaeological discoveries, and to define things, and also our, meaning, you know, those who have interest in censorship, as it starts to be lifted, we'll see things more clearly.
Combine all of that is what's to be looked forward to in the next month, year, and several years.
Well, if you want to specifically look at how certain things play out, we can just look at the prophecy itself.
So, obviously, that is in the book of Obadiah.
Yeah, that's right.
I think it's just dedicated.
Supporting elements from Isaiah 34.
What I did just want to correct before that, I was trying to get in on something before that I might have said the wrong thing on.
So, when I said that Simon Magus was a Danite, obviously, that just sounds wrong on the face of it.
But he came from a village in Samaria called Gita, according to Justin Martyr, which was a site settled by Dan, according to Josephus.
So, that was what I was trying to articulate before.
So, they always seem to, there seems to be certain strings of events that lead out from them that aren't so favorable, which is what I was trying to say before, and it kind of came out weird.
Well, no, just say, just repeat that, because it came, give us that whole thing one more time, that whole thought.
Well, I was trying to say about Dan, when we were talking about the intermarrying, that they always seem to be doing their own thing and getting involved in suspect business.
And then I was kind of linking that to Simon Magus to say that, well, he was from a village in Samaria.
He was a Samaritan, and the Samaritan area was actually settled by Dan early on.
So, you could say that they were partially descendants of the Danites also.
Was that by Lot, if I recall, in Joshua?
Well, Samaria is in the north.
It's in the northern kingdom.
So, I think it's a migration issue that they left, because they were at the coast initially, between Judah and Ephraim or something like that, and then they left.
So, I think it's a migration result of that.
Immigration, migration, all that good stuff, yeah.
As long as they weren't considered to be sick birds, you know, ill eagles.
So, yeah, putting that aside, we can look at Obadiah.
So, then you have the first verse, which is that he has a vision.
Thus says the Lord Yahweh concerning Edom, we hear a report from Yahweh, and an agent has been sent among the nations, rise up against her for battle.
So, you have a prophecy about how the nations of the world will rise up against Edom.
And this is at the end of the age, just before the second advent.
So, continuing, behold, I have made you small among the nations, despise are you exceedingly.
So, I don't know.
Could you say that the ancient Phoenicians were some of the greatest people?
Commerce will then be brought down.
Once again, I don't know.
Yeah, but when you say that in the end times, you're going to have to kind of bundle them together with Sidon and Tyre.
If you fast forward.
And the only way I could see it is by fast forwarding, because I don't see anything developmental right now.
Right.
But you'd have to bundle them in with the west coast of the Levant, in that area, again, you know,
which is spoken of in general terms, just as when you when Babylon and the significance of Babylon and Jerusalem are brought up in the end times,
those are more general terms also, because it's not just the specific, you know, thumbtack on the map, Babylon and Jerusalem,
but it's a large area around it, including the influence that it has on the whole world.
So it's a spiritual thing.
The pride of your heart has deceived you, you who dwelt in the cleft of the rocks, whose dwelling is high.
You say, who shall bring me to the ground?
I kind of mentioned that before regarding the cleft in the rock pit.
I would say loosely that the Edomite central area in their region at a point in time was called Petra.
Yeah.
And that's the place of safety.
They think a lot of Christians thought.
I think it was established as a sort of capital city for the Nabataean kingdom, with the Nabataean people, these sort of nomadic traders type folk.
And that was after the scripture was written, most likely.
But yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, I think it's like 4th century BC or something.
Yeah, it's more recent than the prophecy.
So when people make that association with the rock carvings and Petra and all that, I think it's just too hypothetical.
Go ahead.
So, yeah, it's kind of famous for its rose colored rock architecture and things like that, rocks with very narrow entrances.
So I can understand what the text is talking about.
I'm going to skip some verses because not everything is pertinent.
So verse 8, In that day declares Yahweh, I shall destroy the wise men from Edom and discernment from the mountain of Esau.
So here is where I can say, OK, the Edomites as a people, now we're seeing something that we can use as a marker.
It's saying that they have wisdom and wise men.
OK, so that means that we have to we can find at some point we'll be able to find some literature that validates that.
Right.
And by the way, when you read the wise and wisdom in Scripture, it's not because they can crunch numbers or tell funny jokes.
It's because they know Scripture and know who the gods are.
By the way, I just want to throw that in there again as a reminder.
When Scripture speaks of the wise, it means not the academics that you hear about, but those that know about the gods.
It's knowledge of the gods that considers one's wise.
But anyway, and that's repeated over and over in the Psalms.
It took me like 10 years to before it hit me like a pile of bricks on the head.
I said, oh, where's this wisdom?
All this wisdom is knowledge of the gods, not, you know, how to design fancy hydraulic systems and things, you know.
So go ahead.
Yes.
So that has to be will have to be validatable at some point.
And maybe I don't know if it's I'm sure some people have private records of things because people sometimes just keep stuff hidden.
But that'll probably come out in the future.
And it would seem that that is also validated in Jeremiah.
Jeremiah 49 concerning Edom, thus says the Lord of hosts.
I think this is King James Version is wisdom no more in Timon.
Is counsel perished from the prudent?
Is there wisdom vanished?
Timon is somewhere in Edomite country.
And we can we know that because of the genealogies we can look at that.
Timon was an individual descendant from Esau.
I think it's his grandson.
So you kind of have to use.
And this is for me something that's very helpful.
You have to look at the early genealogies from Noah going down to figure out who the countries what the original countries are, the original peoples or why certain places, different names are used for the same area like Edom.
Then it's Timon.
And I think there's a third one.
But it's all the same people because they're descended from the same genealogy.
Also, aside from the verbal claims about Edom being a source of wisdom, I think we get a historical glimpse of what they're talking about.
If you look at Job.
So this is not brought up a lot, but obviously people have always conjectured about where was Job?
Where was this land of Uz?
Where is he from?
What time period was he living?
One of the three friends that he has that comes to visit him to give him advice when he's going through his suffering.
His name is Eliphaz or Eliphaz.
The Shuhite?
Yeah.
I'm just anglicizing what I'm seeing.
And if you look in the genealogy tree, you will see that this is also the name for a son of Esau.
These are the names of Esau's son, Eliphaz, son of Esau's wife, Adah.
So if we're willing to equate the two figures, which I don't think is a stretch.
I don't see any other Eliphaz around that time period.
You would conclude that the land of Uz is really just an earlier name for Edom.
And actually, we don't even have to guess, really.
I'm just presenting the evidence.
But if you look in Lamentations, which is a book nobody hardly ever brings up, it says very clearly in Lamentations 4, Rejoice and be glad, O daughter of Edom, that dwells in the land of Uz.
By the way, it's funny you say that.
I've brought up in private conversations two or three times this past week, Lamentations.
But go ahead.
I just had to say that.
I mean, it's heavy on poetry, so nobody really wants to look at it.
Right, right.
Yeah, but poetry is different written.
And the way they write poetry then was they tell a story past, present, future.
It's not like Greek poetry or English poetry.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
That's a good thought, though, on that Uz location.
Because it was a central location, even though it was in the south.
It was very centralized between Egypt, which was also at one point sister cities with Babylon, which one, you know, then you consider everything north of that as well.
And it makes sense that they're saying that wise men come out of there because Job is really living in Uz, which is just Edom.
And Job, you know, is known for the characteristics that he has.
And I mean, you can say whatever you want about his three friends.
They don't strike me as being particular.
I mean, they don't espouse unlawfulness.
They're there defending the Most High or defending the way that they know how or think that they should.
So there seems to be some kind of an enclave of lawful people living there doing things that are good.
And so the fact that wisdom would come out of there at that particular time point.
I mean, son of Esau would put him.
I don't know if Abraham is still alive.
You know, Abraham is probably dead.
But Isaac might be alive by the time this guy is born.
Which guy?
Job.
Which guy you're mentioning?
Yeah, Job.
Because Eliphaz is Esau's son.
And Isaac is his father.
So by the time Esau has his sons, is Isaac still alive?
Yeah, I think he's still alive.
He's probably old.
But definitely Jacob is there.
And Esau is there in the time of Job.
Because that's...
Okay.
That's an interesting way to look at it.
For his sistericity.
So the wisdom aspect makes sense from that perspective.
Now I can understand.
Okay, so the Edomites.
When we say Edomites, we don't just mean Edomites.
We mean everybody that comes out of that lineage technically from Esau.
Okay.
Esau has sons.
And his sons might not be called Edomites.
But aren't they still Edomites?
Because here, sometimes the Edomites get called Teman.
Like, oh, Teman.
Blah, blah, blah.
And the King James will add certain things.
Like, I forget the verse.
But it says somewhere in Ezekiel or Isaiah, Oh, Teman.
And then some kind of proclamation.
And the Oh is not supposed to be there.
They just throw it in there in the King James.
So they then want to conjecture that, Oh, he's talking about the Ottoman Empire.
Because it says, Oh, Teman.
It's just nonsense.
But calling him Teman doesn't mean that you're not talking about the Edomites.
That could vary.
Because it's just the son of Edom.
So, yeah, you kind of have to follow those strands.
And I can see why Job is, you know, in the position that he's in.
Because of the location, what comes out of there.
So moving on from that.
And by the way, historically, that community there geographically was quite thriving.
I mean, there's an industrial-sized winery in that area.
That's uncovered today.
I mean, it's made of stone.
But it's made procedurally the same way you would build a winery today.
That would produce a million bottles of wine a year.
Kind of thing.
I mean, obviously, it's not functioning.
But, yeah, there's, yeah.
And also, the people in that area, south, still use the agricultural techniques of flooding fields.
Capturing, you know, wadi water.
You know, when it rains.
And once a, you know, for about a week every year.
And they capture that water and they make it last four months.
So that was, in other words, they had, it was a, the culture was unique to the land there.
And they were quite industrious.
I just wanted to throw that in there.
Because as we're talking about it, I'm reckoning in the, you know, going back in the files in my head.
What I've come up across that part of the world.
But go ahead.
Yeah.
So, lamentations and ooze and, uh-huh.
And the wisdom.
I mean, that's all that I have for that at this point.
But I think it does put some puzzle pieces in place.
As far as understanding.
Hope, understanding.
Okay.
But if you were to spread, if you were to spread that, like toast, butter on toast, right.
So you get a, you know, when you bite a piece of toast, you get a little bit of butter in every bite, right.
When you start looking at the Itamites, the paradigm of the Itamites, you know, the example of the Itamites in the end.
The Itam.
When you see, right before the end, when things start going south, let's say for civilization on this planet, or society on this planet.
There's a group, and a fellow, let's call him the instead of, or the Antichrist, that declares himself to be God on Earth, right.
Let's just use that loosely, that term.
And the whole world falls for it.
So in order for the, that means that the entire planet is going to be in some kind of a religious fervor.
You know, using that in a colloquial sense.
And the Itamites, or those people that are a descendant of that, will fall for it also.
No matter how much they know about the gods.
Do you see that as being something to, yeah, to consider?
So in other words, there's going to be some kind of a prominent, let's say, mouthpiece, or, I shouldn't say mouthpiece, but they're going to be, we're going to know more about who they are because of their wisdom.
In other words, as time goes on, knowledge of the gods and all this religiosity, which has nothing to do with any religion anyone knows about now, they're going to be considered to be the wise men, or considered to have certain knowledge.
Just like you said earlier, there's probably private records.
I mean, and it could be a private, you know, a stash, or a cache of written things that are buried underground are pretty private also until they're found.
So, in other words, with all their knowledge or wisdom, they're still going to fall for it.
You know, the coming deception.
Now, what's interesting is are they going to be some of the people stirring up this religious fervor?
You know.
Are they going to play a significant role in it?
I don't know, but what we can say if we want to nail down what they're, more specifically what function they're going to play in some capacity in the end, and of course this is the reason why they're cursed.
Maybe not directly, because I mean, Esau is cursed before he was even born, because he said that he's the one that Yahweh hates.
But, if you want to look at why they're cursed in the Obadiah text, it gets spelled out from verse 9 onwards.
So, everyone from the Mount of Esau will be cut off by slaughter for your violence against your brother Jacob.
So, they have an issue of always causing problems for the Israelites.
And I believe that during the Babylonian exile, they plundered Jerusalem and expropriated large parts of land there also.
They were being attacked.
That's why the walls needed to be fortified first, I think, with Cyrus.
And in Ezekiel 35, it says Your cities I destroyed let you be a ruin because you have had a continuous enmity and had handed the children of Israel over to the power of the sword at the time of their calamity.
Talking about the exile.
And I think there's two or three other places that say similar things.
So, similarly, I think at the end of the age, Edom will be at the last moment They will provide some kind of a blockage or they will cut Israel off and prevent them from escaping when the nations turn on them, because the nations will turn on Israel at some point.
Instead of supporting them, they're going to prevent them from escaping or hindering them.
It says in verse 14, You must not stand at the crossway to cut off his delivered ones, that is to say Israel.
You must not enclose his survivors in the day of distress.
But he's talking about the future even though he's using the past tense.
So, I don't know how they're going to do that, whether it's literally putting up roadblocks but somehow they're going to create a problem.
Well, aren't they in the Psalms that