And also, you will also look at when it comes time for a leader that doesn't accommodate the people, just like you see in the 20th century, all of the bloody revolutions, you know, when certain dictators took over and they wiped out large swaths of their population.
But I mean, let's be clear, those revolutions were not ground-up grassroots movements at all.
They were manipulated by other institutions.
So the people are just there to be herded left and right, really.
Yeah, but you know, let me just throw this in there.
This is a thought that came in.
I don't want to say Freemasons and stuff, because it sounds silly.
The people are herded, but where do the prophets come from?
Where do the people that did exceptional things come from?
Amongst those same people.
They weren't dropped in.
They didn't have some kind of special bearing or birth into the world.
No, they didn't.
Hold on, but they were someone's son through a lineage of priests, usually, let's just say.
Some were not priests.
But certain people are chosen within the society to give a certain message at a certain time.
Yeah, but they're not chosen at random.
It's not rolling dice.
No, no, no.
It's not.
They're already made for that.
But also, just like maybe going back to what you said, the people being herded is not done by random either, like throwing dice.
That is also prescribed.
Yeah, that's fine, but it doesn't take away from the fact that they still have to act out a certain reality.
So what I was contesting is the idea that the reality is in a different way.
That is, that the people are corrupt and therefore the leader is corrupt.
Well, actually, if you just corrupt the leader, then you corrupt the people by extension, because it's a top-down hierarchy.
But let's say if it's drastic and contrasting, you'll have a subgroup of society that either leaves the country or decides to go underground.
Yeah, that could be.
Look at the, during the time of, one thing that's not emphasized, that you do find a lot of secular, well, you know, other history outside of the Bible, is what happened to the priesthood and other groups of people in Israel during the reign, the latter parts of Solomon's reign.
Right?
That's where Ethiopia comes into the picture, the, you know, Elephantine, all the various pseudo-temples that sprang up, all the various, you see.
Yeah, it's a really rough time.
Here's one thing I want to just throw in.
Someone was asking me about the law recently also, and I thought I'd say this publicly in a way.
You don't have to do any of it.
It's all voluntary, by the way.
If you read Scripture, it says it has to be free will.
Even when you're in a covenant to do it, when you make an offering, it's still called what?
What kind of an offering is it called?
It's still a free will.
Even when you lock yourself up by a pledge and a contract, it's, furtherance of that, it still requires free will.
So there's a lot of free will involved.
And what does that mean?
It's not for everyone.
And it's actually not for anyone.
And what I mean by not anyone, not just anyone.
You see.
But you're going to have a law form regardless.
But in this case, you're doing it consciously.
I'll give you another example.
Like the real piss-poor mentality that you see on the planet right now.
When you go to, let's say, an average Joe, you see how they take certain, if they've been diagnosed with something, a fake disease, and they prescribe medication.
They take that religiously, come hell or high water.
They get very serious about taking that.
Because they've already prescribed their minds and agreed that what the doctor is telling them is true and correct.
And it's like, you know, that's the be-all end-all of reality, right?
So, you know, by the way, the people know more about law by the way they act than the legal society does, by the way.
It has no law.
So, anyway, I always harp on these guys because they deserve it.
And at the last Sonic event I did, by the way, someone was giving away their grandfather's legal, all their law books, and they were in perfect condition.
I've said, of course they're in perfect condition.
He doesn't need to know any law to do practice law at all.
He just has to know how to twist things around and accuse people on the color of law.
Something that, you know, but anyway.
I think that that is the law though.
To be like the goddess religion, I think that that seems to be the thing.
To be underhanded and say that you do the law but you don't.
It seems to be the law itself.
Yeah, obviously, because if it wasn't so, then most people would say, anyone you'd run into would say we're under the goddess religion or being influenced by the goddess religion.
The way she works is that no matter how prevalent she is, her prevalency is denied or not acknowledged.
Correct.
That's one of the attributes of it.
I mean, you're full under it right now, and it's not because it's a female sex or gender.
She's anti-life, anti-duality, anti-creation.
You know, the idea that things are self-sustaining through procreation is a bad thing to her.
Anyway, okay, so what else you got, Sam?
Well, I wasn't too sure whether we would jump into this now.
I guess we have maybe an hour and a half left.
So it's fine if we don't finish, but it's kind of a long tree dice, to put it lightly.
Melchizedek is an interesting character that I've always wanted to look at.
Sure.
King of Solom or Old Jerusalem, yeah.
Yeah, and I've been sort of hesitant to bring it up because these things tend to be very short, but I guess we'll just extend it to the next one.
As an ancient record of history and geography and nations and individuals and gods and things, scripture offers, as you've mentioned, unparalleled levels of details on things, locations, borders, names.
So for most of the characters and the places that are mentioned outside of the genealogies, we can find some kind of expository info on them.
And then you have anomalies from major historical figures like Nimrod, although there's quite enough peripheral information on him.
But then you also have complete aberrations like Melchizedek, whom hardly anyone has anything useful to expound on.
Well, hold on.
Just because it's short doesn't mean it lacks importance or significance.
No, that's fine, but it's just that people don't seem to be able to read anything useful out of it, for the most part.
Oh, there's tons to read out of it.
There's tons to read out of it.
Now, you and I, let's just discuss it.
We haven't discussed this in private, unless you want me to give it a go?
Yeah.
Very simple.
You mentioned, well, I always like to say that there's a lot of, you'll state a name, you'll state a geographic, you'll state a purpose, and then the outcome.
With Melchizedek, we get what he's called, or his name, his purpose, his job, let's say.
And then we state he's a king of Salem, which would be, I guess, the Jebusite area, the area of Old Jerusalem.
So, when they did go into that area, legend had it, or history had it, that this area that they're in right now was ruled by him as a king.
This was his spot.
So, as Israel's history progressed, especially through the end of Judges and when you had Samuel and all that, if they were always pursuing doing righteousness, and they had someone like Samuel who was able to exhibit that, right?
Why not have a king like Melchizedek?
Why not put a king over us?
Do you see?
So, to me, them having to want a king like the other nations is fine, but I see that because of the area being ruled out of that area, which I'm sure there was a residue of his presence.
You know what I mean?
That was known.
So, I see it as simply, this is a time of kings, even from the time of the patriarchs, right?
So, for example, when you bring up the name Jerusalem, it's not like Manhattan or Moscow or Cairo.
It's a tiny little, it's like five city blocks, if that.
It's a tiny little, literally, if you put a dot on a map, that dot in scale is really the size of the jurisdiction of Jerusalem.
That's how small it is.
So, it's almost like a point source area.
It's almost only a name.
There's hardly any land to back it up.
That's why, you know, lately with Trump discussing it being the capital of Israel, I'm like, oh, that's no big deal.
I mean, that's been discussed for a long time.
Okay, he's doing it.
I know it's within the timeline that we're coming up right now.
To me, the issue is not whether or not Jerusalem is declared the capital of Israel.
To me, the thing is, what's Jerusalem?
Show me.
In that sense, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, show me, show me the, you know, what I mean, show me means like, where are you going to squirt the ink on the paper or the pixels on the, in this case, on the rectangle to form the map?
So, and they do have something like that now, but yeah, yeah, it's too, what is this, this quarter, that quarter, this part, this part, no, no, show me Jerusalem.
They have a hard time.
That's going to be the interesting part.
And why is it interesting?
Yeah, why is it so interesting is because it has to do with what's going to be proven.
And what's going to be proven is that this wall that these people are banging their heads on as the Western Wall is nothing worth banging your head on over.
What's going to be proven is the history and the biblical text is accurate.
What's going to be proven is there's going to be an alliance, a loose alliance, or a willing to openly work together.
Everyone in the Middle East will work together.
So, what's also going to be proven is the Gaza Strip will double or triple in size.
The Palestinians will have a nation.
What will be proven is there will be no Palestinians in the West Bank or in the eastern part of Israel in the near future.
You know, what they call settlements and all that stuff that the Israelis are building.
That's going to keep growing.
You're going to have small regional conflicts.
Monarchies overthrown in the Middle East.
Countries like Jordan will be overthrown.
Something like a group of nations that will all probably start changing rapidly like Lebanon, Jordan, Egypt again.
Syria.
You know, big political changes.
You're going to see a massive warming up of the public even though it is private.
It's going on with Persia or Iran and Israel.
They're going to be, I stated them as being superpowers in the Middle East, but they're going to be sister countries in the future.
Financially, you know.
Because you have to remember the Persians or the Iranians are not Arab people.
Yes.
I'm not 100% sure on what you said about Melchizedek being the king when they showed up at the city initially, but we'll look at that.
I didn't say he was a king because we're looking at when they showed up because we're looking at a time period of maybe 300-400 years.
Maybe 500 years.
Because this is pre-Exodus.
Melchizedek, right?
When they showed up and went back is post-Exodus, right?
So at least 500 years later.
But it was known.
For example, let's look at England.
Let's say England was reconquered and all this other stuff and it was emptied out and conquered and redeveloped and resettled.
That will always be known to the people that were there even though they're foreigners as England having a queen or a king.
Where if America were conquered and resettled, it will be known as a place that always had a president as their leader.
Right?
In that sense.
Okay, so you're not saying that he was king of the place when…
No, he was king of the place by name, that little bit of information.
But way after, later, when that place started to become active by the people that were descendants of Abraham, they wondered who their king was because this place was known to have a king known as Melchizedek.
And especially when you have a man like Samuel running around, if you know his history and his acts, trying to keep everybody in check.
Right?
And it was quite well known that he was, even from a child, in direct contact.
Well, not direct as Moses, but…
Right?
So they did have a righteous…
I would say hands down Samuel was righteous according to scripture.
He was a righteous man throughout.
And he didn't have that kingship or that position, but that place was known as a place that had a king of righteousness.
So why not have just a king again?
And also, let me just throw this in.
This is the sentiment.
In other words, when I read scripture, it's like reading a pop-up book.
Remember those old children's pop-up books?
You turn a page and there's a three-dimensional origami thing that jumps out.
And you're like, wow!
So if you start looking at the people of scripture back then, especially in those historical days, where there's more up in the age of, I guess, the prophets and all that's still historical.
Those people were usually well aware of their purpose in the land there.
You know how they say, do the Passover to remind your children that you were taken out of Egypt?
And so on and so forth.
It was always in their minds that they were there on a privileged state.
Until, of course, they went hog wild and did all the stuff that everyone else did around them.
I would say, just as a note to that, that Melchizedek was obviously not the only king of the place.
There were several kings of the place.
The legend could have built up cumulatively over the years, depending on what each of those kings did.
But we'll look at that.
There's very little about Melchizedek.
I think he shows up one more time in the writings of Paul, doesn't he?
Well, you can say that there's not much in the scripture itself, but there's a whole bunch that can be inferred by peripheral material.
There are mentions of not him in particular, but what he represented and ideas around him from other nations.
Right.
And according to the stories from the patriarchs, what did it take to make someone righteous back in those days?
Think about it.
Very simply, it was very simple.
All you had to do was set up a monument as a tribute to Yahweh.
Think about it.
Because even Abraham was told to, presumptively told to engage in human sacrifice of his son.
And he didn't bat an eye over it.
That was normal.
So what made someone righteous back in the days of the patriarchs, directly in that way was to set up a monument in tribute.
Or, you know, some kind of direct, you know, like there was no wavering or doubt, according to the head deity, right?
And then, of course, it was the behaviors that came after that, because obviously Sodom and Gomorrah knew what they were doing was wrong.
Right?
So, it's basically, when you know what's right and you do it, you're righteous.
When you know what's right and you don't do it, you're not righteous.
If you don't know what's right and you do it anyway, well, now that's like a great point.
You know, that's why very often you'll see societies that are full and debauchery and nothing, you know, and they keep prospering.
Well, it's because they're ignorant also.
You see?
That's why I keep saying when you see this perfect society coming on, don't fall for it.
That's just a setup so you can be taken out lawfully.
As far as I know, there's no one saying that.
And I find that to be a big disservice to humanity that that kind of message is not being given.
But who are you going to talk to it?
Who are you going to tell this to anyway?
So, go ahead.
You were going to say something.
Well, yeah.
Let's look at the character a bit more.
He makes his first appearance in Genesis 14 when Abraham is making his return from the war with the kings.
So, just to read that really quick.
Then Melchizedek, king of Salem, he brought forth bread and wine, for he was a priest of El Supreme, or the Most High.
So, as an initial point of inspection, Melchizedek is a two-part name made up of the words Melchi and Zedek, or Melch and Zedek.
Many presume that the name means King of Righteousness because this is the wording that's used in Hebrew 7.2. I'll read that real quick.
For this Melchizedek, king of Salem, priest of God Most High, who meets Abraham returning from the combat with the king and blesses him.
It's translated into King of Righteousness, yet thereupon King of Salem, which is King of Peace.
But hold on.
The prefix of the MLK is also for angelic beings as well.
Yes, obviously.
But not just angelic.
Yeah, Elohim in general.
But it's also used for earthly kings.
Malak.
So, that's just kings, period.
Whether it's Elohim or earthly kings.
Because we have correspondence from back then that shows that the king of Egypt called himself Malak Mitzrayim.
So, that's for both sides.
As far as the King of Righteousness, I think we haven't talked about Melchizedek in private that much, but we've had a brief conversation on it.
And I think you mentioned at that time also King of Righteousness is how you read that, yeah?
It's not entirely an illegitimate reading, if the original Aramaic even says that.
But the name is too flexible for the King of Righteousness reading to be definitive.
And anyone who tries to present it as that and sort of sticks their guns on that is showcasing ignorance of the Semitic language syntax in West Semitic culture.
I mean, these things have to be viewed in their ancient Near Eastern culture.
Which is a viewpoint that I only hear that certain scholars that specialize in that field bring up.
Everybody else just wants to read the anglicized mindset into it.
So, Melchizedek, is that a Semitic personal name like David?
Or is it a title or a royal epithet like Caesar?
It could be either of those things.
You kind of have to establish that.
So, in order to be able to endorse the idea that it's a title, we should be willing to shoulder the task of presenting a precedent for that kind of usage.
Oh, we lost you.
Are you guys still there or is it just me?
Yeah, I'm here.
We seem to have lost Sam.
Where am I?
There we go.
We're going into some etymology and interlinear stuff.
Go ahead.
Okay, so did I cut out?
Yeah, you did.
Oh, okay.
I don't know where I cut out.
But just keep going.
I'm sure it'll tie it all together.
Just to find that thought again.
So, either we're talking about a personal name or we're talking about a title.
So, if we're going to try to endorse the idea of a title, we have to find a precedent for that.
I think that that would be marshalling some good evidence for that.
So, either we can look at ancient Semitic literature or we can look at the Old Testament itself.
On the other hand, if it's a personal name, that is to say a theophoric name like El Yahu, which is in honor of a certain god, or descriptive or an adjective.
In this case, that would be righteousness.
Then we have to find evidence for that also.
Right.
So, looking at the two main parts of the name, you have malak and you have siddiq.
We would assume an X of Y relationship with malak being king and siddiq being righteous, so king of righteous, X of Y, king of righteousness.
But one would presume that if you didn't know how the language works, but once you learn about the syntax of the grammar, you'll see that there's a problem there.
So, there's a suffix that's being used between malak and siddiq, that is the E, malkeziddiq.
So, there's an E sound in the middle, which is the Nikud symbol known as Yud, and it indicates the first person singular possessive, which means my, like my table, my refrigerator, my phone.
So, by the rules of Hebrew grammar, you cannot have a suffix between two nouns in what they call a construct state.
Basically, a construct state is used to show possession, similar to English when you have a, like David's dog, you know, the dog belongs to David, so you put an S at the end, so you're kind of changing what the word is fundamentally.
We understand that in Hebrew grammar that you show that by putting the Yud there, and it's a form that's created by shortening the original noun and joining it together with other words.
So, you have this sort of compound word, malkeziddiq, which is three different words.
Conjunction.
So, malkeziddiq has to be read by that understanding as my king is righteous, or my king is siddiq, or something else, with the I being my.
So, the X of Y assertion is really cancelled out really quickly.
We either have a theophoric name or a descriptive name, but you can't say my king is righteous.
That doesn't really make any sense, or my king is righteousness.
Well, excuse me, let me just interject.
If you go to the interlinear, when Abraham interacts with malkeziddiq, is the aleph tav prior to that?
Because when you see the aleph tav, it means towards.
That's just another thing to consider.
If we're going to start looking at the Hebrew with a very, very fine, in other words, if the letter changes the grammar and the meaning, whenever you see the aleph tav before something, it means it's doing towards that thing.
If it's not there, then it might just be like something, like a form of, like something you would ask an anarchist, like who's your leader?
Well, my leader is the good one, because I don't have an earthly king or something, right?
So, I see it can go either way, but it would be interesting to see the word being used.
You don't see an aleph tav before that?
No, not at all.
Okay, okay, that's interesting.
So, go ahead.
That means it might be this aspect that you're bringing up has more credence without the aleph tav.
We can start by looking at the Theophoric alternative.
So, for those who don't know, I don't think it's generally talked about very much, as far as Near Eastern deities, you're going to have to specialize in it.
Sedek is a known Canaanite god.
That's an idea that's likely to be unfamiliar to Westerners, where we're largely ignorant about language etymology, period, anyway, much less the idea that names have meanings.
Hold on, hold on.
Does this Canaanite god come on the scene after the age of the patriarchs, or prior?
This is one thing that's interesting about scripture also.
But go ahead, consider that as well.
You know, I don't really have any direct references to where Sedek pops up.
I'm still looking into it.
Like I said, it's a very long thing to compile.
I'm sure I'll come across that eventually.
But as far as the name things, just to sort of explain why this, because I've seen some people who want to fight you on this.
We don't know that Sedek existed, and it's like, you know, we think in English that there's a finite category of sonic identifiers that qualify exclusively as personal names, like David, John, Sarah, Luke or something.
And so once you have like celebrities or hippies that start naming their children after brands like Lexus or after natural phenomena like River or Leaf, we start to raise our eyebrows at that.
Like, why do you call your son that?
You know, until somebody like River Phoenix becomes a movie star, and then we act like it's normal.
But the Semitic cultures and the Asian cultures for people and names are often taken from everyday common parlance.
Like there's people in Japan whose name is Strawberry in Japanese, that's their literal name.
So it's not unusual.
And similarly, there are gods whose original names are just words for regular nouns or positions of authority or adjectives.
So Sedek is an adjective, that's a name of a specific deity.
And to, you know, continue in that line of thought, Malak or Malk, the word for king, is also a deity.
That's a specific god.
So we see, and we know that because there are theophoric names that reference that in Genesis and in Ezra.
If you read Genesis 46, verse 7, it gives a genealogy.
Asher's sons, Emunah, Ishva, Ishbi and Bariah.
And the sons of Bariah were Heber and Malkiel, and that Malk is king.
In other words, my king is El.
Your name shows up as a name.
Same thing in Ezra.
The sons of Harim, Eliezer, Asai and Malkia.
It's the same Malk beginning.
Or Malachi.
Exactly.
So the fact that Sedek and Malk are gods can be verified also by credible dictionaries of Near Eastern deities.
So that's back.
And the constituents of Melchizedek's name, it's also worth mentioning that they're referring to concepts within Canaanite society.
This is not Israel.
Israel doesn't even exist yet.
So you can't assume that just because Yahweh is also called El, that they're talking about Yahweh.
It's not a title that's unique to him.
It's the entire, it's like all of Europe has Romance languages, except for the Slavic languages, you see, so yeah.
Satan isn't the only Satan.
There isn't one entity called Nakash.
There are lowly snakes in the grass that are called Nakash.
So El could be anybody, we don't know.
Malk could be anybody.
Well, that's where the context is important.
As far as I know, only the name Yahweh is set apart.
Yeah, sure, the rest are just describing a class or a society, just like you would say people live by the coast versus the desert dwellers, or the mountain people.
It's very similar, it's just a general term so the mind knows where to look for the rest of the story.
We can also see that there are additional theophoric names in the Old Testament that incorporate the name Tzedek.
The one that I was able to find is in Haggai verse 1.
In the second year of Darius the king in the sixth month, on day one of the month, the word of Yahweh came by the hand of Haggai the prophet to Zerubbabel, vice-boy of Judah, and to Joshua son of Yehoshadak.
And Yehoshadak, the last part of that is Tzedek.
In other words, Yahweh is Tzedek or Yahweh is righteous.
Yah is righteous is what Yehoshadak means.
So that's a word that carries once again the title of an actual deity.
And it's worth pointing out that it's not necessarily Yah is righteous, you could also read it as Yah is Tzedek.
You have to keep this sort of flexibility in mind and not go in with this monotheistic mindset, because there are many gods that are on the playing field.
So Melchizedek could be my king is righteous, my king is Tzedek, or Malk is righteous, or Malk is Tzedek.
If you want to be adamant about the Hebrew 7.2 reading, okay fine, but I'd like to see some syntactical or morphological explanation for that.
You can't just run with it, because it's not even written in Greek, it's written in Aramaic.
Or Hebrew, let's say they do an archaeological dig, it won't even be the square type Hebrew, it'll be more the cuneiform type, what they call paleo.
But here's the interesting part, there's a definition in scripture that he states, this is my name and that's just me.
So I'm getting a diversion here where maybe he used a different name with a different culture.
I don't think he would use a different name, I would think he would use maybe an adjective regarding him.
Just like when Moses, when he says who should I ask, he says I am, but that's not his name.
So he could be righteous, he could be the one that always was, he could be various, but that's still not a name thing, it's an adjective.
Or even the morphology in the name still uses his name, unless it's just an adjective.
And any culture can say someone is righteous, right?
I mean look at America, they've got Supreme Court judges, they say they're righteous, you know what I mean?
It's just a name only, or whatever.
But what's interesting is that there's a quality behind an adjective, or what you can call me, and a name.
There's a difference between that.
So where do we leave off?
Go ahead.
Well, we have to sort of move on to this second part, or the follow-up to all this.
We kind of have to ask ourselves, are these names given at birth as personal names that people carry with them all their lives as a theological statement?
Or are they titles given once they inhabit a certain office?
Sort of trying to understand why somebody would be called the President.
That's a big stretch, and I would suggest to relax on that for a minute.
The reason simply is, let's just take the Christ, for example.
His name was given before he was even born, right?
Am I alluding, you see, to how these names work?
In other words, when the name is really, really important, it's stated as being such with the mechanisms behind it.
If you take, for example, all of the narratives in Scripture, why is it so limited to the Middle East?
Is it possible that he sent a prophet like Jeremiah to somewhere like Fiji, or the natives of Australia 2,500 years ago?
Oh yeah, it's clear if there's anyone living there, Jeremiah went to them.
He didn't go to the people, he went to the leader, their priests.
So what name was used then?
And how can we see?
There's plenty of evidence of the direct name of Yahweh throughout the cultures in the Middle East.
Actually, there is evidence of it here in America.
Like in Las Lunas, New Mexico, I've actually seen it, where they've actually used the name carved on stones that are several thousand years old.
We don't really find much in Africa for some weird reason.
Nothing seems to come out of there.
Well, you also have to remember throughout history until this point, when people found stuff like that, they discarded it.
Or when it was found to be important, it got quickly censored.
As it went up the ladder, it got into the Judeo-Christian ethic somewhere, like either a Jesuit, or a church leader, or an academic, that says, oh, we need to hide this, because it doesn't conform to our history that we're telling everyone, you see.
Sure.
You know, I just wanted to bring this up.
Since we're doing the word Melchizedek, you know I use the word censorship often.
In Greek, the word censorship is logokrisis.
Logos meaning word or statement, and krisis meaning crisis.
So literally, in Greek, the word censorship means a word crisis.
So, anyway, back to…
Well, I don't mean to be dismissive of the idea that certain things are predestined, obviously.
But just to give an overview of the cultural aspects on the ground, because people will have certain presuppositions, or they'll make certain statements and say that this can't be that.
And you don't even need to talk about the gods that they don't understand.
You can just look at the culture on the ground and say that, well, actually what you're saying makes no sense.
Like the King of Righteousness makes no sense because of the way the language works.
And then we can look at certain other things and piece together other conclusions also.
So, we can look at certain things written in Joshua to have an understanding of how these names work.
But hold on, if we attach that adjective to a geography and also the relationship and how he's introduced, to completely discard that he was a leader or an authority figure at one point, I can't see discarding it completely that way.
No, we're not discarding that.
Of course, he's a leader, he's a king, he's a priest.
That's a fact.
Right, and not only is that his position, but it also gives you a geographic, and it also gives you the interaction, some detail.
So we have several things to build.
There's enough structure, but not enough height.
But we will get a better view of things if we take into consideration what's been written around it.
The periphery text that can be validated as being pretty solid.
The thing there, let me just say something, is you can't at this point, and this is not to be paranoid and discard any body of work, but the historicity of that time period is a total mess right now, still, even today.
We have tablets.
We have Hittite tablets.
But even then, they'll tell you that these things are 7000 BC when they're only the 1500 BC.
So we just care about the contents.
Right, exactly.
Thank you.
The next thing I was going to say was if you're strictly looking at the content and seeing how that will give you the bearing on where it can be, because you're not going to know where it should be unless it's even more explicit, then you can start to form a body of work and then see how the historicity of it works through rationale.
Because we're being completely lied to about everything.
So if we look at Joshua 10, it provides some interesting tidbits.
Joshua 10.3, it says, I believe when the Israelites were approaching this area, so Adonizedek, king of Jerusalem, sent word to Hoham, king of Hebron.
And that's all I need to read.
I need to read the rest.
So you have this guy, Adonizedek, whose name literally means my lord is Sedeq.
Lord is righteous.
My lord is righteous or my lord is Sedeq.
He's king of Jerusalem.
He's got a similar name to Melchizedek.
Jerusalem is a Canaanite city at the time.
Sedeq is a Canaanite deity.
So I would put to anyone as a rhetorical question, is this really the name that his parents gave him at birth, or is it a kingly title that he later assumed to honor his god?
You know, we can talk predestination, but this is just a Canaanite king.
Nobody gives a crap about him.
Unknown, but because he comes on the scene as an adult only, we have to take it as a title more than a name.
But we don't have to take it either way.
We just don't know at this point.
No, we don't know.
But we can sort of, I mean, you take your guess.
If the name makes sense.
Let me just preface this for anyone, the listenership.
When it's important to know that this was a name that was given, it's usually mentioned that it was given to him.
Right?
You'll see that often.
But you don't see a lot of the historicity or the history and how things developed with the Canaanite kings, right?
You don't get into that.
We don't get into a lot of these other guys too much.
Why?
Because if we go back to the days of Noah and look at the descendants and just look at how things developed from that point of view, right, how come it's just, you know, some descendants here and there are focused on and the rest are not?
Believe it or not, there's mathematics behind all of that, which has not been shown to this point and will be shown later.
But go ahead.
What I was going to say was, you know, in connection with, I know that you stated some aversion to the idea that Yahweh might be using another name.
I can neither confirm nor deny, but if it makes sense in the time of Joshua for some guy to call himself Adonizedek, why wouldn't it make sense in the time of Abraham's day to have a theophoric name for a foreign deity?
Because how can you say Melchizedek is talking about the Most High, and Adonizedek is talking about somebody else?
You have to reconcile that somehow.
We can't discard the descriptive title interpretation, though, completely, because there's evidence for that.
Even if we want to conclude the opposite, I just want to bring that up.
There's some good dictionaries of the Ancient Near East and dictionaries of the Old Testament, particularly one called the IVP Dictionary of the Old Testament.
It has different volumes.
One of the volumes is the Pentateuch volume, so I'm just going to quote from that.
It says, Melchizedek and Adonizedek may have been royal epithets.
E.
A.
Spieser has argued that Melchizedek is just the Canaanite equivalent of the Mesopotamian title Shar-Meshurim, meaning the just or the righteous king.
I'm not saying I agree with that, but this is just what it says.
So this does create a precedent for taking Melchizedek as a title.
Let me just make it a little shorter for you.
When you go to any courtroom in America or whatever, and they have the judge, they call them all, aren't they all of them called honorable?
And how many of them are honorable?
None.
So is it just, yeah, you see?
It could just be arbitrary, obviously.
Yeah.
But what's interesting here is that anything you see with the patriarch Abraham is an archetype that's being formed.
So even to the point where his wife is his sister and she's barren, right?
Okay, that could be something.
Yeah, and the only way that a child can come forward is with divine interaction.
You have a deity that calls a nation his wife, and the only way anything will come out of it is if he divinely interacts, known as the prophets or the Messiah.
You get it?
You see the archetypes?
Yeah.
Over and over and over.
So what happens here is when you read the story of the patriarchs and their interactions, even with the Canaanites and all the other kings and with Joshua and what they did to all the other kings, those are archetypes that are being set up.
Not because, I'm not saying that they're metaphors only like these other idiots saying they didn't happen.
No, they did happen.
But it's, oh, okay, am I cutting out?
Okay.
So when you look at the archetype, you know how things that are done in heaven are done on earth and vice versa?
You know what I mean?
Don't you have, for example, malevolent gods or entities that tell man that they're not malevolent, that they're benevolent?
They flip, right?
So you have to judge it by their works.
So if you tie this back to, let's just tie it all back to Melchizedek, what are his works?
Do we get any of his works, his miracles, his rulership, his, you know, whatever?
Do we get any of that?
Yeah.
No, I mean, we can't say who he is or what his thing is.
Yeah, and here's the other interesting part.
We're just looking at the name.
Yeah, if you look at the name also, there are certain things that are defined, and I will go back to scripture as being pretty solid, that there's only one name that's being used.
It doesn't say that in my description because he's known as many things as well, but he only has one name.
You see the Yahweh, right?
There's only one name.
But he's also known as a man of war.
He's also known as Al Shaddai, you know, which is the leader of the angel armies.
And, you know, the Most High is known as Abba, right, Father.
And what's interesting is you still have people today saying his name is I Am, right?
Now, of course, obviously they're taking it short.
So there's still a lot of that, you know, and a description can be a name, but in this case it's clarified that it's not.
Like, you know, when you run into someone who says Baker or Fisher or whatever, that's because that's the profession of the family, and they took on the name.
Like I use the Greek.
Well, because, you know, I'm the only Greek I know, and I just use that.
But the level here with Melchizedek is it's an archetype within the patriarch, the story and the annals of the patriarch Abraham that were given in Genesis.
Is it possible that in the future we'll have more historicity and more about Abraham?
Oh, yeah, it's very highly possible, and I think it might even happen, right?
But this is still an archetype that's in there, you know.
Also, you have to think about there's a jurisdictional thing here.
How does Abraham interact with him, and how does he interact with all of the other people around him?
Do you remember when he was looking to bury his wife, that they wanted to donate the land for that?
And he says, no, I want to pay for it, right?
You see?
So in other words, he was an important person that they were giving tribute to.
So there's something else there that we're not seeing at the moment.
You know, it seems like everyone else is – I mean, I'm not saying they're suzerain to Abraham, but I'm saying that perhaps that they're being – they view him in a high position, and here's someone that Abraham views as a high position.
And I think to a certain extent, this is what creates a clash with what's written in Hebrew 7.
But we'll get to that later.
Just to wrap up on the title point, I mean, no, I don't think it's a title.
I think it's a theophoric name.
But I did just want to give some brief info on the fact that there are many kings that call themselves Melchizedek.
Well, not Melchizedek, but Melchizedek, they have that title.
You have two kings from Byblos in Lebanon that did the same thing in the 10th century and the 5th century.
You read their records, it says they call themselves Melchizedek.
So that's common fairly.
But we also have to remember that Melchizedek is a king.
Genesis says that he is king of Salem or Shalom.
So if he's a king, how could his name be my king is some other human guy that I serve as a priest?
You know, that's not likely.
He can't have another king over him.
That's human because he's already a king.
So that knocks down definitively the sort of title thing.
My king is Tzedek, that is a god.
My king is righteousness is really what fits better contextually as far as a theophoric name.
And then we can look also at the Salem or the Shalom aspect.
So if you read Psalm 76, that places Shalom parallel with Zion as far as what the Elohim think of it.
It says, he who is known in Judah is Elohim.
In Israel, his name is great.
His abode is in Salem and his habitation in Zion.
So if he lives in Salem and he lives in Zion, then that means they're equivalent.
So Shalom is also equated with Jerusalem in the Targum, in the Dead Sea Scrolls and in rabbinic literature in general.
I also found it to be interesting comically that in 397 AD, the famous priest who gave us the Latin Vulgate, Jerome, he rejected the view that Jerusalem and Salem is the same place.
And he said that actually Salem is just some town in Samaria called Selim.
It's a misspelling.
But since this is Jerome who kind of gave us the Lucifer rendition, you know, it's kind of a joke.
Oh, yeah, that's that's why it's vulgar.
The word vulgar, I guess, is from the Vulgate.
Yeah.
So, yeah, they're vulgar bunch.
But I think that when you look at this, this stacks up further charge against the Hebrew 7.2 reading, because that reading completely disregards the geographical implications of the name Melchizedek.
If I read it again, you'll see that it says King of Peace.
It says that Melchizedek means King of Peace.
And I mean, Salam, Salem, Shalom.
Yeah, but yeah, but if you're only reading it as a title, we just said that that's not legitimate.
I mean, it doesn't say King of Jerusalem.
The Hebrew writer doesn't say King of Shalom or King of Zion.
He just is King of Peace.
Like, why is that?
Why was the author?
Well, also, the Jebusites were the people of Jerusalem, weren't they?
Yeah, and I kind of want to leave that for later.
But yeah, in a sense that they ruled over it, but it was always called Jerusalem.
That never really changes.
So it doesn't explain why you would just ignore the geographical realities and only call it King of Peace, because you've turned the name into a metaphor.
And it's not just a metaphor.
So the writer isn't the writer of Hebrews or Judean.
He doesn't know that this was the king of an actual city.
Okay, let me just interject one thing.
How does he interject in the annals of what was going on at the time with all the other kings, and even within that time period of the patriarch Abraham?
Do you think there was a dynamic there that were not being shown?
Because obviously we're shown a lot of dynamics with other kings, more information with other leaders.
Do you think that is there some duality here?
Or do you think he's individual?
Well, you mean Melchizedek?
Yeah.
In other words, how does he fit in within the annals of the patriarchs?
He doesn't.
He's an anomaly.
Right.
So he still remains an anomaly.
Of course.
But I'm saying just to show how this Hebrew thing is not congruent.
There's some kind of foul play here, because saying that the name means king of...
The Hebrew 7 guy is really saying...
So you can actually see his name is Melchizedek.
You could say his name is Melchizedek, king of peace.
Yeah, but king of peace, but not king of Salem?
Like you're rendering king of Salem into king of peace and ignoring...
See, I'm confused.
Let's just do this.
When you work in Hollywood, they tell you, let's see the end of the movie.
What's the end of the movie?
Give us the conclusion of where you're at right now.
And then we'll fill it in backwards.
Because we've been on this for half an hour or so.
And I'm wondering if there's anything juicy to bite into.
So go ahead.
Give us the end.
Give us the spoiler on this so far.
Where you're at with your studies on it.
No, I'm just taking you through sort of the progression of it.
The conclusion, I'm pretty far from that, because I have a lot left that I still have to do.
I mean, the conclusion of this particular aspect is that Melchizedek is an anomalous figure who's a king-priest.
His name is probably theophoric, referring to some deity.
Otherwise, it would have to refer to an earthly king, which it can't be.
The city that he's ruling over is Jerusalem.
We have a Canaanite orientation.
And the city is later shown to be under Canaanite rulership with Adonizedek.
And that these guys are essentially kings over the same places.
And that their names have something in common.
Okay, good.
And also to give people a flavor, it's not like the king or queen of England or Germany or the Austro-Hungarian Empire.
These were like city-states.
So you could be a king over something like the size of a little larger than a city park.
You know, a few blocks only.
Or 10 or 20 acres or 50 acres back in the city-states.
Or you can be a king over a very vast area, like Nebuchadnezzar or something, right?
So a king is just a title, but it doesn't denote grandeur.
I mean, this is another thing that people have to remember, the concept of a city-state.
Meaning a very small area onto itself.
And that's why you can understand, you know, vying for territory or what they call real estate could render those times very costly to exist.
You know, you had to pay tribute so you won't be attacked.
Or you had to be very militarily strong.
So what I'm leading back to this is if you're able to maintain a kingship, no matter how – especially the small ones would be more difficult than the larger ones in some instances.
How did you maintain that, right?
Why would you have that title when it's just not a bunch of people just living here, you see?
So there's more to it than, you know, are you a self-proclaimed king or are you made king?
Is there a line of royalty that goes back that's not given here, you know?
I mean there's so much stuff when you get into the higher realms of human rulership, the dynamics, the family lines, the rights, the privileges also that are considered that they give.
Because being a king you give privileges to others for your protection.
So what I'm trying to say here is that the mindset behind him or any king back in those days was very different than the mindset that we have today.
Yeah, that's understandable.
Yeah, because you could just be a king over like five-city block area like Jerusalem, for example, right?
But also being a king essentially at that point in the Near Eastern culture means that you have a deity backing you.
You can't just call yourself a king.
Sons of God.
Unpreservable.
Yeah, because in other words what you see in, you know, geography in terms of maps, political borders and rulers and all that, there's a deity behind it.
That's one of those things that's important.
If you're going to give a short message to someone, I believe that's a good short message to tell people.
Especially those that are politically minded and they think they can vote and make a difference.
Even today there are gods behind it.
So, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, I mean I don't go through all this stuff for the sake of just being pedantic or overly meticulous.
But for somebody like our listeners probably haven't looked into very much of this.
I'm just going to presume, forgive me if I'm being bold.
But these historical things sort of do matter because if you want to hammer down who the guy is, you have to look into the Siddic aspect.
What is Siddic?
Siddic is a god.
Okay, well, yes.
Yes and no.
But either way, this is one thing to look forward to.
And I'm talking about temporarily now.
Every day, if not every week or every month or through the years coming now, there's going to be more unearthing, literally, and rediscovering and disclosure about these matters way back then.
So we're living in that time period right now for that.
And it could be just as simple as someone pulling out records that they've always had.
Are you guys still there or did I drop?
No, no, I'm fascinated with the subject.
Yeah, I think we overdid it a little bit with Melchizedek.
Next time, Sam, I would just suggest give us the spoiler in the end and then the support.
Sure.
You mean I bored you, Creek?
No, no, not boring.
No, no, just for the listenership's sake.
Yeah, I don't want to get lascivious, but yeah, you want the second half, not the first half for the sake of economy.
Yeah, just give us the spoilers first.
Sure.
Yeah, because I don't think we're doing this for entertainment, and I don't think we're doing this to convince anyone of anything.
I think we're doing these presentations and these sonic events just simply as such.
In other words, we're not selling.
We're just telling.
This is telling.
I'm not selling.
No, I know, but very often in academia what they do is they give you so many supporting points, so you're already convinced of the conclusion.
In this case, just give the conclusion, hey, did you know this?
No matter how anomalous it sounds, I say, yeah, I know it sounds crazy, but this is what backs it up, and we can get it over with in just a few minutes.
So what else you got?
Well, I couched sort of my mindset for a three-hour conversation.
I'm just going to have to reach for different things that I have in mind.
Oh, that's fine.
Yeah, just reach for anything, yeah.
What do you got?
Well, you know, I'll throw something out on the table.
Remember when we were going to talk about Zechariah?
Right.
When?
No, I was just saying that if we were going to look for a topic to throw around, that would be a good one.
Well, that's a good book to read because the second half was written by Jeremiah, and that's one of the anomalies that's listed.
People say, look, the Christ gives such-and-such written by Jeremiah, but you don't find those verses in Jeremiah.
You find them in Zechariah.
So, see, the Bible is wrong.
But when you look at the history of Zechariah, you'll see that Jeremiah must have stepped in and finished it.
See?
Because the point of these books, these scrolls, as they were written, they were not named as we have them now.
You know, when we look at the top.
In other words, if you went back really far, you wouldn't see Genesis and then Exodus, right, Leviticus, Numbers, Deuteronomy.
You wouldn't see the books labeled that.
That's been labeled much later.
See?
Okay.
Especially during the Septuagint.
So the book of Zechariah was not, oh, the book of Zechariah, it was just like the prophetic writings that were letters and messages given to kings.
And, by the way, when you look at prophets, one of the indirect or unwritten rules, if not written rule, I guess I should say written because I can't cite it, is you go to the leaders of a people first when you have an important message.
And you could see that in Hollywood with the 1950s alien cartoons.
The guy is plowing his lawn and a spaceship lands.
What's the first thing they tell the guy?
Take me to your leader.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I can't really go in on the book too much because I haven't studied it per se.
I know of it and I've breezed through it back when I was a Christian.
Okay.
Well, would you change like a frog into a prince now?
What do you mean when you were?
You never were.
It's just you believed in that stuff.
So you're just a man, right, or a woman, or a dog or a cat or a bird.
You can't change that.
You know, that's one thing.
What's interesting, when you read the book of Zechariah, it says that man wants religion, but I just want man.
Right?
That's a verse in there.
I'm just giving you the anglicized translation of it.
It's a verse in Zechariah.
Do you remember reading that in there?
I actually have to look at that one.
Yeah.
I just want, man wants religion, I just want man is what he says.
But what's interesting about Zechariah, it gives you, that's really loud keyboard typing, Sam.
What's interesting about that is it actually gives you probably one of the most elaborate displays, illustrations of the resurrection, right?
It gives you a lamentation and also a reversal of what is going to happen, right, in the end with Israel.
It also gives you instructions of how to comprehend prophecy.
And I'm just going from memory, right?
Do you remember when he says that I will do it as before, as of the prophets of old, what's going to be repeated?
Do you remember reading that in Zechariah?
I will do it as it was for the days of old, as the prophets of old.
So when you see repeats in prophecy, it's going to be repeats of the book of Joshua, kings, judges, Samuel, not repeats of Isaiah, Jeremiah, and things in the Psalms, no repeats like that, right?
There are verses like that that are key in the, in other words, what got me into prophecy, believe it or not, about 12 years ago was that in book of Zechariah, where he says, I will do it again as the days of old as a prophet.
So he's telling you what part of the history is going to repeat.
So it would be Joshua, you know, who are the old ones, you know, chronicles, kings, judges, right?
So, and then we, we fast forward, by the way, to what they call the new Testament.
And one of the requirements before the mop up crew comes is that the world understands what happened in the first century, right?
And right now, today, still, people don't know what happened in the first century, right?
They still don't know what the, what was going on.
So what the purpose of the Christ was, let's just, you know, shorten it down.
So, yeah, what else?
I mean, you'll notice in the book of Zechariah, again, an illustration of what happens at the resurrection with the high priest Joshua, just happens to be a high priest named Joshua, right?
Which is one of the Joshua's, 25 Joshua's.
Here's the beef anyone can have with Christianity and how they play around with names.
Obviously, Christianity was set up by some attorneys because you just change something enough to believe someone that that's what it is.
But later on, if someone puts your feet to the fire, you could say, look, that's not what I said.
Look, it's different.
You see what I mean?
Right.
So it's a really good coached demonic thing.
I mean, you know, the spirits behind the Christian stuff are operating on a very high level.
But when you understand that they're operating on that level, you can see it.
So if Christianity, all Christianity has to do, if they like the J letter, all they have to do is call their Messiah Joshua.
And that's accurate.
If they call the book of Joshua, Joshua, and no one is having beef with it, you know, why don't they call the Christ Joshua also?
There are 25 of them.
And right there, that would really start fixing the mindset.
Obviously, there's still no letter J, but be consistent.
You know, like if you ask a Jehovah, someone in the Jehovah's Witness Protection Program, they'll say his name is Jehovah.
Okay.
Well, okay.
You want to stick with the letter J, then why are you using J-E-S-U-S?
Because it's also Joshua.
Right.
You see?
So be consistent.
If you're going to be wrong, see, that's why people – that's what makes people crazy when you're not consistent like that.
That's why I said there's not enough Prozac in the world or SSRI drugs to help a Christian if they want to stay there.
If they want to get out of it, all they have to do is read for five minutes and they'll be out of it, no problem.
But here's the interesting point about that, is if you ask your average person what's his name, no one knows his name.
It's just God, God, God, God, God.
That's all it is.
At least the Jehovah's Witnesses, they transfigured incorrectly into Jehovah.
They'll tell you that God's name is Jehovah.
You see?
So at least they're trying.
Obviously, they don't know either.
I mean they're in pretty sad shape like the rest of them, but you see how the counterfeiting works?
Right.
It's very simple.
There is no J-E-S-U-S.
It's an acronym for something pretty bad, actually.
So to make – For what?
Yeshu?
It's an acronym that his name will be blotted out in Hebrew.
Just like, you know, what do you mean by acronymistic?
I'll have to get in front of a computer and start pulling up stuff and show you where it's actually in the Book of Isaiah his name will be blotted.
Right?
It's in the Psalms.
Yeah, and then you start seeing how his name was in the records of genealogies, and you just don't go and scratch a name off.
What you do is you remove a letter.
So instead of Yahshua, it becomes Yeshu.
Right?
That's why they call him Yeshu of Pandora in the Talmud.
Are you familiar with those writings?
I haven't really looked into them.
Okay.
Yeah.
Who knows more about the actual historical biblical Christ or the rabbis?
I think I've said this before.
And that's worth doing a study on in the future.
I need to revisit because I've got a lot of, like, holes, you know, here and there where I didn't follow through on the research on that.
You know, but if, let's say, someone wants to pick up on what, unfortunately, you're not going to get it on the rectangle, but you might get 100 websites saying all the same thing.
Like there was one website and everyone just copied it on what's in the Talmud about the biblical Christ.
And, of course, you're going to get the J-E-S-U-S thrown in, and it's going to be a really bad mess.
But there are rituals that Orthodox Judaism has that actually evokes that name as the firstborn son, you know, Yahshua, and many of their ancestors.
And we start piecing the whole thing together and the history of rabbinical traditions and the secret history that they hold, that they talk about in secret in plain sight using metaphor, you start to see that they actually had a lot of details about this.
And also, by the way, just to throw something else in, I think I might have mentioned this to Sam, is that the entire Christian ethos and all the iconography and the stories that you get out of it were not only created by Simon Magus and later Constantine and all the deviance in between, but the rabbis also backed that up at the time.
The rabbis were like, yeah, he was here and he was crucified by the Romans, three crosses, you know, total fiction, you know.
They supported that also to cover up their involvement in it.
You're not going to get a rabbi who knows what happened to admit guilt that, yeah, it was a death by – give you an accurate account.
He'll say the Romans did it, right?
He'll back you up.
And then you'll have all the deviance that are starting Christianity saying, oh, look, even the rabbi is backing us up.
So they all work together really well, you know what I mean, at the time, to create this fictional account that you have in the Christian world right now.
And the names and the settings and the iconography and what happened and the lack of access to clear texts and archives and all this other stuff.
So that's an interesting part.
There's the guilt covered up that actually promoted.
So, you know, it's like telling people the actual Christian stuff that they believe was actually promoted by rabbis also, you know, just to get away from the reality even further.
How comical.
I hope it makes sense because to say that sounds to some people, well, rabbis have nothing to do with forming Christianity.
I'm telling you they did.
So, and not by giving accurate information, but by giving the contrary.
Well, on the subject of names, is it stretch to say that the Messiah is also Yahweh, just because he and the father are the same?
Yeah, you can, but they are the same.
Yes.
So they have the same name, technically, in some way.
But, you know, I think I've gone through this before.
The reason why he's the son, when you speak to men, is because the son has a superseding authority position regardless of time.
It's non-temporal.
So the metaphor that I give with that is when you, let's say, start a corporation,
and then you have a board of directors, and then like 10 years later you have a son,
and 20 years later he's 20, he walks into that boardroom with all those old men,
you know, he takes precedent over them because he's your son,
and even though these guys were on the board before he was born,
he takes precedent because he's your son, you see.
Now, but contrary to that, that's not a really good analogy, because in Scripture we're told that he came first, you see.
But from him coming first and also from him walking in anywhere with that type of authority, you see, it's a way to tell mankind, you see.
I see similar things going on today with people with various relationships.
You know, like sometimes someone will say, that's my girlfriend, they say, you know, we've been living together for 20 years in the same house.
You know what, that's not your girlfriend, that's your wife.
You don't have to exchange vows down the aisle or whatever, you know what I mean?
That's your wife, you see.
So what people call each other and what is being used is to evoke a mindset.
So when someone says, that's my girlfriend, he's been living with her for 20 years, he's saying, I'm aloof, I'm still Peter Pan, I don't know what I want to do when I grow up, and I'm not taking anything seriously in life.
When you say someone is your son, even if they're not, what you're doing is you're directly giving them authority, you see.
So using the term son, with the Christ being the Messiah, and the first begotten of creation and all that, it puts in man's mind, you know, that there's no question about the authority here.
In that sense.
Yeah, there's many levels to it.
But there's questions about the sons of God authority, and they're called sons, but they're killed off.
Like men.
And that is temporal.
Which is not a good thing to kill a God like a man, it's actually shameful.
You know, it's an embarrassing thing.
But not that they would know because they're dead.
No, but during the time, like, you know, it's, yeah.
Like, to give you another example, in ancient cultures, when they captured a king or a leader, they had a child cut their head off.
So it went down in history that our king had his head cut off by a child, that's like so insulting, you know what I mean?
Versus, you know, the other king killed him.
You know, that sounds like, well, he was gallant in battle and brave anyway, right?
I'll be back in a minute, guys.
Okay.
I might actually have to bow pretty soon.
Just because it's getting late.
Right, right.
Well, we'll see if we want to wrap her up soon when Greek gets back.
We've been at it for a few, three and a half.
Yeah, I can usually go pretty long, but now that I have nine to five, I just don't have the energy to.
Oh, I feel you.
I've been up since four, so.
I'm on my tail end today, too.
Well, let's just wrap it up, man.
I just heard what you guys were saying.
So three and a half is a good enough stint that it'll burn the zeros and ones long enough.
So thanks both to both of you.
Sam, we'll do this every week if we can.
I think the people that do chime into the chat and I get good feedback that they like the way you present things.
And Bruce, of course.
We had 19 on the stream there at a high point, so we were doing rather well that way.
Okay, good.
All right, well, with that said, thanks, Bruce, for everything you're doing.
Not a problem.
And we'll speak again soon to both of you.
Yes.
Cool.
Talk to you guys.
See you guys.
Be well, folks.
Bye-bye.