People in that society, you know, the military society and the idea was that Missing people in the alien agenda are the number one priority of the so-called government, you know the state, right?
You know the under part of the state and I was like, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, of course, you know, but he says no No, it's not anything like that at all.
It's it's missing people and I was like, okay So I started looking into a little bit.
There's a bunch of stuff online.
You got to go through a lot of Basically what is called the alien agenda, you know, or the Alien abduction and I think when you and I were speaking there's a guy politis That's out there.
I was on a Skype call with him.
He's very accessible by the way.
There was about ten people there and
And
basically if you speak to him personally off-air
he will tell you that it's he thinks it's ETS or
Non-human entities doing the abductions because there's no way a dog wouldn't sniff a human or anything else
You know or no footprints and things like that, but publicly he doesn't get into it too much because there's no proof
Yeah, he can't if he's going to stay
with quality
Yeah, but the it's a real agenda actually there's a lot of people gone every year
I mean back.
Do you remember the the around the time of Rodney King?
Fiasco back in the early 90s There was a lot of public stuff That one and a half million black people have gone missing not in jail or lost or murdered But just missing back in the early 90s, right?
It seems like it happened overnight So, yeah the missing people thing I mean, I don't know I think it's you know, the cows saying cows going missing and they end up at McDonald's I think it's very similar, right?
Yeah I know I've heard about the reps the reptilians and all that, you know, they have no qualms about having a human buffet So strapping you down and they come by and lob an arm or a leg off.
I mean I Mean, I think I've been talking calling people livestock for a long time publicly maybe a year or so, but yeah Yeah, you're gone missing and you're somebody else's lunch.
I mean That's not so hard what's so hard to believe about that believe it or not.
It's very plausible Right, right.
That's why I've been saying for a long time if you woke up and still have your internal organs intact be thankful Right.
Yeah Yeah, so yeah, so these morons do take the ETS very seriously and the thing is I've been looking at it now for about six Months, they're not demons by the way They're not biblical demons because they're not possessing people and they're not they're little creatures.
They're part of the ecology so You won't find them in Scripture because the Scripture is not about that.
So you won't find iPhones and airplanes and cars in Scripture either So because it's not about that Speaking of Scripture I've been looking to see there's a little bit buzz going around online about you know Translating or putting out a better version or whatever.
It's all no, they're not so it's not time yet again
Yeah, I got a couple of those
Some older woman I or something was gonna do that and I was like, yeah, okay
Well, here's the thing you don't need to be if you can distill down the the meaning and the story
You know, you don't need to read the Patriot Act to know what it's about
You don't need to read, you know, the Declaration of Independence or the Magna Carta or
Any other religious document to know what it's about?
You just need to have someone that has and does understand it give a concise summary And the proper interpretation not a version of it because you know when you speak of interpretation, there's only one interpretation But there are many versions, right?
So very often you hear these religious morons say well, that's your interpretation.
I'm like, well, no one is entitled You don't have right license or entitlement to your own interpretation.
That's a falsehood an oxymoron.
You have entitlement
License and freedom to do your own version
You see right, right
When someone let's say these state dignitaries go to the UN they bring what with them a translator or an interpreter
Right, you know not a versionist
So in terms of that biblical timeline, you know
That it started around 2018 this period that so far looking at it and the middle of it will be
on the Pope's work schedule the year 2021 and a half for
2021 midsummer and usually these events don't the big turns or changes don't have the each period
Doesn't happen until about the middle of the period right?
I mean you could see 9-11, right?
Example so Which is another thing I had someone approach me about you want to write about axial periods and I'm like no Because the way axial periods are defined anyway Are you know, you have the axle, you know, and then the hub and then the spokes and the rim of the wheel, right?
so it reflects The way it's defined in the way what it really is is not very accurate either an axial period is where the whole world changes its mind about something based on concurrent events or just Natural causes or whatever, right?
Like a natural causes would be you know, climate famine or other things like that
or migration changes, you know people encounter new ways of living because the land has changed or
Thought so when you look at the what they call axial period around the what I've discussed very often about the
religions being similar around 300 between 600 and 300 BC
That was an axial period all the modern religions including Christianity were forming back then.
I mean most people don't understand that but if you study Christianity as a political what it is is political Ideology Because if you know any Christians, they're they're not interested in anything I mean any more than politics right if you know any of those idiots Yeah, they're into politics more than anything.
So
Yeah, so it's a political ideology
But what's interesting when you go back and look at that time period in the characteristics even from a biblical sense
That was the major Persian influence on the world
You know, you you could surmise and infer that the Greek Empire was also a major influence
But there isn't much writings directly of even in Scripture are regarding the Greek Empire influencing world history
You have for example
the later
Persian Kings assisting the remainder of the Judeans to go back and rebuild the temple you have a letter actually that's
In Ezra and Nehemiah, you know
So the point here with that actual period is really you could call it Farsi
Which is a Iranian
Aryan
Persian
You know because they're the Aryans or the Farsi people
They speak Farsi like in Afghanistan and all that
Persia, it's really the Persian world if you look at the Mithra Mithra ism what Mithra ism is
All the way to the occult aspect of Mithra ism, which is you know
The transgender stuff and the influence of the goddess religion on the male
All that started around then all the religions that you see today
Were based on
That axial period give an example just like the you have a modern axial period regarding terrorism
You know it it it started before that
But it didn't stop on the world stage until 9-11 where we were everybody in the world that had a TV said well
How to watch it for three days, right no matter where you were in the world
Well, it started in New York, but now it's everywhere every country you go to they like to bring up
You know terror anti-terror this that and the other right terrorism insurance, which you don't hear about all this other stuff, right?
But I started in New York.
So the the religious axial period that you can Look back on pre you know 2,000 years ago was really an Iranian or Persian influence and Again, if you look at the current situation what they call Southwestern Asia or the Middle East The the two superpowers there are what Persia and Iran right and Israel.
Those are the two superpowers Everyone else is secondary regardless of you know, you might say Saudis or the Egypt or whatever, you know, they're not The the military and political superpowers are Israel and Persia Just like they were back then as well so So much for a better version right, right.
So what else is going on?
We could make this a really short sonic Any questions at the chat or anything of that I think it's a new new Greek speak Chitango, right?
I'm not in front of any computer right now.
I'm purely wireless
so if you want to bring up anything we could you know, nothing actually coming up, but
there was a bunch of talk about how the
different
like the EU is going to be updating its
Infrastructure as far as taking two lanes into four lanes
Making it easier for
Militarization vehicles to get through and all that kind of stuff the introduction of 5g and all this kind of stuff throughout
Which is an interesting one unto itself
Yeah, that's all that's I mean China has the Silk Road right the modern Silk Road they're developing
There's talk in Russia about Gazprom and all the various things that they're doing there to upgrade supposedly
U.s. Is doesn't have anything.
It's just financialism politics and an insurance Right in America because you know people from any standpoint you can go back and research the past 50 years The idea is to turn what they call the United States of America into a huge National Park with very few people, right?
So that there haven't been you wouldn't you know consider it successful so far, but Yeah Yeah, but you know the u.s. Is very simple.
You know what goes around comes around started with stolen land and Slavery and you know genocide or whatever of the native people and that's that's how it's going to end it's if you see really hard times coming to what's called the United States and just I Mean like really hard times and destruction.
It shouldn't be a surprise.
I mean you should actually wonder why it hasn't come yet You know typically a 300-year run is a pretty healthy run.
Yeah.
Yeah, what else?
other than that Not seeing anything in chat and I'm not coming up with anything straightaway Okay You guys been catching some of the stuff.
I've been doing with Sam at the that's designed According to Sam for first-time listeners, that's why a lot of it is just rehashing and nothing major and not getting too deep You've been catching those.
I think it's Greek speak calm That's all Sam's work if you want to send some help his way anyone with time effort graphics credits Whatever just you could go to Greek speak calm and contact him there Okay Yeah Yeah, I mean the last one you did on the political system was very interesting, okay Yeah, it's very simple.
It's very crude what you what people call the state Is really low level it's part of the management.
You know the livestock management does to you know
It's the low level aspect of it, and it's it's a it's not autonomous
You know it's the same powers
You know when you read in Scripture
especially
What they call book of Revelation which I don't recommend anyone get into because you won't understand anything in it
I
Would suggest that when you you look at the anonymity of the leadership spoken
You know there were eight kings nine kings ten kings
The king that was that isn't that was that is you know there's no names
There's just a loose reference to in Egyptian.
You know female Or in other books, and but why because yet they're not known and and they won't be known ever You know so, but they do exist so Yeah, all that stuff is secret in and you know I've been past a year So I haven't other than speaking with Sam and here just locally there's a There's no problem.
There's no movement.
I mean you could you know if he went somewhere else on another World you'd say there's nothing going on on this planet.
They're all idiots all of them And it's pretty accurate except for a very small exception, which you don't run into so It again it goes what I want to just say it goes back to you know your own quality of life You know a food clothing shelter And don't be altruistic Obviously meaning you know when people say make the world a better place.
There's nothing to make better It just needs to be redone right there's a big difference To improving something and I mean even a ghetto rider.
You know like a beat-up Toyota Camry with $4,000 spinning rims on it.
I mean that still works this world is even worse than that right You're not going to put spinning rims on a on this world to make it look better, right?
so
Yeah, you know how you know in the ghetto you see these beat-up cars with real expensive wheels
Yeah, it's not that's not going to fix the car or to make the situation better actually you'll cosmically you'll look even more stupid
To other stupid people you look fine, so the thing is it's about the time that you have left
Right because you're here
It's all the moment you come here
And that's what's how much time you have left, and if you haven't been thrown into a dumpster in a garbage bag
Well the umbilical cord still hanging off
Sorry to hear that because now you got to put up with the old conscious shit that exists, so
in essence
You're gonna just
You know like I say amateurs give advice and professionals diagnosed right right?
that's why attorneys give legal advice because they don't know anything legal or lawful, but Diagnose meaning or self-evaluate evaluate others around you as well, right?
And always proceed on a try to you know on a quantity qualitative
Progression you know how to make your quality a little bit better and a little bit better
So that's all that that's it's really here, and you know you could say this privately or publicly
It's not good to say it
But if you later on when you meet
The more of the higher beings and you got a bone to pick with them about putting you down on this shithole
I mean beautiful planet, but shithole society
It's purely legitimate to pick a bone with them right you know the Creator and his angels later.
It's purely legitimate, but the thing is
You always have to keep in the back of your mind that there's a certain level of wisdom
They have that they set it up this way
For a reason and we don't know that reason and I'm beginning to get very small
Inklings on why it has to be so crappy for so long, and I think you and I briefly discussed it
one reason you might
Harken and say it's selfish because to them a day is no big deal where it's a thousand years for us
But on the other hand they've compensated by making their lives really short
You know 70 to 100 years or what we want to say 120 fine
you know and
So at least you don't have to be put up with it all
But there's a certain wisdom, and I think I've gone over it much more in the past.
We're just numbers You know they're they're great accountants not not mathematicians I should say because mathematics and arithmetic are two different things right Adi's most and mathematics Are two different concepts anyone who wants to delve into that the difference the difference between mathematics and arithmetic, but?
They're not into either one of those or counters and bookkeepers.
Let's say well you know so From that perspective that would be the only path that I could see What's behind the bookkeeping of so many people coming through and such a shithole?
state For so long well, you know consider the short lifespan and The promise of something better that when it does come it'll you'll forget about how bad it was here And it's not really that bad when you you know most people say it's not that bad right, but from my ideological Perspective you know if you're into what's lawful.
What's right?
What's you know real freedom and all that you'll find the world to be deplorable no matter where you are It doesn't matter which country it's all the same It's just different versions right flavors So that is a I think a legitimate and far-reaching question that we may never get an answer to till it's all you know finished You know why you know why is it?
Why are we here like this and we're also in scripture.
We're given an example You know there's a group of people called the Israelites and the Judeans you could lump them up like that You know the the you have the Judeans and the other 11 are the Israelites right other 11 tribes Let's say or 12 because there's really 13 or 14 tribes if you want to start counting They couldn't handle it either so Yeah Got anything else Bruce.
I'm just flipping some doing some stove top potatoes Or patata, you know it's interesting in Greek potato is patata and in India India or Hindi.
It's also patata alright Interesting coincidence Anything else want to get into Are you there Bruce?
Okay, yeah, that's fine Yeah, I figured it's okay Oh sure, or we can just make it a really why don't we just turn it off make it a really short Hello, goodbye, and maybe we'll schedule another one soon.
Okay.
Thanks Bruce.
Take care everyone.
Bye.
Bye, okay Bye