And greetings everyone, we got Greek and myself live and hopefully everybody is hearing us good.
Yeah, probably so.
Okay, Greek, how are you doing tonight, sir?
Yeah, I'm doing all right.
Greetings.
It's been a little while since we've done anything like this, just a sonic, what we call sonic stream.
So yeah, let's just catch up if there is anything to catch up on.
Yeah, well, let's just go right off the bat.
I think you mentioned we were talking about Genesis before we got on.
And also there's been some talk, someone wants to get some kind of Genesis project together.
So I don't know, it might be something to pursue or, you know, I mean, we won't be the first during it, but it'll probably be the first time things like that will be said this way.
So yeah, you want to do a little talk about Genesis, what you brought up earlier?
Yes, I was mentioning how the word memory meant water and light.
And I found it fascinating, right at the very beginning of the book, Elohim's first two things that he touched and played with was water and light.
And it made me question if that was the beginning of memory, time, recognition, and how that played into steering on to the rest of the books.
And I guess I wanted to hear a little bit of your take on that, and questioning myself whether I was going off on a strange tangent or some such.
Well, it is a tangent, but it all ties together.
I mean, it depends on how loosely tied it is, or how tightly tied it is.
Like, for example, to remember in Hebrew is not mem or or, it's zakar.
Okay.
So when you stick within the standard, you know, let's say you're measuring English, you know, imperial measurement versus metric, you know, you can't switch back and forth, you know, it's kind of hard to do that.
You stay within, so if we're going to stay, let's say Hebrew is metric, if we stay within the metrics of Hebrew, mem is water or is light, but in English memory sounds like water and light, right?
The word is actually made up of those two words.
But memory, or to remember in Hebrew, is not mem or or, it's zakar within that standard.
So it only works when you go outside of the standard, or the reference, you know, you see.
But one way to explain Scripture, and if we were to do a study on any of the writs, it doesn't matter what it is, or any methodology, or any concept, you have to give it in the language that the audience is listening to, and you have to give it also in terms that they can associate with, right?
So, in other words, to go, let's say, to a discussion on Genesis, to bring up mem and or, I think that's just a curiosity aspect of language, because, you know, the English language is what I'm presuming everyone is listening to or speaking to.
So, you know, with these sonic events, because they're done in English, I can do them in other languages, but doing them in English, I think, is the standard.
And I would say that the concepts in Scripture are what I'd like to get into, right?
Because that seems to escape the entire world.
It's amazing how much ignorance is out there.
But this is what the gods have chosen for mankind, is to be ignorant at this point, so don't take it personally, even though you should.
You should take it personally at the same time.
You know, in other words, that's why I call it cosmic censorship.
And, you know, I used to be asked, you know, well, if there's cosmic censorship, aren't you censored?
Well, you know, you should think a little bit more before asking those kinds of questions, I think.
So, yeah, so getting into Genesis is going to be interesting, because, you know, what I've always done through sonic events is stating that the last thing to discover is the obvious, right?
So, if you're reading something like Genesis, or anything really, anything, but especially Scripture, you know, when I say anything, I mean also outside of the Scripture.
But if you go back to Scripture, one thing you have to consider, it's written by the gods, for the gods, to the gods, and mankind, and nature, and any other sentient beings, right?
And it's an abridged form of what can be known, obviously, but it's jam-packed.
And it's also given from a human perspective, because you see there's, even when the gods are speaking, they use terms like hand, and face, and eye, and cup, right?
And footstool.
So it's from an anthropomorphic perspective.
Like, for example, one famous thing to consider, you know, everyone's heard of the cities of the plain.
Well, you know, when you read in Genesis about the five cities, and Sodom, and Gomorrah, and Zarah, and these other cities that are listed there, they're called the cities of the plain.
And people have used that term outside of Scripture, you know, but if you go into Scripture, the term that they're translating as the plain, you know, like we would say, like, a plain is like a field, right?
Or a big, flat, open space, isn't so.
It just uses the word kikar, which means circle, like flat, or like a pancake, or something.
It's usually used when you're talking about coins, or bread.
So when you were, now why use that term?
Why couldn't they have used audits, you know, edit something, you know, that means the plain more directly, is because it was discussing the point of view that Abraham and Lot had, when they were discussing how they were going to go each their separate ways, let's say, right?
And it also gave you where they were standing when they were having this discussion.
So that, so in order to pinpoint that geography, you would have to go to the city, or the area, where Lot and Abraham were having their discussion, and then view around and see what looked like a circle.
Right.
So you see it from the reader, reading Scripture, it doesn't make sense.
So they could have been in a valley too, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Well, they were on a higher, they were on a hill, but they were looking down into something that preceded a valley, before the valley there was the circle, correct?
Which was the northern part of the Dead Sea, and Sodom, the city of Sodom, is not where it is on many encyclopedias, on the southeast side of the Dead Sea, it's on the northern.
Because when the destruction came, Abraham was able to see it, and you couldn't see past where they're showing you it is.
So, you know, you see how this discussion can just open up into another discussion, where it was Sodom, and then it goes on and on and on.
But the interesting part about Scripture is that you're almost going to have to understand more about your own imagination, and also how good of a detective you are, before you get into it.
Because most people, when people have tried to get into anything in Scripture for thousands of years, and have left, not really drawing blanks, because you're going to see the word the, you know what that means, or you know, up or down.
But they draw a lot of blanks, because what happens is the imagination has limited capability.
Our own humanness gets in the way too.
Well, no, let's be more specific about it.
Because if you're looking at the cities of the circle, you wouldn't know what that meant, unless you were in the area that they were having the discussion, and viewing it as a circle.
Right.
So, who has the time, or the inclination, even though some do, to read the Scripture, and actually, when there are geographical and historical points made, to actually go and manifest themselves in that location?
Very few.
I mean, it has been done.
You could go on the internet, there's films done about it, documentaries, and all that.
None of it is accurate, of course.
Some of it is, actually, but so little.
I mean, it's one piece of corn in a big pile of poop, right?
Right.
So, what's interesting about it is, that's why I said you need to have a very healthy imagination.
So, when you run into something like the cities of the circle, where in your English it's going to say the cities of the plane, it's not a plane.
So, now, what do you do with that?
You see, what do you do with that?
You're going to have to set that aside, and keep reading, and look for clues.
Now, you're becoming like Sherlock Holmes, kind of thing, right?
Right.
Because most people can't afford, or don't want to afford, the ability to go there, and all these locations, and historically look for evidence, and things like that.
So, you're going to have to do it from where you are, based on the information.
See, that's what makes it difficult, and that's where the sharing, and the communication is important, right?
People like, you know, that's a researcher that could validate what they're showing you, through Scripture, and what's manifest, you know, as evidence.
And that's one of the things that, you know, Scripture either allows or disallows.
It allows, meaning, you're going to have to have a very broad knowledge of all things discussed in there, both in the context of Scripture, and outside of the context of Scripture, but sometimes it doesn't allow the reader to understand what is being said, unless they actually do physically go there.
So, you're at a disadvantage, right?
In some cases.
So, you're being disallowed the information.
So, what I would suggest, in that case, is, you know, the stupid rectangle, right?
You know, some people say, you know, don't you go on vacation, don't you travel?
I said, why?
I've got a big plasma TV.
If I want to go, let's say, to the Congo, if I want to go to the Congo, I just put a DVD of the Congo.
I mean, why would I suffer the jet lag, and the malaria, and, right, just to get a mango that weighs, yeah, just to get a 10-pound mango that is the best mango you've ever had, you know, why?
Why?
And there's no reason to anymore, for the same reason of, what do you want to afford, and how convenient do you want things to be?
So, one thing that I would do is suggest that, yeah, the Scripture itself is a project, but here's the other thing, no matter how simple you explain the Scripture, if the audience is not familiar with it, no matter how simple the explanation is, it doesn't hit home.
It doesn't really register, because it's, there's nothing there.
So, it's a reworking, just like when you read in Scripture, it's not a creation, it's a recreation.
That's why you see there's a delineation between the word to create and to form, but in the English versions it says create, create, create, create, or make, or made, doesn't use, doesn't delineate between the two.
So, most of the stuff that we're interacting with, down to, except for the archetypes, you know, the basic bare bones, is a recreation.
So, what I mean by that is, you've heard of cars being made out of recycled metals, right?
Right.
So, well, what is that metal, you know, I mean, so you have a BMW made out of recycled plastic, let's say, right?
And, okay, well, all right, let's, we can only, as far as we can observe, good observational science can show us, is that this is a BMW, based on its form and likeness, and it's made of plastic material, and we know that it's that plastic material at some previous time had a different form, and it was reprocessed.
That's what you're getting out of Scripture.
Or, you know, the car that's made out of recycled metal, well, can you tell me about the metal?
Well, I know that, I know it's iron and zinc, and maybe it's got some copper in it, whatever, but no, I can't tell you much about what it was before it was melted down.
Right.
You see?
Mm-hmm.
Now, that's a really, that's like a super firm footing to start off on a discussion on Scripture.
Yeah.
And that's all we've got, but there's more, actually more of it is in there, and, but it's not as sure as the rest, right?
Like, we can discuss, again, going back to the car being made of recycled plastic or iron or steel metal.
This goes back to when you were talking about all the errors that are just in the whole, in the book, the King Jimmy alone, which, which is astounding.
Well, because for years, up until, here's the thing we, to appreciate the King James in history, not as a document, but before that time, if you were caught studying or reading it, you were put to death, pretty much, anywhere in the world.
Anywhere in the world, except for the Far East, like east of Jerusalem, which we could get into.
I mean, I've been doing a little bit of research on the Parthians and the Scythians and all that, and they've really been, let's just jump around a little bit here, they've been given, let's just say, what happens when you, when you tell someone to go to the back of the bus or take the seat all the way in the back and you forget about them, what do you call that?
Neglected.
Right.
The Parthian Empire has been neglected, big time, and they played a very big role in all of Scripture.
I mean, you know, past the time of, let's say, post-Exodus, you know, and there's no, yeah, I mean, when you hear of people coming from the East, you know, that was all Parthian Empire, you know, between 200 BC or 300 BC, all the way on till the Roman Empire, and then they subsided.
Like, for example, for the pagans, it's their season to do the Christmas thing, right?
And this is, there's more research to be done on what I'm going to say, but this is something that, you know, needs to be considered.
When you start looking at how little information is put out about what was east of Jerusalem from the 2nd or 3rd century BC all the way to the 4th century AD, that's a time period of roughly six to seven hundred years.
It's really a piss-poor, we have nothing, we know, everyone thinks it's Rome or Greece or Babylon, right?
It's generalized, yeah.
Yeah, so there was a lot of power there.
Like, for example, the Romans weren't able to make peace with the Parthians until about 100 AD, when they sent some envoys there.
The Romans always got their asses kicked.
If you crossed, the Romans only went up to the Jordan River, basically, right?
Which is the smack down the middle there of what they call Israel.
And if they sent anyone past, you know, if you made it to the Euphrates, it was an act of war, you know, which is further east again.
So all that area, all the way to India, and all the way up to China, and all the way down to the Indian Ocean, all that was the Parthian Empire.
Oh my god.
And it was centered, yeah, it was centered around Iran, which was decentralized.
What the Parthian Empire did was what the Americans did with the British.
That whole area was pretty much controlled by Persia, and they had their little revolution where they left the king, they basically rebelled against the king, but it was peaceful, and they went into an agreement, and they became more powerful after they left the monarchy, just like the Americans grew and became larger than England.
You see the metaphor there?
I'm just giving you an off-the-record history, so you have a simple understanding of what's going on, and it's a parallel to the U.S. in a way, how they rebelled from the monarchy and became more powerful later.
The Parthian Empire did not exclude, just like the Americans didn't exclude England, did not exclude Persia, but they were very powerful.
Okay, so they also had tremendous knowledge of math, astronomy, science, medicine, history, that the rest of the world didn't.
The rest of the world had access to the information, but they were the carriers of this information, and they had an undisturbed lineage of this ancient information based in science, math, medicine.
So what I'm giving you now is a little bit of an unofficial, off-the-record, and I'm going off of memory from stuff I've looked at ages ago, a while back, so because this is an interesting thing, it's still not being discussed.
So do you think it was a bit calculated on how they were neglected that way?
Well, yeah, you know, I've discussed in the past how, you know, every country, well before, okay, you know how when you order pizza, you know, it says this is the best pizza in town.
Yeah, every country thinks they're the greatest nation on Earth, right?
So every empire thinks they're the greatest empire, and this is a predominantly Western world, you know, you and I and most people listening are raised in a Westernized world, you know, Levi's, hot dogs, hamburgers, TV, all that, right?
Apple pie.
And before that, yeah, before that it was Westernism also, you know, Victorian and on, right?
So you're not going to hear much about this.
Now, the reason I brought, let's go back, and this is all, you know, if you anyone wants to do more of a study on this, you know, they're not going to find much, but when you do find a good channel or a good line on studying them, you're going to find, you're going to say, holy crap, man, how come no one ever told me about this kind of thing, right?
Wow.
So, but what's interesting about it, two things, when I mentioned the pagan season coming right now, there's something called, you know, the Magi, for example, right?
And what's interesting about that, you know, how they show you, you know, these guys walking along or whatever, you know, and, you know, they look like they're basically nomads, you know, and poor, and they're, you know, they're carrying whatever.
Okay, that's not how it went down, and this goes back to how to read out of Scripture, and sometimes you need a very healthy imagination, and you also have to be there.
And in this, you know, and actually, you know, what, how much of an effort do you want to afford to know what's going on?
And in this case, I haven't been there, because this was a long time ago, and also I haven't been there now, but what I'm saying is, when you do the Sherlock Holmes aspect, and you figure out that these people from the East, now there's more to this, but let me just run it this way.
When they approached Herod, right, and said, we're here to make an offering to the king of the Judeans.
Now, Herod was already king, right, even though he wasn't a Judea, and he had a fake lineage and all that, right, but let's say he sat in the seat.
So why didn't he say, well, I'm the king, and you guys are under arrest, and I'm gonna cut your heads off for, you know, assaulting me, right?
Yeah, he didn't say that.
He, as a matter of fact, if you read the text, when they approached him for that, Herod was what?
He was scared of them.
Think about that for a minute.
No, he was afraid of them.
Hmm.
Because, okay, let me just go forward, okay, let me jump forward, because these guys were so powerful, they had the ability to dethrone kings and put in whoever they wanted.
Right.
Okay.
You ever heard of the Illuminati these days, who'd kind of do that?
Yeah.
I don't want to say that.
This is not, you know, yes, were they conspiratorial?
Yeah, of course.
But, you know, have you ever heard of the, you know, the underground financial powers that were central banking powers and scientific powers that run the world?
The technocracy.
Don't you think, like, if they want to go into France and take out the, you know, topple, you know, and change the government, they can do it?
Yeah.
Because they have...
Lesson of the day.
Well, yeah, they wouldn't do it that quickly now to shock people.
They'd give them a week or so, maybe a month.
Okay, that's being generous.
Yeah.
But these people were, and they also, they didn't travel as shown.
They traveled with a very powerful group of people, you know, maybe a small miniature entourage of at least two to five hundred, maybe even a thousand people with them.
You ever see a presidential motorcade come through?
Correct.
You know, it's not just the motorcade.
You'll see, like, the 50 cop cars, and you'll see the 30 Secret Service cars, and then after he passes, there's another 30 Secret Service cars, and another 50 cop cars, and their helicopters, you see?
Just passing through, you see?
Yeah.
Now, what's interesting is they had secret knowledge of when he was born, because we see, we can, this is presumptive.
Abraham was given knowledge.
You know, when he's told to count the stars, it's not to count the stars, because in other parts of Scripture, it says you can't count the stars.
They're uncountable.
And that just means, because of your lifetime, you know, if there's quadrillion stars, if you counted one a second, you would only be able, not even do a billion in a lifetime, right?
So you can't count them.
There's no way.
So, the point here is, he sent his sons east, some of his sons to the east, with all this knowledge that he had.
See, so these guys kept that, and that's what they, you can easily presume that these Magi that came, that were very powerful, were descendants of Abraham, directly with this kind of knowledge.
And it didn't happen at this time of year, of course.
It was in the fall.
The only reason I'm bringing it up is because it's kind of difficult not to see the little scenes where they have these, you know, piss-poor nativity scenes that they show.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's not what it was like at all.
I mean, what they show you in the nativity scene, does it look like those guys would scare King Herod to his britches, you know, shaking, shaking?
No, I doubt it.
Yeah, because remember, when you were a king in those days, you had armed guards, and they had like, male-scaled armor, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
All this other stuff, right?
Not like the knights did.
Oh no, no, they had massive ordnance and all that.
So, you know, yeah.
So, this is, I just had to throw that in there, because, well, how do you pick up on this?
Well, you have to understand what the Parthian Empire was.
You have to understand who these people were, based on the knowledge that they had.
And also, you have to look at the situation.
When they went to Herod, Herod was frightened of them.
Okay, see?
So, what does it take to frighten a king?
And again, we're dealing with lineage and bloodlines.
Well, they also showed up with quite a bit of might.
They were very impressive to look at themselves when they came.
Right, true.
Just like the presidential, you know.
Well, imagine like, you know, the head of the Rothschilds, you know, came, comes through a city, you know, or something.
But he was overt, or whatever.
Right.
You know, I mean, this is all unofficial that I'm just trying to give, let's say, show through a little bit of Greek-speak.
You know, you guys go out and look at all this stuff, and you'll see what you find.
This is all unofficial.
I'm not giving dates and names and places and exact history here, but this is just a general broad stroke history of what is going on, or what went on.
And, you know, and actually you can compare it to what is going on now.
I mean, I guess I gave the analogy.
Motorcade and all that.
And also, just to piece it together, because you'll see the cards and the artwork and the scenes that they put out with these three wise men.
And it's just, I just want to show that there is, there's nothing there, you see, that resembles what is really going on.
And this is the key.
And it just shows how corrupted it became.
My goodness.
Well, it doesn't even resemble it.
You have to force your mind to agree that that's what happened, because it's so different.
It's like the 19 Arab hijackers with box cutters and turning the World Trade Center to dust.
It's just as ridiculous.
You know, I heard recently someone was doing some 9-11 research, and he has a daughter.
And the daughter, she's, I don't know, 10, 12, something like that.
And, or 11.
And this, you know, what are you doing, dad?
And he says, well, I'm just catching up on some 9-11 research.
And he says, well, tell me about it.
And he told, he told her, like, you know, the official story.
And she goes, I'm a child, but I'm not stupid.
So.
Out of the words, babes.
Yeah, so what you see going on right now is really, you know, stupid.
It's just really.
Why?
Because, you know, what's the, now most people, you can say, well, you know, they don't know about the Parthian Empire and the Scythian Empire and all this other power that was west of the Jordan, really, I mean, east of the Jordan, east of the Euphrates.
But the interesting thing is, if you know scripture, what does it take to get a king scared?
Yeah.
You need a lot of force and might yourself, you know.
And you have to have a history.
Yeah, they were not, they were not up to par.
You know, they were not equal.
These guys were higher in power.
Right.
He obviously knew it.
Well, of course, yeah.
The whole world knew it.
The whole world knew it at that time.
And this is, again, a contrast of what's going on now.
You know, so the operative term there is that, you know, Herod was set aback by these guys.
And what does it take to set someone back?
And then who are these guys from these, what's going on in the east?
And there's no discussion on it.
That's why I figured, let's just throw a little bit of this unofficial aspect of, you know, hey, look everybody.
Appreciate it.
Did you know, you know, look, this was going on over here, you know, let's take a, you know, let's get a little reality check going.
So the scripture is all like this.
It's all reality check, reality check.
The thing is, I've always said, you got to read out of it.
Don't read into it.
There is nothing that you know, that was told to you about scripture, that you could go back to it and use it.
You get it?
Yeah.
So if you start reading Exodus with the 10 commandments and all this, and it's not Moses, it's not the way it happened.
You can't, when you read scripture, there is nothing that you were shown anywhere that you can take with you and put in overlay into what you're reading and say, oh, I know about this.
You don't.
Yeah.
You get it?
You see?
So that's why, I mean, you have to be there if you can, if you can afford to spend a life and umpty amount of resources to go to these places and see what they look like and stand where these people stood.
That in itself would have to be a ...
Oh, it's out of the question for almost everyone, right?
At this, you know, unless you're there already, and even if you were there already, it's still a lot of moving around.
So the other thing is, can you be like a Sherlock Holmes?
In other words, can you look at all the obvious details that give you the real meaning and the setting of what's going on together?
Yeah.
Right.
And the other thing you have to comprehend about scripture is it's the only ancient writ, well, the only ancient writ that one third of it is prophecy, right?
And accurately.
The other part of it, it's the only other ancient writ that gives you accurate history, accurate geography, accurate people, people meaning, you know, nationalities, you know, meaning the lineages in each story.
And also it gives you what they're doing in that geography within that history and why they're doing it and what the outcome is.
You ever notice that?
Yeah.
Almost every single time.
Your setting is complete.
You're given the geography, right?
You're given city names, country names, right?
Sometimes very specific city names and geographical descriptions as well.
Right.
Locations.
Again, you're given, yeah, it becomes a part of the history, meaning you know who this event is happening after this other event and before this other event.
So you could place it in history, right?
For example, like this happened, for example, you know, before the Exodus or after the Exodus or before this, right?
So you could place it in history.
It gives you people.
And sometimes that's when you look at the prophet, it tells you who they were the sons of and what they were, right?
And it tells you what they're doing and why they're doing it and what the outcome is.
Isn't that interesting?
Almost every situation.
Now in some of the prophetic situations, some of the, let's say, aspects of just once these things have been established, the more mechanistic side to say, well, you know, generally this is what's going to happen.
It may not recap on all those things, but all those things are always brought up.
You'll never guess where, you know, you'll never bring up anything out of scripture and have to guess where it happened or who it was or why it happened and what the outcome would be, right?
You never guess at these.
All the questions are answered, always found, right?
What that makes it as a perfect reference document does, doesn't it?
Yes.
So if you look at it as a reference document and, but it's also, you know, put together in a way that it's meant, even though it's everywhere, right?
You can access it, you know, and even if you don't have, if you just have it in a King Jimmy or whatever version, you know, these days you can go and get an intralinear, but even though it's everywhere, it's still a secret.
Yeah.
You see?
So anyway, let's take a break from this topic unless, I just wanted to throw that stuff in there, maybe.
Yeah.
I appreciate it as always.
Oh, hey, remember when you brought that up about the animals?
Oh yeah.
Well, let's go back to, you asked me earlier about, you know, the light and the, and the memory and the water.
Well, you know, there's a lot of things, you know, you can start looking at things and set, yeah, the word is good.
I like the point you brought up, but we kind of tossed it to the side because memory means a car and not memory.
Correct.
I just, I just saw an interesting coincidence, I guess.
For English speakers.
Yes.
Correct.
For the English.
Yes.
And it could be semi-important, I should say, because we, you know, again, this is the English and, you know, it's in the end, we're approaching as we go to the end, everyone, you know, it seems to be the universal language, you know.
But to keep it correct.
Yeah.
But look for patterns.
I suggest maybe looking for patterns.
Like, for example, the first time any, the animal is first brought to Adam to name the different kinds, right?
By the gods, the Allahim brought the animals.
Okay.
Well, then after that, after Eve, the animal skins are brought, which are dead animals.
But then the next time the gods bring animals is to Noah, right?
So they're alive.
So twice alive, once dead, you know, in between.
But most of the time when the gods bring the animal to man, they bring them alive.
But with the animal sacrifices, when the humans return, the man returns the animal, they return them dead.
Isn't that interesting?
It shows you, it's a metaphor of what's going on.
The gods bring the living and man returns to the gods.
Instead of death.
Death.
Yes.
Right?
So this is like someone asked me, you know, why are there animal sacrifices?
Well, they're a pattern.
You know, what are you doing an animal sacrifice?
You know, it's not killing an animal.
You're bringing it to a certain spot, you know, with a certain liturgy, right?
And a certain thing, you know, for purpose and it's killed and then offered.
So when the gods bring animals, they bring them alive.
When man brings animals, he brings them dead.
And they're still doing it today as much as, yeah.
So this is a temporal thing, but there is a little time in between where not, you know, the animal skins were brought to Adam and Eve to cover because they were ashamed to know what was coming in the future.
So, which is another story I can start discussing and when we do Genesis, it's not what you think it is.
So, let's see, is there anything in chat going on?
And I'm going to get some of this Java.
So, you know, keep going and anybody else want to add anything or take away?
So far there is nothing.
A repeat of the advertisement from my radio stream.
If anybody in the channel has got any questions, feel free to put it in the chat tangle there.
We'll certainly bring it on the air.
Any thoughts on Jerusalem macinations and political stuff going on?
Oh my goodness, nothing in chat, but yeah, what a story that's become.
I only lightly skim that, of course.
I don't really like to stay with that.
Well, it's predictable, of course, and also it's what it means is, it does, it's several things.
It's, okay, can you, you know what a drone is, right?
It's control, it's a physical thing that moves, but it's controlled by another, you know, it doesn't work, it doesn't go autonomously.
The political leaders of the world now are just drones.
Obviously, they have their own personality and distinguishing features, their character, but they're acting as drones.
The thing about Jerusalem, I should have said something, but I'm not going to say that, but this is an obvious move.
Why?
Because you need to establish the borders of certain Judean jurisdictions in Israel, right?
Before a certain edifice is built, right?
So this is a first move, and by the way, this is not going to be an easy thing.
It may not even happen right now, but it's an interesting thing to see it come up.
So you're suggesting, possibly, just testing the waters?
Well, I'm suggesting that it won't, the borders, okay, I'm not looking at it just Jerusalem being declared the capital of Israel.
I'm suggesting that the way these nations are going to form and how jurisdictions are going to move and how countries are going to be divided.
I'm suggesting that there isn't going to be any stability in what they call Israel until the Gaza or the Palestinians are established in Gaza, and I mean in a very expanded Gaza, just like it was expanded 10 or 13 years ago, but it'll also mean the displacement of all the West Bank settlers.
Yeah.
And it's not going to be voluntary, if you know what I mean.
Yeah, that's going to get ugly.
Yeah, and we're still looking at another prime minister or two before those issues are settled.
But I just see this going on, because it's definitely in line with what I've been saying about, okay, this is the last period, this past fall and winter, this is it.
Now we're starting a new approach to, you know, manned society on earth.
And now we're going to be setting for the next seven years, prophetically, is setting up the mindset for everyone to accept a Middle East Union, which will be formed by the mid 2020s, 2024, 2025, around there, it'll be in place.
Right?
So think about the mindset that was put in place before the EU was formally established openly.
So these are just lots of little things we still have, you know, like this, today, there was a big thing in Iraq about them, just, just, you know, the prime minister came out and declared Iraq is now ISIS free, you know, so they're like back to where they started, you know, or better off, supposedly, and there's still no Assyria.
And Jordan is still Jordan, it hasn't been changed.
And Lebanon hasn't been changed other than their prime minister resigning, and then going back and then resigning, and then maybe going back, I don't know.
So, so there's still a little while yet.
But all of this movement is very dynamic.
And it's, is it worth really talking about?
Nah, it's not really worth talking about yet.
I know there is going to be one want to have a lot of talk about things that are happening when you wake up one morning, and there's 15,000 Palestinians died last night.
Yeah, you know, not, you know, 1500 or 20,000.
You know, that people are going to say, well, we haven't had a mass slaughter like that since the American Civil War, or maybe what battle of the bulge or something.
Yeah, World War Two.
Yeah, yeah.
So and I'm not wishing this on them, because there's nothing anyone can stop it.
I'm just saying, you know, I don't you know, that's, I think if something like that happens, I'm just going to shut everything down, not go on Skype, not answer any calls until people cool down, because I've said it already, see?
Right.
So, so and also, there's going to be a massive movement to change the borders and not the borders, but the nationalistic aspects of, let's say, the way you view Jordan, the way you view Syria, the way you view Lebanon, the way you view Iraq, you know, I mean, there's, these countries will be basically turned inside out like a sock, you know.
So and this is the period for it to start happening now, you know, so it's going to be quite interesting.
Yeah.
The other thing is, one thing to watch out for, I'll just say this unofficially, how's that?
Okay.
When eminent, when eminent, what they call judgment of the Elohim, you know, when they just punish, you know, destroy the society, one thing that follows, one thing that precedes that destruction from the gods to a particular city or society, if you read very carefully, one thing, one of the details, well, you know, this is what they did all these abominable things and whatever, right?
But one of the things, one fine detail, I mean, everyone's doing abominable things, right?
Right now, every country.
But one little detail that precedes that destruction is that the nations around them cried out about them.
Like if you read it about Sodom and Gomorrah, it was the nations around them, which were terrible, the Canaanites and all these other cried out against, because they just couldn't take it at all.
They just couldn't take, in other words, they prayed against these people also, right?
That's what preceded the destruction.
Because if, you know, to destroy Sodom and Gomorrah because they're evil, well, then he should have destroyed, he should have destroyed all of it, because they're all evil.
Not just as evil.
Actually, he gives you a reason why, specifically in the book of Ezekiel why, but it's not what you think.
But there's a, so what's interesting, if you look in modern history, what is there, is there a worldwide outcry about people being sick of a certain group of people, and that would be the U.S. Right.
The whole world is pretty much sick about how the Americans are acting.
So it's just something to keep in the back of your mind, right?
So I just want to bring this up.
Don't say that I said this, and this is how it is.
No, no.
Think about that for a minute.
It's just an interesting parallel, huh?
Yeah.
It's scary.
Yeah, right.
So anyway, one thing to look at is that, you know, consider the fine points, you know, what does it mean?
The other thing, let's see, what was the other thought to carry on that?
Oh yeah, about the future prophetic events.
I mean, I'm not going to say it's going to be honky-dory, but you're better off knowing what's going to happen before it happens.
I always say, I mean, I'd rather be, you know, I'd rather know if, you know, if I'm investing on the stock market, I want to know if it's going to go up or down and exactly how much.
Yeah, everyone wants to, right?
So that was just one point I wanted to throw in there.
You know, I recently heard, this is a little, it was a law thing.
I actually did an interview with her, Angela, at a talk show thing.
I tuned in, just happened to listen to a, this is a guy, Thornton guy.
He does common law stuff.
I wouldn't say I agree or disagree.
It's just fine.
It's not what's going on, but it's, you know, whatever.
But he gave a lot of legal jokes in the end.
Now I'm going to, I want to repeat one of them.
And these are all true, by the way.
What makes it a really good joke is that it's true.
And this is sort of the thing about, you know, what I just mentioned about when you see destruction come upon a place in scripture, one of the fine details that people don't talk about is that the nations around them, people around them complained about them to the gods also, right?
Okay.
So the interesting thing here, the story is, is there's a bar in Midwestern town and its business is so good and it wants to expand.
So it doubles its size, you know, so it shuts down for a month and builds a, you know, a big extension, you know, it just doubles the size of the building.
But down the street, there's a church and the church is protesting that the bar is expanding its size.
So what they do is a, you know, the bar just, you know, says, no, it's my bar, you know, and you guys are a church, you stay there, I'll stay here, you know, whatever.
And so the church or the congregation started praying and praying, praying that, you know, the bar goes away.
Well, what happens is in the middle of construction, a whole bunch of lightning hits the bar and burns everything to the ground, the old part and the new part, right?
So the bar owner decides to, you know, he knew about the ill intent from the congregation, and he drafted a lawsuit to sue them for being the cause of the destruction of the bar, because they prayed for it, because they prayed for it.
So he put that all in the lawsuit.
And the judge shows up, and he reads the lawsuit.
And he's like, well, I don't know how I'm going to do, how I can rule on this, because I have a bar owner that believes in the power of prayer, and a church that congregation that says that they don't.
Because, you know, the church congregation denied that they prayed for it, right?
I was just to tie in with the praying for destruction.
Yeah.
So, you know, a lot of people, just to tie this, maybe I'm overdoing the American thing a bit much.
People are always wondering, you know, thinking it's changing their own ways, right?
Their political structure or whatever is going to, right?
Is anyone paying attention to see if anyone else is praying for your destruction?
Yeah.
How about that?
No, that's not being brought up at all, because, well, we're secular, man, you know, we don't believe in that stuff, right?
That's right there in the writ.
Yeah.
So, anyway, I just thought, you know, tonight's the unofficial, official, unofficial stories or whatever.
An unofficial mindset.
Yeah.
Just think about it.
Well, you have shared quite the enlightenment again.
Definitely grateful for that.
You're welcome.
Yeah, okay.
Is anybody around?
No, it's absent.
We got eight people in there, according to the toggle, but not an area.
Nary a voice be heard.
Okay, that's fine.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, maybe ...
Perhaps they're shy.
Yeah, anything else you want to touch on?
Well, let's see, let's see.
You covered some very interesting points.
Oh, anything coming about on ...
somebody asked a while back about Wes, and you and him were investigating car engines and modifying, and any news to report on that?
Well, not really.
He's 2,500 or 3,000 miles away, and he's doing the best he can with what he has and what he knows, which is very good.
But no, it's very minor.
I think he recently sent me something, it's actually not minor, some simple things that he did to basically restore an engine that has 300,000 miles on it to run like it's brand new.
Oh my goodness.
According to the reports I've been getting.
Very simple stuff.
I mean, just like ...
he wants to do a sonic event on it and run down on it, and that would be very basic.
Yeah.
I would love to help in any way I could for that.
Mm-hmm.
He's a fascinating fellow.
I remember listening to him on one of your sonic events.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
And somebody had brought that up maybe a week ago or something about that, and so I kind of jotted it down in the memory.
Okay.
Yeah.
But the best thing to do is there's a lot more that can be done unless you're, let's say, well-versed as being a mechanic or really got most of the ...
and also machining skills, there's only so much you can do.
But that so much was enough with Wes's testimony to pretty much bring that car around to a new car.
Wow.
From burning oil and all that to no burning oil to ...
so we'll probably get into it.
It'll make any mechanic cringe, by the way.
I'd love to do that.
Just like a doctor would cringe if you'd ask them how to show me the blood pressure without putting that stupid cuff on.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, if he ever does want to get together for an event like that and he wants to put it on the stream, I'd be more than willing to offer.
I'll let you know.
Yes, please do.
And he could let you know as well.
Yeah, either way.
Yes, yes.
But most people ...
I don't know how many people wrench on cars these days or have the desire to, but if you do ...
There's a few out there that still tinker and have the luxury to do.
Yeah, it doesn't even have to be a car.
It could be a generator.
It could be anything, a boat, trailer.
I mean, not sure.
Usually petrol or gasoline.
The diesel ones just suck so much air.
That, I don't like to give advice on because you could blow those things up.
Yes.
Because of the high compression, right?
Yes, there is.
Yeah, we can get into that.
I've gotten some ...
I'm still getting feedback on the emails on successes with the health and diet and food and just the general mindset of stuff.
Great.
So, I'm glad that's being appreciated.
Yeah, I mean, I think that ...
Go ahead.
Most of the information I give out I consider to be fairly standard, but to some or most it seems fairly esoteric, but what makes it standard is that it works.
Right, right.
And it's basic.
And again, it's stuff that's just never, ever talked about.
And that's the stuff that just blows my mind a lot of the times.
Well, no, you're under ...
Well, why?
Why isn't it talked about more?
And I realize that, and I think there's an indoctrination that goes along with it.
I was talking with the grandson about that.
We're both spoofed by the same BS.
Okay, so let's just go down.
Hold on.
I'm going to interrupt you for a moment.
Let's just go down the three maxims.
Why?
One, you're being pranked.
Two, there's cosmic censorship.
You could do the cosmic censorship first.
There's the pranking.
And then, dummy load.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you're being censored by the gods.
You're being pranked by other men and some gods, some lower entities actually.
But actually to call them gods is only because they're invisible.
And then you're being severely pranked by your family, initially.
Yeah, and the society at large.
Yeah, and if you're not being pranked by your family, you're being pranked by someone else's family.
Right.
And it's just, it's amazing.
Right?
So, it's family.
So, whether it's your own family or another family, family is pranking.
Oh, hey, we got a question in there.
How and what will the Saudi Arabia people play in the future Union Greek?
I don't even, I think they're going to be a satellite.
Saudi Arabia is probably going to split.
And because you have a country, Edom, in the south there, that hasn't been inhabited, you know, south of the Dead Sea in a very long time.
And that might be part of their role.
But...
They stay to themselves pretty much.
Well, have you ever heard me say that the real stuff is going on where it's not noisy?
Who's noisy right now?
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure.
Who's been noisy for the past month, two months?
Hmm.
Yeah, that's another knack.
That's part of the prank, right?
And when someone hands you a chair, you see a big fluffy cushion, and let's say it's a blue cushion on the chair, but you don't see the blue thumbtack, right?
Right.
You just see the big cushion, right?
Fluffy.
You don't see that.
So, you've got to look for the little fine stuff.
So, when they're blasting everyone with...
Because, you know, most people are going to find out about what's happening in the world through the regular channels.
It's done through the mainstream, and then the alternative picks it up and decides to spin it, however they're going to spin it, right?
Mm-hmm.
And they are spinning.
One way to answer, T-Bender, is to answer that question on your own and for other questions regarding internationals.
Because I'm presuming you're in the U.S. somewhere.
And the person who's asking the question is in the States, the Americans.
Somewhere, I'm presuming.
So, in that case, what's interesting is just a little knick-knack file thing.
Ready?
When you go to the rectangle, which is better than the radio or the TV, to look for what's going on internationally, let's say, you're going to be blasted with all the stuff they're making the noise.
And then just keep digging a little deeper into international affairs that are not being blasted.
And that's where the real stuff is going on.
You get it?
Yes.
Like, let me give you a couple of ideas on how to work the rectangle.
Let's say, well, how I do it.
You might do it the same way, but let's just say it.
Most people don't talk about how they do browser searches, right?
It's not a popular thing, but I think it's a necessity to just talk about it, right?
It's just as basic as tying your shoelaces.
You don't think about it.
You just go to the browser and you do whatever you might be used to doing.
Or if you're new at it, you're still going to do things a certain way.
Now, what I do is I put in the topic, and if it's something that is time sensitive, like international affairs, Middle East, or whatever, I'll do a search, for example, Middle East, right, in the browser.
Then I go to the tools and I put in last 24 hours, and I click on that.
Because if you just put in Middle East, you'll get a variety of sundry of things.
You might get some maps, a couple of general references, and then what they want you to see in the news, right, the first page.
But if you go and you look for something that is temporally based, like activity, news, and things like that, put the search in.
If you do see a story, you're like put the search in and go last 24 hours.
You see?
And what that does is it filters out what you've been bantered about for a week or what you want to show everyone else as a general overview.
Did we lose you?
I had myself muted.
Sorry.
No, that's fine.
And then if you want to get a little more nitty-gritty, just go past hour, if it's Middle East, past hour.
And then you'll see, the other day I did this, and it was a corporation that was doing some work for the tallest building in the world, which is twice the size of the Empire State Building.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Personally, I'd like to know more about that than you see.
So I don't know.
There's some serious money moving around there.
Well, yeah, credit.
Credit, yeah.
Get used to using the tools, the time button.
Do past week, past 24 hours, past hour.
That's a good way to look at it.
Even with historical stuff, you'll put in archaeology.
You want to really have a real interesting time?
Put in archaeology, past 24 hours or past week.
Archaeologists are not really like the news people and other people.
Well, when they find something, they're out there.
Yeah.
If you want to be an archaeologist, you're going to spend your whole life in ruins, right?
Right.
But anyway.
Okay.
So there's a lot, but you'll see what's going on.
Tip your waitress tonight.
So what you see about the archaeologists, you'll be like, wait a second.
This is big stuff.
I'm not being told about this anywhere.
It'll be a little blurb.
Or like, wow, man, you just dug out a whole city here?
How come it's not in the news?
Not a piece.
Because they're just finding a whole bunch of headless babies there.
That's why.
Yeah.
You get it?
Yes, I do.
Yeah, it's not pretty.
In Mexico.
Oh, no, everywhere.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, the latest, I think.
Not just headless babies, but bone fragments and whatever.
Yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
That's one way to do the searches.
Yeah, Merry Christmas.
Happy Birthday.
So there you go.
Jesse says, will they continue to have their so-called wealth?
He's referring to the Arabia people.
Yes, yes, and so will everyone else.
Very rarely does someone achieve that much wealth and lose it overnight, right?
Think about it.
It takes a while.
Right, it takes a while.
And also, this entire area is going to go to prominence.
I would suggest that when they run stuff across the border, what is that called?
A gateway or a passageway?
It's a gateway to the Middle East to bring stuff in.
What the heck is that?
A corridor.
It's a corridor.
It's a financial corridor.
Yeah, it's a corridor there.
That's all it is, to that area.
But also, you're going to see a corridor developing from the eastern side as well, which hasn't started yet.
And from the north and from all around.
The whole world is going to go there.
So they're not going to lose their wealth.
No, they're not.
Or their position as they live.
You see, what's interesting is, take this however you want.
Again, unofficial.
Qaddafi, Libya would have been like Saudi Arabia by now or maybe in the next few years if they didn't take him out.
That's why they took him out.
Because, you know, if you live in Saudi Arabia or Kuwait, I think you get $30,000 or $40,000 a year.
Just like in Alaska, when you live up in Alaska, they give you like $500,000 or $1,500,000 a year for being up there as an allegedly share of the oil revenue or whatever.
The wealth, yes.
Yeah, the average.
This is not Saudi Arabia.
I'm not sure what Saudi Arabia is.
But Kuwaiti, the average income in American dollars is $120,000.
That's the per capita average.
That means some are below and some are above.
You know what I mean, right?
Right.
And that's why when you go to places like Kuwait or just do a YouTube Kuwait last week or last month YouTube, look at the streets and all that.
You'll see the indigenous people.
And then you'll see a lot of Asians, people from India, people from Africa, the continent of Africa, all over the world doing all their stuff for them.
You see, it's a very  even Israel, if you know anyone in the agricultural business in Israel, a lot of the kibbutz or masads are places like that.
Masad also just means a group that are doing development.
And you'll see people from Korea, people from China, people from Somalia, people from doing most of the work.
So there's big integration to that part of the world right now.
Well, it has been for a little while, but it's going to grow more, you know, basically in the service industry and labor industry and migrant industry.
I'm going to mute and grab another cup and I'll be right back.
Okay.
Maybe you want to take a break, play some music maybe or something?
Yes, let's do that.
We'll take a little pause and we'll get you folks back in just a little bit.
And stay tuned.