So, I don't know how they're going to do that, whether it's literally putting up roadblocks, but somehow they're going to create a problem.
Well, aren't they in the Psalms that all the nations that rise up against, or the peoples that rise up against Israel with one heart and one mind, aren't they included in there as well?
Yeah.
I think it's Psalm 83.
Ten nations.
And I think it's the world, I don't know if it's the world at large, but I think it's the world at large, because Edom represents all the Gentile nations.
But I think they will lead the onslaught, the ten nations.
Well, the Gentile nations now are locked in sort of a messianism, Christianity, right, what you would call, and then you have Islam thrown in, but Islam is too bizarre to consider, you know, as a worldwide thing, even though it is, I mean, you have a billion of them, mostly in Asia.
So everyone is set up for a messiah, a coming messiah, right, is what all these religions have in common, even Judaism, right?
So that's the set up.
And which is accurate, by the way, it's just what they expect is not accurate.
And their current doctrine is not accurate, or it's downright, you know, adversarial to what's been memorialized from the gods.
Yes.
Yeah, so throw that in, and it gets more interesting.
I still see it, here's one way to sum things up.
Do you ever get the feeling when you look at scripture, whether it's the historicity of
it, the current religiosity, and what's coming in the future, it's all secret, secrets upon
secrets, organized chaos in public division, and it seems like it's going to be this way
all the way to the end, except for the exception of, you know, everyone falling for a particular
deception, which is, you know, a manifestation of a god, let's say a god or the god, the
most high on earth, as in the form of a man, right, which is the false deal.
So when you look at Edom, okay, so let's just to sum up, Edom so far, they have, well, they
by covenant and by relation are close to Israel, but have taken an adversarial and warlike
stance on occasion, and it also formed an impediment towards Israel, and also they represent,
like you mentioned, I'd have to go back and do more of a study to say that I know that
they represent all the pagan nations, I'd have to just take what you've said on that,
but that's quite a burden, by the way, on them, to take on such a character, you know.
Yeah, took it on themselves.
So they're very...
Not on them, it's the spirit behind them.
The spirit behind them, so it's a very worldly spirit.
Yes.
So you'd have to, so you would find that in modern day, what modern day religions you see, they're all...
Here's the interesting part, how would you identify them, I'm not saying there's an answer to this, would they, in the spirits that roam the world today, would you say modern day Edomites would be Christian, would they be Islamic, Muslim, or would they be Jewish?
Or just, it's all still mixed back.
There's two ways, I guess, you could look at that.
The first one I kind of touched on is that you would see their influence as extending through the Phoenicians as far as being very commercial and being very money-centric.
If you, like you said about the Zionists, if you want to see it as extending into what is today modern day capitalism, then I guess that is widespread and has its teeth in most parts of the world.
Another way to look at it is that you have certain people groups that came under the influence of, say, the Edomites or the Phoenicians at one point.
We can look at that.
So I'll just skip to the end of Obadiah, because the rest of the chapter kind of talks about the same stuff.
So Obadiah 21, at the end, it says, and the exiles of the host of the children of Israel, this is talking about once Edom is destroyed and Israel will take over all their stuff, take their land and stuff, the exiles of the host of the children of Israel will possess that of the Canaanites as far as the city of Seraphath.
And the exiles of Jerusalem who are in Sepharad will possess the cities of the south.
So these are two cities that are mentioned.
I don't know if I'm pronouncing it right, Seraphath and Sepharad.
They can offer up some interesting points of study.
Seraphath, also called Sarepta, was a Phoenician city on the Mediterranean coast between Sidon and Tyre.
And it's mentioned, obviously, in First Kings.
This was the city that Elijah went to when he was on the run from Ahab, where he revived the dead son of the widow.
And Sepharad is a little harder to pinpoint, but I've read that it was a Tyrian city on the coast, close to the coast of Palestine.
And at this point, I can only conjecture after this, and maybe you can confirm or negate the following.
So my understanding is the way that the Phoenician mercilentism worked was that if you wanted to go to or trade with a particular nation, you went to a city on the Phoenician coast that had ships that went to that nation, and the exports from foreign countries were shipped back to the Middle East.
And then you had merchants from Babylon and Assyria that would come there to get the stuff.
So you had these two cities, presumably, from what I've seen, Seraphath and Sepharad, which were allegedly two cities that had trading connections with Western Europe.
Sepharad was on the...
Let me just interject something.
Because that entire coast, like even Jaffa or even the Nile, you know, and I've just covered the entire Levant, right, it makes sense to go through.
Well, not really because, you know, you have to cross the Jordan, the Dead Sea and the mountains.
But if you go to that area that you mentioned, what makes a port city give it notoriety is its financial system.
So it's not necessarily the geography.
It's where the bankers or the financial people, the banksters, want to plant their heels.
Like, for example, if you look at America, the States, New York is known as a great port city, you know, and all that.
Well, the bankers are planted there.
But, you know, one of the biggest port cities in the world, if not second or third in the world, is Louisiana, right, in the southern.
So why doesn't Louisiana have the notoriety?
Because, you know, it could house or, you know, birth many more ships, even 100 times more than New York.
But why doesn't it have the notoriety of New York?
Because guess who else is planted in New York?
The banksters, right?
So I would suggest that there's a financial influence and what's interesting is that there's in some prophecies that silver and in the areas of tire, silver and gold or gold will be like dust in the street, right?
So there's a prominent financial center that dictates the prominence of the port as well.
You know, it's not just the...
So I just wanted to throw that in when I was thinking when you mentioned, you know, defining, you know, why would you go there?
Why would everything go there?
You see, I mean, you still have like Long Beach in California where 99% of the stuff that comes from China goes through there in the States, but it has no notoriety yet.
You know, I mean, ask many people, you know, mention a port city, they'll say New York.
Well, Louisiana is the largest, one of the largest ports in the world and 99% of the crap you Americans love to buy comes through, you know, California, that city, not just Long, you know, Long Beach and no one knows that because guess what?
There's no financial interest there.
So...
That's interesting.
So the city of Sefarad, I mean, you can kind of tell by the name and I am guessing here, but I just feel like what I've seen is plausible.
So Sefarad was the city on the Mediterranean that traded with the Iberian Peninsula, which contains Spain and Portugal.
So the Iberian Peninsula area came to be known to the Semites as the area of Sefarad.
And when many Judeans migrated to Spain, they were resultingly called Sephardic Jews.
And Serapath was allegedly the city that traded with what we call France, leading to sort of similar results.
So, other than that, the Israelites, according to this prophecy, will at some point in the future gain control of the former Levantine areas where these cities were.
I'm not sure what the implications for Europe are, whether France or Spain participate or if they're affected.
I don't know.
You mean back then or now or in the future?
No, now.
I mean in the future.
Oh, everyone will be.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I know.
I mean, I think it's safe to say that if they're going to possess the cities of Seraphat and Sepharad, that, OK, then their influence will extend up until these Levantine cities.
Because if we can pinpoint the locations as being such, does it mean that there's going to be a European tie-in as far as Spain and France?
If you want to say that these cities also then extended into Western Europe because of the trading?
I don't know.
Well, I see it as a focus.
Well, what's coming is a focus in that area that no matter how small or whatever its quantifiable substance is, it's going to be the focus of everyone on the planet, right, to a certain degree of it being of capital importance.
So it doesn't mean it has to be large or affecting any specific place.
It's just going to be the center, a worldwide center.
Speaking of speculation, there's been a lot of speculation, especially if you look at current events like the rags like Time magazine or the ones that are put out with large circulation from the 1960s until today.
What was it in the 90s?
It was like, oh, Hong Kong is going to be the biggest city in the world, right, the biggest interest.
Actually, it is in some way.
It has the amount of taller buildings than any other place, right, and many other things, but it hasn't gotten world prominence.
It is prominent, yes, but it hasn't gotten that type of what we read about it that's coming in the end, right?
You see, well, China was supposed to take over the U.S. 10 years ago, right?
Remember?
I don't know if you – the fear of China, you know, Sinophobia.
Yeah, yeah, and so all these things that oscillate back and forth, and yeah, they are building huge, amazing developments in all these places, but according to Scripture, nothing will compare to what's going to happen in that Levant area, you know, like let's say Tyre, you know, or even those other cities in between Sidon and Tyre, right?
So developmentally, again, what's going on there?
I mean, there's not much.
So how is it all going to happen?
Just to paraphrase again, what I've been saying is the purpose of prophecy is giving you the end result.
Sometimes it doesn't – well, most of the time, I should say, it doesn't give you the how it's going to happen, the why we know because it's preordained, but it gives you the result, right?
And even if you read in Scripture prophecies that had taken place, they'll just bring up an event, you know, like let's say Jezebel's death, right, and they'll say, well, look, this was prophesied, you know, and they'll give you, you know, but you didn't see it coming until it happened.
I mean, you didn't acknowledge it as prophecy until after the fact.
But, you know, when you read something like, for example, Jerusalem will be destroyed in ancient times and you knew this was a prophecy and you were able to time it right because you knew how to keep time and you knew, you know, all the other markers around prophecy, you know, even up until a few weeks or months before it was destroyed, it was still very optimistic.
So you would know, since you've known this prophecy for a long time, not to heavily invest, no matter how optimistic the worldview was, you see.
So you end up being like this crazy guy if you know prophecy, you know what I mean?
Because very often these things happen suddenly or it seems like when they do happen and even you say, I told you so, they're still ignored.
It's like, well, look, everything was so great and it just happened, you know, it's just the way things are, you know, I'm like, no, no, no, this was prophecy and the people still don't acknowledge it.
So when you start to figure out prophecy, you're like this almost spiritual outcast as well, you see.
Because you go back to, let's say, for example, Jeremiah, even when the Babylonians were at the walls, you know, they thought it was going to be the Assyrians, right?
And even when the Babylonians are at the walls, they're like, oh, yeah, why is this happening, right?
Why?
What did we do?
You know, we're so prosperous all these years, you know?
So, yeah.
And, yeah, that's the interesting aspect about it.
I'm bringing that up because one of the things that I stand on and being what I like to do personally is, again, bring, figure out what history is pertinent to explain what and why we're doing what we're doing today and also what's coming, you know, what's next and how is it going to come or, you know, because it's pretty easy to see the prophecy.
You just read it literally.
If it says, for example, this place will be destroyed, well, what is there to explain or interpret?
But the thing is then to figure out this is the most amazing and glorious thing if one can do is to see how it's going to end up that way, you see, and give specifics on the way.
And that is extremely difficult, but I assure anyone that once you start looking at everything, you know, mythology, tradition, real history, if you can find it, the bullshit history that's taught, scripture, archaeology, you look at everything and you have to do it with a lawful mind and then you have a narrative that's pretty solid on explaining these things.
So, again, to tie that back into Edom, I think Obadiah is the one that I mentioned earlier that is committed mostly to Edom, right?
That's the one you just read.
Right, it's a short one, yeah, because that's what came to mind.
There was a minor prophet that committed most of his works.
And also, Edom is brought up over and over in other places.
But, again, who are they?
Is it strictly geographical?
No, but I think the geography is very important just to sum things up.
And if you look at what Edom, historical Edom is, there's nothing going on there right now.
Just like Babylon, there's nothing going on there right now.
But these are things to watch.
One thing that I like to always bring up is that it's interesting when you warn someone about something and they acknowledge it.
It's one thing when they just do it with words.
But when you warn someone about something and they acknowledge it and they take action to prepare themselves, that's another completely different aspect of the information retrieval or conveyance, right?
So when you look at, for example, so I don't like to bring this up much, but the book of Revelation, these things will happen quickly with speed, right?
That doesn't mean that it's going to happen quickly after it was written.
It means that when they start to take place, they are going to move at a very high rate, right?
Like one example, two examples I give is the collapse of, let's say, the communist bloc in 1989, what they call the Soviet Union, and 9-11.
Like a week before 9-11, if you told people after this week there's going to be a huge state security apparatus employed in America that will spread to the whole world and this new thing, war on terrorism and all this will happen within a few weeks or months, people would say there's no way something like that could happen so quickly, right?
Or if you mention the Soviet bloc in 1989 in the summer, that after this fall it will be completely dissolved and balkanization will take place and all the, you know, it doesn't make any sense to say it then, but division of all these will be re-divided back into maybe closer to antiquity and all that.
I said, oh, no way, Greek, that can't happen because it took 50 years to build it.
It's probably going to take another 50 to break it down, but it happened within a year, you see.
So getting used to very rapid changes, which you're warned about in the bloc revelation, the word that's used is tachy, with speed, meaning a tachy, like a tachometer or something that measures a rate.
So you could be revving an engine with a tachometer at a very high RPM, you're not going anywhere, it's just how the engine is moving.
So one thing to watch for is in the coming future, meaning a week, a month, a year, next few years, is because you can more than speculate that there's going to be a Middle East Union and there's going to be a prominence of that area worldwide and, you know, we see the divisions of who they are, you know, by bloodline and name.
How does it come together?
And when it does come together, it's going to happen very rapidly once it starts.
The interesting thing that I always say is that once these things start to form and they become very prominent and powerful over a short period of time, everyone will be like, oh, well, I guess that seems natural, it doesn't bother me.
Yeah, you know, like, yeah, six months ago there was nothing there but sand and a few people living in tents and now it's one of the most prominent cities in the world.
I mean, I'm not saying it's going to happen that fast, you know, and people just feel like, oh, yeah, that seems normal.
You know, like after 9-11, you know, oh, it seems normal that we, you know, have an extreme security apparatus employed everywhere.
It seems normal.
But before 9-11, a week before, if you told anyone, like, ah, no way, that can't happen.
No one will allow that to happen.
So what I just spend a few minutes speaking on is, I guess in paraphrasing here or in air quotes, the psychology of this, right?
So when you know what's coming and you start to glean how it's going to come by seeing what's going on and it comes so abruptly and so quickly and so dynamically and no one seems to bat an eye about it and you're like, oh, this is prophecy taking place.
I mean, obviously, you see.
This is the time period that we're living in.
So, and if you start trying to make a point of it that this is prophetic and the next thing is this, eh, no big deal.
So this is almost like there's something in the air.
Like, what do you call it, like an opioid or something that makes, who was it that said religion is the opioid of the people or the opiate of the people, right?
Was it Lenin or Stalin or one of these people, right?
So it seems like there is like a numbness or I wouldn't say an apathy.
You can call it an apathy or indifference to these two prophetic events, by the way, by the world at large.
So, but these discussions that we have or the Greek speak narrative is always pounding the basics of it because that's essentially what you're going to see.
In other words, people are going to wake up and about a decade from now or less than that and there'll be a Middle East Union running the world, right?
And right now it sounds like absolute madness, right?
But, so, anyway.
Yeah, I mean, from my end, I think we're done with the, we went through the whole book and I feel satisfied with that.
I don't know what more else I could say or anybody can really say.
It's something that has to be watched and contemplated.
Yeah, I think it does.
I have to get more esoteric if I want to continue and I think that's meaningless.
Well, it's not always because it's part of, you know, looking at everything, right?
You know, like I mentioned earlier, where's...
I mean, if it's esoteric into the place where it's absurd, then you're talking about Gnostic stuff or things that can't be really...
Well, look at, you could look at that too, but you have to remember now you're eating something with a Gnostic flavor, right?
So, you know, put it this way.
There's enough Gnostics out there that it was put out to and preserved even though it's fiction mostly or wrapped in fiction and injected with a lot of...
You know, Gnosticism is a form of syncretism, right?
It's a mixture of things here and there.
It needs to be looked at as well because you know how I always say, are you able to pick edible corn out of poop, right?
So, are you that hungry, right?
Well, maybe not, but if it's...
All right, then.
Yeah, yeah.
But it's still, I mean, is it worth looking at?
Eh, not really, but yeah, it should be looked at.
For the same reason, for example, people always still message me and say, well, which version do you read or what should I read?
Interlinear or whatever.
I said, you have to be familiar with all of it because if you want to discuss scripture, 99% of the people you're going to run into that want to discuss it know what?
The King James, which is all the other versions also.
So, if you know nothing on how the King James, the narrative works, or the mistakes are, or how it's set up, and you only know, let's say, the Hebrew and the Greek or gone further and gone into the Aramaic and other things like that, you're not able to have a discussion with them, are you?
So, now you've separated yourself and you really are up in a tower.
And, you know, when you get into the top of the tower, it's too small to have a party, right?
So you have to go down to the lobby to have the party.
And in the lobby, you don't have the view, but at least you're at a party.
So you're never going to be invited to the party if you just know the strict aspect of what was supposed to be done.
You also have to know, you should always know why the right way things should be, but you also have to know, unfortunately, the way it's been done so you can communicate, because the people that exist on the world today don't have abandoned the way that things should be for the way things are.
So you have to know both the way things are and the way things should be, or what's true and correct, unfortunately, right?
And, you know, what's interesting, that Christ knew that as well, you know, how he criticized them.
He said, you don't do Elohim's law, Allah's law, and you don't do your own laws.
He criticized them on both.
So how would Christ criticize them for not doing their own man-made written laws if he didn't know them?
You see?
You know, I mean, how much more?
You know, here's the interesting part about it.
There's, you know, you've heard that people are creatures of habit and such.
Well, you know, if you were to, let's say, index the fact, meaning make it very mechanical, like in machining and indexing is you don't have to keep measuring, you make a jig, you just make a thing, you move it, and it's always exactly the same distance, right?
If you just make it rote to study any field or any subject, you just schedule it or schedule it, if that refrains.
You just say, look, today I'm going to spend a half hour looking at this subject for five days.
So that's two and a half hours, you know.
Or if you read, let's say, three pages a day, that's a thousand pages in a year.
You see how simple these things can be to look at?
And, again, I'll share a personal note.
I stopped really studying five, six years ago, you know, where I would really just make it a full-time thing to, you know, if I were a laborer, you know, digging, you know.
And for the past five, six, seven years I've just been meditating and brushing up little by little on other things if I, you know, want to look at on what I've studied and how it applies, you know.
Which is fine, but you do have to get back into studying at some point.
Oh, yeah, I'm beginning it little by little on a cursory level with things that I know.
I'm mentioning it on a personal note.
There are two things that we know for sure will not be revealed until the time is right, in Scripture, for example.
I study other things, too, but let's just, Scripture, right?
One is the book of Revelation and one is the book of Daniel, right?
Those are two books, and one literally does state sealing, and the other one implies that it's sealed, right, the Revelation.
Those two things, as time goes on, and the time period is now, you know, reading them again and studying them again, you will see things that was not possible to see earlier, and those do require attention, serious attention, and I mean the most serious attention.
And then, of course, on a personal note, again, I do study, to my dismay,
the natural sciences, you know, what they call physics, material science,
energy science, and all that, and I can tell you that it's in a rut right now,
and I don't think it's going to progress much more from where it is, you know,
because if you were to state, let's say, from a relative point of view,
I wouldn't say the past decade,
but from the mid-'90s until about the mid-, you know, 2004, 2005,
there was a lot of advancing, you know, in materials, computation, you know,
miniaturization, right, if you looked at how things were moving,
certain things with efficiency, all of that has come to a halt,
as far as I see it in a general industrial way right now, so it's kind of dismaying,
because you know what, you know, I'll say very simply why,
because they don't want to acknowledge that what is being taught at university
regarding all the physical sciences, which is chemistry, physics,
and on and on and on, is very limited.
You know, how many times have you heard people say,
well, that breaks the laws of thermodynamics, or that breaks the laws of physics,
you know, they're still relying on that jargon, which is holding them back,
because there are no such thing as laws of physics or laws of thermodynamics,
those are just repeatable concepts that have been, you know,
memorialized and taught to people conventionally,
but there is no such thing as laws of thermodynamics, you know,
as being as rigid as they explain them.
I think they're just being used to control people, you know,
because right now there's an emergence of, or there has been,
but I wouldn't say it's very active, let's say, you know,
you don't hear too much about the free energy stuff anymore like you did ten years ago, right,
the reason why is because they found that it couldn't be explained using the conventional stuff,
you have to totally abandon the concept of an electron moving down a wire,
and once you, you know, in order to break free and actually use things in efficiency,
the same thing with chemistry, you'll notice that the study of catalysts has gone away,
because they have a hard time explaining how catalysts work, you know,
catalytic reactions, you know, where you have one material pass over another
and there's no bonding or depletion,
but it changes one material into something completely different sometimes, right,
changes its properties.
So if you look at the physics or any of the natural sciences,
what's being proved out is all the formalization that was done in the 20s, 30s, and 40s,
with all the physics and science and chemistry there right now,
has done great injury and harm to them,
and they can't advance any further unless they break away from the, you know,
the atomic planetary model of the atom and how chemistry really works,
and the laws of physics and thermodynamics and Einsteinism,
and realizing they've come to the end of the road with that crap that's been taught since the 30s.
They have to go back before the 1930s and the 1920s and revisit electricity, chemistry, physics, all that stuff, because that was far more reaching back in those days.
That's the other part of my personal study.
And I have, for example, there's a group, Science Direct, you know, they do publications, you know, online you buy them, you know, for research, right?
They'll give you like a page synopsis or an abstract, and if you want the article it's $20 to $70 or whatever.
Well, I'm starting to read some of the topics, because I also work with acoustics and sound reproduction and various things like that, and I start looking, and they're almost, you can see it in their language, that they've reached a point where the conventional science that's taught, even on the highest university level, is very limited.
They have to go to another, they have to go beyond it, and they just can't because they'll be ostracized, right?
And the pressure relief valve on that system is what they call quantum.
You hear quantum physics, quantum this, quantum computers, that's all bullshit.
There's no such thing as quantum, by the way.
That's like an Einsteinian derivative of crap.
So they're using that just to cover, you know, the inadequacies of the past, what would you say 1930s was, past 70, 80 years.
So those are the things I look at.
I look at the natural sciences and scripture, basically, and those things from a personal note where I'm at with it.
But, you know, again, just to throw, again, the concept of free energy, that's already been established.
That was established 40 years ago, and one of the ways to do it is if you really understand nuclear energy, I'm not a proponent for it, you can do it with that.
If you really understand transmutation or what's called LENC, L-E-N-C, which is low energy, or L-N-R-C, which is low energy nuclear conversion, right, if you understand that.
And also if you understand something like the Joseph Newman machine, right, how electricity is just really, really a form of magnetism.
Yeah, that's already been done.
It's already been, you know, what they call anti-gravity, that's already been done.
J.J. Thompson, you know, all that stuff that people are still wondering about, it's already been done.
Transmutation and all that stuff, that's already been done.
So all these things that people are wondering what we'll be able to do in the future, that's already been done, folks.
Just go look at it.
So there's not much in the natural sciences anymore, really.
Because think of it this way, from the natural sciences, if you can have a machine that, you know, electrical, that creates electricity, based on just the mechanism itself, it doesn't need any external input, you know, like fuel added to it, well, you're done.
Now you can power a city with just, you know, keeping the thing going, right.
And when you understand low energy nuclear conversion or transmutation, well, you know, now you don't have to do mining anymore, right.
You know, do you need platinum?
Well, let's just go make some.
We've got plenty of iron scrap.
Got lots of copper and magnesium.
We can make gold, yeah.
You see, that's a problem, though, isn't it?
Because what does that use?
So who has more power in the world?
The people who are interested in the furtherance of the natural sciences and industry or the banksters, right?
So let's say I can prove to you that 40% to 50% of all the platinum that the Russians put on the market, by the way, they control the platinum market since after the Yalta conference, you know, that was given to them, by the way.
If you try to open up a platinum mine that's outside of military intelligence and Russian control, it gets shut down.
I don't know if people know that.
I'm not going to talk about it too much.
But why do the Russians get away with putting out most of the world's platinum, you know, on the legitimate market, and 40% of it is proven to be made in the laboratory from iron, let's say.
I shouldn't be saying this, but let's say I just said it.
Why don't they get in trouble?
But if you try to do it, you'll be in big trouble, right?
Well, let's just – why don't we say this then?
Why don't we further natural science, let's say, in education and also in industry by promoting mankind's, you know, low energy nuclear conversion of iron into platinum and just start putting platinum in places where it would make things better, right?
We could, you know, start making it.
What do you think will happen if you start promoting an agenda like that?
You're going to get shut down by who?
The financial interests.
Aren't they going to shut you down?
The same with, let's say, the energy machine of Joseph Newman.
But let's just invest about, you know, $300,000 to $400,000 and get enough copper and, you know, magnets.
You know, you teach children how to put this thing together.
And it's a 1,000-volt system, by the way, and you could just, you know, step it down to whatever voltage you want and just put up, you know, a steel building somewhere, put four of these in there, and it'll run the whole town.
That's it.
You're done.
You don't need any coal, any, you know, any nuclear power, any waterfalls or anything like that.
Why don't we promote that in industry and all that, right?
Who do you think is going to step in and tell you you shouldn't do that?
The financial interests, you see, right?
So, in other words, you see that there's a control.
People think they pride themselves.
That's why I can't stand, especially the people in the natural sciences, you know, physics, chemistry, and so on, and energy and all that, because only the most limited people are put in those fields to excel in those fields because once they realize what I've just told you, or it becomes a realization how it can be applied, they get shut down by the financial interests.
So, again, it's the financial interests.
And you know what?
The interesting thing about that is there is no money.
It's all credit, and that's being run by who?
The law merchants, the attorneys.
So they're the trustees.
They're the ones that are deciding who goes to jail.
You know, if you understand legal studies and you start getting active in it and you start, let's say, go question an attorney general or someone high up in the state, certain questions, and they don't like them, you know what their response usually is?
Because obviously, you know, they don't know any of these laws, by the way, because if they did, they wouldn't get a bar license.
They wouldn't be there.
But once you start bringing that up and say, well, if you keep talking like that, you're going to go to jail, mister.
Now, this is coming, like, from people that are supposedly, you know, have master's and doctor's degrees in laws and are the head legal person in the state.
This is the best reaction you get from them, right?
And the reason I brought that up is, have you ever watched interviews of, I'm not going to mention specific names in there, like let's say treasury chairman or banking chairman of, like, you know, think of the major banks, especially the ones in America.
Have you ever listened to an interview with some of these guys?
You know what they sound like?
They sound like the hot dog vendors on the street.
That's the level of, this is how they present themselves.
Yeah, have you ever been to New York City and got a hot dog?
You know, you want ketchup or mustard, you know, you want some sauerkraut.
If you're like, listen, like the diamond guy, the guy of Citicorp or the guy of, you know, J.P. Morgan or whatever.
You listen to him speak, you're like, this guy is like, is he like the pool cleaner?
Is he the guy that changes the oil down here at the, you know, is he like the repairman for, what the hell?
You know, just like when you listen to the high-level legal people.
It's like, oh, you're running the legal system of the country and you know nothing about law.
Well, the joke is not on him.
The joke is on the people.
And the joke, well, the prank now will be on you if you push the issue.
Anyway, it's really a funny thing.
So how does this tie into study?
If you study enough and you realize what I just said, you're going to realize why, you know, why study anymore?
Because it ain't going anywhere in the current condition.
And who was it that owns the hospitals, the financial interests also?
Oh, yeah.
You know, here's the thing I tell people about hospitals or banks.
Don't even think for a moment they are what you're told that they are.
You know, the main purpose of a hospital is to produce paperwork, you know, titles of human bodies, right?
And go to any hospital website and look at their financials.
Even like a medium-sized town, not even a big city, a medium-sized hospital approaches almost a billion a year in earnings.
You're like, how the hell are they doing that, right?
So, you know, well, you know, hospital, hospice means where you go to die.
For up until the 19th century, well, actually the early 20th century, if you told anyone anything with hospital and they were like, oh, someone's dying, you get it?
So, and, you know, I'm not talking about actually, you know, in the medieval ages you went to the barber, right, for medical stuff, in most places in the Western world.
Now when you say barber, it's just for hair, let's say.
You know, typically men's hair because it's been boutiqued as salons now, hair salons.
But when you say I'm going to the barber, it's usually it's for a shave and a cut or something, right?
But back in the early days it was a place where, you know, you had limbs mended and, you know, burns and cuts and, you know, all that stuff, right?
Right now people are thinking the hospitals where you go for, it's a place you go to catch infections and also to be, to get your credit line used up pretty quickly.
Not that you can use it up.
But in the future it will be viewed as just being a bank, as just a scam on the people.
Just start with the, hospitals are quite simple.
You know, I tell people if you go to the hospital and they make you sign anything, ask for a cash receipt for it.
I want to speak to someone in the administrative department because they just have these workers, you know, that hand you paper, if I sign this, you know.
Like if I sign this I need a cash receipt.
Well, there's no cash here.
I'm like, well, let me speak to someone in administration.
You see this piece of paper here, this financial document, if I sign it I need a cash receipt just open.
You know, like just say, you know, I've given you some unknown cash value for signing this.
And they freak out.
They run, they're like, oh, you're not supposed to know that.
This is planet earth, right?
And then people say they have hospital bills and things like that.
So anyway, it's just absurd.
The whole thing is absurd.
Here's another thing, back to the legal system.
This is like the mini Greek narrative rant.
I dare anyone to go into any Ivy League law school and look at their curriculum.
Do they teach any law?
Nope, none at all.
What you're going to see is classes in administrative law.
What is administrative law?
Okay, if you go to work at a sausage factory, their administrative law is this is how you chop the meat, this is how you stuff the sausage, this is how you wash your hands, this is the temperature of the fridge.
If you work at Wal-Mart, this is their administrative, they give you a little administrative law, you know, this is how you treat the customer, you have to show up before you, this amount of time before your shift starts, right?
You notice how I'm changing it?
Because administrative law means how you're going to administrate a particular deed or act in a very specific venue.
It has nothing to do with you.
There are no law schools anymore.
There haven't been law schools in a long time, hundreds of years.
It was always up to the people.
Actually, there's the Army Manual that was written, I think, in the 1920s, and it says that the only way for the republic or any republic to withstand, you know, any society other than, you know, the one that it's formed under is for the people to be educated in law.
They're not administrative law, but law.
So you get 12 years of high school, how many years of law do they teach you?
Do they teach you five minutes?
Nope, not even that.
So anyway, when you talk about study, this is where you're going to end up, and I'm just giving you the punchline.
The reason I like to give the punchline and the finale on many things is because if you've ever been around these Hollywood types, you ever watch these two-hour movies, I'm going to tell you that unless that movie is formed around a book, someone came up, a writer, with a great scene for 15 minutes, and they're like, we should make a movie based around that.
I'm like, yeah, but the problem is we've got an hour and 45 minutes that we have to build around that great 15-minute notion.
You see, it's all filler.
You can see it, by the way, once you know that, and you watch a movie, you're like, oh, yeah, this was like a really short idea, and they had to just fill in the most of the movie was just filler around this one little idea.
So why not just do what the independent filmmakers did 20 years ago?
There was a big whole rash of movies from independent filmmakers that were 20 minutes long.
Do you remember those?
They were really good, a little 20-minute story, and Hollywood didn't like that.
They've kind of gone away now.
They were around in the 80s and 90s.
And that was, you know, you watch it, and it's like it leaves a 20-minute, some of these indie films leave more of an impression on you than watching five two-hour Hollywood films, you know.
By the way, I want you to look at something, perhaps, if you would.
Sam, Seth left a question earlier when he looked at the Ten Commandments written on stone.
He says he only found eight.
Do you have an answer for that?
I'm going to mute, and I'll be back in about 30 seconds, okay?
So Ten Commandments on stone.
I think I have an answer for that, not definitive, but in the meantime.
And also, Bruce, how are you doing there?
Doing great.
Yeah, we're great.
We're doing fine.
You sound like you're doing great, yeah.
Okay, I'll be right back.
I don't have anything on that, honestly, because I have not really studied that part of the text.
But, I mean, if there are ten, there are ten.
I can't really comment on that.
I have to take a look at it.
I'll see if I can pull it up real quick.
It could be that they're mentioned in such a way that two of them seem joined together, as in the separation doesn't seem to be very distinct.
But I'll have to take a look at it, because I don't know it off the top of my head.
I haven't memorized it.
Maybe like the first two or three, but that's it.
But, yeah, I mean, anybody can read it to see what it is for themselves, but I don't think I can be helpful for that right now, partially because I'm tired and I'm not looking forward to pulling that up and going through, because the interlinear doesn't present things in clear English.
You kind of have to put up with the fact that it's sometimes giving you very literal translation, so the English grammar is not always correct.
So I'm actually hesitant to pull it up right now.
But it's something that anybody can look at.
I'm putting them up in chat right now as we speak.
No covenant with pagans, no molten gods, keep the feast of unleavened bread, firstborn are his.
And it's stopped right there so far.
Yeah, I might bring it up the next time we do a stream.
But, I mean, if he's saying that there are eight, he should probably list them so that we can see what it is.
Okay, I'm back.
What did we ask earlier?
Seth left a message about Ten Commandments written on Exodus 34 in stone.
There he finds eight.
There should be ten, supposedly.
Is that where we left off?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
Okay, yeah, I would suggest looking at it in an interlinear, of course.
I know Seth knows that by now, or he's experienced that world.
And perhaps one example would be you are to ransom a donkey with a lamb, and if you don't, you are to break the neck of that donkey.
Is that one commandment or two commandments, you see?
Yeah, I did mention that.
Oh, you did?
Okay.
Yeah, in other words, are there more than one within the phrase?
You know, in other words, are we looking at phraseology?
Because I think Exodus 20 is more phraseologically set up with ten phrases, right, especially when they get really short.
They're easy to look at.
But the importance of the Ten Commandments, or now are there ten or are there eight, right?
That's a good point.
Let's resolve that.
Those were placed in the Ark, right, with Aaron's budding rod and the manna.
So there's an interesting aspect to it.
Here's an interesting aspect, by the way.
I'm reckoning around the first of the twelfth, right, the first day of the twelfth month.
And a recent conversation regarding, like, I wouldn't say numerology or gematria, but just the way there are patterns in Scripture, and when one thing ends, it's really the beginning of another, but the end of that thing is really the beginning, and the beginning of the other thing is really the end.
Yeah, okay, first will be last, last will be first.
And how certain things seem to end, and that's just the package, like it's a parcel.
You know how, like, again, the tablets of stone, the manna, and the budding rod were put into the Ark of the Covenant, right?
So what, can't put anything else?
What about the skins or the animal skins that Adam and Eve wore?
Or what about, you know, is there anything else that we can think of, you know, maybe?
Or why wasn't it continually added to?
So that's like a closed thing.
But what's interesting is, you know, when you look at the seventh month, because it's, for the people down under, they're going into the seventh month, right?
Let's say, if you base it agriculturally, you know, there's a centrist view, which is it should be based out of the center of the world, which is basically the northern hemisphere, but you have the first day of the seventh month is the Feast of Trumpets, right?
I want to revisit that.
But the tenth day is the Day of Atonement.
But in terms of generations, if you were to look at the seventh month, Noah was tenth generation, right?
Okay.
Now, what's interesting, the 23rd day of the seventh month is the last great day, right?
It's the 15 plus 7 plus 1.
What's interesting in terms of generations, 23 generations after Adam puts you where?
Right into what?
The Exodus, right?
Time of the Exodus is 23 generations, Moses.
And what's interesting, when you go back to the first month, the reason for the Passover and Week of Unleavened Bread is for what?
To remember what?
The Exodus, which ties you back to the generation of the last great day.
But there's roughly a six-month period in between the seventh month and the beginning of the first month again.
So there's this huge interim period.
So when you look at timekeeping, generational counting, the function of the feasts, these things are packaged, right?
So if you look at what was written on the stones, which were broken the first time and then rewritten as they were the first, why do you write something on stone?
So it lasts, right?
And also stone is a form of judgment, right?
Because how is capital punishment done other than beheading and whatever?
Death by stoning.
You want to get academic?
You ready?
Lapidation.
Yeah, go talk to someone at the bus stop.
You know what death by stoning is?
I don't know, but I've heard of it.
Have you heard of lapidation?
Or is that something they do when you get your nails done?
You know?
Anyway.
So anyway, Bruce, what did you come up with, with the folks in chat?
I need to go back to the office and see what's going on, maybe on the computer or not.
We've been on for quite a few hours.
Seth has just been typing in the commandments in the chat.
Yeah, I'm probably not going to be able to keep going for much longer because my eyes are starting to get tired.
But on my end, I'll just bring up one thing real quick.
So there's this question that I have.
I'm trying to find some specific markers for the progression of events connected to the Antichrist.
And I'm kind of using the two witnesses for that because they're obviously going to play a key part.
But Revelation and some other books obviously talk about them coming and how the world won't look upon them favorably because of what they'll be saying.
And they have the power to stop the rains and they can turn water to blood and stuff.
And then eventually they'll be killed and everybody's going to be happy.
The two witnesses, yeah.
Yeah, the two witnesses.
So Revelation 13 talks about the ascension of the beast and the false prophet to become world leaders or running everything.
And since the false prophet is going to be able to bring down fire from heaven, which is similar to Elijah, and Malachi 4 says that Elijah will return and the world will at least – you combine that with the fact that the world will gain a working knowledge of the scriptures and the Antichrist will claim to be the returned Christ at some point later on.
Isn't it conceivable that when the two witnesses get killed – I'm not sure if he's going to really be the returned Christ but just Christ himself.
But go ahead.
Yeah, but if he's Christ himself then he's returned because people thought he was gone just by implication.
I think there's a dynamic there that we could get into further but in the meantime, go ahead.
Okay, let's retain the point you're making.
So isn't it conceivable that when the two witnesses get killed based on all these aforementioned points that the Antichrist will then point to Revelation 13 and say, Oh look, the rise of the beast and the false prophet, those are the two guys that just got killed.
That's possible.
Right, and then once they're dead he'll be like, and now I'm the Christ and here's my prophet Elijah that's going to reign.
Well that depends on whether or not for the, what is it, for two and a half years they're doing what they're doing, the two witnesses?
Two and a half or three and a half?
Two and a half, right?
Yeah, they give it in a number of days because being able to reckon time falls apart with moons, right?
Just a day count there.
When you don't see months means that something's going on with the moon, right?
But the sun is still prevalent.
And the thing is, will the people know their identity?
I would suggest that the people will know their identity and that's going to be a hard one to pull.
I think there's going to be a fervor of religiosity that the world has never seen before.
And it's mentioned that way indirectly.
I'm paraphrasing.
Mankind will be in a state that has never been in.
And how can we describe a state something, it's like trying to describe an apple to someone who's never seen it or tasted it.
How do you do that?
Especially when you have it yourself, right?
This is a very unique time period.
But also the parallels.
You see, when you read something like Revelation, you'll see that when you go back to all the rest of Scripture, all the rest of Scripture shows all the parallels to that, right?
Like, you know, why does the false prophet have horns?
He comes out of the sea, out of the people, he has horns.
Like a lamb.
Well, Moses doesn't come out of the sea, he comes out of the mountain and he has horns, right?
In Exodus 34 also, right?
I think it says, not 34, Exodus 32 is it?
Where Moses comes down from the mountain or somewhere, yeah.
Yeah, his face is shining, well he has horns.
But he doesn't come out of the sea, he comes out of the mountain, which is, right, different, right?
It's a kingdom, the proper kingdom, where the sea is not.
The sea is the people or it's this, you know, man system.
Well, here's a little tidbit on the Antichrist.
He's entering his 20th year now, right?
And in a recent discussion, 20 is when you're a fighting age.
You know, you're allowed to be a bodyguard or a soldier.
And do certain duties, be a go-rim, go-rim, you know, guardian.
At 30 is when you can be a priest.
And at 40 is where lawfully and legally, in the biblical economy, you become a judge.
So what's interesting, the Antichrist is going to be roughly a fighting age coming around here soon.
What does that mean?
Well, it's just another marker.
And he's on the planet now.
He's roughly 20, roughly coming up by this fall, his 20th year.
He was born around the year 6000.
Yeah, and the thing is, he will be extremely charismatic all the way to the point until he suffers an injury that recovers, supposedly fatal, and recovers from it with the use of loss of an eye, loss of an arm, which may not necessarily be publicly known, but secretly known.
But you would know that, you see.
Because it's too obvious, again, if he shows up on the scene, let's say he's in a car accident, he's dead, and then they announce he's alive, and look, he has a patch over his eye and he's missing an arm.
You're like, oh, that's the Antichrist.
So they're probably going to fit him with a prosthetic so you wouldn't know, you see.
But if you do know scripture, you'll be able to tell someone who does know him he lost his eye and his arm, didn't he?
How do you know that?
It's a secret.
You see how scripture works?
Right.
Yeah.
Because otherwise, like I said earlier, if you put 7.5 billion people in a room and ask them, who's heard of the Antichrist figure, or even just heard of it, raise your hand, I've been told most of the people will raise their hand.
So how are all these things going to take place without people calling foul?
Well, they're going to take place and people won't be able to recognize them.
And here's the interesting thing about the Christ figure, and I've said this as part of the Greek-speak narrative.
In terms of the biblical Christ, or the one that was prophesied since Adam, let's say, it's completely unknown, even today.
Christians don't know who the biblical Christ is, no way, at all.
Neither do the historians or most of the people that you see out there.
There might be a little bit of an inkling of detail on it by certain rabbinical communities because of what they've held, but what they're putting out in the world as J-E-S-U-S and all that other stuff, and all the academia and religiosity is completely false.
Completely false.
So, like they say in gangster New York, you ain't got nothing, right now.
So what the world is based on when it comes to the Messiah or Christ figure, historicity or religiosity is demonology or really straight-up syncretized mythology.
And politicized history.
Because there were many people claiming that position back in the first century.
So, they don't have nothing.
Malachi says that Elijah would be sent to the Judeans right before, the Israelites, before the day of the Lord to turn fathers back to their children or children back to their fathers.
But my understanding is that Elijah will come to restore the keeping of the Torah and such for the Israelites only.
Because let's face it, the law of Moses is the proper legislation for the nation of Israel.
Well, Hebrews to the Hebrews first, right?
Right.
I don't think it's designed to be used for the Gentile nations outside of Israel's boundaries.
So, by expanding it to extend to the entire world the way that the Antichrist will, isn't that unlawful?
Well, yes and no.
There's a very simple thing that I've always been saying.
The kill shots are coming for sure.
And they're not going to implement the kill shots unless they're done lawfully.
So, in order for the victim or the one that is receiving the kill shot to receive it lawfully, how much information of why the kill shot is being delivered does that victim or the assailant, the previous assailant, have to know to make it lawful?
So, in other words, of all the Satanism, Paganism, and Atheism in the world today, which covers most of the people, how much knowledge of the gods do they have to have before it becomes lawful, where now it's okay, now we can take them out?
So, later on at the resurrection they can't say, well, they didn't know.
Does it mean they have to come in full knowledge of all the identities of the Christ and the law and all that?
Nope, not at all.
I think the amount of knowledge that they have to come in, the world has to come in, the world at large, has to come in before the kill shots can be done lawfully is that they know that it's something they have to inquire about.
And, of course, there are places in Scripture that talks about, lead us to a mount or a person, someone who's going to teach us the laws and the ways of Yah.
In other places, like you just mentioned, bringing the fathers to the sons and the sons to the fathers.
And in Zechariah, there's going to be a great wailing and an acknowledgement of the Christ at a certain point.
By Israel, right?
So, these are like little smatterings of details that you'd say, well, you know, does this mean full knowledge for everyone?
You know, the world at large, like you'll see it on the news?
No, I don't think so.
Right.
So...
Technically, you could still...
I mean, the law is still just meant for Israel.
It was given to them.
It doesn't say...
Right now...
It's the opposite.
It says if the Gentiles want to be a part of you, that's fine, but they have to come into your covenant.
It doesn't say take the law and put it on the Gentiles.
No, there is no conversion that way.
That's the thing that people don't understand when they read the New Testament.
The point of turning around...
Even Isaiah, I think it's like chapter 6 or something, that's when he first comes into prophesying.
It was Uzziah, the king died and all that, right?
He says, close the eyes of the people lest they turn around, right?
And see what's coming.
So...
So these things are done a certain way.
But when you read the New Testament, the conversion aspect has nothing to do with a religion.
It has to do with turning around from what you believe and acknowledge that the real reality of what happens after death already happened.
So you don't have to follow this dumb shit.
When you die, you go to heaven or hell or whatever.
Which came out of many places in ancient times, right?
Or reincarnation.
Actually, I never really found anything.
It's like flat earth.
I haven't found anything on reincarnation in ancient texts.
It's a very recent propagation also.
Here's another interesting aspect.
And I've had discussions with this in the past.
And I believe it to be true, but I think it requires study.
And this is what I believe to be true.
A very harsh repeat from an academic point of view, a knowledge-based point of view of the first century.
Because the first century was the time of the Christ and this is the time of the Antichrist.
So there's a parallelism there, right?
What was going on at the first century?
What do you know about the first century?
And the days of the Christ on earth.
Especially his latter days.
Political, I mean, also.
As far as what you said about reincarnation.
I don't know if the first century is ancient.
I don't know if that's ancient.
But definitely Simon Magus' stuff propagated the reincarnation.
Because he was supposed to be some reincarnated god.
And his sidekick, the Helen woman, was also supposed to be reincarnated.
Yeah, and they kept changing their story depending on who they spoke to.
But the first century was an interesting bag because the phenomenon that was going on, and there was no doubt, east or west, north or south, anywhere in the world, something important was going on in Judea.
No one could explain it.
It's kind of like 9-11.
They tell you energy satellite weapons and nanothermite.
You know, stupid stuff prevails.
The conspiracy theories are being taken advantage of the same way in the first century.
Who can explain all these things that are going on about this guy who rose from the dead?
It was all about, if you read the ancient or the older writings that are more objective, not Gnosticism or Simon Magus' stuff, the early what they call New Testament writings and what was proliferating was the resurrection of the dead, was the teaching.
That was the whole teaching, basically.
But that can only be done logistically to people who knew the Torah or the Old Testament, or the first five books of Moses.
It couldn't legitimately be done to the Gentiles because they're like, what do you mean Noah?
We know Poseidon.
What do you mean Noah?
We know Dagon.
You see my point?
Whenever you brought up anything with water, it was like, you mean Dagon or Poseidon?
No, no, no.
You don't know Noah?
No, I don't.
So that was another group of people.
So they had to be brought up to speed.
When you told them the resurrection, this is about the resurrection, they're like, what are you talking about?
But if you went to those that knew scripture, they're like, yeah, wonderful.
Then what happened is, just like I've seen people, when you tell them about part of the Greek-speak narrative, you know what lawful is?
Lawful timekeeping, lawful food.
If you work in a pet store, it's lawful to give the dog dog food, the cat cat food, and the bird bird food, and the fish fish food.
You don't give the fish food to the dog.
Even though you'll eat it, that's not lawful in a pet store, right?
So do you know what lawful is for man?
And a lot of people hear that stuff, and they get really excited, because they've never heard it before.
And they're like, holy shit, my parents never told me.
I don't see that in the world, but it makes too much sense.
I want to learn it, right?
You see how easy it is to do that in any time in man's history, is to appeal to what is basic and good about humanity.
Because, you know, again, we're born seeking joy as children, and that doesn't just because you're 60, 70, or 80, doesn't mean you're still not seeking joy.
As a matter of fact, if you look at a lot of the greed and debauchery and stuff that people do, it's because they're seeking some kind of pleasure or joy again.
So why not do it lawfully, if you know what's lawful for mankind, you see?
So that's a very simple way to start.
So when these things were happening in the first century, and you tell someone, say, I just came into your town, and even you guys are talking about it, well, let me tell you, it's really about the resurrection.
They're like, oh, we've heard of that god, Horus, or whatever.
And it's, no, no, no, it has nothing to do with Horus.
So where do you start with those people?
Let's see.
You've got to start now with what's called a synagogio in the Greek, which is to bring everyone together.
They call it synagogue.
It's a Greek term, by the way, right?
So that's what was going on back in those days.
And a lot of people got turned on to that, and it became problematic in a lot of pagan cultures.
Because, like in Rome, if you, every Sunday, if you didn't, or one Sunday a month or twice a Sunday, depending on who you were, if you didn't bring an offering, an animal sacrifice, to the Temple of Hercules, you were fined in Roman culture.
So all of a sudden you've got all these people now, they're like, no, we want to do things lawfully according to this law.
Now, the Roman people that were making money off of this stuff and the priesthood and the government got upset.
So we've got to stop this, right?
It's kind of like here in America where they have that quote-unquote patriot movement, which is, I cringe about it.
They're like, we've got to learn law because these attorneys don't even know their own law.
And the government cringes on that.
They're like, come on, man, you know, the total attorneys, we've got to beat these guys up, even though they're right, because you still want your five-car garage and your million bucks a year cushy life attorney, don't you?
Yeah, of course these guys are right, but we've got to go after them anyway.
You see these kinds of movements in little form pop up all over.
Don't you have the separatist movement in Spain with Catalan, right?
And all these other things, you know, like we've got to stop this because it's going to disturb our cushiness or it disturbs the way things are.
So, you know, part of the narrative that I have is be lawful in anything.
You know, I mean, in terms of, you know, you want to do timekeeping, well, you know, whose clock are you on?
You know, we were given a clock that you don't have to buy or, you know, learn some arbitrary crap.
Or what about food?
You know, if you work in a pet store, again, you give the fish fish food, the dog dog food.
Why are you eating this?
You know, you were made, you know, for that.
And I'm not saying that anyone should do this, but most people were never even given the option to consider what lawfulness is.
And even in the codes, they tell you there's lawful money and then legal script, private credit, you know, in the American codes.
Most people are not aware of it at all.
I'm like, you guys are always complaining about this and that and the other thing, and you don't know, you have no reference point at all.
So you've got to develop a reference point.
That's what I mean by lawful.
The medical system is the same.
You know, they're completely unlawful.
But, you know, if you look at the work that they've done, the grunt work and all the cadaver research and all that, that's valid, you know.
If you want to know what the inside of a body looks like, because it's kind of hard to turn someone inside out to study their bones and then piece them back together, you know.
So you're going to have to go to the anatomy of the medical idiots.
But the function of it, they know nothing.
I recently got an email about the new chat.
Someone says, I want to just come to the new chat.
And, by the way, I like what you're saying.
It's better than what they say in church.
And I was like, okay.
You're not getting it.
Of course it's better because they're getting zero at church, and anything times zero is what?
Zero.
It's not a matter of it's better.
It's just you're getting nothing in church.
So zero times any number is still zero.
You know what I mean?
But anyway, where are we resolved?
Okay, I'm back in the office here.
Let's just take a look.
Sam, you're getting tired, and I don't know if Seth is at home.
Maybe we'll call it a night.
I'm good for the questions.
I mean, if I have to jump into another subject, it's another three hours.
No, that's fine.
Let's just save it for another time, perhaps.
And also saving it easier for Bruce, who's been doing all the handiwork on scheduling and compiling these sonic events, or attempts to do sonic events, I should say.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, thanks, everyone.
Yes, thank you.
Well, thank you, Sam, and thank you, Greg.
Okay.
It was a fascinating journey through the scriptures again.
And, Seth, we really appreciate your efforts.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we'll dive in with Seth soon enough.
Okay, we're burning up the what do they call the memory storage bytes on the thing now, three hours, 15.
So super duper.
Okay, we'll see you guys again.
Thanks, Sam.
Thanks, Bruce.
See you all, folks.
Good night.
Good night, Noel.
♪♪♪