Okay, folks, we're online here with Greek and Sam, and how are you guys doing tonight?
All right, cool, we're going to do a little project, an experiment for all the lazy asses out there to see if they still know how to draw or look stuff up, and I'm being facetious of course, and which is the best way to be.
And I would suggest that we're going to do a little mindset tweaking tonight, and if
you're immature and you like to hear stuff that's quote unquote nice, and all that, then
make like a tree and get the F out of here, and that's the warning, because what we're
going to be discussing tonight has nothing to do with all the political sentiment and
sympathy and empathy that you idiots on this planet think that you are engaged in, because
as per any discussion regarding this, especially with Sam in the past few months, has been
about, if you haven't heard it or listened to it, I'll say it again, what we call the
scriptures is written by the gods, for the gods, to the gods, and we happen to have it.
How do I know that?
How do I know that for sure?
Because I don't see the eventual light bulb in there, I don't see that you're going to be flying around in planes in there, and I don't see all the stuff that you guys think on this planet is so great in there at all.
It's basically part of the manufacturing process, it's a manual, and most of you will never understand anything in the Bible, that's for sure, but it doesn't mean you can't understand, you won't be able to understand what's going on around you if you did have at least someone bark at you what the Bible is about, or what you call the scriptures, or all that other stuff.
So I just got a message and I just answered it, that's fine Sam, less than that is even better.
I was thinking of doing it, since tonight was going to be sort of a pedantic exercise, I'm going to sort of speak in a way tonight that whoever is listening to this downstream, and is listening to it on a, let's say, downloaded file, right Bruce?
This will probably be available just like you've been diligently doing all the rest of this stuff.
Yep, as soon as we get done.
Right, what I'll do is I'll suggest that when I'll make certain statements and then pause, pause the actual recording, why?
Because it's going to command doing some reference searching on the rectangle, and I'm
suggesting the rectangle because it's fast that way, and I'll walk everyone through this
on what I'm suggesting, and let me just repeat what I, the caveat in the beginning, if you
are one of these earth fairies, you know, breakfast cereal types, fruit nuts and flakes,
peace, love, and happiness, and all this other stuff, you're an idiot, and you shouldn't
be listening to this, because this is not about what you think the world should be,
but what the world will be, and it's, any kind of, let me just say this again, any kind
of peace, love, and happiness that you surface-dwelling, earth-inhabitant morons with a capital R are
going to be experiencing from now on is part of the setup.
It doesn't mean you can't enjoy it, right?
But it's part of the setup, and you're going to be going up and down on a rollercoaster
ride with all your political nonsense, and all your religious nonsense, and your familial
nonsense, and your friendship nonsense, and all the stuff you're looking for to give
you that cool, warm, and fuzzy inside feeling, oh, I like the way this guy talks, or I don't
like him, but I like him, but, you know, this kind of stuff is going to transcend all
of that.
Why?
Because we're going to be talking about what's going to be happening, and how it's going to be happening, and why it's going to be happening, and why the if, what, when, and where of these things, and the why people are not going to be liking some of it is not part of this discussion.
And what does that mean?
It's like, what are you saying?
It sounds like your usual pissed-off self.
Well, the theme tonight is very simple.
One thing, and let me just, it's very simple based on this, let me just say this.
You know, no one really wants to read the Bible, I've found out, or the Scriptures, and I don't blame them, because they're not going to understand anything in it, right?
So the important thing then is, if you don't understand anything in it, do the gods act in futility?
And the answer is no.
So the answer then would be, what are they trying to communicate?
It's no different than walking on the street and seeing a tourist from China, if you're in an English-speaking country, and he's moving his mouth, and you hear a language you can't comprehend, but he's trying to communicate something to you, you see?
So you get someone who can interpret it, and it's called an interpretation.
So you can get the communication over, and the intent comes through, right?
That's why, for all these years I've been discussing, what is the intent of the Scripture, because the rest of it is futile.
Whether you think this word means this, or it should mean that, is irrelevant.
Can you piece it all together and make a harmony out of it, and making the stuff meaning the communication work?
Because what you always have to keep in your mind, the back of your mind, is that God's acting in futility, and the answer is no.
And if you don't understand what they're saying, you're being censored.
And I just want to bring up something tonight, and again, I'll say it again, tonight we're going to be talking about what's coming, and it's going to be based around Israel, and we're going to be doing certain exercises using reference material that you'll need to pause.
But one thing, I was either going to save it for a small talk or conversation, but this has been in the back of the head for a couple of days now.
You've always heard about the cosmic censorship that I've discussed.
And this little thing has been bugging me, and it's just, you know, Greek, you've got to say this to these people that are listening, you know, because it shows you how you can apply what you hear on Greek-speak.
You've heard of the cosmic censorship.
Now, this might sound like a minor detail, or it might be a big thing, or whatever, just don't turn a molehill into a mountain or whatever, but just take for what I'm saying as it is, okay?
Now, the cosmic censorship is obviously, you know, someone is being blocked, yourself or someone else regarding certain information.
Now, when we go back to scripture, what's interesting is there's something called these appointed days and appointed times.
You'll find them in Leviticus, okay, the book of Vayikra, and you'll see these are my appointments.
It literally means that, like moed, moedim, words like that, meaning a time that you set aside or you recognize or acknowledge, and it's a special time.
And the way that these things run on a temporal basis is not on the Pope's work schedule.
And most people are cringing now saying, yeah, Greek, we know that.
Yeah, but you really don't.
You don't know what the rest of it I'm going to say is.
Now, if you've heard Greek-speak before, you've heard me say very simply, lawfully, the day starts at high noon and the moon rules the month, period.
Every culture has had this.
This was either worldwide or observed lawfully at various points in history.
It has nothing to do with timekeeping today.
Not all ancient cultures did that, obviously, lawfully, but that's another discussion that has been had in the past.
So I want to go back to the censorship, the appointed times, and the timekeeping.
I have spoken to many people that have listened to Greek-speak for years, actually, whatever it means, and they cannot get the notion of timekeeping.
Now, I'm going to put this together very subtly, but it should hit you across the head, and whatever you want to do with it, you do with it.
The subtle aspect is even if you're speaking to someone who's five years old or eight years old, they know what the sun and the moon is.
It's a very simple concept, lawfully, which is a simple concept also.
The sun rules the day, and the moon rules the month.
Okay?
So the full moon is the new moon, obviously, because you can take measurements with it, and the solar noon is pretty obvious also.
Now, again, I have discussed things.
Sam, would you mute for a moment?
I hear like washing in the background or something.
Oh, my bad.
Just mute, and when you want to say something, unmute.
So my point here, I'm stretching this out because it has a lot of impact to whoever is relating with other people on many levels.
Someone's been familiar with this concept of the sun rules the day, and the moon rules the month, and how their alignments are actually measurements are taken.
Sam, you're not muted.
Yeah.
I actually don't know how to mute in Skype.
I need to Google that.
Oh, that's fine.
Oh, you have the newer version then.
Yeah.
The computer should have a mute.
Oh, for the mic, yeah.
I'll go with that.
Yeah.
Okay.
So the thing is, regardless if you know Greek speak or not, I've run into people that listen to Greek speak, and they still don't get timekeeping.
I'm not saying you have to be an avid observer or someone asks you what day it is or whatever.
They just don't get it.
Subtly, you know what?
That's a form of censorship, but it's not a censorship to Greek speak per se.
It's a censorship going back to the Levitical appointments.
So it's like cut to the chase.
When you run into people who have an interest in scripture or not, it's worse when they have an interest in scripture, and they don't get the lawful timekeeping.
Let me just lay it out, Bruce.
What do you think?
I'll just say it, right?
Yeah, go on.
The gods don't want to see you.
In other words, if you see you run into people who are censored about timekeeping, that's another way of saying these appointed days, nah, don't bother showing up because you're not invited.
Because many places in scripture, it talks about, especially in the New Testament, I think there's more than one occasion, you don't invite yourself.
You get it?
It's not advised.
Yeah, it's not advised.
And I see this spiritually and cosmically.
People are like, Greek man, I love the stuff you're saying, but I don't get that timekeeping.
I'm like, oh yeah, that's fine.
I don't come out and tell them the gods don't want to see you.
Well, obviously they don't because you don't know when to show up.
And I'm not talking about showing up anywhere because the gods are on this temporal inertial plane.
There's no place to go.
You see what I mean?
In other words, you acknowledge those days in your mind now.
How are you going to do anything else?
They just want acknowledgment.
I have discussions with someone, for example, that's from Israel and he grew up secular, which means you don't live under a tyrannical rabbi.
Most people in Israel rather say they're secular because the rabbis are tyrannical if you say you're religious.
And he's recently started reading scripture and he's like, man, Greek, it's like you say, it's real simple.
I'm like, yeah.
The interesting thing is, where do you go?
How do you do it?
So again, with this fellow from Israel, I've discussed basically the gods, all they want is your acknowledgment.
It's really a personal thing that you acknowledge them because what else are you going to do?
It's like the old adage, what do you give someone that has everything already?
Acknowledgement.
Okay.
Your presence.
Right.
Yeah.
So I've noticed that the people that were made aware of lawful timekeeping and don't get it are actually censored from another way where it's like, no, the gods are like, no, we don't want this one.
So he's not going to understand when to come to acknowledge us.
It's really, it's kind of a harsh, I don't mind being harsh because I'm not doing this for a popularity contest and I really, I'm kind of apathetic towards the human condition right now.
You have to be, by the way, in order to be able to look at it objectively, right?
Because, and I'll talk about, I've spoken about the hypocrisy before, you know, these Americans, I like calling them because they don't do anything.
They complain about bloodshed and war and all this and they don't even know in their own country there's over two or three million people a year being eliminated by their own institutions.
And I mean children, you know, medical industry.
Easily.
Yeah, easily.
It's really upwards in the five or ten million a year and they don't even want to acknowledge half a million children being sacrificed a year or, you know, so screw them.
But anyway, so the thing here is, again, the gods are on this temporal plane.
It's like, let's say you got a rat in a box and it's a small box and no matter how much it runs back and forth, all you do is reach in and grab it.
Now, to you, standing over this rat or mouse in a box or whatever other vermin, squirrel or whatever, and if it runs to the right side of the shoebox, big deal.
You just put your arm in there and grab it.
It doesn't matter if it's running towards the left or the right, the north, the east, the west.
It doesn't, right?
So the gods are in this plane where it doesn't matter where you go right now or do, they're there.
They're in this inertia.
It means there's no movement.
It's like total stability, right?
So what I wanted to mention was the level of censorship is not to be judged strictly by what someone sees or doesn't see, but also to be judged from a point of view, meaning the quality of that censorship, acquiring a sense of it, is to judge also what the gods want that person to do or see or whatever.
And the same thing is about the money system.
The money system is one of the simplest things to explain, real simple.
And I find that 99% of people don't get it.
Why?
Because if they did, it would really upset the wagon.
So one thing I haven't brought up again that I'm bringing up now is the aspect of censorship.
And you can judge the quality of the motions or the life of the person that's going to have regarding the gods, but what they are censored to.
And one of the things that, again, just to sum up, is I've run into a lot of people, well, like five or six, that have heard Greeks speak and they still don't get the timekeeping.
And I'm like, that's okay.
But in the back of my mind, I'm like, oh, yeah, the gods don't want you to acknowledge their pointed times.
It's like, that's fine.
You kind of see how the gods are working through the population.
And the exercises that I'm going to go through tonight, I'm going to tell pretty much with great detail that anyone can acquire what is coming in the next three, four years, and especially before the next seven, geopolitically by using a very simple method, okay, on the rectangle, because it's all been put together for us.
And when you look at that, when I was younger and dumber, whether it was a few years ago, I said, oh, yeah, I'll put a presentation together and maps and all that.
You know what?
I ain't doing squat.
You guys do it on your own.
I ain't getting nothing for this.
So I ain't going to do work for it anymore.
So I'll tell you how to do it.
If you're interested, I think you'll get more out of it if you do it yourself.
Agreed?
Agreed.
So let's start.
Now, I don't like mentioning the two old beef patty special sauce.
You know how the evangelistic Christians always start out with their bullshit verses and chapters?
I'm not saying that the verses are bullshit and chapters, but their methodology is bullshit, because the charismatics, the Christians, the religious, even the messianics who try to put Judaism, Christianity, anything, the reason I'm bringing this up, because when you speak about Scripture, that's what you're going to find, presentations that come from those sources, right?
Messianic Jews who wish, if you put cow dung and dog dung together, you get something good, right?
Or, you know, you put Christianity and Judaism together, you get something good.
And they have this evangelical charismatic thing where they try to make their audience feel good, and they always have to mention stuff that their audience already knows and tie it in.
So they like them, and, you know, everything's at the end of the presentation.
Everybody's happy, everybody goes home, and their wallets open up, you know?
Or they say, oh, this guy's a really good guy, or whatever, you know?
That's not the purpose of Greek-speak or any of this stuff.
And just to begin, when you hear, let's say, a topic like I'm going to bring up tonight, the future of Israel and its aggression in the Middle East, I'm not going to give – I'll mention books, but I'm not going to give you chapter and verse, because I'm presuming that you've read it already and you know it.
And that's why I brought – I asked Sam.
You know, Sam didn't really have anything to propose to discuss this week.
I said, why don't you come along anyway, because if – during the discussion, he's got – I think Sam, if he was an engineer, would have two or three sharpened pencils in his pocket, and he could put stuff together really fast, so it might help.
But the books that I'm talking about generally are the Book of Daniel, which really won't kick in until, like, the next seven years, the Book of Zechariah, and the Book of Revelation, which Book of Revelation has already kicked in.
Book of Zechariah has already kicked in.
So those are the three points.
And one of the points that you're going to find also in the Book of Joel, and the Book of Zechariah is really the crux of tonight's instructional sonic event.
And the crux of it is that when you read Zechariah several times, and especially Joel, which is really short, it does mention – and Isaiah as well – look at the former days, okay?
Anyone who's read Scripture, you'll hear that term, you know, the former days of your forefathers.
For example, in Book of Zechariah, it talks about the prophets of old, okay?
It's not talking about the prophets in general or the days of old Israel, because this was written around, you know, the 5th century B.C. It's talking about addressing the reader at the 5th century B.C. to look at the times of their forefathers and the prophets of old.
So that is directing the reader now to a time period of, let's say, the Book of Joshua, the Book of Judges, Chronicles, Kings, okay?
And this is an instruction.
If anyone's heard Greek speak, you might have heard in the past the instructions of how to understand prophecy are in the Book of Zechariah and Isaiah and a couple of others.
Those are the instructions, and I just gave you the instructions.
Now, you could go figure out, if you want chapter and verse, you know, to all beef patties and all that, you're on your own.
But I'm presuming that you know what I just said.
If it rings a bell and you said, yes, I've read that and I see where it is, you could look it up on your own.
So let's get started.
Now, the reason I want to get started is because this is a little technical, and I think we can explain more as we go.
And the technical aspect is very simple.
We know that the gods have chosen Israel as their central clock or focal point.
And I'll say this again.
The reason why Israel is the chosen people, which pisses off your common human idiot, is because they are a timepiece.
Just like if you said to someone, we're going to meet at the coffee shop tomorrow at 3 p.m. on the Pope's work schedule, let's say, on the wind-up toy, you have chosen the clock to make that appointment.
The gods have chosen the people of Israel to be the world clock, right?
He's chosen people.
But also he's chosen them to hold what he's going to do, like, you know, take this message at this time, right?
You see?
So you watch them, and it could have been any other random group, but we know that it's not any random group.
It could have been any random group before Abraham, okay?
But at the point of Abraham in the book of Genesis there, we knew that this group and who he was choosing was established.
Because when you read the biblical story, it's not religious.
It has to do with the events on the entire planet.
Okay, so here's the technical aspect.
The former times of Israel refers to what Israel, in other words, modern-day Israel is going to reflect back and resemble its former days.
So one way we start by doing that is because what everyone has access to informationally is what's going on geopolitically, right?
In other words, without doing any research at all, if you go to the rectangle right now and put in Israel, past 24 hours, what do you get?
It's all geopolitical stuff, maybe some archaeology.
So what we want to find out is what does the gods have in store for Israel.
So what I did here is in the chat I dropped in a link.
It's a Wikipedia link for modern names of biblical places.
And below that I wrote, any search result for biblical cities or Bible cities on the rectangle will do.
So in order to start this, what I would suggest is just go to the rectangle, the stupid rectangle, whatever browser you use, and put in biblical cities.
And the more comprehensive the better.
The Wikipedia one, if you put in biblical cities on a search, it says list of modern names for biblical place names.
And you'll see Old Testament, and it's all alphabetical, there's a chart.
It says biblical name mentioned in.
It gives you the verses.
This is why I picked this one.
And the present name, which you could find it on a map today, and the province and the region and the country name and the flag.
So it's a pretty easy one.
It's in Wikipedia.
I'm not picking this over other ones.
It's just got a convenience, and it seemed to, within the first few search query results, it gave the list of modern names for biblical places and the verses where the city is mentioned.
Now what's important here, if you, I'll pause the audio here for a moment.
Bruce, if someone in chat wants to, or Bruce, are you with me on this?
Yep.
Go ahead.
Do you see the Wikipedia page opened?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
So you know what's interesting?
I was mentioning earlier the instructions to understand prophecy is the former days, your former prophets of old.
And this was the directions that were given to the people living in the 5th century B.C. So that means when you're in the 5th century B.C. and you're reading something, or 6th century B.C., and you're reading something that says you need to go back to your forefathers, the prophets of old, well, that doesn't mean Haggai and Isaiah, because they're contemporaries, right?
That means you've got to go way back.
You've got to go back 500 years more.
All right?
So I mentioned earlier it's the Book of Joshua, Book of Kings.
Okay?
Book of Kings, there's first and second Kings.
That's one book.
Chronicles.
So now what's interesting here, and I'm going to also refer to a map that I started drawing up, what's interesting here, when we go, let's say, Bruce, on the top left of the column says AI, and it's mentioned in Joshua 7, verse 2.
You better look at that.
And what you'll find out also where AI is, and its present name is Kabet Hali, or El Tel, right?
And you could click on that on the Wikipedia if it's blue, and it'll take you there, and it'll show you a map.
But what you'll notice is that's already within the jurisdiction of Israel right now.
I am going from memory.
I haven't clicked on it because I have some other ones I want to look at.
Now, if you go below that, you have Almon, and that's in Joshua 21.18. Yeah, you better look at that because those are the former days now, right, Bruce and Sam?
Right.
I forgot.
You're so quiet.
Sam, do you have that page open?
Are you capable to have it open?
Yeah, it's open.
Okay.
So the reasoning I'm giving the instruction here, it's in the West Bank.
Now, what's interesting, is it really under current what's called Israeli jurisdiction?
And if it's not, it will be, right?
So let me give you an example.
If I go to a map that I've been putting together, let's say we want to use the cardinal north and south.
On the very top of the map, this is from doing research a while back, I have Hamath, H-A-M-A-T-H, as being the northern border of Israel in the next four to seven years.
So let's scroll down to H on this alphabetically organized biblical cities chart.
And if we scroll down to H and we do find Hamath, and it's in 2 Samuel 8-9, right?
So we see that that is within the time of the former prophets, right, and the early kings, right?
So let's just search those verses, 2 Samuel 8-9.
And the reason why I pinned Hamath up there is because, if I go over here, I have a Bible gateway.
It's considered David's victories.
In the course of time, David defeated the Philistines and subdued them, and he took Metheg, Ammah, and control of...
Okay, so this has to be included because it's the times, you see, these times will return back to the days of old.
These days we're living in today.
It shows that David was victorious over this, and you could use a little bit of research on this and see if the city was kept.
Was it a passing thing and they gave him tribute?
And were they Susanin to them?
You know, were they just subject to him?
So if you look at it, chapter 8, in the course of time, David defeated the Philistines.
So, okay, I'm going to go through this quickly.
Okay, this gets into the intricacies of the conquest there.
So I would say that they were conquered people, and they gave tribute.
So there was a jurisdictional reach to the place of Hamath.
And today it's in Syria.
And if you look to the right, on 35, it's Hama.
I'm going to open it and link it in a new tab, and Hama, Syria, to find it.
And it's a city, and if you click on it, on the map of where Hama is, you can do a small drawing and find out that it is way up there in Syria.
Yeah.
Now, do you see that?
You could just put in Hama, H-A-M-A, Syria on a search.
Right now I'm going to just do that longhand and click and look at the map, if they give you a map.
They do give you a map on the Google Maps.
I'm going to click on it, and it's going to open up.
And I'm going to – it shows a zone in pretty much really close.
So I'm going to zoom out, and that place is way up there.
It's just east of central Lebanon, really.
I would say that it's about 100 miles or about 60 miles or 80 kilometers – oh, no, north of Lebanon.
I'm sorry.
It's way up there, north of Lebanon.
It's way north of Damascus.
You see how north – I'm sorry, my mistake.
I need to zoom out a little bit more.
I would say that in terms of miles, it's 150, almost 200 miles north of the current northern border of Israel.
So modern-day Israel, political, geopolitical sense, is going to have control over that city in the near future, near future four to seven years, tops.
Now, do you think that's going to happen just like that?
Or do you think there's going to be a lot of bloodshed over it?
Yeah, there's going to be some troubles.
Yeah.
Now, it doesn't matter whether you like it or not.
I'm just telling you what's happening.
Most people are like, oh, that won't happen.
I'm like, well, it's not a matter – this is not a matter of geopolitics.
This is a matter of prophecy.
Now, what was interesting, as I was thinking about doing this a few days ago, I dropped it in chat.
I just searched northern Syria, and they're saying that there's a war because the – what is it?
ISIS and all that didn't work out in the eastern-southern part of Syria.
They're going to try to start again in the northern part of Syria.
Interesting.
OK.
So that would be the most northern place that I've found.
So we could go back to the list of modern biblical places.
And you see like Hamath below that, Joshua mentions it.
And you could see the research that you'd have to do because you look at this Hamath.
OK, well, is that – what is that a jurisdiction of now?
Well, it's northern district of Israel.
Well, it's there.
OK, they already have that.
So you go through all of these cities, and you look at books like – yeah, look at the Exodus, Genesis, Exodus, Leviticus, Numbers, Deuteronomy.
Look at all that as well, but you'll find that those places are mostly in their jurisdiction of current geopolitical Israel now.
And you go through all this, and you will find what Israel will be involved in geopolitically in the near future.
So with that said, I think it's a pretty easy concept.
Sam and Bruce, are you with me on this so far?
OK, now a little map drawing that I have here.
You know, the thing is I was going to do like a map and then just do drawings over it.
I'll give you an example.
You know, Hamath is about as far north.
It's 150 miles north of current Israel, 200 kilometers.
To the east, it would be Hazarinan, which is the City of Springs, is what it means.
And if you look at the eastern border, it's going to drop down to Damascus.
They will go all the way to Damascus on the western side of Damascus.
Damascus will still remain part of Syria, you know, from Damascus' western border all the way east, straight down to a place called Tamar.
OK, which goes into Jordan, and they're going to be roughly 20 to 50 kilometers east of the current Jordan River.
Oops, what did he just say, Greek?
Yes.
Let me ask anybody right now, where is the current Israel-Jordan border?
Isn't it smack down the middle of the river?
And halfway down the Dead Sea?
Anybody want to check that out?
That's a rhetorical question.
You can answer it or not.
Yes.
Well, we're looking at, if you look at, let's go back to that, let's go back to that chart and scroll down to where the T is.
They have Timna, Tadmor, Palmyra.
Let's see.
Maybe I didn't have it spelled right.
Timna, Harris, West Bank, Palestinian territory, Tadmor.
What are we looking for?
Looking for the southernmost, the easternmost city Israel will have in the future, based on looking at the cities there.
Sometimes I can't read my own handwriting.
How about, let's see, the Kedesh Barner.
Let's see.
In other words, just before we get on a different subject or continue more, just to give the general idea of how much bigger the borders are going to be.
Now, it doesn't mean that they're going to keep this land.
It just means that they will go into it as they did before.
You weren't thinking of Tabuk, were you?
No.
Okay.
Maybe I'm looking at an Arabic name that's not in here.
That's why I'm going to look again.
Let me see.
Maybe the next city next to it would be Kedesh.
Let me see here.
Kedesh.
Okay.
Petra, Jordan.
That's in Numbers 21.
They're not down there right now.
So if you do a map search of Petra, Jordan, that would be the general area.
Petra, Jordan, and let's find it on the map.
So just do a general search, Petra, Jordan, and it's going to give you a little Google map.
I just click on that so it gives me the full page map, right, and it's got the Nabataean Theater and all that.
So I'm going to start shrinking, zooming out.
And I'm going to see where the border from Petra to Israel is, and there it is.
So they're going to expand in that area about 20 kilometers towards the east.
I guess that's what I meant to Al-Talifa perhaps also.
So do you see that, Petra and Jordan?
Yep.
And you could take a line straight up to that.
This is if you do all this splaining, like I say, pretty much to Damascus.
You could almost do a straight line up to that to Damascus, and that will be the new borders of Israel.
Now I say straight line.
Borders are usually defined by these mountainous passes and rivers.
It's very easy.
The natural borders are typically mountains and rivers, right, and seas.
So you could go up to Amman and that area there.
So the beauty of not presenting a finished product on this and just directing the listener with the tools to do it on their own, I think it's kind of like the old coloring book idea.
When you sit there and you color in a letter, you're going to remember it better.
Right.
And I think the Wikipedia page, which is called List of Modern Names for Biblical Place Names, is very helpful because it does have an alphabetical order.
Actually, the alphabetical order is not as helpful.
I wish it was in time.
It does give you the verses, which lets you sort out the requirements of being the prophets of old, Joshua, Samuel, kings, judges.
But it also gives you the present name city.
So you can use the present name city on the search, right?
Right.
And it gives you the country name.
So, again, back to going to this chart, I would go look at all of the cities, the biblical name mentioned in, whether it's Joshua, kings, first or second, chronicles, first or second, and judges, and sift through all of that.
And remember the old-style map on the wall with the thumbtacks?
Yeah.
And do that.
Just find all those cities specifically in those older books and just dot it or pin it, and then get a piece of string and wrap it around all those thumbtacks or pins, and that will represent roughly the new borders of modern geopolitical Israel.
Wow.
Yeah.
And this is, okay, this sounds kind of radical, I know, but I'm bringing it together with the instructions that are given in Isaiah and Zechariah and Joel in the book of Joel, which is, look back to the former days, the former times.
Do you remember reading that anywhere, Sam or Bruce, in the scripture, the verses?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
It says, they didn't listen to me, and you're not listening to me, but if you turn to me, I'll turn to you.
Right?
And this is an early part because, remember, later on, he turns to them whether they like it or not.
Right.
Because they do reject him for a short time, and he says, no, it's okay, I'm doing it for my namesake.
And, you know, there's a verse that says somewhere in scripture, people, remember, turn your swords into plowshares?
Right.
But very few people quote where he tells them to take their plowshares and turn them into swords and spears, and their pruning hooks into spears.
Do you remember that?
That's in the book of Joel.
That time has come.
See, Israel right now is known as a major agricultural provider.
I dare anyone in any metropolitan city in what they call America to go buy hothouse tomatoes and not be able to find ones that are not flown over here from Israel.
Right?
Wow.
Especially on the East Coast.
You know the real premium hothouse vine on the vine tomatoes that cost as much as steak?
You know, you've seen those in the market sometimes?
Right.
They smell fragrant.
Yeah, made in where?
Made where?
Where are they grown?
Israel.
Wow.
You ever heard of something called cherry tomato?
Yeah.
Guess who crossbred, hybridized, and created that?
Oh my goodness.
So, you know, what's interesting, once you study the current condition and how they glean their notoriety economically, I'm not saying mostly, and you start looking at agricultural metaphors, you know what it's talking about now.
Right?
I'm talking about realism here, and that's what you hear politicized in the media.
Right.
So in the Book of Joel, I think it states that you're going to take your plowshares, turn them into swords, and your pruning hooks and turn them into spears.
Okay?
So what is the significance of just discussing Israel and its borders expanding?
How many times in the past decade have you heard of aggression against the Palestinians and the world outcry is like, oh, those damn Israelis.
Right?
How many times do you hear that?
You know, when that starts happening.
Okay.
Well, that ain't nothing, folks.
That's nothing compared to what's coming.
Does that mean World War III?
Nope.
But, you know, the World War simple packaging of world conflicts is stupid.
Right?
You're always, you know, what world war?
You know, there's always a war going on.
You know, the world war, I guess, is whatever is marketed to you as such.
So does it mean the end of the world?
Nope.
You know, that's another thing I want to discuss maybe is the end times.
You know, end of what?
End of all this crap?
And then what happens?
It's really the beginning of something else, you know?
Anyway, so what you're going to hear, what do you think you're going to hear in the media when these borders or these cities that we kind of gave an outline of that people can map on their own are going to be realized as being aggressed upon by Israel?
What do you think you're going to hear in the media about it?
Ain't going to be good.
Yeah.
So what are you going to do?
Are you going to start getting into your pillow and sob and get on a protest or a chat group about how bad Israel is?
Or are you going to sit back and say, I knew this was coming?
So I think that helps.
I think of what I've said before.
One of the things is why not live a life of efficiency, right?
You know how efficient it is to know what's going to happen before it happens?
Well, it seems to me like a conditioning that they're trying to make Israel look bad because you know that's exactly where they're going to go in the mass media.
That's a good point you made there, Bruce.
But you know what?
Not only is Israel going to look bad, they're going to be doing bad.
Right, right.
In reality, yeah.
And how do we know that?
In the first chapter of the book of Isaiah, if anyone's remembered in Greek speak, I've brought this up many times before.
In the first chapter of the book of Isaiah, he says something like, When I return you back into the land, I will restore to you your former judges, and then you will be known as a righteous people.
Okay, so that's a very benign verse.
Anyone that reads the first chapter of Isaiah will probably read that and keep going, right?
Sounds pretty okay, right?
Well, when I came across that, to me that was like a four-foot speed bump.
I remember you discussing that, yeah.
Okay, when I return you back into the land, when he talks about the land and you, he's talking about the land.
Whenever you see a land in Scripture, it's the geography.
It doesn't matter who is living there.
He's talking about the land.
And if who is living there matters, the Scriptures does give you the details.
They'll tell you whether they're right.
They'll say, well, the land was occupied by the heathen, and they're going to kick them out.
Or the land was occupied by these guys, and I'm protecting them, right?
You always get the detail on who is there.
In the book of Yeshayahu or Isaiah, it says, when I return you back into the land, we're looking at the land.
I will return to your former judges.
So when this land was established by what is known as the Israel identity, they were ruled by judges.
And today, meaning the past mid-century, they went back into the land and established a quote-unquote Israeli state, however it was done.
And they're ruled by prime ministers.
And a prime minister is a prime judge.
A judge is a ministerial position.
Israel also has a president.
So whenever you hear of a country that has a prime minister, they also have a president.
But they're not the front man that runs the show, let's say.
So what the interesting repeat here is that there were 16, roughly, judges of ancient Israel, and the fourth one was a woman, Deborah.
And the interesting thing here in modern-day Israel situation, the fourth prime minister was also a woman.
It was almost like it's repeating, right?
And the only woman.
And I think I mentioned when there was another woman.
There was a woman running Teporah Livni against Netanyahu.
When I said, no, it doesn't matter, Netanyahu's third or second term, whatever, he's going to win.
She's not going to win because Israel is only going to have one female prime minister, woman prime minister, not two because it's repeating.
And they were like, oh, no, no, no, no, Greek, you're wrong.
Your prophecy stuff doesn't work.
She's 90 percent in the polls.
Like, no, no, no, no, no.
Right?
It's very, very simple to rely on, right?
Once you know the prophecy.
But, you know, the rest of it is interesting.
He says, and then you will be known as a righteous people or a city.
Right?
Because a city is a city if no one lives there.
You know, I don't know.
It's a ghost town.
But, you see, so this is not telling you in reverse that as long as Israel has prime ministers, they will not be known as righteous.
Because it says then, you see, so as long as Israel has prime ministers known as their rulers, will they able to do anything that the world and the people will say they're known as righteous?
And the answer to that is a big, fat no.
Like a four-year-old would say.
Hearing those little children when they want to be emphatically, oh, it's a big, fat yes.
Big, fat no.
Right?
Yeah, it's a big, fat no.
So as long as you see prime ministers running the show politically, nothing they do is going to be considered righteous.
No matter how much it is, you see.
But I'm telling you that they're not going to act that way either because it's in the prophecy.
So I wanted to bring that up because very often people read scripture.
I don't understand it.
Well, you know, because the thing is, you know, let's go get some three-foot-tall shock absorbers and those really big 40-inch tires so we can ride over speed bumps at 50 miles an hour.
Right?
You know what a Unimog is?
Mercedes Unimog.
You ever heard of that?
Look it up.
U-N-I-M-O-G.
Anyway, it's an all-purpose vehicle that was built in the late 40s.
It's still around.
It goes upstairs.
It goes downstairs.
It can go on a 40-degree angle.
You know, you could go over speed bumps.
You could go over curbs.
You're like, what was that?
I don't know.
I didn't feel anything.
Right?
This is how people are trying to look at scripture, and that's why they're not getting anything out of it.
But it doesn't mean the communication.
You see, it can't be gotten through.
You know, in the Army they have code.
You know, military and corporations do also.
They send stuff that's coded, and years ago they had a code breaker, right?
You know, it's like, what is this code?
Or another thing is a radiologist.
You ever walk into someone's viewing, you know, someone had an X-ray taken, and it's up on the wall, and you see three doctors just staring at it, and you're like, what does it mean?
He says, I don't know.
We're waiting for the radiologist.
I'm like, you're a doctor.
You don't know.
You can't say, well, the radiologist will be able to read that for us.
You know?
At a cost.
Right.
Yeah, a regular doctor looks at an X-ray.
He's like, I don't know, man.
It looks like a pretty picture to me, right?
So the interesting thing here is, you know, why don't you guys become radiologists and code breakers on your own?
So I think that actually just giving the instruction or the very layout, let's say, the recipe, starting with in terms of these days that we're living in, the instructions to understand prophecy is to look at the former days, the former prophets, as was directed to the people of the fifth century.
So that means just because you're living now, you don't look at Isaiah and all that.
You have to look at what was considered the former days back in the fifth or sixth century.
And that would have been the 10th century, 12th century, you see?
So that's why you look at Joshua, Kings, Samuel, Chronicles.
And we know that there's going to be some stuff happening in the Middle East, and some of the stuff is Israel is going to be restored to a, quote, unquote, powerful position.
And when countries are powerful, what do they do?
They expand geographically.
And if you look back at all the cities I've mentioned, and the names for biblical place names are on the Wikipedia page or any – there's lots of other websites that have this kind of stuff.
You'll see that there are cities that are not in modern-day Israel that will be in modern-day Israel.
And how is that going to happen in the news?
Well, how are you going to find out, for example, Bruce and Sam, that places like Hamath and all these other places are now part of greater Israel?
How are you going to find it through the news, what they call the news?
You know, the show called The News, the media, right?
And when you find out about Hamath and these other places becoming subject to Israel, it's not going to be in a positive light, right?
So that's what I would suggest to expect.
So that was pretty much the crux of this whole thing.
It was basically to give people some tools in a way to understand what's coming.
Because even the most breakfast cereal type, you know, fruit-nut-and-flake type person, if you tell him what's coming and they get it or she gets it, you know, like you show them on a map, you see here, well, this is going to be part of Israel.
And, you know, they drop their eyes down about three inches and they're like, well, wait a second, the northern border of Israel is here.
You mean it's going to go all the way up there?
You're like, yeah.
And you say, well, do you get that?
Can you remember that?
They're like, yeah, I think I can.
Well, when it starts happening, they got no excuse to call up and chat or protest or call you and bitch and moan about what's going on, do they?
Not a bit.
Right.
I didn't say you have to like it.
That's why the caveat in the beginning was if you're one of these breakfast cereal types, which is pretty much it, you're either a breakfast cereal type I found on this planet or an idiot or a moron, you know, so take your pick.
And this doesn't mean it's terminal, you're going to die that way, but 99% of you are or have been or whatever are on your way out from being that way.
So stop it.
Grow up.
You know, that's the purpose of this particular sonic event.
There's a lot of unpleasant shit coming down the road, not necessarily happening to you directly, but it's going to be stuffed in your eye and stuffed in your ear, you know what I mean?
Because when a real heinous event happens, everyone starts talking about it.
Don't you feel like they're stuffing it in your eye and in your ear, you know?
Yep.
But the real heinous stuff, they just sweep under the rug and ignore.
No, you're not going to hear it.
Half a million children in the U.S. alone missing, and the authorities don't want to look at it.
You know, even in a southwestern town, whenever I see a child missing, I'm like, you guys go talk to the judges, lawyers, and doctors, and the bankers.
That's where the child is.
That's who ordered it.
Why don't you do a cell phone search, tracking on all the police cell phones, and you'll find out where the child is.
What do you think, the child just disappears on its own like that?
It had help.
Yeah.
Just get a record of all the police phone calls, and all the lawyer phone calls, and doctors' and bankers' phone calls.
You'll find those children lickety-split.
Lickety-split.
Yeah, go ahead, put a chip in the child and take it out when it's eight.
You ever notice that they're not doing that?
Chip them like a dog.
I've seen the way that children are treated is the only difference between them and animals is they don't put the cereal bowl on the floor.
They just put it on a table.
They're not treating their children like they should be anyway.
So put the damn chip in the child and take it out when he's eight, nine, or 12, or whatever, because around eight, nine, or 12, I don't think they're as sexually attracted to these degenerates.
You know what I mean?
And I'll tell you, like even in the southwestern part of town, whenever I see a child being missed, I say, oh, they're going to find this child in the desert in six months, and guess what?
There's a big hoopty-doo of missing child when it's missing.
When they find the child, there's almost no media of it at all, no reporting.
Maybe a day.
Yeah, not even.
No, actually, in many cases, not at all.
Maybe a news broadcast.
Yeah, you have to research it, and you'll find the idea.
Right.
So stuff is not like, I mean, the average citizenry or whatever, the average surface-dwelling earth inhabitant is finished.
You're just here to take a place.
Never mind.
So the purpose, again, of this sonic event is, here's a very simple example of what to look forward to informationally being stuffed into your eye, being stuffed into your ear, in the next three, four, and seven years, that you can sit back and say, I knew this shit was coming, and there ain't nothing nobody can do about it.
So there you go.
I have a question.
And this is just a small aspect of prophecy.
Please.
So can one expound a bit on how the United Nations will be tied into this?
Because obviously they have to have a hand in almost any major global development.
Underhanded.
When you say on the United Nations, you can't leave out NATO, right?
You can't leave out England, America, New Zealand, Australia, Canada, Japan, Russia, even though they're not all in NATO like that.
Those are the people that are running all the rat lines and all the various things that we consider geopolitics.
But here's the thing.
What most people don't know is that UN is not what you think it is.
It is not a peacekeeping.
It's peacekeeping through aggression.
NATO is the North Atlantic Terrorist Organization, right?
If you ever look at any major terroristic geopolitical events going on, it's openly NATO.
So, yeah, they're going to be used.
They're nefarious and malevolent organizations.
Yeah, they're going to be used.
Since when did the UN ever do anything benevolent and follow through?
Again, it's like the missing children.
They're going to get you to gain sympathy.
They're going to put, oh, UN wants to stop this.
And then you keep following through, and it's like they didn't do anything.
Or they did the opposite, right?
You ever notice that?
Yeah, I was just trying to think of the last time they did do anything.
I'm not going to blame them in a detailed way.
Yeah, they were set up at the Presidio in 1941 to fight Japan.
Yes, yes.
They have nothing to do with, like NATO is the North Atlantic Terrorist Organization.
You know, I mean, who do they always have as a head of NATO?
They have a high-ranking Marine, usually.
Why?
Because Marines actually represent the State Department.
The military is Army-Navy.
The Air Force came out of the Army, and the Marines are there to represent the State Department.
You know, if you go to any State Department in the world, who's guarding it?
Marines.
That's why you always have a Marine as the head of NATO.
I don't know who it is now, but it's traditionally the way they do it.
This stuff is really nasty and dirty.
But, you know, they could get away with putting it in your face, and you think it's good because, hey, just go shopping.
You ever see people, especially white people in the Midwest, shopping cart full of stuff that, you know, if you put it on the sidewalk, the EPA would give you a fine for toxic material?
The people have already been sold on toxicity as being good.
It sounds like a rant about the UN on the question you asked, but I'm telling you that all that stuff, I'll give you another example, and this is, like, sidehand.
Recently I saw a news thing where, you know, Trump wants to do on Veterans Day or whatever, Military Day, a parade in Washington to show the military parade, right?
You know how, like, other countries do, right?
And I'm like, oh, I wonder if he's going to have a bunch of tan-colored Toyotas with some towel heads in the back, you know, flying a black flag, you know what I mean?
Also as part of the U.S. military, because they are.
In other words, when he does the military, is he just going to show the bullshit that they get all the young, dumb people to recruit in, or is he also going to show the proxy military that the U.S. has?
All the quote-unquote terrorists also, you know what I mean?
Is there a particular reason why the narrative at this point is that ISIS has fizzled out because allegedly they've been defeated?
Put it this way, you know, very often, and this is a simple, maybe I'll take you back a long way.
Years ago, if you knew anyone that worked at the IRS, Internal Revenue Service, who prepared the payroll for the IRS?
Anybody know?
This is the Department of Agriculture, and if you ask people at the IRS, why does the Department of Agriculture do your paychecks, it's because they have better bookkeeping systems.
Wow.
Anytime the government does a project, they screw up.
That is an American government proxy, in other words, has a seal of approval of the State Department, they screw it up.
Like the post office.
Think of ISIS like the post office.
Who do you think is going to do a better job, the post office or like DHL or UPS?
Private.
Yeah.
That's a rhetorical question.
Whether you answer it or not, the answer is clear.
Right?
Right.
Okay, so who can, you know, why do you think they're getting a lot of private companies now when they need to get something done in terms of IT or research, the government labs take second, play second fiddle to the private, because they could do it for less money and be more effective.
ISIS was basically, ISIS, Nusra, Muslim Brotherhood, they're all, Al-Qaeda, they're all the same thing, same sources, they just change all the names to confuse the people, you know, in the media.
Right?
That's all State Department funded.
American State Department funded with seal of approval and funding from France and England.
And then, of course, Saudi Arabia, Qatar, right, because you always have to have someone's boots on the ground invested.
Like, for example, when they bring drugs from South America to the U.S., when it gets to the U.S., it goes through various properties and things that the drug dealers from South America also own here.
You know what I mean?
So it's like a safe haven.
Yeah, yeah, so this is ridiculous.
It's just a waste of resources and it's old shape.
What you see now happening in the media is stuff that these guys shook hands on 20 years ago.
Right?
Like 9-11 happened when it did and how it did because it was stuff that was, you know, hands were shaken on 10, 15 years before 9-11.
And it gets way down the line, it gets watered down, and the moment you have the, quote-unquote, government officials and all that involved in it, it gets really, really wasteful.
So, and also you have a radical mindset from bad religion.
Like, to give you an example, let's go to the Western world.
Like, if you're a panty sniffer, a professional panty sniffer, which is an intelligence agency, FBI, well, it's not really considered, but CIA, NSA, and all that, they always, if not always, all the time, 99% of the time, if you go into these agencies, what religion are the people that work there?
They're either Mormon or Catholic.
You don't think so?
Then you don't know them.
You haven't been around it.
You haven't investigated the culture of the NSA, CIA, DIA.
They're always Mormon or Catholic.
And, of course, they have a few Jews thrown in there, you know, for this and that and whatever, but the majority are Mormon and Catholic because those are the most brainwashing type of, you know, religious upbringings you can have.
Don't ask any questions, remain dumb, and you're going to get all the popcorn and jelly donuts and bacon and the rest of your life, right?
So with the radical Islam, what they did was they went through the whole world in Europe and to all the mosques, you know, in the 90s and early 2000s, and they paid off all the imams running these mosques and said, listen, you got any nut jobs visiting your congregation?
Let's start recruiting those ones that are unstable, you know, ones that have drinking problems, drug problems, parental problems, social problems.
Let us know who they are.
And they got recruited through the mosques all over the world, right?
I don't know if that makes any sense or if you guys know about this.
No, that would make sense.
Yeah, I really don't care about it because I don't see that as being the cause of anything.
I see it as being the effect.
The gods don't think anything about any of the world religions right now at all, but the people do.
So these mechanisms are, you know, the religious mechanism, the lack of education, of knowledge, of just in general.
When I say education, I mean real education, right, which is direct observation.
I think I put something in chat earlier today.
The skill and art of direct observation.
In other words, how many people do you know or have heard of, if not yourself, at one point, were told something was something or the way it was or how it is?
Well, right in front of you, you could see with your own eyes it's not that way, but you agreed to it anyway because who are you to buck the authority or the established fact that what you're being told, even though you can look at it and say this is not what they're saying it is, but I'll just go along with it, right?
That's the opposite of learning from direct observation, you know.
It's just like the money is the best one.
You know, go to a bank, I dare anyone, go to any bank with a check or whatever and go to the teller and she's going to help you and you say, yeah, I'd like to have Federal Reserve notes for this.
Every time, every teller will say, oh, I don't know what that is.
Let me get the manager.
Did you ever try that, by the way?
I have not, but I'm tempted.
Don't say I want to cash this.
Yeah, don't say I want to cash this or anything.
Just say, do you have Federal Reserve notes?
Just go to a teller, ask her if you have – oh, I don't know.
And then just take out a dollar bill.
What does it say on the top?
See, if the teller was capable of learning from direct observation, the first day or the first time she handled the money or whatever as a job, she would pick up a note, whether it was a 1, 5, 10, 20, whatever, and read it.
That's direct observation.
No one looks at that.
It's part of the censorship.
Go into a doctor's office and say, look, I don't want that magic cuff.
Show me where the pressure in the body is.
He'll just fall apart because if he was paying any attention all those years and the hundreds of thousands in credits he paid to get that education.
You see, the reason why you have doctors being in such a training is to – is because the actual training is so self-contradictory, the dropout rate is high, not because the information is technical and difficult to learn.
It's because the schools are so self-contradictory and they only take those that can be easily mind-effed.
You know what I mean?
You ever hear people dropping out of medical school and you ask, oh, it was a lot of work.
They put you through a lot of stuff.
I said, really, it was a lot of bullshit.
Oh, yeah, absolute bullshit.
See, because they're able to – More than you'll ever know.
The medical dropouts were the ones that had more direct learning by direct observation.
The ones that do get the doctorate degree and all that are not capable of direct observation.
Now, once they get into the field, they do a little bit, but if they do too much, guess what happens?
You're going to find them serving donuts.
So put your head down and shut up.
So this is not explained by what man is doing or what is, but what the gods are telling us what man is.
I'll be back in about 30 seconds.
Make some talk while I'm gone.
Okay.
Make some talk.
On demand.
Yes, this is spontaneous.
I was wondering about that.
Erdogan vows to recapture all lands once held by Ottoman Empire.
That was an interesting one.
Do you know what the problem with Turkey is up to?
He's a little out there, and he wants to go back and claim a few places in Europe there, Bulgaria, Romania, Yugoslavia, Algeria, Syria, Iraq, Israel, Egypt, Algeria, Tunisia.
Are you talking about Erdogan?
Yes, Erdogan.
There's that movie Scarface.
He's Fertilizer.
He's going to go.
You want to ask him whatever the guy is, you want to ask about him, he's Fertilizer.
He's done.
Do you remember, not because it's in Greek-speak, but a few years ago I used to say that, how can you have a union of nations if each one is fiercely independently nationalistic and not cooperative?
It's not going to happen.
But it makes sense that they'd have to get rid of him.
Oh, yeah.
Or the gods will, when the time is right.
One or the other.
But it's done in such a way, see, you have to know what's coming before it's coming, and you really have to stick to it.
Let me just go back to the idea.
This is a refresher.
You know when you hit refresh, right, and all the junk falls off the page and you start from scratch, right?
So hit refresh.
Okay, how clear is it in the vernacular out there in Commons, you know, talk about things like the apocalypse, Armageddon, the Antichrist?
Everyone speaks of these things like they've heard of it and they know them, right?
I'm telling you no one knows shit about it at all.
Why?
Because, okay, so let's say these things start taking place.
You think you're going to have all these billions of people?
Right now if you put 7.5 billion people in a room and said, who's ever heard of Armageddon, this, that, and the Antichrist and whatever, raise your hand.
How many of the 7.5 billion would raise their hands?
5 billion?
Maybe?
Let's be conservative.
Easily 3.5. I'd say 5 to 7 would raise their hands.
Okay.
Okay, so how the hell are these things going to take place without 7 billion people saying, oh, no, this is coming, oh, look at it.
Nowhere in Scripture does it say these people are going to know it's coming.
What hit them at all?
All it says is they're going to fall for it.
Right?
No, there were no guarantees.
Yeah.
So my point here is very simple.
Everything that you read in Scripture, and you've heard me say in the past again, is a secret.
And you have to stick with it.
What do I mean by that?
Once you learn a particular premise or a precept that's in Scripture, you keep in your mind that no one else, once you can piece it and harmonize it within the way the plan works, these things are going to happen without anybody noticing.
But they're obvious.
So here's the interesting thing.
Let's go back to Erdogan.
He's talking all this smack, right, and whatever, and some people somewhere are going to start focusing on whatever he's speaking, if it was a program that were to be rolled out into the future.
Now, the program that Erdogan was mentioning is total rubbish when you compare it to what's going to be happening in Scripture, right?
Right.
So you could spend all this time rolling out the possibilities of what this guy is going to do, and what does it mean, nothing but a hill of beans.
Here's the other aspect to it.
It's very, very, very subtle.
You know what's interesting?
I like there's a verse in Zechariah about identifying the creator, the man who forms the spirit of man within the man, right?
So what's interesting is that this condition of the shit moral condition that humanity is in, and if you're one of these breakfast cereal types and love, peace, love, and harmony, and whatever, and you're still hanging around on this sonic, maybe now's the time to go.
But it started 100 years ago, meaning about 85 years ago, in the 1930s.
In other words, what do you know what happened to the, let's say, the morality or ethics, I'm not going to say values because values don't mean jack, to humankind in the 1930s geopolitically?
They flushed the toilet.
Yep, yep.
You had a group of leadership that was put in place, whether it was Stalin, Hitler, Roosevelt, who was the little guy in England, Sam, come on, with the cigar?
Yeah.
And all the little machinations of all those wars and all those things that happened was to set you guys up into being ethically and morally void.
The money system is a real good premise.
I was texting, someone was messaging on Skype about a week ago.
He's concerned about the dollar collapse.
And I said, okay, you idiot.
I wrote, you moron.
I called him a censored moron.
I said, when you do PayPal or whatever, you're sending dollars?
Or is it just pixels?
Right?
It's not lawful.
The dollar's gone a long time ago.
Money, you know, all your stuff has gone a long, long time ago.
You see?
Your medicine has gone a long, long time ago.
You know, it's interesting.
You want to know your medicine's gone a long, long time ago.
We've never done a sonic event, or I don't think I've ever done one on AFR or with Ocelli on hygiene.
I think I did food.
I was discussing food.
We did food, how to cook perfect rice, I recall.
The container.
But I never got into the hygiene.
I should do one on hygiene.
You touched on that lightly, and very lightly.
Okay.
And the thing that keeps ringing, and really this is where you expand hygiene out.
A 19th century nursing manual, nursing book.
Okay?
When they got patients, you know, admitted under their care, the first thing the nurses did was clean under their fingernails, make sure their fingernails were trimmed and cleaned underneath the fingernail.
Because you can imagine, it's like the space between the finger and the fingernail is like a neat little package to harbor all kinds of stuff, right?
Oh, yeah.
Clean the armpits, the neck, and the groin.
All the stinky, where the most dirt can hide under the fingernails, and the stinky parts of the body were washed immediately.
And then they checked the feet for worms and things like that.
Right.
Let me ask you, I've been through hospitals before.
I've seen people sitting in hospital beds with dirt under their fingernails.
Do you ever recall a scene like that?
Yeah, they don't even consider it.
Right.
So we don't have to do a sonic, I just gave it.
A 19th century nursing manual.
That's it.
Anything that goes below waist cannot be considered sterile, by the way.
So let's say you walk into a room where some surgery is going to proceed.
It doesn't have to be a special place.
It just has to be clean.
And you have some towels on the side.
They're on a tabletop.
If one falls to a chair or on the floor, you cannot use it.
It has to go into a pot of boiling water.
But, Greg, look, it's still clean.
Nope.
Anything below the waist is an off zone, if you're going to open or put anything near the body.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
What's cleaner, a freshly wiped table or a chair?
Someone's ass was on the chair a minute ago, let's say, right?
So, and also what you'll notice is when you read in these old, ancient, might as well be, they talk about tomain, tomain condition, P-T-M-A-I-N-E, which is the Greek word for dead.
Tomain, radiation, tomain condition means death condition.
So, or decay.
So there's your sonic.
Make sure you've got clean under your toenails, your fingernails, your armpits, and your groin and your neck, if you want good hygiene.
And then eat seasonally and watch what happens.
So, anyway.
And fresh water?
Fresh water that's been moved in a way that the water prefers to be moved.
Correct.
Without a pathetic fallacy that, you know, water can't be happy or sad or mad or whatever.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yeah.
Well, it's just a matter of it's part of the environment.
So, okay.
I think just how clear, if anyone goes through the sonic on the archives, how clear would it be, should I give just from the top, again, the purpose of the sonic is just go to the rectangle, do a general search on biblical cities or biblical place names, and you'll see if you get a chart, and if it has the verses where that city is mentioned would be best, and the modern name.
We're using the one tonight from Wikipedia.
It's called List of Modern Names for Biblical Place Names.
And I think it was third down on the search.
All I put in the search was biblical cities or cities of the Bible.
There are quite a few websites that list all the cities mentioned in the Bible.
And then seek out the ones that are from the prophets of old, the former prophets, Book of Joshua,
Book of Kings, first and second, Book of Chronicles, first and second, Book of Samuel,
and find out what you can about those cities and those verses and how they applied to Israel back then,
is how modern-day Israel in the next three to four years, especially for sure by the next seven,
will be under some influence of modern-day Israel geopolitically.
And, of course, the further away the city is from the current border, especially if it's outside of any current border of Israel, you could say, here comes trouble.
So once you do a little bit of charting and mapping on your own, you can't say that, well, I didn't know.
Right?
Because you're probably going to be, you probably know for sure, you know, if you are somewhat social,
someone who is a breakfast cereal type, fruit, nut and flake, or a love and light sympathetic to the brainwashing
or whatever typical human garbage, and you don't have to be around them or it when it's tried,
they try to stuff it into your eye and into your ear of how bad things are happening, right?
How bad things are.
Oh, that bad, bad Israel.
Well, you knew it was coming.
All right.
You know what a good example is, guys, on this?
It's financial collapses.
You know, all of a sudden, there's a big, like, financial crash.
All the idiots on the planet, oh!
But the bankers, are they complaining?
Nope.
Not a bit.
Yeah, so.
They're rich.
Oh, yeah, because they knew it was coming.
So, you know, this is a setup.
And once, you know, there will be peace when this setup is, you know, you're going to, well, it would be safe to say that most people will never perceive peace in their life, what they think is peace, what they've been told is peace.
But in terms of what the Middle East in relations to Israel is considered, yes, there will be world peace from that perspective.
You know, why do I say the people are not going to see things as being peaceful?
Because when you read about a situation, for example, of this particular instead of Christ or anti-Christ type individual coming into power, don't you get the sense, at least literally, that he's going to be oppressive?
In other words, if you don't, it's either his way or the, not the highway, but underground.
You ever get that impression?
So, even though there's going to be a sense of world peace that's described in Scripture, when this particular group, because it's not just individual, is going to be in power, you do commerce his way or else you're not able to do commerce, right?
You worship him or you're not able to worship, right?
He's going to go after people that understand what's going on is, you know, works of the devil.
As they say, right?
As it is the works of the devil, Satan himself.
So, yeah, anyway.
So, how is there really going to be full on peace?
Well, geopolitically there will be.
So, anything else?
We've only been at it for 1.21, which is about half the stretch we normally do.
I'm ready to call it in unless there's anything else.
I just opened up the Uncommon Sense radio email.
I have just a couple of neat images that were sent over by DY.
Thank you.
And check out chat.
Is there anything in chat that we need to address or not really?
No, I'm good.
So, I don't remember exactly the detail.
I put on a comment.
Maybe we'll discuss it with Sam.
It was a few days ago.
I think did we cover everything that we said?
You know, I was going to explain how to map this out.
Yeah, I think we did, or you did.
I didn't really have much input this time around.
As far as the ancient Israel borders and things of that nature, that is something that has to be kind of studied as a package for its totality.
I could probably throw in one city or one place here and there, but it doesn't really help with the holistic nature of what has to be understood as far as the northern, southern, eastern, and western borders.
Well, it goes beyond that also.
It goes across the water also.
But this is basically what's on land.
Because remember, there's going to be a loose...
I think the last time we spoke about the aspects of Egypt and northern Africa's influence on this as well.
We haven't gone that far.
But you also have to consider, was it 1971 or something when Egypt, the Six Day War, beyond that, they captured the Sinai, but they gave it back to Egypt, right?
So, let me see.
I don't have any notes in front of me on that.
But in 1979, I think they gave it back.
Was it 79?
To Egypt.
But they're going to return back to that and perhaps give it back again.
Well, we know that Israel's original borders are supposed to stretch from what denial to the Euphrates.
Yeah, that's right.
And that's why I think we brought up in the past when this figure, this world-powered type young man who's about 20 years old right now, when he's around 27 or 28, he's moving between Tzor or Tyre, Jerusalem and Babylon.
And it doesn't say that he's going from one country to another.
He's going from one city to another.
Freely.
Let me just put it in common terms, like you almost don't need a passport for that because you're in the same jurisdiction.
It's going to be strange.
I don't know how it's going to happen, but I know what's going to happen.
If that makes sense.
Yeah, it's just one of those things that you're going to have to develop on your own.
Because we're commanded, each one of us, each individual, to when you do inquire and approach the information from the gods, that we are each given a very unique piece.
This is maybe not as directly implied as indirectly implied, that there is a special piece that everyone can get if you do so.
Right.
But then again, let me just say, this is not a reverse psychology thing, whatever.
I find that I get more out of telling people, don't even bother reading scripture because you're not going to understand anything in it, than telling them this is what it says.
And you better listen to me or else, or this is the way, you know.
Because when you tell someone, don't bother reading it because you're not going to understand anything in any way, and they have a natural desire, or at least it's part of their makeup to do it, they're going to say, screw that Greek asshole.
And at least they'll have some motivation.
Where when they listen to a lot of the quote-unquote stuff that's been done through the ages, I think it kills the motivation of the individual.
And they fall into the Gustav Le Bon, oh, as long as I go to this group, or go read this guy's book, or go listen to I'll Get What It Means, you know, what does that do to that little individual key that everyone could have?
Destroys it.
So, anyway, there's more to this, like for example, you know, Bruce brought up Erdogan, right?
And there is a, the last book, which is the first book in the Bible, let's say, there are seven, Sam, mute for a moment, Sam?
I'm just going to mute for a sec.
Okay, thanks.
There's, I don't even like to use the CH, the circus word, you know, the circus word.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's seven of them, and they have angelic providence.
Those are in Asia Minor, which is in modern-day Turkey.
And those are, you know, I was saving, let me just, can I drop a, should I drop a nugget that I'll continue?
I know this is going to get some people really activated, maybe that's why I'll do it, it's a teaser.
What do they call it, a teaser when you give just enough to get people interested?
Right.
Okay.
All right, now, do you get the feeling that the Magi, you know, the ones that came and issued the decree and honored the Christ as king of Judea, you know which ones I'm talking about, right?
Right, right.
I think, do anyone remember that these guys, there is a very strong, more than a presumption and possibility that these are descendants of Abraham that were given special knowledge of this alignment?
Because when they did make it to Jerusalem at that time, King Herod didn't even know, it was a very, even though the sign was seen in the sky, it was very subtle, they didn't know what it meant, right?
Right.
If you remember reading in the New Testament, when Herod didn't know what it meant, that sign meant.
So you had to have very highly specialized knowledge.
Why do I suggest that these were Abraham's descendants?
Well, there was a time in Abraham when he was asked to reckon the stars, to count the stars.
You don't count the stars.
It was to reckon an alignment.
And he comprehended the alignment and he was complimented by the Elohim on that, right?
If you remember?
Right.
Right?
Yeah, he was complimented as I counted the stars when I was reckoning.
And he sent, didn't he send a bunch of his sons back east, to the east?
Almost to protect.
You know, let's say you have a room full of people, 10, 20 people, or even 12, Sam, and you give them, Bruce, Sam is probably listening, you give them special information.
Don't you think it's safer to split up the group and send, you know, let's say you're in the Midwest, send half the group to the east coast and half the group to the west coast, instead of keeping them all in one room?
Preserve the information.
Right.
Because if you all live in the same town and the town gets blown up, what happened?
Right?
Your information's gone.
Okay, now let's just tie this back in together.
Do you remember when these Magi, when they approached Herod, this was two years after, two years after the Christ was born, wasn't Herod, like, shaking in his britches?
Yep.
He did not like that visit.
Why?
Because these guys, these Magi, come from a group of people through the ages that have been running shit behind the scenes and you guys don't know about them.
Ha ha.
Remember the Simpsons?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, the bully.
Right.
And all, you've been getting all your attention, Sonny.
Illuminati's this, and the rule world order that, and the deep state idiot's that.
Panty sniffer's here.
Everybody just cover your ears.
Bruce, you know these people don't know Shia.
Shia.
Right?
They don't know anything, and they never will.
But, anyway.
So, when you have this particular organization happening in Asia Minor, you think it's going to be a bunch of idiot Christians or Jews or whatever?
Or do you think it's going to be made up of a bunch of people who know the deal, man?
Yeah.
And has it come into fruition yet?
No.
But it will.
Yeah, and I'm the only one, whether it sounds egotistical or whatever, tough shit.
Only one discussing it this way.
Only one discussing it like that.
Sam, did you get that whole story about the Magi?
No, I had to step up.
Okay, well, you'll hear it again later maybe.
That's why the Pope's work schedule, yeah, it's really dumb.
We all fell for it, yeah.
I'm not going to say I never fell for it.
Of course I did.
Uh-huh.
I've fallen for all of it.
But the thing is, I don't have to stay in it.
Anyway, you know.
So, I got a shower and a new set of clothes, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
So, new duds or whatever they call them, right?
My new suit.
So, what I'm trying to say is very simple.
Do you know how you could look at the alignment?
It's around 3 B.C., right, which would be two years before.
There's no year zero, right, in the year.
That's like right when the year ended, right, he was born.
But do you know how they reckon as if there's a year zero, year one?
You know how they do it on the square?
It's two years after, you know, on the Gregorian calendar.
Right.
Right, like 1 A.D. is not 3 B.C. You know, like right now people think that he was born 2018 years ago because it's 2018.
But it was really 20 years ago, right?
Because you've got to add another two years to bring it to 3 B.C., roughly.
Well, the reason why, why did they bump it up two years?
Why don't they just tell everyone, well, he was really born, you know, it's not the year 2018 A.D. It's really 2020 A.D. right now.
Why is it 2018?
Why?
You get it?
It's the Magi again.
Because it was two years after he was born that they came to him to honor him as king.
So until they made it there two years later, when they said we've acknowledged the king, that's when time starts.
And they have an influence on the Pope's work schedule.
See, that's why you have that two-year discrepancy.
Do you see how simple this is?
Interesting.
There's power behind, it ain't the Illuminati.
It ain't the guy with the ridiculous fish hat and that big discotheque called the Vatican.
I told you before why it's a discotheque.
There ain't no guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper with long hair.
There ain't no shroud, right?
There ain't no nails.
There ain't no cross.
His mother's name wasn't Mary.
She's dead.
She died probably after he died.
As the head priest says, we need to kill everyone that he was ever in contact with.
Or she was killed when Jerusalem was destroyed if she was still there.
And she was not a virgin because she had children after him.
Perpetual virgin, right?
All this mythology that's put out there, you look at the crap that they put in front of you and you will see there's some truth in it.
But that truth is based on the structure of the actions of these Magi.
You see?
Because the structure is based on A.D. 2018 but it should be 2020 because he was...
Ah, the Magi acknowledged him then, that's when we start time.
So actually who takes precedent over the current world system?
What is really going on or what the Magi acknowledge?
Do you see my point?
What the Magi acknowledge, obviously.
Because it would be 2020 if it was when he was born.
Because we know we got it right.
This is just a small tidbit, I've got a whole bunch of tidbits about it but...
Look, not to disparage anyone, I see what's going on around me whether it's emails, chat, people I speak to and I still get that blank stare, I ain't going to get into the Magi.
Who they are, what they're doing and all this other stuff.
That's like, people want to hear that, I've got to set up some kind of site or whatever.
It's $100 to talk, to join the site and it's $100 for a minute to get it.
I mean that kind of stuff, you know why?
I'm not saying it's whatever, it's just speculative.
The reason why is because I've noticed that if you give stuff away, it means it's no good.
But this is how twisted and hypocritical and sick people are.
If you give them stuff for free, you do all the work and just give it away.
Because you know, cupcakes, lemonade, whatever.
Magi talk, right?
That's just bullshit, I don't like the guy.
That can't be good, whatever.
But if you charge them for it, they're like, oh this guy's charging for it.
So either way, it sucks.
But as I'm doing it right now, I didn't get me cigarettes and coffee.
So anyway, the whole thing is just a mess.
So I'm not complaining, I'm just stating the facts.
So I ain't going to get into it, the Magi.
Didn't I say Bruce's teaser?
Yup, you did.
Here's the thing, you guys go figure out who they are.
Oh I will, but just not right now, but later.
But you gotta look, this is the key, alright, I'll give this away.
And you did give helpful hints many times before.
Yeah, all the junk that you see, that everyone says is what describes this current society, is to call it a civilization is freaking ridiculous.
All the junk that you see, the bad education, the papal, all the religious crap, the timekeeping, the science that you have, even downright to how the censorship is managed.
Because there are people that exist on this planet that have power, that know how stupid and censored people are.
And they can't see it, and they know that the gods are doing it, and they're running it that way.
They like it that way.
They understand, just like for example, I was communicating with someone in the IT business, and I think I had a conversation recently.
Years ago when the internet first came out, they knew where it would be right now from this person.
And basically they said all they needed was 55-60% of the population to get heavily involved to the point where they use the internet for almost everything they do informationally.
But they have about 90-98% of the population right now involved.
What I mean by that is when you use one of those silly pod phones, not only do they know what you're looking at, what your interests are, and who you're communicating with, but your geolocation, and if it's an Apple phone or something, they have some biometrics, like the fingerprint and all that.
And even a lot of the laptops do that.
So in other words, to control the whole world using the internet, they only needed half the population, but they have more than 90%.
That's not good odds there.
No, no.
So what I'm saying is when you go on the internet, and I could prove this, give me any site and I'll show you how to dummy load all of it.
Lately I've been looking at all the new shit in the alternative media that's coming out.
It's shit.
It's amazing.
Yeah, it doesn't matter who it is.
I see all these new people, they sound good, but they don't know Jack.
Now, you could polish a turd, you can chrome plate a turd.
You know what?
It's still a turd.
The reason I said chrome plating a turd is if you've ever been to a chrome plating shop, and if you've got avid Halloween followers, they'll take a jack-o-lantern and spray some zinc chromium conductive paint on it with a spray can, let it dry, and they dip it in the tank.
They chrome plate the jack-o-lantern.
It'll decay after a few days or weeks.
So here you've got this bitch-ass looking jack-o-lantern, and it's really freaking chromed, you know?
But you know what?
It's still a turd, right?
So I'm sure everyone's been around.
You could polish, you know, you could talk to someone for years, and it doesn't mean they're just more polished, but they're still inherently the same.
And they know that.
They meaning informational control.
So get into the magi, get into the study of things are the way they are because you're being controlled.
Well, duh, Greek, we know that.
But no, no, it's not what you think.
How easy, you know, who's that idiot, Cooper?
Bill Cooper or whatever?
Oh, Illuminati, New World Order, all that stuff.
You know, ask that idiot.
I mean, he's, you know, I should say he's dead now, whatever, but who cares?
Ask him what day it was or, you know, anything about scripture, anything about how the body works or whatever.
Doesn't know jack shit.
Alright?
Whatever happened to being a well-rounded, whatever happened to the true nature of philosophy?
You know, go to any college professor, all these people spewing whatever venom or garbage that you like to hear on the Internet.
Ask him what day it is.
Ask him how the body works.
Ask him about food.
Ask him about anything outside of the garbage they're spewing.
They know nothing.
They're like a chrome-plated jack-o'-lantern.
I wasn't going to say turd because maybe it's not good to call people what they are.
But, do you see my point?
Yes, yes, I do.
So they're not changing anything.
What they're doing is they're managing you.
And who's behind it?
I wouldn't say solely, but yeah, let me just say, the magi.
Sorry.
Ain't no Illuminatis.
You go on these turd channels, all of them, not some of them on the Internet.
Illuminati!
New world order!
Nope.
Sorry.
Ain't it.
So, with that said, a little more of what's coming.
And don't be a moron.
Yeah, just flip the switch.
Yeah, so you've got to go.
We've all got to go somewhere eventually.
But Sam, you've got to get going.
Anything else from anyone?
That's why I said I'd start another thing.
No, I think you're self-propelling.
So I think I can step out in good conscience.
Okay.
Well, maybe we'll stay on for another minute or two.
What do you think, Bruce, to round it off?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Sam, thanks for being present.
No problem.
I guess they're quick with their pocket or quick with their thumbs, I guess, in your case.
Yeah, happy to help.
Okay, thanks.
Take care.
Talk to you guys later.
Be well, Sam.
Anyway, and that's pretty much it.
I think we threw in quite a few nuggets.
Yes, you did.
I think it's all good.
And if they pause like you told them and actually do the rectangle searches or books or whatever they can put their hands on.
Yeah.
It's going to be an interesting map.
All right.
I think I'm good to do it.
I cooked a bunch of veg from the garden, and even though it's around what they call 9 p.m., I'm going to go eat.
Okay.
Thanks again.
Thank you, Sam.
I think this is going to be archived.
Yes, it will be as soon as we're done.
Okay.
All right.
Well, thanks, Bruce, and we'll see everyone again soon.
Okay.
You take care now.
Ciao.
Bye-bye.