Yeah, they were brought out of the society that they were a part of.
He was holding those things written on stone tablets.
And I like to tell people, well, he went up to get the stone tablets with another set of commandments.
Those were just directives given at the base of Mount Sinai.
The other thing I like to bring up about those commandments is that if you look at them, in the order that they are and in the sense that they deliver of what the covenant is or what to do, is all prophetic for the coming of the Messiah and the world of the Messiah.
Right?
The coming of the Hameshech, as in Yeshua?
Yeah, Yeshua.
Or as in what is yet to come?
Both.
Okay, so…
What's the difference?
Well, there isn't.
The thing is, it's two.
You know, the Beatles say one plus one is one, right?
Is that how it goes?
The thing is, it's…
One and one and one is three, right?
Or that too, yeah.
Well, let's just say, if the entire program is laid out prior to it happening, when he was born as a human to show he was the one chosen and most fit to give the proof of what happens after you die, the first to be resurrected, that was his purpose.
And to manifest that way.
Otherwise, if it was to teach people, his existence wouldn't have been a secret.
It was to teach certain people.
And I assure anyone that reads what they call the New Testament or even the Old Testament, and I've said this publicly before, don't bother.
It has nothing to do with you.
What they call the Bible and the understanding of it has only always been for a very, very small group of people, so small that it's, you know, if you've got enough hands and fingers and toes, that's how few, ultimately.
And that's shown in the scripture itself.
But there is going to come a time where it will be for everyone, you see.
And that is also predestined.
So, none of these things that I've mentioned are in the public eye or in the public view as being so.
Then, if we can view this conversation as not in the public, and, I mean, there's, I don't know how many people are listening, but regardless, it's people that choose to.
Like, this isn't something that is easy to find.
This is something that those who have heard you speak have sought out.
And that is why they are here.
I don't think there's any argument to be made against that.
I could be wrong.
I'm often wrong, actually.
But the eight that I have are do not make covenants with pagans.
I'm horribly paraphrasing as well.
No, no, go ahead.
It would be do not make covenants with pagans.
But hold on.
The one right before that is do not have another Elohim.
Why don't we just read it?
OK.
Before the – so you missed – I think the first one is do not have any other Elohim other than me.
And then do not go into covenant with the pagans.
People, marvels I will do such as not have been done in all the earth, nor in any nation, and shall see all – this is Exodus 34.10. Where does it – Sam's idea is pretty good.
Let's just read it.
Where does he tell them to carve out two stones like the first?
And is he talking to Moses?
But anyway, that's another thing.
What does it say after that?
And write on them what was written on the first.
And then immediately what does it go into?
Put yourself atop the Mount to me there, and man shall not come up with you.
Neither let any man, neither – I'm reading the inner linear.
So if it seems broken, that's why.
You could read it out of anything.
As a matter of fact, I almost prefer to just read it out of one of the versions because that's what people are going to be accessing.
And then if you read it out of the version, if you know that there's a mistake, go ahead and correct it.
Because let me just throw this out.
This is a rare thing I'll say.
One of the benefits of reading the versions is even though it has a lot of mistakes, if you know what the mistakes are, make the correction.
But the benefits of reading the version is that it's structured within the construct, the literal construct, that people of that language are used to listening to.
And it's easier to remember because that's how they speak, right?
Even if you read King James with these and those, just don't use the these and those and use what you know the correction is.
Okay.
So this is King James.
By the way, let me just speak for a few seconds while you're getting it together.
One of the things I put in chat a while back was how about making a project of whether you want to look at it as 66 books or 49 books, just whatever's published as the Bible.
Why don't you get 49 people or 66 people, each one grab a book, or two or three people grab a book, split it and whatever, and go through an interlinear and see where the fatal mistakes are and what was left out, what was put in that shouldn't be there.
And what is mistranslated and make a list.
You have to know 66 people interested in doing such a thing first.
Yes.
Well, actually, I don't have to know them.
They just have to appear somehow.
But I know what you mean, right?
And just make a glossary.
So let's say someone takes the book of Genesis.
You would say, well, you know, you would do chapter and verse.
Chapter, verse one, this is what should be there.
This word in English should be that.
Go to the next one.
If there isn't a mistake until the next chapter, then just show the chapter and verse.
This is wrong.
Put this in here.
It doesn't make for a big body of work to do.
And I'm not talking about the ultimate fixer-upper.
I'm just talking about a cursory correction.
Because if we go through, I think Sam and I have done private conversations, and he'll read something and say, it doesn't say that.
And he'll pick stuff out of the Old Testament or the New Testament.
And just out of memory, I'll say, that's not what it means.
Let's go to the interlinear.
And when the interlinear, you know, sometimes I'll be off.
It really is what it says.
And sometimes I'll say, oh, yeah, that word doesn't mean that.
Yeah, right, it doesn't.
So after a while doing this, you commit enough to memory.
But why?
Why not have a glossary of it?
Certainly.
It makes it easier to communicate if you have – especially if you're talking to anyone who is familiar with any religious dogma or the text upon which these dogmas are not based.
Well, yeah, it's just strictly the text, the received text, the accepted text, the version, versus what's in the interlinear, without even making it too much of a, let's say, a stretch.
Like, for example, I was going to translate the book of Joshua, and I just put it down because it was like, I've read too much scripture to be able to do that because every other verse was a hyperlink to another book.
You know what I mean?
So instead of the book of Joshua being 15 or 20 pages, it would have been 500 pages because I wanted to explain it.
So I said, oh, I'm going to put this down.
But while I was looking at it, I was looking at the words that were – could have been translated better with more accuracy, you see, and made a list and all that other stuff put together.
I was like, hey, this should be done with the whole scripture, but I'm not going to do it.
There should be people out there interested in doing it if they have that much interest.
OK.
I have the King James brought up here.
It says the first time the stone tablets are mentioned in chapter 34 is …
Verse 3 or 4 or 5, somewhere around there.
Yeah, it's 4.
And he hewed two tablets of stone like unto the first.
And Moshe rose up early in the morning and went unto Mount Sinai as Yahweh had commanded him and took in his hand the two tablets of stone.
Yahweh descended in the cloud and stood with him there and proclaimed the name of Yahweh.
And Yahweh passed by before him and proclaimed Yahweh, Yahweh El or El Yahweh is how they would – how that would be in the Hebrew, El Yahweh.
Merciful and gracious, long-suffering and abundant in goodness and truth, keeping mercy for thousands, forgiving iniquity and transgression and sin.
And that will by no means clear the guilty, visiting the iniquity of the fathers upon the children and upon the children's children unto the third and fourth generation.
And Moshe made haste and bowed his head towards the earth and worshipped.
And he said, Now I have found grace in thy sight, O Yahweh.
Adonai, actually, is how that would – I have found grace in thy sight, Adonai.
Let Adonai – Adonai is how they would pronounce it actually.
I pray thee, go among us, for it is a stiff-necked people and pardon our iniquity and our sin and take us for thine inheritance.
And he said, Behold, I make a covenant before all thy people.
I will do marvels such as have not been done in all the earth nor in any nation.
And all the people among which thou art shall see the work of Yahweh, for it is a terrible thing that I do with thee.
Observe thou which I command thee this day.
Okay, that's where I started my list.
Behold, I drive out before thee the Amorite and the Canaanite and the Hittite and the Perizzite and the Hivite and the Jebusite.
Take heed to thyself, lest thou make covenant with the inhabitants of the land wherever thou goest.
Okay, stop right there for a second.
I just want to – I remember from doing a study on that.
When you take the six names, I think, of those countries, those people, make a list of what each one of those names means and read that.
And it ends up being exactly what he just said before that.
Indeed.
So go ahead.
In that, I condensed – as I said, I made notations here as I was going through last week.
I mean, it's written on the back of a gas bill.
But it says, do not make covenant with pagans.
That's, as I said, a very abbreviated version of that right there.
So, okay, where was I?
Now art shall see the work of Yahweh, for it is a terrible thing that I do with you.
Observe thou which I command thee this day.
Behold, I drive out the Amorite, and the Canaanite, and the Hittite, and the Perizzite, and the Hivite, and the Jebusite.
Take heed to thyself, lest thou make a covenant with the inhabitants of the land whither thou goest, lest it be for a snare in the midst of thee.
But ye shall destroy their altars, break their images, and cut down their groves.
For thou shalt worship no other god for Yahweh, whose name is Jealous, is a jealous god.
Lest thou make a covenant with the inhabitants of the land, and they go whoring after their gods, and do sacrifice unto their gods, and one call thee, and thou eat of his sacrifice.
And thou take of their daughters unto thy sons, and their daughters go whoring after their gods, and make their sons go whoring after their gods.
Thou shalt make thee no molten gods.
So I took from that, and like I said, there's two in there, and that's, so I've got nine now.
Because yes, it's, there shall be, for thou shalt worship no other god, and, okay, three, if you take the, destroy their altars, their images, and cut down their groves.
No molten gods, yeah.
And the no molten gods is the second one that I have written down here.
That's okay, okay.
So you could paraphrase each, we could do like groupings.
So let's say that first grouping is don't go in a covenant with the pagans.
Also group with that one, only worship him and no molten gods, maybe.
So yeah, like the first grouping, let's say.
Yeah, do not make covenants with them, because...
No covenant, no gods, and worship one.
You have me, you have Yahweh.
Yahweh is your god, and so you will make no covenants with them.
And by the way, just to interject, when you traveled around the world, even today, they'll say, each country will tell you who their god is, by the way, even today, to a certain extent.
That comes later on, other studies in scripture, where the sons of gods were given to rule and create the nations, but go ahead.
Okay, observe thou, let's see, but ye shall destroy their altars.
I'm catching up with myself here.
Thou shalt worship no other god, for Yahweh, whose name is Jealous, lest thou make a covenant.
Jealous, no.
Heeded the sacrifice.
Thou shalt make no molten gods.
That one is the one that I took as number two.
Do not make covenants with pagans.
Two, do not make molten gods.
Okay, go ahead to the next one.
The next one, my paraphrase is, keep the Feast of Unleavened Bread.
We've talked in the past that this is not the only place that is stated.
It is stated at least seven times very clearly, given as a commandment, to keep the Feast of Unleavened Bread.
Yeah, even in the New Testament, what they call it.
Yes, absolutely.
Do this in remembrance of me.
The Feast of Unleavened Bread, I'm reading again here, this is 3418.
Right, and by the way, most people think the Passover is a high, it's not.
It's the first month, it's the week of Unleavened Bread.
Okay, I'll just throw in the commentary as we go.
What is known as the Peshach is the Feast of Unleavened Bread.
Peshach is...
Prior to, yeah.
Yeah, prior to, it essentially is the beginning of the Feast.
Okay, so the Feast of Unleavened Bread shalt thou keep.
Seven days shalt thou eat unleavened bread as I commanded thee in the time of the month of Abib, the first month.
For in the month of Abib thou camest out from Egypt.
And apparently that was made the first month when they came out of Egypt as Abib for the observance of festivals.
It's the first month.
As opposed to the civil, which is determined, what, six months prior.
And here, let me just throw some commentary.
You know, they were not officially out until the second day of the second month.
So that's another thing.
Because, you know, Scripture is not very...
Yeah, Peshach was observed, they were still there.
They were still there when it happened.
You could do, if you do a study, you'll learn that when you do a study on the Temple.
The Temple was started exactly the same day that they were out of Egypt, which was the second day of the second month.
480 years to the day.
So anyway, I just want to throw out, I can't help it, I have to throw in trivia, right?
Oh, don't help, please.
Please throw it in.
All that opened the matrix is mine.
Matrix is another word for womb.
All that openeth the matrix is mine.
And every firstling among thy...
Okay, so that's the one that I paraphrased as the first are his.
And do not send them empty-handed.
Because it continues on.
All that openeth the matrix.
So the first out of the womb.
And every firstling among thy cattle, whether ox or sheep, that is male.
So the first male is his.
But the firstling of an ass shalt thou redeem with a lamb.
And if thou redeem him not, then thou shalt break his neck.
The firstborn of thy sons thou shalt redeem.
And none shall appear before me empty.
So that's like three commandments, as I said, that is simply, at least in my reading of it, just clarification of all that openeth the matrix is mine.
And it says, and every firstling among thy cattle.
So that would be the same with the cattle, regardless whether it's ox or sheep, that is male.
But the firstling of an ass shalt thou redeem with a lamb.
And if thou redeem him not, then thou shalt break his neck.
And all the firstborn of thy sons shalt thou redeem.
And none shall appear before me empty.
So that was, I suppose, my first confusion in enumerating them.
Is that I read that as being because all that opened the matrix is mine.
And then the continuation of that thought is all that follows.
And all the firstborn of thy sons shalt thou redeem.
And none shall appear before me empty.
All right, so five is, you know, six days thou shalt work.
But on the seventh day thou shalt rest.
In earing time and in harvest thou shalt rest.
And thou shalt observe the feast of weeks.
This is the, that would be the sixth one.
So fifth, paraphrased, work six days, rest the seventh.
Although in earing time and in harvest thou shalt rest as well.
Should certainly be considered in with that one.
And then the sixth commandment in Exodus 34 would be.
And thou shalt observe the feast of weeks.
And the first fruits of wheat harvest.
And the feast of ingathering at the year's end.
So that's two.
Ingathering is sukkot or tabernacle.
Okay, so if those, if that is two.
It could be one.
Meaning that he wants to observe these feasts.
But then if we go on there's others as well, observances.
Is that the only commandment dealing with days to observe?
Appointed, those are moed I think.
And also I'm curious just to go back for a study.
My memory doesn't serve me right.
When we were talking about opening the matrix.
I wonder how many times the word Hanuk or Hanukkah comes up.
Which is to dedicate.
So anyway, continue.
Okay, so seventh day shalt thou rest.
In earing time and harvest thou shalt rest.
And thou shalt observe the feast of weeks.
Of the first fruits of wheat harvest.
And of the feast of ingathering at the year's end.
So that seems to me as one commandment.
To observe two different feasts.
Okay, and there's a grouping there of two different feasts.
Okay, go to the next.
And the next is an interesting one.
Because I'm curious as to how.
I suppose.
But thrice in the year shall all your men children appear before the Lord God.
This is not just the first born.
But this is all of the children that are masculine.
Shall appear before the Lord God.
The God of Israel.
For I will cast out the nations upon thee.
And enlarge thy borders.
Neither shall any man desire thy land.
When thou goest up to appear before Yahweh.
Elie thrice in the year.
So the three is the spring, summer, fall festival.
Three times men shall appear before Yahweh.
What does it have in the interlinear for three times?
In the interlinear?
We could put a question mark.
Go to the next one.
Okay.
Might as well go through all of them.
For I will cast out the nations before thee.
Okay, this is 25.
Thou shalt not offer the blood of my sacrifice with leaven.
Neither shall the sacrifice of the feast of the Passover be left unto the morning.
That's a reiteration of how Peshach is observed, actually.
But three times a year.
Okay.
So there's another one.
I think I'm actually up to like 13 now with clarification.
Okay.
For I will cast the sacrifice of leaven.
It's very clear in verse 28 that there's only 10.
So we can't just arbitrarily add.
Some of them are combinations.
That's okay.
Let's go through all of them first.
Yeah.
Okay.
Three times a year before Yahweh.
Thou shalt not offer the blood of my sacrifice with leaven.
Neither shall the sacrifice of the feast of Passover be left unto the morning.
That's another one that I didn't actually enumerate.
That's okay.
The first fruits of thy land shalt thou bring into the house of the Lord thy God.
Thou shalt not seethe a kid in his mother's milk.
That's the last one.
Yeah.
Don't boil an animal in the milk of its mother.
Or it could mean don't cook a suckling lamb.
A lamb that's still suckling?
Yeah, one that is still – okay.
Yeah, absolutely.
I can see that one that is still – It's a difficult one to go either way, but that always has spiritual – I understand that.
As I've heard it used in literature as young children, youngling of animals even being referred to as still in their milk.
Right.
It's kind of like isn't there something in Leviticus?
If you take a bird, don't take the eggs and the bird.
Take one or the other.
Right.
That's interesting that it said thou shalt not seethe a kid in his mother's milk.
It seems relatively specific, although the – Yeah.
And a kid could be a goat or a lamb, but it's a – in other words, it's kind of like when you run into somebody who's steeped in tradition they got from their parents, you don't have to really – if they're not open to figuring out the truth about it, making fun of them or trying to convert them.
My comprehension of the New Testament is certainly inadequate for my own desires.
There is no conversion, by the way, in the New Testament.
Calling them fools or whatnot would be counterproductive if one is going just by the writings that are available.
If the concept of conversion comes up, that was only strictly associated with those that wanted – that accepted the testimony of the Christ being resurrected and also learning the law and the history, the real history behind it.
Right.
I would like to read just the verse that is directly after that because it says, And Yahweh said unto Moshe, Write thou these words, for after the tenor of these words have I made a covenant with thee and with Israel.
Just leading more – very obvious that these – the words preceding that phrase right there are what were written in stone.
And does it say word?
It's interesting.
Do a quick look.
Is it d'var or is it another word?
Because there's another word that's also used that's translated as word and it means to emanate or project out.
Just real quick, does it use the word d'var?
I'm looking.
I shouldn't be asking.
It's kind of minor, but just out of memory I remember.
No, no, it's – minor clarifications are incredibly useful.
Let's see.
And said Yahweh unto Moshe, Write to you words.
Hadabarim?
Had, had, d'barim.
Okay, so it is d'var, d'barim.
Yeah, the words.
Okay.
So it is literal, the words meaning.
There's no – there's nothing else.
So yeah, strictly like literal.
Like words on a black ink on white paper or something carved in stone.
So it refers back to that.
Sam, what were you saying about the verse on the ten before?
Sorry.
Do you want to – anything you want to bring up, Sam?
No, I was just saying that it's – the total commandments are ten because it says that very clearly in verse 18.
Can you write these ten words down?
Or these ten d'barim?
How do we – got it, right.
Verse 18 of 34?
Yeah, the last verse.
Now here's the interesting part about it.
You know, is anybody here familiar with Linear A or Linear B, which is the old prehistoric Greek writings?
You know, Minoan Linear A would be Minoan and Linear B Mycenaean writings where it was like one symbol actually meant an entire phrase.
Are you guys – I think, Sam, you might be familiar with it.
Are you familiar with it?
It's still allegedly not translated today only because they haven't found a Rosetta Stone type thing, but I assure you that once you understand the culture and the culture around it, these things can be presumably, you know, translated.
But I would suggest that, you know, as it is today, what is known about it is you would have a symbol and it could mean a word, it could mean a sentence, it could mean an entire concept, you know.
Is this how these people were conveying meaning, the people that saw what was written on the stone?
Because, you know, it was put in the Ark of the Covenant, so it was, you know, not just Moses who was able to witness what was on the stone, but nothing is said about it, nothing about language.
Now what we're reading is what Moses was told to write down.
I'm curious.
I'm still curious.
I just can't find the 18th – is it Chapter 18?
Sorry, 28.
Sorry, I misread that.
Is it Exodus Chapter 28?
No, it's Exodus 34, Chapter 28.
That's the one that starts with, and he was there with Yahweh 40 days and 40 nights.
Bread not that he eat, and water not that he drink, and he wrote on the tablets the word of the covenant, the 10 commands.
Yes.
So there's 10 of them.
Right, but what we just read, what Seth, my point maybe wasn't that clear, what you just read in Exodus 34, what we just went through, is what Moses had written, known as the Book of Exodus.
Shemoth, the words, right?
Or Shemoth meaning, you know, the document that Moses penned.
Yeah, on the stone.
That's what you're talking about, the commandments written on the stone.
No, no.
What Seth was reading was what is in the Book of Exodus that was part of the Pentateuch, the five books of Moses.
How it was written on the stone, we don't know.
We've never seen the stones.
So I suppose that's where my confusion came in.
As I said in chat last week, was that I counted eight, and as we went back through them, I found more.
So I suppose it's just the grouping I need to look at a little bit more carefully.
Sorry, I wasn't entirely sure what the Greek was saying.
Let me just say back, when Moses wrote Exodus, in other words, we could find old copies, for example.
You know how the king is supposed to make his own copy of that, right?
Alright, so we have what's called the first five books of Moses.
What we just read was in the first five books of Moses, regarding what was written on the stones.
How it was written on the stones is, I'm trying to maybe stretch the imagination in a semi-lawful, rational way, that back then, contemporary, there was something going on, known as Linear A and Linear B, in another part of the world, let's say.
Where one symbol can be a word, it could be a sentence, it could be an entire paragraph, phrase, you know?
So this is something that we have been deprived, visually.
So you're talking about the manner in which it was recorded?
Right, on the actual, you know, if you want to listen to or observe what's been, you know, like in the last Sonic event, I said, look at everything, you know?
A lot of the, I hate to say it, rabbinical texts talk about it was written on sapphire, right?
Because, you know, supposedly, wherever he goes, there's a sapphire floor, you know?
And it was like sapphire, you know, blue like the sky.
Well, it doesn't say it was written on sapphire.
But, you know, you look at all that stuff, you know, let me just put it this way.
The way that we are given what was written as the Ten Commandments, the way Seth read it, clearly there isn't a short laundry list of ten items.
There's phraseology in there, there's meaning that we get, because it's, should I say in a loose way, a form of poetry, you know?
That the way you remember these things is when you put them in a poetic form.
But maybe the way it was written physically, if we were to see the stones now, would not resemble what we just read in Hebrew or any language.
It could have been just ten characters resembling something.
We don't know that yet.
Some people want to, in the occult mysticism, say, well, they were using the language of the angels or something, you know?
And there's so many ways you could look at it.
So no one that we know of has seen the stones.
We don't have, I don't feel like I have any rock-solid research where I could say, well, this is what the stones look like in the Ark of the Covenant, you know, when they were placed there, you know, for safekeeping, let's say, or memorialization.
We have very little information on that, how it was actually recorded on the stone.
And that aspect is always in conflict with what we just read.
You know, where are the ten?
You know, it's not that clear, but is it supposed to be clear?
We do know that there are ten of them.
As it states, correct, in Exodus, yes.
But as it reads, it reads like an entire soliloquy of a covenant of things to do.
And really how to do them as well.
Certainly.
Knowing, I suppose that knowing how to do them is my own motivation for trying to discern.
Whether it's censored or not, it's something that I find value in, and finding value in that, I would like to have comprehension of it.
Well, you also have to look at the whole picture, right?
You know, the helicopter point of view of the forest, right?
Instead of the tree that you decide to build your treehouse in and live in.
And let me just sum it up again.
You're living in a time period where in the near future, not so near, it's going to seem like a long time, but in historical time you're half a second from midnight, not even a minute.
The inhabitants of the earth are going to be slaughtered at a rate of 90%.
And what kind of a setup is required mentally with each, you know, whoever is listening to me, myself, you, Seth, Sam, or anybody, in order for these events to happen where it's acceptable, and comparative to the entire history of, you know, the plan that, you know.
Acceptable to whom?
Oh, it's, in other words, when, quote, unquote, the end, you know how people talk about the end times, right?
What's going to be happening?
I don't see anyone really complaining.
I see a group of people being angry at these things happening, but I don't see that there's going to be any allowance for anything other than that, you know, to follow through.
You know, in other words, what you read about man's behavior and what is going to be happening on earth makes it something to be considered when one wants to observe these things personally, right?
Let me just say it another way.
Let's say we lived around that time, and you heard, you know, around the time of Moses or so, and you found out about this, right?
And you just rocked on over to the border and said, Hey, listen, guys, I heard about your L, and I'm just a pagan.
As you can see, I come from these people over here, and I don't want to do it anymore.
I want to vow to be, I want your L to be my L, and I'm going to vow to live the way he wants you to live as one of you.
They will accept you, just like I think there are several books that state when the stranger or the sojourner comes around your camp and he wants to do these things, you accept him as one of you or as one of yourselves, right?
Yes.
Right.
Very different than what people think it is.
It's kind of like the way it's done now, let's just say from a loose point of view, with nationalism.
When you want to become a citizen, let's say, of the United States, I'm oversimplifying it.
They make you study a little bit of history and the Constitution, and you swear an oath, don't you, right?
And become nationalized.
Which is unlawful, apparently.
Yeah, well, yeah, because there is no united.
I mean, it's just…
No, I mean, as I've stated earlier, my comprehension of the New Testament is lacking.
Oh, the New Testament is something different.
If there are commandments given, that's certainly one of them.
Did the Christ offer any commandments in the New Testament?
No, the New Testament is very simple, and it's simple to the point where it really shouldn't have been made public the way that it was.
But it is, so no one is without excuse.
The New Testament is for a very specific group of people, which Christ specifically stated in different ways in different times.
It's for the deceased of Israel.
Basically, he came to anyone who passed away that knew the Elohim, Yahweh.
What happens after death, knowledge of the resurrection.
He was there to prove that basically Elohim keeps his word.
That's all.
It wasn't about starting another religion or anything like that.
Regardless of starting a new religion or anything like that, there's what has been shared of what is memorialized, which unfortunately, being a native English speaker, I only have what is available to me to refer to.
But even in that, if that was solely his existence, then why the teachings?
There are very plain, easy commandments given there.
One of them being, make no vows.
Take no vows.
Let your yes be yes and your no be no.
That's very basic, straightforward.
But at the same time, it's completely and totally detrimental to the society in which we live.
Well, the vow aspect also, you have to realize that there are things in Scripture that counteract cultures of humanity, known as the goyim, the nations.
That word just means the nations, right?
Right, but in that same aspect, the way you were to interact with the nations is the same way that you would interact with your brother.
As I've stated, and I can't make clear enough, my comprehension of the text is very limited, but it's something that I'm striving for.
And these are very plain words that are given.
Before you answer, Greg, I'm just going to step out because I'm getting kind of tired.
Okay, man, well thanks for coming in.
Yes, thank you, Sam.
It was always good to hear your voice, man.
Thank you, Sam, and good night.
Be well.
Talk to you later.
Here's a very simple explanation.
If you read in other books like Zechariah and Isaiah and all that, it talks about the entire world being brought into this.
If you read into this knowledge, right?
Not just Israel.
Also, if you read other places in Scripture, the sons of gods were to be the Elohim of mankind based on different nations, right?
And they screwed up.
They didn't do their job right because they led man astray and various other reasons.
But essentially, if you look at Zechariah, Isaiah, Psalms, the nations, those that are not of Israel, will also acknowledge the Christ.
And I'm not talking about the second time it comes around, the first time.
Just to show that this is for the entire world, not just for Israel, because obviously the gods that they have were made by this god.
So the simple way to look at it is that, you know how we were discussing with Sam earlier that there's a primacy, that when people are listening to you, it's not because you're such a good whatever orator, it's because it's meant for them to listen to you.
They were brought to you, if it's regarding these matters especially.
The same thing is with Scripture.
What was being shown in the New Testament was certain people were being called out
of society that were not of Israel, did not know, were not raised in what was lawful,
basically pagan, and they were, through inspiration,
and I'm using that word etymologically, which means divine influence,
acknowledged the resurrection of the Messiah and what happens for sure after you die,
what we are to expect.
But they lacked tremendously on how to live.
They didn't know what was fit and proper.
And they didn't know, like if you mentioned Noah, they were like, oh, you mean Dagon, the fish man?
Or Poseidon, the fish, I mean the god of the ocean?
That's not Noah, right?
He's the only person around on the ocean?
No, no, no, no.
So they had to go through a retrospective or a retro-training where they get inspired to show that symbolically that the resurrection was for everyone.
These people have full faith and credit, as the American money system says, that for sure they understand and believe and know that the Christ proved the resurrection.
But they didn't know anything else.
They were steeped in paganisms.
And that's where the quote-unquote conversion, the teaching, the going to congregation was about, to bring them up to speed.
Does that make sense?
It does.
It absolutely does.
But at the same time, I mean, I'm not of, at least unbeknownst to me, I'm certainly not of any particular bloodline or lineage that would have had a specific covenant offered or instructed.
Neither were these people that you read about.
So that's – in reading what was spoken to them by the person of the Hamashiach, the Messiah, the Christ, it seems like these words should have as much weight as any of the words of the prophets before him.
But then it would be redundant.
In other words, if you don't understand – It is absolutely redundant.
Things of import bear repetition.
They bear being repeated.
But what I meant by that is the Christ would say, if you want to know who I am, well, I don't have to tell you.
Go read the prophets and the Psalms.
He did, though.
In private, yeah.
There's a big thing about how the things that he spoke – there's a hint, if you read in the Book of John, for example, when he does a blessing, almost like a prayer about these that he taught.
Here's an interesting aspect.
The purpose of the Christ's resurrection was for all mankind, right?
No one goes to hell.
There's a fire of eternal or whatever, and you don't go to heaven plucking a harp and all that other stuff.
This was something that people had been taught, these things.
Ridiculous, torturous, or pleasantries that you get after.
They had no idea of the resurrection and all that.
Once they got an idea of the resurrection, well, they didn't know anything about what came before the Christ.
So this is a situation that is beyond your bloodline and who you are.
Certainly.
It's a cognitive one.
I would say that that is something that I have recognized in and of itself.
Otherwise, there would be no point to this study at all.
Here's another way.
Here's the antithesis of it.
If you go to your run-of-the-mill Christian and ask him to define the Christ, he can't.
Why would he do that, though?
I know.
But I'm just saying.
And also, they tell you all that stuff doesn't matter, right?
So once a Christian can define the Christ, then you have a desire to go define the prophets, the psalms, the laws of Moses, and all that stuff.
And you have a desire to do that.
Now, I'm not saying this to be dogmatic.
But, for example, if you ask a run-of-the-mill or even the Pope who the Christ is and all that, they have no definition.
And those are the same people that tell you the Old Testament doesn't matter or they have no concept of it.
And that right there is an interesting spiritual paraphrasing of what's going on.
Right.
But you and I speaking, I'm certainly not of that mindset.
I'm one who – I want to know.
I want to know.
Sure.
Not for the sake of being right itself, but because I would like to be as good as I can for the – I have no idea why.
It's a desire and a – Well, you want to be as good as you can during the time where mankind is being set up by the gods.
Certainly.
For the worst possible scenario ever.
Yes.
And also you keep that in mind because that also puts a limit.
Also, let's put another example.
Could you imagine living in Europe and wanting to do that?
You'd be burned at the stake.
Well, now you won't be, right?
Because, you know, we're actually discussing sometimes personally and publicly how to be lawful.
And there's people in the chat talk about that.
What people don't appreciate, I think, is that if you wanted to live biblically, you were persecuted and put to death, right, in most Western cultures for the past thousand years.
Maybe the last 500 it's eased up, right?
So isn't it interesting and ironic how there's a liberation of that punishment or penalty now?
Certainly.
But we're living in a time and place and admittedly, you know, my own experience is what I draw from aside from the scriptures.
But at the same time, we're talking about a collection of information that has been systematically and intentionally obscured from those that is presented to.
It's used as a tool of war.
It is used as a tool of subjugation.
It is used as a tool in the temples of Eustacia here in the States where they ask you to place your hand upon this book that in this book specifically states to not idolize material objects.
And yet in presenting it in that way, they are asking you not only to place your hand upon this book, but to also make a vow to swear, which is also specifically verboten.
But it's specifically verboten in the New Testament where the Christ says to make no vows, to let your yes be yes and your no be no.
But at the same time, I want comprehension of what the Christ is saying there.
When he says to make no vow, it's very plain regardless of the language in which I read into it.
It is to make no vow, to make no pledge.
And here where I live in my locality, you sign your name for everything.
And in signing that name, it is taken as a vow, it is taken as swearing.
When you join the military, you vow, you swear.
When you join the judiciary, you vow, you swear.
When you join the police, you vow, you swear.
When you join anything…
Whatever…
So to one…
But Seth, I'm going to stop you for a moment.
What about appearing as a dove and being wise as a serpent?
Here, I'm going to share a little thing with people I've never shared before publicly.
I might have mentioned this to you.
I'll sign my name every day on anything you ever want me to sign.
People say, don't sign.
I'm like, I'll sign anything.
Well, have you ever seen a doctor's signature?
I'll sign anything void.
And you'll look at it and you'll be like, that looks like a scripture.
That looks like your signature, Greek.
But if I just tell you I just signed that void, you'll see, oh, shit.
I do see the dot over the eye.
Yeah, it is.
Now, why do I sign everything void?
Well, if I sign a traffic ticket void, I'll put in an affidavit.
I said, I signed that void because that is a farce on its face.
It's a legal farce.
There's no legal awful bearing.
Why did you sign it void?
That's why.
And here's an affidavit on how I signed my name.
And here's an affidavit of evidence how I signed void.
And I'm signing all your stuff void because it's illegal.
Even you are in the legal system.
This got so bad at one point that people here in the local jurisdiction, whenever someone signed, they started asking, let me see your ID, how you really signed.
I mean, because it got out.
So that's your pure, you know, I'm not going to sign that traffic ticket.
Shit, I'll sign your traffic ticket.
I'll sign my traffic.
I'll sign everybody's traffic ticket.
It don't matter to me.
And everybody walks away happy.
But when it comes down to pouring a pound of flesh and blood, I'm like, oh, you can't, hold on, that's void.
That's been issued void.
Why?
They won't even get into why.
That's all unlawful stuff.
All those mortgages, checks, police tickets, contracts, everything is signed void.
Now, they don't scrutinize that.
You just scribble V-O-I-D, scribble it like a doctor's signature.
It looks like a signature.
I'll give you an example.
When the election was going on, I had to sign something, return something at a major store, and she said, you've got to sign for it.
And I just wrote void, of course.
And she looks at it and goes, what kind of signature, what does that say?
I said, it says Donald Trump, because it was a Mexican lady, you know.
A Mexican lady with a Hillary shirt on.
Oh, wow.
Because Donald Trump is this racist.
I'm not pro either one.
And I said, I'm going to get her in her face.
I said, what does that say?
It says Donald Trump, I told her.
And she was like, oh.
Because she had the Hillary.
I'm voting for Hillary.
So this goes back to what Sam was saying.
What do you say to who and what, right?
I mean, the woman at Home Depot or whatever is asking me, what does that say?
And I see she's got the Hillary shirt on.
I lean over and go, Donald Trump.
And she just jumped back three feet.
She's like, oh.
But if it says void and you're telling her that it says Donald Trump, that's, I mean, you're lying to her.
Yeah, but in a sense, it was she overstepped her bound.
Because nowhere in her instruction manual does it say she has to read signatures and make sure that they're official signatures.
Well, certainly, but someone else overstepping their bounds doesn't, I mean, it's a lie.
So did I lie to her, but maybe it was a lie worth telling to give her the shock of her life that day?
I suppose.
And I certainly wasn't lying under oath, right?
But anyway, the reason I brought that up is because one of the things for tonight was communication, right?
Certainly.
Absolutely.
Yeah, so will you communicate to what?
Why would you tell anyone you signed to Donald Trump when, well, you had to be there?
It's one of those things you had to be there.
A real cocky Latina woman with a Hillary shirt.
It's around the election.
And she's looking at a little bit beyond what is her pay scale, literally.
And I just had to, you know, I was just like, I just got to give this woman something she's going to remember, you know.
That's understandable.
It's just, what about, you know, not bearing false witness?
Yeah, well, no one asked me, did I witness that being Donald Trump's signature?
Anyway.
You just don't look at it, right?
Obviously, the whole thing was done in humor.
Bruce, I think you got it.
You got a pretty good laugh out of that.
Oh, God, yeah.
Yeah, because you can picture the situation, right?
I laughed as well as soon as you said that you signed void.
That's beautiful.
What about David at the gate?
Well, also, she's inquiring, and I'm noticing I'm going to use what she has interest in, which is the election, against her, you know, in a way she will never see it.
And, you know, she probably hasn't gotten a surprise like that ever, publicly like that.
So, but here's my point.
You have to have fun.
And what about David feigning being mad at the gate of the Philistines, right?
That's being as wise as a serpent and as harmless as a dove, right?
Well, certainly.
And I would completely and totally agree with you that on the aspect of signing void as…
Oh, yeah, because all this stuff is not even…
That's beautiful.
It's illegal.
All this stuff they're doing is not only unlawful.
It's illegal, according to their own laws, not because I say so.
According to their own laws, absolutely.
And that in and of itself is important.
Oh, yeah.
They've got it.
Here's the thing.
A lot of people get angry at other people and institutions and all that.
I'm like, if you only knew what they were going to get, you would just sit back quietly and just relish when it happens.
And even if it takes you out, it's okay.
Well, it's interesting that that's what you just said, because that's another one of the commandments…
Oh, yeah.
Don't do anything.
In the new – what they call the New Testament, given directly by the Christ, not commentary on his teaching or anything like that.
But supposedly the record that we have available to us as English speakers as what was written or what was said and then written is – that's another one of the commandments, is do not be angry.
Don't get angry.
Oh, no, no, no.
But you are packaged in a physical body that is quite ready to enable endorphins and adrenal glands and things to…
No, absolutely.
But it is overcoming that that makes us different than animals.
Well, that's discipline.
Well, it's the discipline of that, which is an interesting thing.
Because it's one of the things that I read recently and looked at the text and found that what is preserved in the English is different than even what is preserved in the Greek, is that in that sentence, the don't get angry without cause, the without cause is nonexistent in the Greek.
It's something that was added in by the quote-unquote translators in the English.
And what was added in in the Greek was from the Aramaic, which remember the Greek is a translation which is just as bad as what the English…
Is the Aramaic any better though?
Oh, yeah.
What the English does to the Greek is what the Greek did to the Aramaic.
Okay, so the Aramaic being – is that what – because we've spoken before of the New Testament being actually preserved in the Hebrew.
No, it's not preserved that we have access to.
It's preserved that we have access to in the Greek.
In the Greek.
But it was originally written in Aramaic and Hebrew.
The Greek didn't start until the 2nd or 3rd century.
This is another – I'm going to jump topics.
I don't get into those kinds of discussions because people are so far removed from anything that even approaches this reality that going that way is like wanting to use a Formula One race car to go to the Walmart.
Here's an interesting point, at least of interest to myself, perhaps to others, is that there is a phrase that even in the King James Version is memorialized in Hebrew that the Christ spoke from what the pagans would refer to as the cross and what I would call the almond tree.
And that phrase is Elie, Elie, lama, ha-sabachthani.
Why am I up here so long?
It literally would be Elie, Elie, which is my god, my god, lama, which is why even in modern Hebrew it's the same.
Elie, Elie, lama, ha-sabachthani, which would be why have you forsaken me?
My god, my god, why have you forsaken me?
Delayed me.
It's delayed me.
Ha-sabachthani.
But it's of interest to me because people speak of the Aramaic as being the language that is most likely to have been native to the Christ, Hamashiach, Yeshua.
And also of the area.
It was the language of Syria, Babylon, western India.
Yeah, absolutely.
And there is certainly credence to that.
But my question is then why upon his virtual execution by the Sanhedrin, why then would he speak out in Hebrew if the language that he taught in was Aramaic?
It was an Aramaic phrase.
Have you gotten it?
How did you glean that it's Hebrew?
Elie, Elie, lama, ha-sabachthani?
I gleaned that it's Hebrew because it is preserved in the text as being Hebrew.
Elie, Elie, lama, ha-sabachthani, that's a Hebrew phrase.
There's an interesting aspect.
If you look at it in Aramaic, it means why do you delay me here?
Why so long?
Not forsaken.
Why would it be recorded in Hebrew if it is an Aramaic phrase?
Because it's interesting that it wasn't.
What they've done back and forth, there was an aspect of writing it in Hebrew at one point.
But what they did in the Greek text, they went back and resolved Hebrew characters and Hebrew words in some of the early Greek texts.
And you will see that, I think there's fragments that have been found where you will see the father's name, the YHWH in Hebrew.
And any of those phrases that were put in the Greek text were typically lifted off Aramaic text but recorded in Hebrew.
But let's just look at the law for a moment.
He was never forsaken by the father.
Well, yeah, certainly.
What does forsaken mean?
I'll give you another example of how the play works.
When you look at the – what's son in Hebrew?
Ben, right?
Yeah.
But why do they use Bar Mitzvah all the time?
Bar is son, like Bar Abbas, son of the father, remember?
It's not Ben Abbas, it's Bar Abbas, you know, the man who was let go?
Yeah.
Okay, well, why do they use – see, so then when they switch to Hebrew and you use the Hebrew, it might as well switch to Greek also.
Like, for example, there is a mixture, for example, today in the Hebrew culture, they don't have a Ben Mitzvah, they have a Bar Mitzvah.
Why are they retaining Aramaic?
Why don't they say Ben Mitzvah to present, right?
So there's this mixture, and there was an idea that when the Greek texts were being put together, if they were to retain any of that, it should be written in Hebrew, in the ones that we see.
There are some records, for example, some of the popes wanted an inventory of their oldest texts.
This is a whole other study and a whole other four-hour conversation, but I need to dig in and give references so people can look it up if they can on the rectangle.
But whenever any of the popes – actually, there were two popes.
Do you know that one of the popes, by the way, just to stay on the subject, do you know that I think it was the fourth pope or the fifth pope of the Roman Catholic Church was a Torah-observing pope?
Did you know that?
He got a lot of crap for that in private.
Admittedly, my knowledge of the history of the Catholic Church is certainly lacking.
Yeah, mine isn't, and I don't talk about it because I find them repugnant, which is disgusting.
I suppose that's why I haven't spent a lot of time studying it.
The reason I did is because there was one of the popes in the 1700s that asked a man – he was a scholar.
He was well-versed in Greek, Hebrew, Aramaic, and Latin.
You couldn't get a more perfect fellow to go and get an inventory of what was in the Vatican repository and the oldest texts that they had going back as far as possible.
And he says, yeah, we've got a bunch of 1st century texts of Matthew and whatever, and they're all in Aramaic.
And then all of a sudden it jumps to the 2nd or 3rd century, there's a big gap, and all of a sudden we have some texts that are in Greek with Hebrew.
But wait a second, the oldest ones that were from the 1st century were all Aramaic, and all of a sudden we jump 150 years to the next set, and it's Greek, or 200 years, let's say, and now it's Greek and Hebrew.
So how did it go from Aramaic to Greek and Hebrew?
Exactly.
So changing one letter makes a difference, and this is something that could be resolved.
If you look at that phrase that the Christ said before he gave up his spirit, right?
So the aspect of that in Aramaic, the definition is not forsaken, if you find a word very similar to that.
Just like you would find, for example, all of the mistakes in the New Testament by being well-versed in the law.
Like we know that Christ was never forsaken, not even a moment of that.
We know that he was the most evil, he had to have been resolved as the most evil person that ever lived, but never forsaken.
How do we know he was resolved as the most evil person who ever lived, by the Father?
Because he says he took all the sins of the world on him.
So that means that would make him the biggest sinner that ever lived, you see what I mean?
That, you can see, you could rationalize, but him being forsaken cannot be rationalized.
It's just like you can't rationalize that Christ was having a supper in the city with a leper, right?
Okay, so what you're saying is that...
There's a lot of things that can't be rationalized.
You're suggesting that he didn't say, that what he said was, why has it taken so long?
There's an Aramaic word, I'm not as well-versed as I should be to have this conversation.
I have to start looking at notes and splitting hairs and explain why the mistakes are the way they are in the Greek and the Hebrew resolution.
You know what I mean by resolution, how clear something is, versus what we could look at in the law and what was preserved in Aramaic.
In Aramaic, you're only going to find the first couple of books, maybe Matthew, Mark, and Luke, maybe.
Because Luke, you have to understand, was well-versed in Hebrew, Greek, and Aramaic at the time.
And one thing that another study can be done, is that all the other books that you see in Scripture, especially around the contemporary writing of Paul, were not until 30 years after.
The only thing that was available as known as the New Testament up until the destruction of Jerusalem around mid-60s or so A.D., was the book of Matthew.
And one strong clue of that is when you read, for example, Paul, and he quotes, he says, as it was written, and he's quoting directly from the book of Matthew.
He's not quoting from Mark, he's not quoting from Luke, he's not quoting from John.
He's stating as it was written, and he's giving accounts literally from the book of Matthew.
So the book of Matthew was the only book that was around for 30, you could stretch 40 years, and the rest of what you read, you know, Mark, Luke, and John, and the writings of Paul, were 30 years later.
So now you're looking at a...
Oh, I would say that common, I don't know, historians would say that it's around A.D. 70, that most of what they refer to as the New Testament was...
Sure, I'm being conservative, but that's a long time where you have one...
No, certainly, absolutely.
And then all of a sudden, you have a movement that takes place near the end of the first century, that everything is up in the air.
Meaning, the very threat of Judaism becoming extinct is very possible, because a lot of people are catching on to what just happened.
Right?
And you have a lot of competent scribes, people with abilities, even though Jerusalem was destroyed, and they were scattered up until, let's say, the northwest part of the country there, there were still competent scholars and competent scribes to preserve these things.
A lot of people got involved, and if I say there were hundreds, if not thousands, of these texts put together, Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John, the writings of Paul, by the end of the first century, mostly in Aramaic, and some Greek was coming out then, right?
And all that.
So, that's basically the history of it, but there is a Hebrew and Aramaic primacy to this.
I mean, there's so much history, but it's all blurred, because none of it can be confirmed, because what the best confirmation is, is if I tell you, Seth, you go five miles east, and you make a left, you're going to see a white building, there's something physically there, yet you can confirm it.
So the only confirmation we can have on these things now, other than what other people have written, is archaeological proof, or physical proof, right?
Certainly.
And would older texts being found and made public be considered archaeological proof?
Like, how does one study what is actually memorialized, if that's what one wants?
Well, what's interesting is, the Dead Sea Scrolls, for example, confirming that the delivered Masoretic text at a rate of about 99.5%, can be confirmed to the 2nd century B.C., is a big deal.
Like the Isaiah scroll.
Absolutely.
One can presume that if you looked at Genesis, if you found what you see in Hebrew, let's say in Genesis now, if you found a scroll that was 2,000 years old, it would say pretty much the same thing.
That's a very strong presumption.
So now, what's lacking in the New Testament is the presumption that how we have what we have is the real thing.
And I'm telling you it's not, other than it's what you've got.
But the Greek can almost be as accurate, or loosely accurate, as the King James.
You have to go back to the primacy of the Aramaic, and dare I say Hebrew, but not Hebrew put in with the Greek, as you have now in some little spots.
I'll give you another example.
There are writings where complete sets of the New Testament, or fairly complete sets of the New Testament, were discovered in the 1.5 centuries A.D., and were destroyed by rabbis because it had the sacred name in there.
And if it did not have the YHWH in there, they would have left them alone.
Because they viewed it as something...
Oh yeah, there's writings, Talmudic writings and historical, that they would capture these guys to get all their scrolls, and they would burn them, because they had the father's name in there.
And when you look in the modern text today, you see Theos in the Greek, you don't have any of that.
Yeah, Theos.
Yeah, so there's Archidios, which is Zeus.
Which just means it's a title like Lord, but to the Greeks, when you said Kidios, that was Zeus.
So, there's many levels to this.
What I'm curious about is...
See, what I focus on is prophecy.
If anyone's ever listened to Greek speak, I'm into prophecy.
And it's good to focus.
In the amount of time that's left, in the amount of lawfulness that has to be instilled or considered by humanity, in order for the kill shots to be lawful, because if the gods came and administered the kill shots, and no one knew what the hell was going on, or who was doing it, it would be unlawful.
You're going to have a bunch of sniveling humans at the resurrection.
Who's law, though?
Like lawful to El Shaddai?
Who's doing it?
Because remember, when you read...
Elohim?
Yes, when you read about the, let's say, the destruction of man's society, what they call apocalyptic literature from the Bible, who's doing the destruction?
Is it the good guys, the good Elohim, or the bad Elohim?
Is it the evil spirits, or the good spirits?
It's the good spirits that are doing it.
It's the good spirits, unless we're talking strictly about Revelation and viewing the horsemen or their equivalent as...
Remember, there's horsemen in Zechariah as well.
Everyone tends to forget those.
But their horsemen are always around.
That's another thing.
We should get into all these topics, right?
They could be viewed as being good, absolutely, and yet they're put in charge, or their contract is basically to eliminate X amount of humanity.
Right.
And by the way, the ones that remain are not necessarily special, either.
They're just a representative sample.
It's kind of like when you move horses in a trailer.
You don't want to put too many of them in there, because if they panic, they'll hurt each other.
So you want to limit their number so you could deal with them.
It's not that the gods can't come back now and manage society.
It's that there'll be so much of a panic that people will just start killing each other for no reason.
So at least if you have a slim, spaced out, minor population, they're easier to manage for their own good.
I mean, they could still be managed now, but anyway, that's a whole other speculation.
Yeah, but that's anthropomorphizing the logistical restrictions that we have based upon the physical constraints that we find ourselves in.
Subjecting the evolution to that seems absurd.
The gods do consider it.
If they willed to take a trillion versus willing to take a thousand, it seems that they would just address it and do it as they willed as opposed to sticking to the constrictions of the arbitrary physical existence that we find ourselves in.
Sure, but you know what's interesting?
When you study the way the Elohim do things, and you study creation, you know, the natural world, they do work in accordance with it, right?
Like, for example, when they do things to mankind, why do they need to send a special, you know, how the Greeks would have a spear, an arrow, or a shield of Athena, something that unique to do the damage, why?
Why don't they just use the natural world?
Just send a flood over here.
Just send fire down over here.
It makes sense that they would use the natural world.
They don't have to send a special envoy or a special unique object.
Certainly, but at times they do.
I mean, there's a lot, right?
They send a special envoy, it's a lot.
Oh, no, I mean, like, and also what was used was a natural element, you know, to do it.
It wasn't anything very unique.
So once you understand that they work within the physical realm, but here, we've gotten off the subject.
The point is, how much of the New Testament, what's known in the New Testament, is going to be revealed to humanity, and it's true, let's say, how its intent, whether its intent intact, right, to humanity.
So they lawfully understand who the Christ is, right, because they will, right, for a short time, and then they're going to, you know, turn away from it, right?
So that's the main curiosity that I have is how much validation or verification of the true identity of the Messiah or the Christ in typical English-speak colonialism do people have to know about?
Well, I would speculate highly that the current J-E-S-U-S character and religion that's formed under that will have to go away, because it was totally in conflict with the scriptural one, the biblical one, and the historical one, right?
So, in other words, at this point, I can only speculate on the events coming in the future that either directly or indirectly are a product of, you know, real knowledge of the New Testament, right?
Right, certainly.
I suppose I'm just kind of grasping at what is there.
Like I see, you know, a fruit that I would like to partake of, you know, and that's, I suppose, a multi-sided metaphor.
Well, the thing like with Sam, do the best with what you've been given, right, first.
Right, certainly, but at the same time, it's like if you were given a piece of information,
and this piece of information could benefit a number of other people, and you share this information with them,
and they shrug it off, you know, that's on them, but what if the information that you were given,
that you were sharing with people is wholly inaccurate or completely falsified or, you know,
what's the stuff that's really good for growing flowers?
Bullshit.
Right.
Well, what if that happens?
I mean, that's part of the mix until the time is right.
But what I'm suggesting here is there's going to be a time where there will only be accurate, precise information, and only enough where then mankind can be lawfully considered to go to the next level.
No, absolutely, and not only do I comprehend that, I understand it, but at the same time, if at the same time we're not in that time currently, then grasping – are we grasping at straws here?
It's like I try to observe the beast, I try to observe the time of day.
If you ask a random person on the street what day is it, you know, like, but at the same time, so if everything that is being shared is false, and all of humanity is under a delusion, being intentionally deceived, I would say that we are, to one aspect or another, everyone is shared – there is false information shared so profusely at this point in time.
But it's nothing different.
This is what is the fulfillment of the Gentiles, the nations, you know, all the various sons of gods and all the deities is still around.
But what I'm suggesting, and I have for the past few years, is starting in 2018 in the spring, in the next seven years, is the precursor to the formation of the final power structure of mankind on Earth.
And within this next seven years is also the precursor and the introduction to the lawfulness that's required for mankind to know, just like when the Christ said, this will be preached and then I will return, that time has not yet come.
But the deception, what you see now, actually, I think, what I see is the very fact that things that people held true, in many ways, is starting to either be sloughed off as not important, or starting to be rejected by a few, is just laying the groundwork for more things to be rejected and more things to be considered untrue.
And then there will be an amount of lawfulness accepted and acknowledged by people, and then it's all going to swing the other way, right?
Then the major deception, because when you read scripture, it's not about you, it's about the gods.
So when they tell you there's a deception, it's not, you know, you're being deceived by the taxing authorities, or your mom, or the doctor, it's being deceived regarding what subject?
Regarding the gods.
Certainly.
I would say that if you were reading scripture, that it does pertain to you.
I mean, if you have access to this information, be it, you know, if it's set in front of you, or if it's shoved down your throat when you're younger, having access to this information, having access to any information incurs a responsibility.
Even if that responsibility is simply choosing to accept or reject that information, you know?
Water is good for you, okay.
Water is good for you, or water is bad for you, you know?
I mean, that's a choice, but what it seems, and I suppose something that I struggle with personally,
is that if all of the information that is being presented is false, or based upon false information one way or the other,
then the idea of choice, the idea of responsibility, both of those ideas, things that make us what we are,
as opposed to just another animal on this planet, very, very, they're lessened.
And there is inquiry, but if the inquiry is answered with half-truths, or information that is based upon false things, then there is no choice between right and wrong, unless you pull that back to the instinct.
And if it's all simply instinct, then we are no different than the animals, but we have eyes.
A simple way to say it is, you've been underwater.
Okay, that's fine.
I've been underwater.
You ever try reading a book or inquiring on information and studying underwater?
You'd be like, you know, dude, that sounds kind of like arduous.
Let's go up to the surface and dry off.
You're living in the age of the Piscean, the fish.
You're underwater.
You might as well, everyone might as well have gills.
The deluge seems to be of information currently.
But it's no, well, yes, but it's not information about the gods yet.
It is a little bit, I've been saying for years, there'll be more attention in that direction.
It won't be any accuracy or precision, but at least you're being set up.
Just like with 9-11, everyone was set up for 30 years that the Arabs are terrorists, even though there were no Arabs involved, unless they just happened to be around, right?
Oh, yeah, way back when Arafat was in the news and things like that.
I grew up with that image in my mind.
And they created Al-Qaeda in 1996 with the Khobar Towers being nuked and all that.
But here's the thing.
Right now, from video games all the way to the man on the street to anything, there's talk about just the very fact that there being a caliphate-based army, ISIS or whatever that's religious-based, is enough to get people focusing on what's called spirituality.
And that focus then, once the entire category is established where people no longer balk at, well, they're doing that for religious purposes, when that becomes normal, then the other stuff starts to get injected in, which is going to lead the next seven years, basically, to watch.
But the interesting thing, okay, let me just sum up what I have to say, I think, based on the intent or the sentiment of what you're trying to bring forward, is the reason why there's so much deception and all this other stuff are several.
And many of them are obvious, many of them are not.
So the ones that are not obvious is that in classical human education, when you deal with a master, the master will deliberately deceive you to see if you've learned the lesson.
This is done in martial arts, for example, with samurai training and things like that, right?
So what's going on right now is there's never been a time where, like I was mentioning earlier, if you were out in public a thousand years ago saying that you want to observe biblical feasts anywhere in the world, pretty much, you would be killed for that, as a witch or as a heretic, right?
Especially in the Western European society.
So now that's not true.
But you've got really poor quality versions, but you know what?
How difficult is it to grab an interlinear with inquiry and start getting a pretty firm handle on this?
It's not that difficult, really.
So the intent here is, yeah, is there deception?
But so what?
That just means the master is getting closer and closer.
And here's the other thing.
The malevolent spirits, even the great adversary, is still doing marching orders from the Most High.
I know it's kind of hard for people to believe that.
No, that's a very important point to make, actually.
Something I've asked you in passing.
It's been quite a while.
There's time that has passed.
But is that our – everything, everyone is a servant of the Most High, whether they are doing it willingly, unwillingly, think that they are – what do they call themselves currently?
The Satanists?
The secular humanists and things like that?
Everyone, all things, all time, all occurrence, everything is a servant of the Most High.
I wouldn't say direct.
When you read scripture, by the way, that is a more direct, poignant – that is focused on a certain group of people.
So when you understand that the scriptures are focused on a certain group of people, and then within there, there's a servant mentioned, that would be more like a servant in someone's house.
Just like the metaphor of a house is given consistently in scripture, right?
But what I'm suggesting is that entire creation is under the control of the Creator.
There is no rogue spirit running around that is all-powerful.
There are rogue spirits running around, yes, but they're not all-powerful, and they could be shut down in a nanosecond if the Creator wanted to.
But their ability to interfere with the Creator – and I mean interfere as in to get in the way of or to change the direction of something – that doesn't exist.
No, it doesn't exist.
That's right.
So anything that they do or anything that they can cause to happen by rote would be the will of the Creator.
By allowance.
Well, it doesn't even have to be direct allowance, but He already knows what's going to happen, so you could loosely say by will.
And I do.
I'm certainly using the term loosely, but I don't know if it's important.
It's an interesting thing to me to realize or to have that lightbulb, that euphemistic lightbulb, that if the El Shaddai, if the Most High, is omnipresent or – what is the word they use?
Omnipotent.
Omnipotent is all-powerful.
Omniscient is all-knowing.
Omnipresent, everywhere.
That's why when you read Scripture, it's the only…
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
It's the only thing you could read where the author is always present, right?
Right.
Yes.
If that is the case, then we as a people are missing the concreteness, the heaviness, the weight that there is to that point, and that being that all are serving whether they are acknowledging it or not.
Yeah, but there's different levels too of servants, right?
Certainly.
Well, and within that, I don't mean to remove free will or choice from the equation, because that is our experience.
That is – we have our will, and we are able to live up to it.
But thinking that that will is outside of what is possible through the Creator would be false.
Well, a simple way to say it is that for people that think that it's all free will, it's not.
They're going to be in surprise.
And for people that think that there is no free will, well, they're going to be in surprise in how much free will they actually had.
Right.
You see, so there's a middle – it's just like when I come out and I say about creation and evolution, both what you hear about creation is wrong, and what you hear about evolution is wrong, so there is no side.
So I'm kind of one of these oxymoronic – that's why they're morons and then they're oxymorons, right?
– about all this stuff that's going on.
I see the moot point.
Another thing is economics.
It's echo comics, because there is no money.
What are they talking about?
What economy?
It's all credit, right?
So it's echo comics, not economics.
There's nothing new to address.
People say, what do you think of cryptocurrency or the economy?
What economy?
It's credit, man.
You've got these creatures called attorneys and government agencies.
They were all in a panic earlier today, just following what little news there is.
They were all in a panic today, and then they were not, and it was echo comical to watch.
Echo comical, yeah.
It's all ridiculous, and the thing is set apart.
It's a planet full of assholes.
Sorry to use that physically, not to derogatory that part of the body that preserves…
It's useful.
It has a very natural function.
If anybody is listening to this somehow and they're cruising in their star cruiser, just go hang out at Saturn or Mars or the Moon.
Don't even bother.
There's nothing going on here.
Not until later.
Certainly.
On the back of the Moon, yeah, turn around is your last chance before you go into oxymorons and oxymorons.
That's all you got.
And it's shameful.
I say I'm ashamed to be called human.
That's because you've observed what humans do.
All of them, with very little exception.
I mean, the exceptions are so small that statistically it's irrelevant.
And by the way, if anyone's hearing this and you have problems in your life, it's not you.
It's the people around you.
Sorry.
And I'm taking a presumption that you're inquiring on what's right and what's wrong, which is, you know, it's pretty safe not to just be a contraire, but it's the opposite.
I would almost proffer my own experience as adding to the credence of what you just said.
Yeah, and all these, it's funny because they have these life coaches and gurus and psychologists and spiritualists telling you, oh, it's you.
It's your outlook.
No, it's sorry.
You'll find out.
You'll be surprised about that later.
So, just hold tight.
Again, can you read underwater?
You're underwater.
It's not a good thing.
But you know what is good?
Getting up in the middle of the night to go get a drink of water and not stubbing your toe on the chair.
That's good.
Dogs, man.
Dogs are good.
I really enjoy the company of dogs, be it mine or any that I run into on the street.
Well, the animal intelligence is something that I appreciate by the minute.
It grows every minute for the past two decades or decade and a half.
The more I inquire about reality, the more I appreciate the animal intelligence.
Well, it appears that at one time, that's what we experienced ourselves.
Well, here, this is again the salient point.
We're open almost 100% input, we have to be told.
But the animals, where do they get their spirit?
So they're getting some kind of quote-unquote divine download.
If you want to witness how the divinity works when they work directly through something, look at an animal.
Well, who taught a bird its song?
Well, there's a lot of equation throughout the equation and equivalence to gods represented in the animal form.
Not just in places like Egypt, but throughout the Greeks.
Well, what you're witnessing is what I mean by download is who taught them how to do what they do.
It's download, so it's like getting the computer with the operating system and all that and the program already pre-downloaded without you interfering, without the human question enabling it, you see.
Yeah, certainly.
So if you really want to see what the gods are up to, go see, be a little Dr. Dolittle if you want.
Check out the animals and who taught them what they do.
I mean, I know there's a school of fish, but there's…
There was a contentious moment in chat earlier actually where we were talking about there being mean dogs.
I was saying that there are not mean dogs.
There are dogs that have been taught to be mean.
And insecure.
There are feral dogs.
There are wild dogs that are acting purely on instinct, but there are also domesticated dogs that have been taught that if you show me a domesticated dog that is mean, I will show you a person that should probably not be allowed to have in their possession dogs.
Sure.
Yeah, improper use of a tool, let's say, if the dog is mean.
Yeah, and also maybe that dog feels like he's unemployed.
Dogs always have to feel like they're doing something.
They're a pack animal.
So anyway, I think we've been burning up the bits and the bites and all that enough for tonight.
I don't know how much can be gleaned off of all these hours of talk.
Hopefully something.
Well, I apologize if I got into my own personal pursuits and whatnot.
That's fine.
There's others similar.
Save it for a time where there didn't seem to be a particular subject being discussed.
But yeah, thanks for your time, Greg.
I appreciate it.
No sweat.
And thanks, Bruce, and anyone who cares to listen to this.
I don't think any of it should be listened to by anyone.
So listen to this stuff at your own risk.
And I guess that's the only disclaimer I could come up with at the moment.
Well, I want to thank you both and Sam also.
And we had 27 listeners on the stream tonight at peak.
And so the word is getting out there.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
If we talk about politics and Bitcoin, maybe we'll get 5,000, right?
The dummy load, right?
Yeah.
It's just bizarre.
Okay.
Interesting subjects as all.
Yeah, there's so little.
Here's the interesting thing about tearing down and building and all that other stuff that is part of the reality.
I don't think there's anything.
To me, I see no value in building or breaking down or whatever.
If I just skate through till my last breath, I'll be totally successful because there's nothing else to do.
I'm just watching this madness.
So anyway, just guys, be safe and whatever.
Thanks again.
Well, again, thanks for your time.
I appreciate it.
Thanks for letting me come on and join into the conversation.
Sure.
And I've gotten lots of private messages.
People were interested in having you on again.
So thank you for doing that.
All right.
Well, good night.
Good night, Bruce.
Good night, Seth.
Good night, everyone else.
Good night, both of you.
Be well.
And good night, folks.
And be well, all of you.