There's a reconciliation between quote-unquote Israel and Judah and the modern-day Philistines to the point Where you cannot discern them apart.
They almost almost acting as brothers It sounds insane when you look at the current situation, right?
Are you familiar with these verses that I just brought up?
I haven't studied them, but I know of them.
Okay, so the fate of the modern-day Palestinian or modern-day Philistine is very very interesting because believe it or not.
They are destroyed by the way When what that kingdom come right?
They are destroyed if you remember the verses about that utterly, right?
But before that time they act in unison with Israel That's another thing to watch and I think in short I've given how that's going to happen the the Gaza Strip is gonna just explode in terms of you know size Back to its older borders.
There will be no Palestinians in the contended West Bank
like there is now and
If you know if you're Palestinian you live in the West Bank or know anyone there get out
You've got a buffer zone of several years, maybe four to five years seven years tops
You don't want to be there
so
But you will have a pretty cushy
Compared comparatively to now the Gaza Strip will expand all the way to Tel Aviv and beyond
Towards, you know the land inward much much more and south southward
And you will be considered a state and all this other stuff so
Though that's that's believe it or not
Other than the it watching Israel and Judah the Palestinians or the modern-day Philistines are very important to watch in terms of the geopolitical
prophetic position that they're going to have with Israel, so
Yes
Mm-hmm.
And the other thing is you really got to focus on East going West meaning look at Iran Persia.
What's going on there?
Don't take it lightly Of course they've been demonized because what one of the right from a juke from a secular point of view Iran will always be demonized as long as their central bank is state-owned.
I'm going to repeat that again.
I know it's not it's not conspiratorial It's the truth the central bank the fiat currency the credit line that is issued in Iran to their citizens and subjects is Issued by the state not a private bank like everywhere else Like, you know, North Korea same thing the state owns the bank, right?
Somalia same thing that's why those places are on the hit list
Because these are really show you the people that run the world are shallow minded idiots in case you didn't get it
The people that run the world are shallow minded idiots, I didn't say they're stupid
But they do I mean obviously you can say that about most of them so I think Somalia got taken out though
Yeah, they did yeah, but they still have a feudal I don't think they have a centralized system at all there
That's feudal lords like the Congo, you know, I think right isn't Congo still the same you're so feudal
It's a broken up into like 300 different
Districts or something
Anyway
well, the reason to watch Persia is because they are going to be
Let me just not say what they're going to be let me say what they are
Who are the two superpowers in the Middle East right now?
Persia and Israel Iran and Israel Right now they're gonna work together.
Actually, they are working together behind the scenes.
That sounds a little conspiratorial But Here's the only thing that I admire the Persians or the Iranians for is They have a very subdued way of showing the West they can do and have everything the West has and how do I know that?
When a couple of years ago when they took down there was a fire in Tehran something called the Plasco building a
Mine a minute minor fire and the building imploded exactly technically and scientifically the same way the World Trade Center did
Which was using an underground nuclear demolition charge
exactly
Now most people don't know that but the was a message a clear message from the Iranian government to say
We can do it just like you do it, but we're not going to do, you know
These huge buildings and incinerate 3,000 people were just vaporized 3,000 people
We're just going to do it with this, you know, what was the tallest building in Tehran, you know a while back
We're just gonna do it and just you know, maybe kill 50 or 100
But we can do it exactly the same way you do it and its scale doesn't matter just that we can do it
you see
So
Yeah, look up the Plasco building it just it just it had you know, it's interesting
Crackling sound and you know, most people don't know anything about even professors that are nuclear physicists
Don't know anything about nuclear atoms or or you know atomic energy or anything like that, you know
But if you want to go work in the nuclear field
You you are taking they laugh at you and it doesn't matter if you have 15 PhDs
Which is probably not possible to get it is laugh at you like dude.
Just shut up.
You were gonna this is how it really works Okay so Yeah So what they're doing the Persia is showing that Iran is showing the West that we can do everything you can do What we don't have to do it as big and we're not as spread out But we have the ability and who else who else in the Middle East can do anything just as well as anyone else can do it Israel Right.
Israel's got nukes.
Israel's got jets
They've got a mountain that opens up like in Switzerland where the Jets shoot out of you like an aircraft carrier, you know
They've got technology they've got
Where with all the finances all this
So those two those two are going to be working together and when I say working together predominantly in what
The temple being rebuilt there's going to be a strong seal of approval from the current
Government let's just say use it loosely I spell that government G UV MNT
Government of Iran assisting the building of the temple or the real estate
Because remember when you read in the Himalayan Ezra it was taking control of the real estate with finances and and
protection, right
Because the Persians didn't build the temple
They just provided a the protection or B and B the real estate wherewithal
You see right if you recall in the Himalayan Ezra
We're no Persians building the temple
But without them it couldn't have been done because of they needed protection and they needed the finances
So, do you think right now if a temple were to be built let's say south of the
Where the current dome of the rock is they're going to be Muslims
Screaming about it.
Yeah Do you think that if Persia or Iran steps in and quells that it'll make it easier to build the temple Because they're Muslim Even though it's a different sect.
Let's say yes.
Do you see how this can be rationalized?
Do you see that if you ponder?
How is Israel going to help?
How is your Iran going to help Israel in the next seven years if you really sit down with a fine-toothed comb and look at?
All the current geopolitics and look at biblical prophecy You can actually write a pretty detailed scenario That'll be probably plus or minus five or ten percent off from what is going to happen in the next seven years With great detail How it's going to happen using you know?
You have to understand human rationale and the way you understand human rationale is just look at what's on the rectangle what people are talking about And their mindset and that's all going to change.
I just gave you one little scenario there How can Iran help modern-day Israel build the temple?
Well if they try to do it now Muslim Muslim to the left Muslim to the right and oops we just stepped on a Christian over here, what's that on your shoe and Do you think?
Persia or Iran helping to jump in and quelling that kind of dissent would help of course.
That's just one way I Mean there's other ways to but See if I went to the mailbox and there was a hundred donations of us a significant amount I'd say let's let's get the brightest and the best people around to look at what's going on and look at these things They don't have to try to figure out prophecy.
You just spell it out for them.
This is objective is what it says Let's put something a scenario together on what's coming in you know in the next seven years.
Let's do that It takes a lot of time by the way to do that All right to look at all the various happenings and mastinations in the current day world because Believe it or not when this prophecy starts to come in fruition.
It's going to happen in line with what we see happening today You know we don't see video games and plasma TVs and iPhones and all this other stuff in Scripture But when the prophecies do take place these things plot You know iPhones and video and plasma TV all this stuff is going to exist so that has to be integrated in also you see You know what I mean?
So this this someone needs to sit down and
Objectify what's written in the prophecies read out of it and start picking up
You ever see those those arcade games where you put a quarter in and you have this hook
Robotic arm moves around you try to pick up a prize and drop it in you know
You know whatever so you understand the prophecy which is the robotic arm now you have to start picking up all the pieces that you
See around you iPhones video games the current central banking situation jet airplane everything that you see in the world today and
rearrange it
To fit prophecy I didn't say rearrange prophecy to fit the world today
Rearrange all the various appliances in your modern world including the mindset as an appliance of people
How would you move it left or right up or down in and out?
What do you eliminate?
What do you add in order for prophecy to take place, and then you will be able to compile that and have a really accurate Forecast of what's coming down the road But I ain't spending eight hours a day for the next six months to do that you know Other people have to do it, and there's no support on something like this by the way As far as I see right now.
Do you see what I mean by that Sam and Bruce yes?
You You have no license to rearrange the prophecies to fit what's going on But you have a hundred percent license to rearrange what's happening what you see going on around you to fit prophecy It's the other way around details Yeah, there are a lot of details, and it can be done.
I've done it before with certain things You know Well like I mentioned earlier when the Arab Spring happened in 2011.
I was like oh wow look at Egypt big deal Is there a woman ready to take office?
Nope?
Yeah?
It's just a a Precursor to the precursor you see I had people say oh look the Middle East Union is gonna form it after the spring thing on that No, no, no, it's not So yeah, it's pretty interesting there's a lot of a lot of work to be done if you want to do it Should it it's these things don't have to be done what I just mentioned piecing all these things together They don't have to be done.
You know why because they're gonna happen whether you do it or not anyway, right?
That's why they don't have to be done You know it's not like organizing the shed.
You know if you don't do it.
It's not gonna happen anyway No, you if you don't do it ain't gonna happen This is something that whether you understand it or not whether you piece it all together in parallel to what's going on to make it Work yes, you can do that You don't have any license to change scripture, but you have lots of license to change What's going on in the world around you obviously?
I mean, that's why I've come out and said like in the next less than a decade if you know anyone That's invested in pork futures get out because it's ain't gonna ain't gonna be viewed as a food anywhere That doesn't make any sense right?
Because they loved that pork So You're seeing more and more hardies closing down lately Yeah So You know why would I say that you know because there?
It's very more than implied that the whole world's going to be going under Some form of harsh biblical law and biblical law is very clear on that pork issue But people don't want to hear that because the only time people want to listen is if you're coming to take bacon off day back They know somebody's coming to take bacon off day back.
They'll they'll stop and listen.
They'll scatter
Yeah, am I implying that they're pigs yes, I am so
What I'm going to what I'm going to just say about prophecy is
That again
And I haven't said this this clearly before is you can go ahead and rearrange what's going on right now in front of you on
The rectangle news and society mindset and all that but you can't rearrange the prophecies there you see so how do you rearrange the current?
Ephemeral world which changes into to make it fit
You know the like and you know how you pour water into an ice cube tray
If that ice cube tray is full you stick it in the freezer when you take it out
You're gonna get the exact shape
That was in that ice cream ice cube tray no matter what where before you poured it
And it was could have been anything that water any shape
So prophecies like the ice cube tray, and what's what you see going on in the world today everything whether it's your own personal life or
International is the water
Mmm.
Can you pour it in your mind into the ice cube tray?
Which is prophecy and see what it looks like after a day in the freezer pop it out you see But you can't take a Dremel to the ice cube tray and start changing it.
That's the prop you know what I mean And you can't make things fit you can't take a square peg and say well I'm gonna whittle it down to make it round so it fits in the right hole.
No you can't do that Either I'm saying about rearranging things around you know How do you like you know how many times have I said?
The end what you see on the internet is a beta test.
How do I know because it's commercially driven But the presence of the Internet offers what?
Instant sight and sound to anyone in the world that has a handheld device pretty much doesn't it so
That's what you carry over into the prophecy side
The ability for anyone on the world or in you know by the way to look we were speaking of Africa was watching a cooking
documentary recently and they were in Ethiopia and the people lived they had a dirt floor in their house, right and
But through the door I saw a child about eight nine ten with a
Device in their hand you know looking down on it
So the people there had so what does that tell you the they're going to get a handheld?
Rectangle with internet before they're going to get a tile a finished floor Right yeah Now is it do you think that they got that so they can buy stuff on eBay or?
Just the ability for them to have instant audio and visual communication the latter obviously So that's what I mean Yeah, that's what I mean right.
That's what I mean about you can restart rearranging these things around People say you know the Internet's gonna be shut down.
No.
It's not he's of course not good for two reasons one is you know the Later on it's gonna be necessary necessity later on and also right now If the Internet shut down how our banks gonna do anything right Shuts down the bank, so it's not gonna happen So you could look at various things that people discuss and you're like oh That's never gonna happen and the ever that's left.
You know when I say never I mean in the ever that you have So if you if some if you know someone lives till 70 And you'll say you're never gonna be in the Olympics You know because you know let's say walking with crutches all their life.
That's pretty accurate statement You know what I mean right Because you know they are within the ever that when you're discussing this with someone you know they have an ever that's about 70 80 90 And in there's you know see so So when I say never I mean within the ever that you have This kind of talk by the way will piss off your average space heater so Yes, so from my end.
I mean I sort of
The only thing I really have left that I could I guess
Bring to the discussion at this point is the rest of the thoughts that I have on the least matter of the countries
I mean if you're tired because sometimes you know I pour the Greek with my pedantic presentation thing
We don't we would need to be redundant if we're just gonna focus on what we see now
Well, I you know I I loosely define boredom as being anger, so are you pissing me off?
I wouldn't say you've ever pissed me off, and I don't think you intend to so and you haven't and you are not so
well
Well now to find the last thing
Was them the mountains of a short thing I think
hmm
Either way, I mean if you let's say southern that's a north-south range isn't it or runs north-south
Right I'm not sure what the mountains of a shore are because I think a shore you tie that to a Syria
And once again like I said the
Caucasus mountains see are connected with that because the Empire extended that far
You also have the Zagreb how do you pronounce it the Zagreb or Zagreb mountains?
But I think that that's in a completely different place so I Don't really know what it is, but either way when you look at Ezekiel 3535 you have the the Ludd What was it the the kush the put and the Ludd being talked about I think it's a mistranslation That's just oh really really.
I'm being sarcastic now Well, it's not New Testament where it's like obvious that shit is not right almost all of it's not right Yeah, so at least I'll tell you what New Testament almost no one's impression of it is right that I've seen So the text itself shouldn't be completely blamed.
I think it's what the New Testament has done is
satisfied the
Fulfillment of utter freakin evil in the world taking hold before these things take place you know
So evil what the gods think is evil you know when you have these idiots running around there
You got to love everybody in peace that that you know the root of that is completely evil you know
Right because they can't define any of it
So it's just as good as them not knowing what you know not saying that and and then if you eliminate that they have nothing
They're just jellyfish so
But go ahead
Yeah, I think it's a mistranslation load and usher.
I think Ludd is actually Ludden
Because like I said, they're similar, and they seem to get mixed up
It feels like a scribal error because the people of Ludd like I said you tie them more to the Lydians which is
Anatolia and the people of Ludden
Are more that's a son of Mithrim
Son of an Egyptian the Luddite the Luddite people have already been pointed out as being adjacent to Egypt
I don't see how you know Ludd is a shaman is is related to the Africans
and if you look like
What's it called?
King of the dirge against the king of Tyre and is equal 37
So Tyre is a coastal city in modern Lebanon
And it says Persia and Ludd and put were in your army they were men of war shield and helmet
They hung on you and so on and so forth
So Persia obviously at the time of the neo-babylonians was very far from Tyre
And put is in North Africa
so it sounds like they have these are just mercenary soldiers that are brought in from foreign countries to strengthen Tyre's armies and
That would make Ludd another far-off country
Presumably in Western Anatolia that I see how that how that can work
But if you look at Ludden, you know, Jeremiah 46 verse 1 talks about
Something the word of Yahweh came to the Prophet Jeremiah concerning the Gentiles for Mithrim
Concerning the Pharaoh Naco
Prepare the large and small shield and draw near to battle Mithrim rises like a flood in its water surge abroad the rivers
And let the mighty men go forth cush and put who handle the shield and Ludd who handle
the bend and the bow in this sort of situation
You have Yahweh telling Pharaoh to go to war and to take some people with him to Kushites and the putites which wouldn't live
close by and
cushioned Libya and the Ludd who are
Archers and so here it makes sense that you have sort of three adjacent African countries that you know, he takes to war with him
and it's the same thing in the book of Nahum Kush and Egypt were her strength and
Put and Lubbom were your helpers talking about the downfall of Nineveh
so here again put and Lubbom are ancient Libya and Kush and
And
Lubbom here is very clearly shown to be in association with that
so
Everyone if you knew you were going to be attacked by the Assyrians and you didn't capitulate.
Who did you go to for help?
you always Egypt and their allies Right their allies.
Yeah Yeah, you know when you look at these military things by the way campaigns.
No one wants to use their own people Look at the American Army You know, I mean or any army, you know, I mean smaller armies yes that are great, you know, you know Indigenously based are of the people but you know when you're you're in business to do war you have foreigners in your army, right?
Yeah, I'm seeing that So moving on from that in the same Ezekiel 35 it goes on to talk about all the mixed people cushion put and load and all the mixed people and the curb and the sons of The land of the Covenant shall fall.
This is talking about when the Antichrist invades North Africa But it's um, it puts this all the mixed people phrase in there Followed by the nation of Cooper.
I can't find anything on curb really most commentary say it's close to Egypt, but that's just guesswork
But the the mixed people bit is interesting because in English it says all the mixed people but in the Hebrew, it's only one word
which is Arab or
Depending on the vocalization, so it's only three letters
And it's the same word for a bunch of different things
It's the same word depending on the vocalization for the nation of Arabia
It's the same word for the one of the chiefs of the Midianites, which is in Arabia same word for evening
Or dusk what they're calling that same word for the raven
Which is a dark colored bird and then also for mixture, which is why they're rendering it as a mixture
now
Arabia by the way, you know the UAE Saudi Arabia all those
Qatar all those places there.
They're they're not going to go away there They're you know what?
I mean, there's they're very wealthy because of the way they've been dealt from the Balfour Accords and all that later on
You know early 20th century till later
If you study a little bit even cursory
the development
You know the actual real it let's just use the term real estate or building an industry, you know, which is basically there
They have oil and then they they're tourists, you know, and and you know, basically attractions, right?
if you if you study Who is actually building?
That part of the world all the architectural I go go look at some tacos online
They're there from India Asia
You don't see any
The there are people that are their own people that are working on are wearing the the white hard hats with the engineering badge
But the guys that are actually pouring the cement and
Piecing together the steel and the glass and all that are foreigners
all of them
And once all these projects are finished these public works or private works.
Do you think these foreigners?
All of them go home or do you think a fairly good percentage a little bit more than half but maybe around half stay They stay You know, unless they're actually, you know contracted in Exclusively lots of people to do crunch it How difficult would it be able to throw them in a uniform?
And give them a gun pretty pretty easy You know, it's very easy to look at any country that has an immigration population that comes in to do grunt work Well, that's your future army.
Those people stay there and they have children and you need people in the military.
Guess who's gonna go?
Look at America.
Yeah, you got a lot of white trash or whatever it's still enlisted in the military, but most of the military is a good significant portion say most is as foreigners Well, you can go to the to the next level and say well who in America is not a foreigner or the Native America who's Been genocided, you know, I'm not speaking on that.
I'm speaking about when you say America you think of a white boy white girl flat booty and Apple pie still and whatever, you know You know, I mean so, you know think about burritos and rice and beans and whatever You know, this reality is harsh folks So You don't have a lot.
Yeah, there's still a lot of white boys in the military, but I wouldn't say that that mill It's a white military just like this Yeah, when you look at this Saudis, this would be the same thing you in the future if they're if they're going to take any place in a tribal way or Cultural way or nationalistic way.
It's it's going to be a pretty mixed multitude Looking at the Arab or Arab word That gets used in a bunch of different places I mean It's the word that you have in Genesis 1 5 and the evening came to be in the morning came to be day one That is Arab And then you have other places that it's something else Is the top to emanate from the top of the house?
Hmm ERB The letter yeah, yeah So, um As far as trying to put that into context in the Ezekiel verse you kind of have to figure out what's being said There's a list of nations and if it's an Arab if we know that Arab is already used for Arabia Then I think you have a good candidate there and is the similarity between Arab and it's Arab a coincidence.
Not really.
I think it would be an olive not an Needs to be investigated Well, there's some you can provide some historical context and things like that I mean you find an interesting intersection between Greek Arabic and Hebrew when it comes to this particular word So it means evening or dark in one sense In the sense in Genesis, it's it was evening.
There was morning.
I mean there was morning There was evening and there was morning right that's in reverse almost right So there's a plane a Wall or a plane or a membrane when does morning end and when does evening start?
At noon you still see a lot of people used to hear when I used to listen to internet radio more The guy would come on and say good morning.
Oh, no, it's 1203.
I'm sorry.
Good afternoon Right.
Mm-hmm people almost have it as a strict application If it's by the wind-up toy within their limited stupidity If it's 1201 if they say good morning, they will catch themselves and say good afternoon.
Are you feeling me on that Bruce?
You ever notice that?
Yeah, if it's 12 if they see 1204 and they say good morning, they'll catch themselves up so say no, I'm sorry I meant afternoon
That it
Now there is a noon time when the Sun is absolutely thought had there's another word in Hebrew to describe that
But from a Genesis point of view, it's the point where morning ends evening ends and morning starts and vice versa
And that's at noontime for timekeeping purposes cause we're not but we're not saying that evening is the same as noon
No, generally it stretches all the way down till you go to sleep
Exactly from noontime till right before you go to bed
It's it's evening, you know, right because I mean if you go
I mean that word is obviously all over the place if you go to Exodus 16
It says and when they came to be evening, then the quail came and covered up the camp.
That's not That's specifically noon Yeah, because for quail to be out In other words, they covered the camp.
It's an unusual thing If you know about birds, they they're out between 7 and 10 and then they come out before dusk Hmm if you tell anyone the birds came out at noon and cover this a holy crap, that's a miracle Birds are around between said by the wind up to between 7 and 10 and then they come out again like after 4 or 5 For it till he was Bruce.
So you've ever been a bird you ever gone birding?
Oh, yeah Yep Specifics reasons why they do that mostly for food and foraging Yep early in the morning late in the afternoon or towards evening.
Yes.
Yeah Yeah, if you see him out at noon, it's yeah, it's rare Well, usually depending on the climate if it's very hot they seek to be out of the Sun For preservation kind of thing Yeah, other than the tropics, but I know but you're saying it's a range Temporal range.
Yeah, and it includes it includes sunset But here's another thing to consider whenever you're dealing with the first five books You're dealing with a there's a precision in the placement of the meaning and the word It means more than than what you're you know?
Oh, yeah I'm not I mean we've already seen especially in the first five different things it's it's not as poetic as the prophets get because you know what I mean poetic is if you have a Someone who likes to read and they've never read the Bible He told me to read the prophets who say what a bunch of whiny bastards.
These guys are you know?
That's what they come back say they don't understand it, right?
But when you have them read the first five books of Moses, they say oh, this is heavy-duty.
I don't understand it
You know, I mean, what does it make a lot of sense the big difference between edib used and in other places
Not a big difference, but the word still needs to be considered as it is in the law
And I'm not trying to divert from that
But I'm trying to draw sort of a general connection between the way that this word is used in one language in another language
So in a general sense
It's used to point to this
Range of time which includes say the setting of the Sun since evening extends beyond just your conventional 12
Sure, or whatever and then when you go to the Arabic language the word for the evening time or when the sunset is
Magrib, so let's go.
Let's go back in context.
You pull this is what you we've pulled out of Ezekiel, right?
Yeah, it's equal 35 as far as the mixed people.
I'm trying all right.
I'm getting to that But like to identify who they are because who are it says it just says the order or just as order as far as The Kush to put the load order and cope as far as the nations that are gonna fall once Egypt gets conquered and To sort of try to figure out what it's what it means by that Unless of course, it's completely redundant and You know not of any interest.
It's to be investigated Ezekiel's a funny book that way, you know Ezekiel's all over the place, right?
temporarily Yeah, it bounces around a little bit Sometimes I can't tell whether it's talking about the end times or talking about something in the past.
Yeah, or after the end times Yeah but um The Arab or his or his day I Think the easiest thing is his day Yeah, there's some stuff with that.
There's a lot of stuff in his day
But okay
so yeah, you have the
Like I said the Hebrew aspect of it of a certain time that includes the what they call the evening
You have the Arabic word for dark or evening being the crib which stems from
It's the which is where the Maghreb area gets its it's a word from in the Maghreb is the region of North Africa with the
Arab population
Which has itself three sort of interrelated meaning Maghreb means West
So in this case, I guess lands west of Egypt or lands west of the homeland of Arabia
It also means time or place of sunset since the Sun observably sets in the West
And it also means evening since the Sun sets in the evening
by conventional
Interpretation used to be considered.
Yep moving on from that you get to the Greek and in the ancient Greek the word for
What they used to call in North Africa was
Hesperia because of the Hesperides which was a mythological race of nymphs of the evening or of the sunset who lived in a garden that
Near the Atlas Mountains, which is a mountain range in the Maghreb in North Africa and Hesperia also means the Western countries
I think they used to call Italy
Hesperia also because it's directly west is west of Greece
So these references keep reoccurring in different languages to something in the West and something that happens around what they call the evening
So
I'm guessing that this Arab people that's being talked about in Ezekiel 30 or presumably either from
Indeed in North Africa or Arabia or descendants of Arabians living in North Africa, which is what we see today anyway
So it keeps things tied down to that region
And then after that it goes on to say that the men of the Covenant shall fall
And that's the last group of people
after all these Africans
But I don't know I guess the first thing I thought is whoever who's heard of a covenant people living in North Africa
Ezekiel's covenant land would have been Israel is what I initially thought but then I guess there's a two-sided way to go at that
One is that Abraham had children that he fathered with other women and the Midianites were one of their offspring or sort of
Nations later on down the line.
So the Arabs are technically part Shemitic
And also Josephus has given accounts that in
That there was a entire Arabic tribes that were converted to Judaism and began to worship as the Jews or the Judeans did
But you know that has me thinking like it's not really lawful if you force them
So I don't really know what was going on in his time that he would say that
He also wrote that there were Edomite
tribes that were
Also converted into Judaism, so
I'm not exactly sure how
They don't seem to be lawful at that point
Right, right a lot of conversions were you'll read about the conversions.
It was their political reasons, you know You know, like you've heard I forgot there's a term for it if you're not if you're conqueror subjected by Muslims Subjects of Muslim government.
There's a tax you pay if you're not Muslim, right?
I mean people people would sell their children for food right so If they you know in history or if they would sell Children to be sacrificed just for some coin so they can go and buy things, you know so if they're gonna do that, they'll you know, imagine you have a Jewish influence and they don't treat the non Jews.
Well, let's just say or the Judeans Well, you're going to convert just to be treated better Mm-hmm.
There's that aspect because you know the aspect of there being a genuine
Allegiance to the God of the Judeans is difficult for me to see for two reasons
One is well if if they did that then you know
Where how did they end up not well and also the Judean authorities were very hush-hush and
sequestered the general public from any knowledge of scripture and things like that in order to overlay their own laws, you know
Which were non-scriptural right?
This was done through history at least post temple, you know So, yeah You did end up with a group of people who called themselves anyway Jews or Israelites living in North Africa But I think yeah, that goes back even to the time of Solomon.
You know, yeah Sure, that was the other disgruntled priests let's say in their families or the families of the priests Because they couldn't leave their posts up until a certain age or whatever unless they've got totally, you know Discussed it by what's?
Solomon was doing which wouldn't be that difficult by the way
But there was a big diaspora scattering even back then always they always I
Think it was after Solomon, you know where there was
You know, they started leaving right Israel
You know the king and split with his son
Yeah, and all the massinations because they had some pretty cruel times there, you know
That's some pretty bad Kings that were doing some pretty crazy stuff
and
And also they remember they they promoted literacy and the sciences and when I say science
I mean, you know, I'm using modern terms with modern concepts here.
No, I mean, you know knowledge of the natural world medicine
Just net nature in general how to organize things engineering math that is, you know
money system economics
So if you left Judea or Israel and you went to another part of the world and you you know
The people that knew that you came from there invited you in usually
Because you were well learned usually
So was it was easy to spread around I
Mean look at for example now like play in India
I give it an example in India where they do promote a rigor of education of you know
Advanced math even in science, which even though it's not really
Viewed I don't view.
Well, it shouldn't be viewed.
Well, you'll find people from India going all over the world and getting technical jobs, right?
They're invited in because of their discipline
Yeah, the spreading of that culture and that quote-unquote style
You know, here's another thing Sam to consider when you say Judaism or we call you know in an inaccurate way Jewish modern-day
You know, we really have no idea what it was
Like what it was like back then because there were still so many sects that developed especially around 200 BC
right
Mm-hmm.
So all we can we you know was a sect that was known and I don't think they would they they it was easy for Them to travel and be welcomed or spread because of the actual just religious aspect.
I think it was because of their literacy in education level So when you see them spreading or Certain people being converted or whatever.
It was for literacy science medicine economics.
Do you see what I mean?
It wasn't it wasn't like, you know in America go to you know I believe in this go to church on Sunday or some stupid stuff like that was nothing like that Right, you ever notice with the modern Christian religion.
There's no literacy.
There's no promotion of Of the sciences the natural world economics any knowledge and anything like that.
It's just anyway fairies pixie-dust and So, you know, yeah people don't don't understand that because they're looking at the religions or you know, look at any other religions today Buddhism even Judaism today and all that they don't view that they view that solely as a religion.
They don't view that there's any attribute They look at the secular attributes now You know what the government, you know, the government demands you get like in India you'll get a by the sixth grade You'll get a math education that in America.
You will never get unless you go into advanced, you know college courses So But back in those days it was promoted, you know culturally in tradition through what we call today religion religious practices Right, yeah, so, um, that's kind of it.
I mean the conclusion I guess what's the only thing I have after that is the Ezekiel stuff
But it kind of like it's kind of hard for me to tell what it's happening
Like Ezekiel has prophecies about Egypt's as well as far as is equal 29 and 30
The land of Egypt shall be desolate and waste and they shall know that I am
Yahweh because he is the one who has the power to make the world a better place
He has said Pharaoh has said that the river is mine and I have made it and no foot of man shall pass through it for
40 years
so
Ubris, yeah, because yeah bristle their leaders
But this was something that Ezekiel was saying specifically at a particular time and most people
Commentators have felt like the 40 years that's being talked about here
Happened in the 6th century when Nebuchadnezzar ran through the place and supposedly destroyed
What's the context of that being brought up it sounds more futuristic doesn't it it does
But it appears to be past
Here's the thing the canonized Egyptology puts the 26th dynasty of Egypt in power at that time and even the Greek
Herodotus said that the
Egyptian priests and monuments and stuff that the 26th dynasty did
That that stuff was in the indicative of a more prosperous Egypt
And so there's no way that
Nebuchadnezzar could have ran through the place and destroyed it when the 26th dynasty was so prosperous
But the Egyptology records are lies
We know that yeah, because they have a timeline wrong and then you have to also add in the flawed calculations of this
Greek Greco-Roman historian or astrologer told of me Claudius told of me concerning how to date that
6th century BC 7th century BC
This is what most of the secular historians are using as a reference the work of
Claudius told of me and it's actually wrong when you look at it
So there's no really easy way to nail down the events of that time period
Because on one hand it says that Nebuchadnezzar will destroy Egypt like specifically in Nebuchadnezzar in Ezekiel 29
Thus says the Lord God and reading from King James behold
I will give the land of Egypt unto Nebuchadnezzar king of Babylon and he shall make her
Multitude and take her spoil and take her prey right there two separate events.
Yeah Right, but you know the third so the third but the the 40 years thing is sandwiched in that prophecy in is equal 29 So then it's like oh so you did that in the past, but I don't get it.
I thought it was for the future So I can't really discern that yet or haven't looked at it close enough If you read the whole thing in context and you know, the chapter breaks, let me just say one thing are Generally good Okay, where they where they start in one chapter where another one ended, right?
You know the numbers that we have in chapters in the King James in many Actually, all the scriptures follow the same thing Even when you look at the 1998 scriptures, the chapter is the same as the King James, right?
So The problem that I have with chapters is that it has a negative effect on the mind Those books need to be written read I should say like any other book Right, if you picked up Emerson or Melville and you saw chapters and verses numbered you'd be kind of pissed off, right?
But you don't get pissed off when you read it in Scripture.
We believe it's easy to communicate that way What if I were to tell you that Certain books in the Bible if you removed all chapter and verses no matter how long the book was and you read it in one Sitting you will walk away with a completely different mindset And if you read it with chapter and verse, does that sound plausible to you?
Sure.
So what I'm struggling here thinking is from what I remember from Ezekiel, it's all over the place, but That requires study and unfortunately to study that point Guess what?
You have to do
You're gonna have to sit down
You get a million dollar donation
Yeah
and read the whole book of Ezekiel without chapter and verse and walk away and see how that fits and
At the same time guess what else you have to do see how well it harmonizes with the rest of Scripture
What a concept yeah million dollars in donations
I don't even think that would be enough to get a brick-and-mortar building by the way, and I don't know what in America
You need sixty sixty thousand a year salary
You know 1,200 a week if you're not making 1,200 a week your poverty by the way
Considered poverty.
I think poverty is like 35 or less or something.
But anyway So, how do I you know, how do I get two or three people a year?
That's a quarter of a million a year salary Plus a building plus all the toys that you need to start putting information together a million ain't gonna do it Why even build why build a tap start was in Scripture say though who builds a tower without the wherewithal to finish it?
Ain't gonna happen it.
I'm I've been snubbed out of this equation.
It's not for me to do I think in terms of this is my own personal study.
Do you know how often we have conversations Sam?
Um, I don't care you'd say I'm doing it for my own knowledge.
Well, of course, that's its own No, having knowledge is its own greatest reward, right?
I'll just say this publicly.
This is not for me to do I mean, yeah I've been doing these minor Greek speak events and you know Whatever I could speak to a hundred thousand people and like for understand what I'm saying This is not for me to do.
Am I able to do it?
Oh, yeah
Yeah, I could do it, but I'm not gonna do it alone, you know piece things together and explain things
You know, I already got my reward which isn't I'm quite happy
With what I've discovered if I were to breathe my last breath in the next five minutes
I would feel as one of the richest people who ever lived
Am I naive and stupid for saying that well, that's whoever's deciding to hear what I'm saying
But no, I don't think it's my job to do it
I
Think and you know what?
I think that it may not even happen.
I would like to see it happen I Think we mentioned earlier you did there's with the video games.
There's someone in the elite or Whatever Illuminati's or whatever someone of that knows the gig knows what's going up?
I mean, why the hell else would they put an Antichrist looking figure in a video game, right?
Someone knows what's going up up there enough to influence these video games or is it just you know, the ether again, right?
I would suggest a combination of both primary the ether But yeah, I mean, let's just divert from the conversation.
What if I Said Sam we got a million dollars in donations.
Let's do something.
What?
Oh shit.
What do we do now?
What do we do first?
You want to complicate your life like that?
I Welcome that it would do it Yeah, it's not enough by the way a million is not much bullshit just because High net high net worth stuff.
Oh, look.
I'm gonna budget work.
Well, I could I could give you I just gave you the reality.
You need 60 grand a year salary three people.
It's a hundred eighty grand a year
You're gonna have to throw some perks in so a quarter of a million a year take a pay cut
Okay
All right
Cut that in half right or double the amount of people then I'd rather double the amount of people six people a
Brick and mortar building with any kind of function and appliance is gonna cost you a million alone
work from the Greeks house
Yeah, you see I like how you invite yourself over no, it's your project who's gonna get the million
It's gonna be your account or my account.
It's your
No, no
I'd rather turn it into notes and use it that way
But now I would have to set up a trust and have a someone handle it as a trustee
Because you don't want just the hardware alone is your
100,000 right off the top just for the hardware and resources and you're gonna have to go to load do library research and all that
Look exactly
You could look
University the University of Ohio
Back in 2006 or 2005 or 4 somewhere around there
I don't even have the University of Ohio one of those Nebraska, Ohio
they got a two million dollar grant from the US government to
To write up why water is good for plants.
Oh My goodness.
I know it's it sounds like idiocracy, right?
Remember like we put water on plants.
We put Brondo Gatorade right Brondo on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, so this is going on That's what I'm saying a million.
Yeah, that's an insult if I got a million in donations to do this or be insulted It's an insult That's why I'm not getting anything Because I'd rather not be insulted with a million.
Does that make sense?
No, but think about it No, it doesn't.
Yeah, just just because you don't know what to do with a million No, I do know what to do it.
I could stretch that million out to kingdom come but not with a project like this
Project like this to do it, right
To do it, right
Which would be to actually not only put the information together with the time required to put it together
As well as can be done temporarily with our understanding
By the way, these little Greek speak things I've been doing the same is probably full with more accurate and
Let's say deep bone penetrating information anything you're gonna get on the internet regarding these subjects period
Yeah, I don't even have to speculate on that
And it's not because you know, it's me and Sam.
It's just because it is The other thing is to continue this type of work I if I were to tell you 30 to 50 million, that's not a lot.
That would be the best What most comfortable way to do it believe it or not?
I think Bruce will understand that a little more than you Sam
I don't mean to be I'm not berating you Sam
But Bruce if I said we got 30 to 50 million to progress the scriptural study you'd say yeah
That's about right
You know that almost gives you a kind of a time marker of how long you can invest your time into it
It's it sets a precedent
Yeah, I think Greek is a you're probably setting aside a large chunk of that money for like bribes and stuff
Speaking of bribes I remember back in days.
I'm not admitting maybe this is let me just say this is a story
I was around a construction white collar
You know the smallest project they did was two million and the bigger projects were ten times twenty times
That amount and a million bucks fits in a suitcase very very comfortably
you know a
handshake and
Yeah, I think you left this at my house and you give them the suitcase is the way the conversation goes.
Yeah It's there's not a lot in yeah million is it?
Yeah, there's as a matter of fact actually ran into somebody wanted to buy a house all cash
And it was a quarter of that, and he didn't know yeah
He thought there was you know whatever he carried it around for a week in a backpack
Even in the shower like right at the you know not in the shower, but and once the deal happened
He was like oh, I'm so glad he's you know it's because I had to carry around this money for a week
You know
It's just it didn't it was like a roll only a few inches
You know thick all around a cube
You know if you dropped it on your foot.
It wouldn't hurt your foot quarter of a million in cash so Yeah, I mean I could yeah Think about it You know very frugal with the whole thing you you there's a lot of time that could be had with that And a lot of this kind of a project What is Bruce what I was saying?
What is a B movie cost these days ten million twelve million a B movie?
Gonna be fair I would say I mean you can they're movies They're movies that are done for a hundred thousand fifty thousand.
I'm not talking about that
I'm sorry movies that you can make what's the name of that horror movie paranormal activity wasn't that made like ten grand
Yeah, I was like yeah, right a million three million or a million three three four million
Yeah, or the one the witches one of whatever before that that made like five million witches of whatever you know
Yeah
Yeah, so if you're resourceful, you know that's on you if you're not resourceful, and you need to pay bribes and splurge
Then I guess you know no not bribes.
Oh, here's the interesting part
What once you get the information because let's say let's say I were to say something like the statement
Maybe I know someone who has a lot of information in between their ears right where they have access to it
And it just hasn't there's not enough time and resources to put it all out
Then you're like, okay
Well, then how do you get it out of the person's head and their ability to communicate it into the resources?
And then what do you do with it?
What are the resources?
What are you talking about things in print books websites movies documentaries?
What would how are you going to do it and then yeah?
And then how are you gonna get it out there?
Right and and and then the next thing would be Marketing of some sort.
I mean, I don't know.
What do you need marketing, but we're not we're not If you're gonna try to get it out to different people You have to have some way to get On a website you mean Are we starting a publishing house or something?
We don't need to do nothing.
No actually right now.
You just put up a website I mean, yeah, and and the domain then then it's not the website itself then though Then it's just getting the link to that website out to places just a stupid little link, right?
Right But who are you gonna here's the final point who's gonna who's gonna even uh, yeah, who are you gonna sell it to like five people?
It's got a million dollars take the money shut up.
Oh, that's a different story
But but here's the thing how many people on the planet you think there could even understand this information even if they you know right
Like a few hundred maybe a few thousand maximum on the whole planet
Yeah, you want to be McDonald's no no no no I never said that
We don't it's not a concern I think personally I mean just let's say we're having a private conversation right now
The the greatest reward for knowledge and wisdom is it is it within itself?
Yeah Yeah, I can agree with that.
Yeah, that's the greatest prize You know how many people are out there?
You got this guy in a wheelchair cripple and some other guy a physicist They say oh, they're so smart and they make all these theories about things that don't exist Talk about you know pixie particles and black holes and stuff, and you know it's total stupidity the whole world thinks He's wise and smart He has anything he ever wants now, what's the reward in that you know deep down?
I'm talking about the guy a little cripple guy in a wheelchair or whatever and some other ghillies people going around with CERN and all that stupid shit Deep down inside.
They know what they're doing is bullshit, but they're getting rewarded with all this material stuff and praise How about did you revert that what you know is true wisdom and the truth, but when you go on to the world?
They think it's bullshit, so where's the real prize these people that are running the physicist and religious institution Bible Teaching and science and medicine all that they know no matter how much praise they get In the world you get to know them personally.
I assure you deep down inside.
They are hollow.
They are rank.
They are depressed Right you know the truth Let's say in Scripture, and you're living out of a garbage can you will have a joy that these people will never experience Yeah, I'd rather personally do Personal experience.
I know a guy's a billionaire and with a B Not a millionaire 65 his wife leaves him after 40 years of marriage and has conversations with him And he's like what is life about it's just you know it's like dude Fucking stupid you're a billionaire.
I mean you could actually go and buy a hundred wives if you want Maybe not in America, but in another country trust me.
There's a someone in Saudi Arabia already has an agency that does that You know You want him pretty fat ugly stinky smelly clean, whatever you want What do you mean if it's just the wife that messed you up after 40 years.
We're talking about you know you see cuz he didn't
right
He's a billionaire come on if you're a billionaire your wife leaves you after 40 years like shit, man
I'll go out and buy me a hundred of them I
Couldn't buy me a hundred of them when I had you yet
Do you see that do you see the wisdom in what I just said Oh God yeah
What it's first of all the whole thing of turn it's not off
It's not lawful what she did because it was no premise of adultery
So the whole thing was a sim so just make up for it a hundred times
But anyway, this is not what I'm saying what anyone should do, but I'm just giving you an example
What is true knowledge and true wisdom is is its own reward sure and you know what it's very powerful reward
It's kind of like the goose who laid the golden egg every day you get more and more
You know as long as you have that knowledge and wisdom
Because it actually has an infinite sense about it if you go, let's say you have knowledge and wisdom and you speak
to people and they reciprocate you know you have a
Active let's say publishing house, and they're actually reciprocating.
They're buying the materials right so you can grow the project right And you're putting out knowledge and wisdom you put keep putting it out is that diminish it for you No, it seems like this endless fountain, right?
If you have knowledge and wisdom and you speak it no matter how even if you're doing you're speaking at ten hours a day or
performing
The necessary function to impart that to other people does it diminish your knowledge and wisdom no not it seems like this
It's like an infinite
source
But these other people let's say we're running CERN or the guy in the wheelchair talks about black holes
Or these other people that are viewed as you know having knowledge or whatever
It's the opposite do you know that the more they speak it because it's bullshit eventually someone's gonna call bullshit on it
And they're always in fear
They're running out yeah, they're gonna keep repeating the same bullshit, and then it starts to run out, and they're like oh, man
I know this stuff.
I can't explain why it's bullshit.
I know it's bullshit, but everyone tells me it's great So I better keep doing it what a way to live Yeah, that's how they are So Yeah, what project and the other thing is what to who's gonna listen, I know it doesn't matter yeah It's only like a few hundred people on the whole planet that are worth even talking to where are they?
That's why that's why people say Greek you you've been here.
You've been talking for 20 minutes You haven't let us speak so who cares what you have to say.
I don't talk with people.
I speak at them.
It's a difference.
I Don't care about what you have to say Look at you Anyway, I mean that you know that's not true.
I do listen to some people But essentially that's that's the the right attitude for this planet I was having a conversation recently with someone about you know Politics, but in a loose way they I'm not political, but everything came out of their mouth was you know this country?
This is country that meaning America.
I'm like dude.
Let me ask you where's America.
What do you mean?
I say is it on planet Earth once you stop looking at what America's doing and start looking at what the
condition of the planet is
So if you really want to put what's happening in perspective
And start looking at the history there you never had they're talking about executive orders
Executive orders are stupid you have a prop you should why aren't there general orders the government should be the president should be issuing
General orders not exact when you have executive orders that means you're going into an executive dictatorship
Anyway, I don't want to get into it
It's just so stupid.
I mean, I don't know we have a new president is Donald duck or someone.
I don't know it doesn't matter It's a ridiculous President and why would you why would you have a good president?
We're good presidents rule over good people crappy presidents rule over what kind of people Crappy people what do I see crappy people means you can have a crappy leader?
the It's so simple But it's an earth.
It's not a matter of which country now
Here's the other thing Sam in terms of getting a wherewithal to moving this information forward
And if if knowledge and wisdom is its own reward
Then you might as well say that we're let's say in Bruce included here, too
we have three very happy people just having a conversation that happens to be streamed and
If you're going to let this happen organically then whoever is listening
It's up to them to tell like the shampoo then they tell two friends
He tells a friend and they tell two friends and so on and so on right, but that's not happening.
I
Remember years ago when I was more social by by now
I'm not that social and I'm gonna say I'm not not social bum not that as social out of choice
I remember when I found something good whether it was information or shampoo or anything or a place to eat
I've made sure I told people about it
Right, yeah, and if you look at for example chat or people listen to Greek speak
I'm not I'm not saying this is definitive, but are they telling anyone?
Nope, not really.
Yeah, there's some comments here and there Yeah, I try to talk to someone they didn't get it or whatever.
No, I'm not talking about that They don't get it.
They don't get it.
But is it being promoted by those that find worth in it?
No, very little if not at all That's your other sign if those that are close to you and I mean in other words close to the emanation are not promoting it Going even further out.
It does it means even less It tells you what so badly you got out there Yeah, it's not even a battle.
It's what it is.
It's it's a mindset about the people you're trying to converse with it It's appalling Yeah, but even those that are listening can't promote it Yes, you know, so so forget it.
It's just the reward But here's the thing those that that I've communicated with whether it's in writing or speech that do get it Do find it as being a reward within itself in the beginning.
It's always very frustrating Of course, you try to communicate any truth about anything to anyone you think with resistance But but then it's just better to you know, keep your mind your mouth quiet and enjoy Do know?
Right.
Well because the knowledge of it a chat with you Yeah, and the knowledge that you gain from it is its own reward Yeah, exactly exactly and like I said earlier Bruce You know if we did get a million or so in donations now, do you think it's gonna complicate things a bit now?
It's like okay now I've got to go Together Yeah, I Wouldn't let it.
That's why I said you need three people at a good salary.
Mm-hmm and brick-and-mortar place and and by the way, the brick-and-mortar place will be you know, a decent brick-and-mortar place and You need a I guess Sam would just a web You wouldn't have to do print anymore because if the closest thing to print now is Kindle, which is a little thing That's supposed to be like a book, right?
No, don't worry Yeah All right.
So if print is I don't think print would be considered at all.
Sam Ray would be all digital, right?
There's some things don't exist in digital format Right, but then you put them in digital format, right and I can get them out the library Yeah.
Yeah, that's true So I found that the like one of the libraries here what they do things that don't come out of library They have for a fee a scanning area and in certain things if they're too fragile, they don't let you handle it at all, right?
Because it's just the book basically it's amazing You set it down and he just turned they give you some gloves and you just turn the page in it and it photographs it Right.
Mm-hmm very clearly But I think what's more important now, yeah I think now they have that already done Prior to you wanting to look at the book and handle it Yeah, most places.
Yeah, I'm your draft or something that do have these these older texts
but I think now the way things are is if you can read something and
Break it down
For someone and you know, if you in other words a 200 page book
Which would take 10 hours or 8 hours or 5 hours depending on how fast you read
Would be better served if someone did a one-hour let's say audio on it explaining it accurately
So the so the reader or the listener, right?
so And that's why very often basics the permers Like I always bring up Gustav Le Bon, you know The crowd mentality.
I just give the salient points Yeah, there's an audio book seven eight hours or whatever you can get into it But what you're gonna walk with is is a point there that yeah, basically what the Greek says about it in three minutes It's pretty accurate.
I mean I try to leave out the part where he attributes Phenomenon, you know to a source of forces unknown, you know, and there are some good things that come out of the crowd But the reason I use the Le Bon metaphor is to show what happens when information is put out and people are drawn to it Yeah, usually it's not a very good thing.
There are good things that come out of it Of course in some cases very rare.
Mm-hmm and good one if you're familiar with Le Bon's book
he does attribute some of it to he can't explain the phenomenon of how you know, there must be a mystical or
Godlike or angelic presence that draws people the other he can't objectify that but other things he can't you see
And I think I've already objectified that by in one way saying it's all external input anyway and cosmic censorship
So I borrow from him and just give you know
And that's why some people when I started bringing up goes over on Le Bon.
I get emails and messages I just ordered his book.
I'm like why?
Why I never said you should get the book.
I never endorsed it Yeah, if you want to read it read it, but don't tell you know Whether you tell me you got or not is irrelevant to me and you can get a free PDF Or an audiobook is better on YouTube or whatever.
You could you don't have to sit there, you know
You could be doing other things and I basically broke it down
I mean that is you know, it's very simple and I just like scripture is really easy to break down
You can have a three-minute conversation
With people and about scripture and basically you if they don't know scripture and you're going to explain it to them in three minutes
The best way to leave off when you're ending it is just do what you're told and it's better that you don't know
But let me just these points that I just gave you in the past three minutes explain all
The stupid questions that you're asking why things are the way they are, right?
Someone asked you why is there so much suffering in the world?
Well because the gods have no regard for your physical condition physical condition They have a very high regard for your spiritual condition And the only time they have any regard for your physical condition is when it affects what?
Your spiritual condition you see anywhere in any ancient rites is brush your teeth and exercise and eat healthy Nope tells you eat properly.
So what this makes you clean this makes you unclean what physically or spiritually you could you can you someone who just had pork or dog or a rabbit Can you tell if they're clean or unclean physically maybe so to a certain degree?
Yeah, because there's trichinella and those other things, but No, typically it's spiritual So anyway Oh you guys you've been reading up on any of the archaeology lately anyway, yes Someone brought toleration a little while back the archaeology over in Israel Yes, so a fascinating Okay, I got an email I think Was Vandy or someone else about it was a tour of the city of David and all that.
That's a propaganda.
Yes.
That's the one What what was that?
It's a propaganda thing don't it's semi-accurate It's Things that you know the stuff that they found I tried I tried to keep Off of what he was saying.
It would have been better just to watch and look at the pictures It is there's many levels That's why I mean propaganda was like all the if a bell falls off a priest's robe Come hell or high water.
They're gonna find it.
Why because it's a set-apart thing Right, you know it won't the only way that would be that way is if There was a chest or a cache of those things around when they were making them and when the temple where the area was Destroyed it got scattered.
Right, right.
That's what I mean.
It's a propaganda thing They're trying to they're doing the reverse of what I said They're they're trying to take what they know and how their behavior is and overlap it and force it into what happened I'm saying look at what happened and then and then rearrange what you see happening now to fit that because that's what's going to happen hmm You see what I mean, right?
Give it a loose example you're just some guy watching movies and You'll notice that you've been watching movies the past 20 years and whenever the terrorist is brought up.
They're always an Arab or Muslim descent For decades in the movies, right right and then all of a sudden you start seeing in the news There's acts of terrorism that might happen Well, you better start If you're wise you're gonna say oh shit.
We Hollywood has been showing us that Terrorism in the movies and they're always Muslim So when the now in the news are talking about possible terrorist events, we better take that and force it in To what we just heard To come up with in the future when they're going to be talking about terrorists.
They're always going to be Muslim How accurate is that going to be?
Pretty freaking accurate.
You see what I mean, right?
So if but even though it's all contemporary so Anyway, so you rearrange what's being said?
So will you look historically?
Right now that there is no other than archaeology there is no acknowledgment of the truth of history, right?
so for example When you look at Israel in Jerusalem, the only acknowledgment you're going to get of anything real as the Gihon spring They can't tell you the Gihon spring.
That's not the Gihon spring.
They can't do that But they will never add right now They know they have not and they can't politically add two and two together and tell you well the temple was over the Gihon spring So they haven't done that yet Bizarre because it's the only spring that's there.
That's right.
And what they're doing in this video and other videos I've seen they're looking underneath the Fort Antola for for Yeah, Judea.
Yeah the wall thing.
They're not gonna find That's all that's what they're gonna find.
The only Judean artifacts are gonna find there is the booths and the commerce that was set up
You know on the outside of the city right right to them
They're not gonna find the hardcore stuff there and actually the hardcore stuff was either taken away before or it was just literally destroyed
So, you know when it's gonna get really hardcore when you go opposite the Gihon spring and up about 50 or 100 meters
And you start digging right there and you will find a carbon ash layer
with a tree stump
Burned out
Yeah, and that will be the area of several things that happened there so what they call a destruction layer
So anyway, the the stuff is really simple
I hope you guys and the listeners of the three four people that are able to listen to this are getting a reward by just
knowing on their own
Quest of stuff.
Also, that is the real reward Well, we have 22 of them on listening right now, yeah Yeah, so sorry 22, yeah They could be sleeping.
Yeah Certainly, it's only three or four really Maximum five but but here's the the the point is When you go on the rectangle there's so much stuff that you can discover on your own and go on the rectangle and not find it at all and But you will find it in libraries Well, I shouldn't say no you won't find in libraries either in a good library.
I should say look I've once discovered a library here in town.
I didn't even know it was here I was walking around in a mall and it said public library.
I was like I walked in I was like Is this a government sanction?
Is this a government public libraries?
Yeah, it is.
I was like, I didn't even know it was here and The librarian was so proud.
She was like everything on this side is fiction.
Everything on this side is nonfiction
I looked at her I said, it's all fiction, baby
Not that kind of library because the FBI has a book seizure list and
Most of these public libraries even the main one and and
in 42nd and 5th Avenue, New York City
There was a policy that started 30 years ago any of the old stuff that had to do with science religious texts or whatever
That was hardcore was removed and put in storage
Yeah
Or or discarded like the Ben Franklin library in Philadelphia that had a lot of early
19th and 18th century texts they started either discarding them or putting them in storage as a guy
Who found out this was happening from one of the janitorial staff?
He went there and scored 20,000 books that were you know 150 year old on science electricity and all this stuff that are far more accurate on Electrical phenomenon than what's going on today, even though they didn't have a Radio Shack voltmeters and all that shit.
Yeah So you don't want that kind of library so anyway look I'm not blaming these libraries because they're accommodating who the general public which is disgusting.
Yeah, I Might have to take off As I have work in six hours Well, I thought it was off time Yeah, it is until the next day.
But um, okay for me.
It's Wednesday morning Okay Yeah as the Pope Work schedule goes have you by the way before you go Sam?
Have you ever brought up the Pope's work schedule to anyone just in passing?
Not not that you need to get into the details of the mechanism of lawful timekeeping But have you ever brought up the Pope's work schedule as a farce?
Yeah once Okay, only once.
Oh, that's fine.
You don't have to bring it up more than that Whether you okay, what was the reaction you want to share it with the rest of the class?
They found it to be Some kind of I think ponderable material, but you know They they were silent and they were like, oh Yeah, that makes sense.
You know, I didn't bring it up with you any hope or any expectation I just sort of did it because I hadn't done it before and I saw an opening Okay, you know So as well-received it wasn't outwardly rejected or you Right.
Yeah, I mean you can't hold it.
There's nothing to reject Right.
Well, sometimes you say stuff like that You know, they either reject it or they give you the same look a baby seal gives you right before it gets clubbed I love something like that.
I got the look but you know, it was acknowledged I mean, you can't fight the presentation that the presentation is, you know Done well, and it's pretty simple and ironclad As soon as you say that the animals don't go off that they can't argue with you Nothing goes off even people don't I mean people real people Yeah, well, this is a nice Thank you guys again.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
Maybe in a snake.
Thank you Sam That's in six and seven eighths days Yes All right, so I think So we'll just we'll call just a Voix hasta luego till the next time Yes, indeed.
Thanks for doing this later guys.
Not a thank you Bruce.
Be well You well, bye.
Thank you.
Night folks, and we'll Get you folks next time The place Well