And greetings folks, and we are on live here with the Greek, and shortly Sam.
Greetings, greetings.
How are you doing tonight, Greek?
Okay.
Good.
We're doing another ritualistic sonic event.
Seems like once a week on the Pope's work schedule we just seem to come around.
We seem to do that.
Yeah, I don't know why.
I think, well, I do know why, because it's easy to fall into these things, right?
It's kind of like a drive home.
When you're going home, you don't really think about it.
You just kind of put yourself in autopilot.
Yep.
So you kind of got this autopilot thing going.
Oh, yeah, it's what they call Tuesday on the Pope's work schedule.
Sam will probably be around.
We'll jostle some people around.
And here's the interesting thing, and maybe Sam should volunteer this information, but maybe I'll do it for him.
He didn't really get on this path until he heard Greek speak, right?
And I'm sure he – well, it's not a matter – you know, it's a matter of character also.
You either have it or you don't.
So when you – when we do this every week with Sam, it's – or almost every week, it's really a form of enthusiasm or a form of his pursuits along the lines of things that I've mentioned.
Not that I've mentioned anything that anyone else couldn't see or figure out, just that I happen to be the only one in this direct way.
So that's why we kind of keep it going in a way, as maybe a model or a paradigm for others.
And it's well-appreciated.
It really is.
There's a lot of things that I think – I myself for certain have learned an immense amount, a wealth of information.
Well, it makes one of us.
Speaking of learning, folks, if you learn to apply what's called the right-hand rule, which is, you know, you make a fist with your thumb pointing out, the current moves one way and the magnetism moves the way of your thumb, you know.
The curled fingers are the current and the thumb direction is the direction of magnetism, right?
Correct.
Well, you turn that around and you have a magnetic – you have a current vector and you have a magnetism vector and then you have a coherent vector of force, which is not acceleration, which is a sense of doing work.
You know, when you say force, you know.
Right.
So when you start playing around with these things and you figure out what gravity is, how do little droplets of water evaporate?
You know, people say, well, the air is light.
You know, it's as light as air.
No, it's not.
The water droplets evaporate.
They're not lighter than air.
They're heavier than air.
They have to be because it's still water.
It's not another phase or – I mean, yeah, it's not.
It's just regular liquid water in small droplets going up against something that is heavy.
Right.
So once you put these together, what is water?
It's pretty interesting.
And then you learn to make things lighter than they are because weight is not mass.
You know, you can put – you know, you can move a – someone wading in water, like waist deep, can move a rowboat with ten people in it easily if they're walking beside it.
You know, you can pull it.
Let's say if you tied a rope to a rowboat with ten people and you're on dry land, you can pull it pretty easily, even 20 people.
But if you put the 20 people on a crate or ten people on a crate on land and try to pull them, you're not moving.
Do you see the analogy?
So there's several things here going on.
Are you still there, Bruce, or did I lose you?
Yes, I just noticed that I was over-gained on something and it wouldn't let me start.
There we go.
Okay.
So until Sam comes on, anything else going on?
Let me get the chat on.
Is there anything that's not cringeworthy in the chat?
Well, we had a little discussion about the Assyrians – no, Pythians.
Pythians?
Okay.
Are you sure?
I think it was.
Parthians.
Okay.
Let me scroll.
By the way, whenever I turn on a chat, I just look at – right now I see one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Eight or nine comments is what the screen allows.
Oh.
I take the scroll bar and I just keep pushing it up.
Oh, no, I'm afraid to push the scroll bar up.
I don't want to.
So whatever is in front of me – yeah.
I understand.
It's still an Earthly-based chat, but nothing against those in chat.
I'm grateful that people are getting together and, I think, are discussing this kind of stuff.
It goes in all different directions, but a lot of times it touches on things that have been spoken about, which is always good.
Or beyond.
Or beyond would be better.
Yeah.
Because the things that have been spoken of, now you're just parroting.
Correct.
Okay, so I don't see – Go ahead.
I'll just wait for the – put the road on the show.
Right.
Anything else you wanted to bring up?
Well, other than I was talking with you a little bit before we came on and talking about the hive mentality and how unnerving that was.
Yeah.
Well, the division – this is a time of division on Earth, and you can divide it many ways.
You know, good and evil, hot and cold.
But I would say the hopelessly stupid and moronic, and then the semi-intelligent, semi-rational.
That's the division.
And when you get – people can go between those two groups, but unfortunately the condition is terminal.
If you're in the hopelessly stupid and moronic, you will probably always be there.
There was no changing that around.
No, no.
And to your grave.
Okay, let's bring in Sam.
He says he's ready.
There's that.
Let me just add to that.
Education, college, you know, stuff has nothing to do with what I just mentioned.
So it's actually true.
Sam.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
Yes, you made it.
All right.
I'm on a new computer now, so I don't know how I sound, but I hope it's fine.
You're fine.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
A little bass.
Yeah, you could always do what's called the Echo Sound Test Service with Skype and use headphones, and it gives you all the nuances.
They don't use a very good – when Skype does the Echo Sound Test Service, they don't – when they record yourself, you know, on a little trial, 19 seconds or so, to listen to yourself back, they use a very low-quality playback.
It still gives you a sense.
We could hear you.
I would say there's – I get more ambient.
I get more room.
That mic is a wider mic than the other mic.
Whatever you're using was narrower, but that's the critique.
So what's on your mind this week?
How are you doing?
I'm doing fine, much the same as last week, and looking into different things, most notably, well, some things about North Africa and Egypt and things of that nature and how that pertains to prophecy.
Not much.
When you say North Africa, that's a pretty long stretch.
I would go definitely Levant and east all the way to Afghanistan, and I would consider the northern Mediterranean rim more so.
But nonetheless, Egypt is there.
It is defined by North Africa, and that's very important.
But the stretch of it going west, not much, other than it being a satellite, you know, influencing.
So if Egypt needed something, guess who's going to step and fetch it?
Yeah.
I mean, I think you've made it a point to continuously point out the role of the coming Middle Eastern Union
alongside certain current world powers playing second fiddle in some Mediterranean countries,
like Cyprus being satellite powers, and that kind of emphasis is certainly all very well,
and it's in line with Scripture, but I think it does make itself a little bit guilty of omitting,
in much the same way that almost every commentary about world affairs does,
whether future or past, it sort of omits the role of countries in, say, Africa or North Africa,
which Scripture prophesies about also, right?
And it's definitely not a nationalistic thing because I could care less, but there are things said about those countries that one could take note of.
And I don't just mean Egypt.
I mean, the Egyptian pharaohs don't even look like the sub-Saharan Africans or the current Arab populations, and hardly anybody ever brings that up, that they're a race unto themselves that much isn't known about.
So these sort of pan-African or black nationalist folks that use Egypt's symbology, that's a joke.
But we can sort of establish that not only is there going to be a Middle Eastern Union rise to power, but also a sort of African or North African Union, Central African Union also, that comes on the scene, and that the Antichrist actually takes issue with that.
And, you know, I think that that's discernible.
Let's not sell that region short.
I think it is, I mean, size-wise, it certainly, it has stagnated under Western influence, but it's bigger than America.
Oh, and it's very rich, yeah.
Yeah, very rich.
Oil reserves, mineral deposits, lots of stuff for archaeology to find.
And I think...
Cultural art and tradition that is almost based on, like, xenophobic preservation like the Chinese hasn't changed, so it's a good place for study.
And it does receive acknowledgment from ancient cultures like Greece, and it does intersect with the Aegean cultures like the Minoans, being dark-skinned also, so it's not insignificant.
Now, if you were to talk to me about, say, South America, I don't know anything in Scripture that talks about South America.
It might be in the Table of Nations, I haven't seen it yet, but it doesn't ever come across as being prominent.
I don't see anything about Australia in there.
No, and the antithesis is true, there's no one in South America that knows anything about Scripture.
Sure, but we do get some artifacts that come out of places like Ecuador and Klaus Don and stuff, that stuff is interesting.
But Scripture doesn't really talk about it, unless, of course, I just haven't scanned sufficiently through the Table of Nations, which there is a good chance I haven't done that.
But prophecy shows that some kind of a union will be created, led by Egypt, and extending in scope some thousands of miles southward into the area of Sudan and Ethiopia at least, and westwards some 2,000 miles maybe, to include Libya, Tunisia, Algeria, and maybe even Morocco, to create some kind of a combination of nations that have influence.
Sure, if you want to, just from a resource perspective, the use of hippopotamus and elephant ivory was so common, I would say it was prevalent in the world.
Where did it come from predominantly?
Where is your biggest crop for that?
It's deep down into the continent almost, right?
So there had to be communication, and what would you call it when you have a reciprocating culture?
Trade, commerce, a treaty, and you do that with organization.
See, a government doesn't want to deal with people, it wants to deal with another government, like with like, right?
So there's going to be some organization.
Right.
And yet, I mean, obviously, the further that you get from the Middle East, the less potent the narrative becomes, but we do get a cutoff point around what they're calling the Kingdom of Eritrea, which obviously, not Eritrea, Ethiopia, but that's obviously not current-day modern Ethiopia, but it would cut off somewhere around Central Africa somewhere.
So I think that one of the bigger, even when you look at Egypt, one of the bigger obstacles to Egyptian expansion, and I mean ancient Egypt or Egypt of 2,000, 3,000 years ago, was difficulty in securing the Libya area, and now Libya is in shambles, or what they call modern Libya.
So it wouldn't be hard for Egypt to push its influence westwards in years to come, and what a coincidence that Libya is now a failed state.
I wonder why that happened.
Right.
Well, because of many reasons.
I think there's some hubris there, too, but that's okay.
But sort of cosmically, I can see it making sense, because in some way, Libya has to come under the influence of Egypt, based on what, at least based on what I'm seeing, we can take a look at it.
So you have the book of Daniel, Chapter 11, that provides some info, but it's easy to overlook it because it's only a few sentences, and essentially what I'm looking at is just a few sentences, but you can sort of read a lot out of it.
So it says that you're going to have the king of the north and the king of the south situation, and there's going to be a bunch of different ones, and you have verse 36, and the king shall do as he pleases and exalt himself and show himself to be great above every mighty one and speak incredible matters against the L of the mighty ones.
We know this is the Antichrist.
Anybody who doesn't know that sort of has to validate that on their own.
It's not too difficult.
And then you move on into verse 40, and it says, and at the time of the end, the sovereign of the south shall push at him, and the sovereign of the north will rush against him like a whirlwind with chariots and with horsemen and with many ships, and he shall enter the lands and overflow and pass over.
So not only is this Antichrist figure coming with land forces, but also naval forces.
So we know that the kingdom of the south is not a landlocked country.
It has to have a coastal region.
And also you have to ask yourself, south of what, north of where?
And obviously this is one of the harder things to nail down with regards to this part of Daniel.
I can only speculate, but if Jerusalem is, quote-unquote, more or less central of the world, then I'm thinking north or south from there.
And if it's not Jerusalem, then it could potentially be north or south of whatever kingdom the Antichrist is reigning from.
Which is basically Israel.
Right.
Something I wanted to add in, by the way, when you look at the key cities, and this is after 2028, right, the spring or fall of 2028, spring of 29, right, on the Pope's work schedule.
Okay, when you look at the key cities of Tyre, Sidon, or Tyre and Jerusalem and Babylon, it doesn't denote those are three different countries like they are today, Lebanon, Israel, and Iraq.
It denotes three cities of the same, this is a strong inference, and a strong, it's beyond speculation, by the way, but it's an inference.
Don't ask me to go anything beyond that, because my answer to that at this point, you'll see.
But I would suggest studying maps of ancient Israel, their borders, you know, as far as they went.
Now, the way they did borders was whatever, if you followed the laws, you were under their jurisdiction.
You see how it worked?
It wasn't like the Egyptians where they ran through your country and they put a marker and then they ran out and said, well, okay, our border extends to this marker that we just placed, right?
So, the reason why I'm saying this is because, you know, when Solomon extended his sovereignty to the Negev, that meant that the people of the Negev obeyed his laws, right?
So, wherever his laws you obey is where your borders are, boots on the ground.
So, I would suggest more of an inference and less of a speculation.
I would infer and suggest very highly that Israel, not as the state known today, but the cities of Tyre and Babylon close by will be under what's called Israel.
Right, okay, but this is after 2028.
Yeah, 2020, 2029, right.
So, you know, just like Lebanon, you know, I haven't gone, I'll go out on a limp.
All this stuff going on in Syria is to break up Syria and parts of Syria will now become parts of Israel, sorry, and parts of Syria will become parts of Assyria, Iraq, right?
Sorry, you know, I'm not making this up.
It's not that I wish it or whatever.
This is what can be read out of prophecy.
So, if you want to overlap what I just said on what you see on the rectangle based on the news, I hope it makes sense.
So, and I've actually gone on a limp.
Oh, back in 0304, I did a public speaking venue and I described how Israel is going to really quadruple its landmass, you know, in terms of jurisdiction into these areas, and a lot of people were just very upset by that.
And I was like, I'm not making this stuff up, neither do I wish it, nor do I wish it doesn't happen.
I'm just saying either way, leave myself, this is not a political statement that I'm making, right?
So, anyway, back to the concept of the continental Africa, which is Egypt as well, which makes Egypt unique, by the way, because it almost is like a different race of people.
So, I want to just tie that in with a lot of the propaganda that's – well, I shouldn't say a lot, but there is these Hebrew Israelites, whatever, these black folk that think they're the original Israel and all that.
I once left a comment about a decade ago on a talk show or something, I said, you're never going to find a pharaoh with an afro or a pick in his hair, you know?
I mean, I was being derogatory there.
Yeah.
Remember the 1960s, the Black Panthers, they'd have the picks with fists in the end of it?
Yeah, so, you're not going to find one of those.
As a matter of fact, you can validate what I'm just saying through archaeology, and no, they didn't pull all the mummies out and replace them with the beef jerky looking white guys.
So, anyway.
Yeah, I mean, it would be nice to get a little more exposition on that aspect of things, aside from the humor, but yeah, I do know that the black Israelite movement sort of are on their own sort of fringe thing.
Yeah, I just want to throw that out there, because people are going to hear this, and they're going to be thinking, well, what about this then?
So, there's a lot of what abouts we can throw in and interject while we're speaking.
That comes to mind because I have firsthand experience of dealing with those idiots.
So, anyway.
Go ahead.
Yeah, I mean, as far as the Antichrist and his base being out of Jerusalem, that comes later, though.
First, he starts off with his base in places like Babylon, Lebanon, and Assyria, and then...
Hold on, hold on.
First, you know where he's really going to start, right?
In the UN.
Well, yeah.
You know, those international...
Because here's one thing, he doesn't come into power secularly in Israel.
He comes into power spiritually in Israel.
Secularly, he comes on the scene as a world-known character.
We've had certain precluding paradigms or foreshadowings of this.
For example, remember when Obama was his first election?
He visited Germany a month or two before the election, and half a million people showed up to applaud him, right?
What the hell does an American candidate for the executive presidential seat get so much support in Berlin for?
Yeah, that was odd.
I don't know if you guys remember that.
It's a little tidbit.
So, you're getting a lot of this international stuff going on.
So, he will be favored internationally, secularly, and it's very clear in the book of Apocalypses that he rolls with a crew.
And the only way he gets the seal of approval with a quote-unquote spiritual Israel...
Because Israel is going to be very spiritual by then, by the way.
They're going to be more spiritually minded as opposed to being atheist or agnostic like they are now.
The only way anyone with that mindset will accept them is from a spiritual perspective.
That's why when you read in the book of Revelation, he is a prophet that comes out of the sea, which is the people or the multitude with horns.
Because who do the Israelites consider their greatest prophet?
He had horns, too.
So, anyway, I had a discussion with someone regarding the word keren.
And it's such a universal term that you know what horn is in Greek, right?
Kerata, or kerenta, again.
So, there's an aspect here that has to be considered.
When we bring up this Middle East Union and the agreements and all this, it's got two sides to it.
One is the secular side of the age, the material greed and the power and whatever is sold to the people at the moment.
Then you have the spiritual side.
So, it seems like the people who are spiritually minded of the gods, knowledge of the gods, and those who are worldly minded will accept both.
Where now it's very contrary.
You have people that are secularly minded or worldly, they don't accept spiritual leadership.
And then you have those that are more spiritual that don't like the worldly leaders.
This is a unique thing that's going to happen that we have never seen before.
So, I just wanted to throw that in there.
Sure.
But I guess what I was, what was I saying?
The Jerusalem thing comes later.
Because he does have other bases first.
And I actually think the Jerusalem thing comes really close to the end, like a few years before.
Right, because he has to finish up there.
As a matter of fact, he's dragged back to that place.
Exactly.
And using an Assyrian method, which is a hook in the jaw.
So, before all of that happens, we have this Daniel bit with the king of the north versus the king of the south.
And my thing is, I'm just going to...
We know that one of the kings of the north is this Antichrist character.
And he's moving up against the king of the south, which is some kind of...
Now, hold on.
I'm going to stop you right there.
Is there really a word in Hebrew for north and south?
I know that sounds philosophical.
Go ahead.
I mean, if it's a literal question, I can address it.
But I'm going to guess, yeah, cardinal points are pretty important regardless of the language.
Well, they don't really...
What's interesting, if you do some history on those cardinal points, they don't really...
It's just east they have.
Then they have anti-east, and then north and south are not clearly defined.
But anyway, that's just a phenomenon in the Hebrew tongue.
Go ahead.
Okay.
But is there still a directional element?
And, you know, you have a central reference point.
And north from there, it's whatever.
And south from there, it's whatever.
Of course, if you change the reference point, then north now becomes something else.
Like north of America is not the same thing as north of China.
So I'm still going to, unless, of course, there's an objection, because I don't want to sway too much on this.
I think that, yeah, it's north of something and south of something.
Sure.
Let's just say that needs to be investigated for more accuracy.
But as a matter of fact, I might do that right now.
I mean, it's north and south of something.
So I'm going to take it that it's the center of the world.
In other words, it's an axis point.
In other words, it's a point from a center point away from one point, let's just say, in opposite directions.
But let's just, while you're, go ahead.
I'm going to look at something in the meantime.
Okay.
So, like I said, if not Jerusalem, then one of the other Antichrist bases, which is going to be Babylon or Lebanon, and possibly Assyria.
I don't know if Assyria is officially stated as a base.
But we know he's from there and he does some stuff out of there.
So we're looking at countries that are south of that region that have coastal access.
And when, you know, if you look on a map, like immediately Egypt is the lead suspect.
And if you have any other candidates, you can, you know, throw them out there.
But as far as coastal access, I don't really.
I mean, it can't be Arabia because their coast is to the south of them.
Right.
If you look at Egypt, their coast is to the north of them.
So you can come downwards into Egypt.
You can't come downwards into Saudi Arabia.
And going on in doubt.
That's good.
Okay.
Look, I just pulled up Strong's Concordance north.
It's Zafon.
And it's not defined as a cardinal direction, but it's defined as north or a place upwards of the east bank of Jordan is Zafon.
It's a city.
So if we go back to the words that are being used in the Book of Daniel for north and south, you might be surprised.
Are you looking at Daniel?
Do you do the Daniel specifically or just Strong's?
No.
Just Strong.
Strongstein.
What are you looking at in Daniel?
I'm in 11, but let me just find north somewhere.
King of the Southland.
Well, in Southland it has Negev.
Yeah, that's right, which is a specific place.
So if I said you're in China and you're going to the Negev, that's very different than say I'm in China going to the south.
Oh, that must be India.
Right.
The Negev is in Egypt or close to Egypt.
Yeah, right.
So if you're starting in China, it's way west and then a little south.
So, okay, Book of Daniel, let's see, 11.
This is just something I came across a few years ago.
And when I pick up studying, this is a good time, this springtime, to pick up studying the Book of Daniel, by the way.
And the Book of Zechariah and the Book of Revelation.
Sorry.
Revelation.
No, that was a deliberate cough, sorry.
Because I don't want to say the word.
I don't want to suggest anyone study that because you're not going to understand it.
But the place of Daniel is a good place.
To start this spring.
Actually, is it?
Not really.
I don't think anyone is going to understand anything in scripture at this point by the looks of humanity.
But I'm just saying, let's just say you and I are just speaking and Bruce, you're listening and you're speaking to Bruce as well, right?
Book of Daniel is a good book that will start opening up.
And so is the Book of Zechariah in specifics.
So the King of the North is King of Saffon in Daniel.
Yeah.
Which is an area, is Philistia.
Saffon is, King of Saffon is, Zephon is, it's a place in Palestine.
Hmm.
Remember, they're going to have five kings there.
They're going to be ruled by, they're going to get, the Palestinian state will come into fruition with five leaders.
Five, like if you look at Hamas right now, I dare anyone to look at the leadership of Hamas.
How many leaders, how many are there?
Five.
Always.
Isn't that interesting?
Hmm.
Are you aware of that?
No, I did not know that.
I haven't pursued it.
Oh yeah, I've been looking at them for 15 years.
They always have five.
You know, the IDF, the Israeli Defense Force, will kill one of them or two of them, and they get replaced, and they still maintain five.
Hmm.
So you're getting some, I just turned on the email, getting emails as well.
I mean, currently, they're saying that the Negev sort of sticks to southern Israel, but I'm guessing that in ancient times, that may have, that could have been any region that extended into Egypt or even further south, which would then hit into Egypt.
But we can't.
Your audio sounds different.
How about now?
But as far as Safan, I don't know that that can really be limited to just the Palestine area, because the King of the North, this Antichrist character, doesn't come into that area to really reign until it's really the end.
Well, he does reign, but by word, by jurisdiction, by eminence.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
We don't dwell, he doesn't dwell there.
I mean, who knows?
They might have a good massage parlor there.
He rules the world by jurisdiction.
So we can't just isolate this Palestinian area as being the only area of focus for that.
This is just for public, let's say, expediency and for everyone.
Any discussion on the book of Daniel, Zechariah, and Revelation, all this?
The amount of Revelation on those things is going to increase so much starting now that pretty much anything that we might have perceived in the past might be discarded or reevaluated.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, sure.
And this is a caveat to anyone, not because I say so, but because these things need to be examined temporarily.
Like, who are you, where are you, and when are you?
The when.
It doesn't mean we shouldn't do it.
I just think it's funny to, have you ever done something and a few years later looked at it and said, oh, this is ridiculous now, right?
That's why you have to really be careful.
That's where objective comes in, objectivity.
Things we know for sure about what I just mentioned, the one that temporarily would be most effective the soonest is the book of Zechariah, which we discussed slightly last week.
We brought up the concept of the Temple and people turning away and certain perceptions of religious leadership.
That will come before anything in the book of Daniel and the book of Revelation.
Even though those book of Daniel and book of Revelation have taken effect already, the comprehension of it won't be as clear as it is now beginning to be.
Now meaning literally.
We're going into spring here soon.
Yeah, I'm not going to push too much on who are the king of the north and the king of the south.
If it doesn't tell us, we have to wait.
Right.
Or as far as the geographical locations.
But we know that, I mean, you can use a common sense to figure out that the Antichrist is one of them and that we see him acting here in a certain way.
So if you look further down into verse 40, no, I just did 40, 41.
And he shall enter the splendid land and many shall stumble.
This is after he's crushed the king of the south.
But these escape from his hand, Edom, Moab, and chief of the sons of Ammon or Amnon.
I'm going to assume that the splendid land is Israel.
I mean, scripture is the gods talking, and I don't see that kind of language being used for other countries.
So, and then you have three countries east of the Jordan River that avoid being defeated, which are these other ones, Edom, Moab, and Amnon.
And then after that, he targets Egypt.
Verse 42, and he shall stretch out his hand also upon the countries, and the land of Egypt shall not escape.
But he shall have power over treasures of gold and of silver and over all the precious things of Egypt.
And the Libyans and the Kushites shall be at his steps.
So, Egypt today is sort of a land that was in recent history impoverished, and that was in the 90s and the 80s as far as I know.
And then they had their government overthrow in 2011, and it hasn't really regained its footing.
So, I think it might still be one of the poorest countries.
And that's still all Western influence to set up even more tension for what's coming.
All that Arab Spring stuff, by the way, I have contact with people there.
No one there with their right mind knew that that was not an organic thing that happened, by the way.
But it's there just to set up.
But by the way, let me just throw this in here again like I always do.
The gods don't give a crap about you.
Let me say that again.
No, I don't have to because I've said it so many times before.
What I mean by you is when you love someone or even if you're just discussing your own self, if you have physical harm done to you, that is not considered as something caring.
The gods do not care about you.
They will grab a million people and throw them in a meat grinder.
And if you ask them why they did it, they will say, we don't need a reason.
How dare you ask?
All of them.
So, have you ever heard somewhere, fear the gods?
And people say, oh, I don't fear.
That's fear.
I don't want the New Age idiots.
Why do they say that?
Because this is how they operate.
This is their MO.
So, when you read about these things coming about, this power is given to this Antichrist figure.
It's almost like a godlike power where there's an indifference to human life, let's just say.
So, I don't know when people are going to figure this out in mass.
Maybe later after the resurrection, most likely, most things will be figured out.
But they still think this, when we discuss things of the gods, they think it's a joke.
So, anyway.
It's like atomics or nuclear.
If you set one off in your living room, it doesn't care that it's your living room.
It will incinerate you, just the same as if you did it out in the middle of the desert.
Wherever the gods are, bad shit's going to happen, unless they want it to be otherwise.
And I'm talking about the benevolent ones now.
So, anyway.
I don't think people are paying attention.
You ever get that feeling?
I'm seeing it more and more.
I'm getting used to it.
I ask these morons, what god are you talking about?
The gods have no qualms at all about incinerating you and your children.
At all.
How do I know?
I've studied the scriptures.
What's wrong with you people?
You can't approach them with faith only.
Faith in what?
How can you have faith in something you know nothing about?
It makes you insane.
So, you better know how to play the sport.
It's a sport.
It's a cosmic sport.
You better be aware of the teams and the rules and all that.
So, anyway.
I just had to throw that in because people think this is either academic or spiritual or religious or whatever.
Or they like it or they don't like it.
They have no idea.
I think it's best that they don't.
Yeah, it's fine.
Either way.
So, yeah.
Egypt coming into prominence is interesting because they're really poor right now.
So, when it says that the Northern King comes into Egypt at the end of – close to the end of the age and says that he will have power over traders of gold and silver in Egypt, you have to ask, like, how do they acquire enough riches for the Antichrist to want to covet them when they're currently poor?
So, the whole country has to do a 180 for that to happen.
Well, they're poor because they're maybe dubbed.
I think Egypt has their own – I know Iran does their own manufacturing of cars and planes and things like that.
I don't think anyone is really poor right now because you can glean resources from the earth, you know, water, fuel, fuels, and minerals and things like that.
I think the poor is the restrictions put on by certain entitled classes or the masses, yeah, because the masses don't know the laws.
So, I think that is the culture of poverty more than the true poverty.
Right.
I don't mean that the land is poor.
No.
I mean the culture has made them poor and the restrictions that are on them.
But that has to be lifted.
Yes.
So, that will be lifted for the place to become prosperous and not prosperous by some small measure either because why is this guy targeting them?
He could target any part of the world, but he targets them because they have something that he wants and also probably because they're resisting him, which is what I – which is why I speculate that they're the king of the south because the king of the south creates a problem.
The antichrist goes at him, and here I see him running over Egypt specifically and Egypt's allies.
But it puts Egypt at the head of that confederation.
And then it goes on to talk about the other countries, the Libyans and the Kushites shall be at his steps.
So, he's going to attack these areas corresponding to ancient Libya and the kingdom of Kush.
And like I said, modern people will make the mistake of imposing modern boundaries on these places, but modern boundaries don't even have bearing on the real ground because I've heard that you can walk from Egypt into Libya without even knowing you're in a different country.
So, what you're saying – That's like the US.
US and Canada is the same, forests and places like that.
They're not going to paint a line like they do in the middle of the street.
By the way, I want to interject something.
When the antichrist is using mechanized military to do this, and I said when, not if, or let's say if also in there, let's say tanks, planes, soldiers, what flag or by what jurisdiction are those military machines going to have?
You know how tanks and planes, they have a – what country they're from on there?
Guess what country when the – let's say hypothetically the antichrist does this with Egypt, right?
And he comes in with jets, tanks and things like that, right?
When you look at those jets and tanks, what flag will they be flying?
Israel.
Does that make any sense or no?
I'm only skeptical because he only takes Israel after this stuff happened, after the Egypt stuff happened.
He doesn't take it before or he doesn't move into the – he doesn't put his palace in between the two seas as it says until it's after all this.
So, whose flag is he going to be flying on the tanks and on the jets?
I didn't say it wasn't Israel, but if you're just going to say it like out in the open, I have a sort of instinctive pushback.
Maybe because I haven't read everything that I need to read, but is it a Syrian flag?
I don't know.
He's an Assyrian.
Yeah, but to the world, is he really an Assyrian or is he a Judean?
No, he's not a Judean.
Why would he be a Judean?
Yeah, that's a good point, isn't it?
Better look into that in the future.
There are those that claim they're Judeans and they're not.
Yeah, but we have – we already have people that we can point to with that.
Sort of.
Remember, there's a precursor to everything, right?
This is part and parcel of the mindset.
The Samaritans are already those.
They're the ones claiming to be Jews or not.
Historically, they are.
Yeah, well, we're looking forward now.
Forward.
I'm just throwing things out because – let me just put it this way.
There's a lot of people that are Judean that deny being Judean, especially in Europe.
There's a book written about that, several books.
There's one that I heard of.
I don't have the author or even the name.
It was something in the title about the secrets of Jewish women, like women living in 19th century, early 20th century Europe in Italy, Spain, Portugal, and they would meet every so often in private and in secret and proclaim their Judaism.
But if they were out in public, no one knew them as such.
They thought they were regular Catholic indigenous people.
They kept it in secret for obvious reasons because of the – we want – the history of the quote-unquote Judeans is come to our country because we want your technology, your science, your ability to deal with math, numbers, money, medicine.
And then once they did that for a generation or two and trained the people, then they said we don't want you anymore.
Get out of here or we'll persecute you.
That's the story for the past 2,000 years, I think, even in America.
I think it was – most of the American presidents in the 20th century were extreme anti-Semites, openly, openly, not secretly, schematic.
And when I say that as Semites, I mean for non-Judeans as well, but anyone that was of Schematic descent.
So anyway, I just – okay.
I'll digress from that.
Let's go back.
That's fine.
In either case, you have the Libyans also and the Kushites getting overrun, and we have to consider their ancient borders.
Kush was a grandson of Noah, eldest son of Ham, and brother of Canaan, Mitzrayim, and Put.
Even though it's said that there's another nation of Kush somewhere in Afghanistan or near Afghanistan, I feel like we have sufficient evidence to this particular Kush being south of Egypt.
There's a verse in Jeremiah that points to them having some kind of skin color or skin pigment, Jeremiah 13, shall a Kushite transform his skin or leapart his spots, things of this nature.
And you have the Septuagint consistently translates Kushites as Ethiopians, and this is what the Greeks called them.
Strabo indicates that they looked similar to the Indians.
I think he said something like those who are in the Indus and those who are in Africa do not differ from each other.
So both dark-skinned people, and Josephus will always be there to give an account of something, and he says of the Kushites, for of the four sons of Ham, time has not at all hurt the name of Kush, for the Ethiopians, over whom he reigned, are even at this day both by themselves and by all the men of Asia, called Kushites, antiquities of the Jews.
So Afghanis would be called Kushites or Ko, I don't think people, but anyway.
No, I think he's Africans.
Yeah.
So Kush in the Old Testament period, I believe, included Sudan as well as modern Ethiopia.
And I think it actually went down to the River Nile area, all like all of the River Nile area, actually.
So going like 2000 miles away from the Mediterranean Sea down into central Africa.
But I haven't been able to pinpoint exactly where I'm still looking into that.
But it's a pretty big region going southwards.
And then regarding Libya, you know, Libya is funny.
The Hebrew says Lubim, L-U-B-I-M, which is a word that is found on Egyptian monuments.
I've read that it means people who dwell in a thirsty land, which I guess would suggest a desert.
And it also gets equated with the land of Put, not Punt, which is something else.
By the way, the desert would be the wilderness, but go ahead.
Yes, it would be.
Land of Put being Libya.
Right.
Thirsty for what?
Water or knowledge?
Maybe they were blocked.
Have you ever heard of censorship where information is put anywhere?
Now we're getting philosophical.
It sounds platonic now.
Go ahead.
No, I think it's thirsty more in the literal sense because, you know, cosmic censorship has been in place since the beginning.
So I think that these kind of references are not quite that present.
For example, Saudi Arabia, up until recently, if you were caught with a Bible at the airport entering the country, they confiscated it from you.
Which is fine.
I think they should all be confiscated at this point.
So people will say, wait a second, I've got to have this.
No, really?
I think you have to take a competency test before you get one.
You should have a license to get one of those.
Anyway.
Anyway, so Put, as I said before, third son of Ham.
He's also a brother of the aforementioned Kush.
And we know that Ham gets associated with dark-skinned people of Africa quite often.
I think Josephus also writes, Put was also the founder of Libya and called the inhabitants Putites from himself.
But the name, it has now, it has now has been by change given.
What's it saying?
But the name has been changed by one of the sons of Metzrayim, also called Libyos, antiquities of the Jews.
So that would explain the name change.
But Put and Libya, from everything that I've looked at, generally seems to be the same.
And the historians generally seem to say that.
Not to say that the historians are always right, but I found enough different references of that.
Metzrayim, obviously, was another son of Ham who creates Egypt, which is actually called Metzrayim and not Egypt.
Also a fragment, you have a fragment from Nebuchadnezzar II's annals that talk about his campaign in Egypt and defeating the soldiers of a place called Putu Yavan.
Which is literally Greek Libya.
And that would make sense as far as its positioning.
So in any case, ancient Libya goes out way into the West.
It's not just modern day Libya.
It was the whole African continent west of the Nile Valley into Morocco.
And I think even Herodotus validates that.
So when this king of the north takes over Egypt, he's also going to conquer the entirety of North Africa because that's what Libya is.
And also going down to southern Africa.
And this is sort of why I brought it up initially that that sort of area does have some kind of irrelevance.
It's not just this sort of like Australia place that it doesn't really matter what happens there.
And after that, when he's done with this place, he turns his attention somewhere else.
Daniel 11 continues in verse 44.
So to harmonize that with all this directional talk, I think you do need to have some kind of a point of reference.
So this is continuing on the same book?
Yeah, same book, Daniel.
So right after he goes at the African, let's just say the North African Union, which extends all the way to Africa.
Or let's just say the African Union.
Once he goes at that and defeats them, then he gets news that there's some kind of trouble brewing in the north and in the east.
It doesn't say north or east of where, but once again, I'm just going to take the sort of…
Well, it does.
Well, just from a loose perspective, the word for north is the name of a place, more than a cardinal.
And east, usually, I forgot the word, but there's only one cardinal direction in Hebrew, and it's east, which actually is a description.
And guess what the description is?
What happens in the east every morning?
Sunrises.
Yeah.
So let me look up the word.
I wasn't looking at it in the interlinear, that's why I keep saying the wrong thing.
I wasn't either.
No, it's not wrong.
It's to be considered.
We're not saying anything as it is.
We're considering these things.
By the way, all of this stuff that you and I have been discussing and actually typically I discuss are things that need to be considered, and I ask questions about them, and not in a way to send the conversation of the dialectic into a wild spin, but to have them reconsidered and reconsidered again.
I think that there's more, I wouldn't say Cartesian coordinates on where these places are, versus a cardinal direction.
You see what I mean?
I think these are more Cartesian than cardinal.
Cartesian meaning, you know, you have two locations, you find the third, versus, you know, the way we, when we say northeast, southwest and all that, we think of it as directions on a compass.
Well, you know, if you keep going east, eventually you'll be going west to come back around.
So, I mean, you'll go to the west.
So I think these are more Cartesian than cardinal, even though there is no such term in scripture.
You know, this is for the reference, the mindset.
Right.
Well, as far as the interlinear, which I probably should have been reading from, yeah, I've been taking from the scriptures 98 just because it's easier to copy and paste.
Let me ask you, by the way, I might have to, are you looking at the scripture 98 electronically?
You said copy and paste, so it's electronic, right?
Yeah, e-sort.
Okay.
I was thinking of getting one of those again.
I have only the 2009 one here.
You know, by the way, I used to buy cases of those Bibles and give them away to people who wanted to read it.
You know, those were when I was younger and dumber and wealthier, I should say.
But, yeah, okay.
But I'm looking to get one in print again, so I guess eBay.
Anyway, yeah, but you said copy and paste.
I gave it away, so disregard.
Yeah, it's digital.
Yeah.
So it's actually saying in the interlinear that reports shall fluster him from the, and this is where the ISA is kind of confused.
It doesn't really know what it wants to say because in the translations box it has sunrise.
But what it does is that it sort of fades out the word sun and just leaves the word rise as if it's undecided.
So when you look in the actual interlinear it says misrock, which means…
Well, it's like saying dawn.
If it's not a lady's name, when you think of dawn, you're going to look to the east if you know by definition the description of what dawn is.
It's first light after a lot of darkness.
Even if you don't know where east is, you're going to turn your head around, you know, 370 or 270 degrees until you find it.
You see, it's kind of like that.
Right.
No sun involved.
Yeah, because believe it or not, at dawn there is no sun yet.
The first hour you don't see the disc is still below the horizon.
Right.
And then when it says the north, it's Cephan.
So, something shall fluster him from misrock and Cephan.
Then he goes forth with great fury.
But, I mean, lightly translated east and north, I guess.
No, it's fine.
It's fine to be…
You consider it that way and then you consider it more literally, which is not the literal that we get in English, meaning the literal in the interlinear, let's say, or the language of preservation.
And it wasn't the book of Daniel also written in Aramaic?
I think so.
Originally?
Well, it was preserved in Aramaic and then of course it was canonized and reconsidered and re-scripted in the Hebrew.
There are Aramaic fragments of that, so I think that is what it is.
Predate the Hebrew, yeah.
So…
First century, I think they did it in Hebrew right before.
Okay.
I mean, yeah, this kind of does have to…
It redirects the thoughts because if we're going to go with the cardinal stuff, then, well…
You just look at all of it.
When you look at the center point, if we're going to look at Jerusalem as being the center point or some kind of Middle Eastern area, whether it's Babylon that he's based out of or Lebanon or Jerusalem, well, if you look north of that, you obviously have Turkey and the Caucasus regions and Russia all the way to the north.
And if you look east of that, you have Iran and Central Asia and then East Asia and China all the way to the east.
But either way, we're not talking about the North or South American continents and we're not talking about Africa and we're not talking about Australia.
So, I mean…
Nobody should be talking about Australia.
But anyway, sorry.
So basically, once this guy gets the African Union, this is just conjecture, but he hears some kind of news that makes him mad and makes him go after other people.
So maybe the rest of the world starts murmuring that he's taken over too much territory, he just invaded and took over half of Africa, maybe they have to do something about it.
I don't know.
Either way, he goes out to subdue them, which he does.
He has success with that, meaning that he essentially takes over most of the Eurasian continent, I'm guessing.
Of course.
Afghanistan and beyond, yeah.
India.
Right.
And then it's only after that he conquers this Eurasian capital that he makes Jerusalem his capital, which is at the end of Daniel 11.
And he shall plant the tabernacles of his palace between the seas and the glorious holy mountain, yet he shall come to his end and none shall help him.
So between the two seas, I'm guessing that's the Mediterranean and the Dead Sea, which is where Jerusalem is located, which is also equated with the holy mountain.
And I think this is what Paul is referencing when he talks about a man who goes into the temple, sets up the abomination of desolation, and then starts calling himself Yahweh or God.
The previous one by name, yeah.
Yeah.
Because at that time people are going to start to delineate names because they're more than they are now even.
Right now you're still in stupidity beyond the eye, way above your ears in the world regarding all of these matters.
So in general the point that I'm trying to show is that the last two things that this Antichrist has to do to finalize his world domination is one, take over North Africa and parts of Central Africa, and then the countries north and east of that in Eurasia.
So only then does the last sort of phase start.
And then it says that his time is quite short because it ends with Daniel 11.
He shall come to his end and none shall help him.
And this is right after that.
And then it goes right into Chapter 12.
And it says that this is when Michael stands up, the great prince of Israel, and there shall be a time of trouble.
Speaking of which, let me just interject something.
I just got an email.
Ha ha ha ha.
These people who make video games are OBVIOUSLY AWARE OF SCRIPTURAL HISTORY or JUST HISTORY.
In a game called MGS5, the Phantom Pain, the main character has a missing eye and a fake arm, and his base of operations is on the Sekiles.
I just thought I'd throw that in because it pertains to what you're interested in.
You and I have brought up in private conversation how there's an underlying current that underscores what's coming in the video culture.
Or, you know, video games and other things that are geared to young people.
So when these things do happen, the young people who are going to be most active, which I suggest, are going to already seem to look at these things, oh yeah, naturally.
You know, of course, right?
I never thought of that.
That's true.
Didn't you say once that they always go after the newest generation?
Oh yeah, or do it for the children.
Yeah, you do see a lot of interactions with the spiritual realm in video games and superhero movies.
But I think video games, frankly, is the most potent because it's the most taken-for-granted medium.
And it's also, I think, one of the most subversive ones because you're allowed to vicariously live through the characters in a way that you can't on a movie screen where the narrative is already laid out.
Well, and the fact that you used this in the naming of the characters, which I really found that interesting.
Yeah, there's some kind of a secret society.
I mean, obviously, secret societies run a whole lot of things.
But there's some kind of thing in the video game world that I have not been able to figure out as far as these people who create the games have some kind of a background in some esoteric collective that is never really talked about.
Because once you hit the 1980s, especially out of Japan, there comes this whole culture of anime and video games, which espouses things that don't seem to have anything to do with traditional Japanese history or Shinto anything.
And you see them in sort of the 80s magazines when they're doing interviews wearing t-shirts with the Star of David on it.
And they're making video games like Shin Megami Tensei, which is essentially a supernatural video game about demons versus angels.
And they're essentially depicting gods that are in the Bible.
And it doesn't make any sense where the Japanese would be getting that from.
Right, it's extracultural for them, yeah.
Yeah, but there's something very organized about it.
It's not just sort of a passing fad.
It's been going 30 years strong.
It's external input.
Yeah.
They're getting it from the ether, literally.
Don't try to define the ether.
Just learn what it does.
Like a bear.
Nobody knows what a bear is, but we know enough about it that when we say bear and I ask you, do you know what I'm talking about, you say yes.
But when you say ether, do you know what I'm talking about?
Most people don't.
Learn about the ether.
Recently listening to someone also, just to interject, like how screwed up science is, when you ask someone what light is or energy, they say waves.
What a bunch of crap.
If you're waving your hand, what is that?
That's your hand moving.
You cannot define something with a wave.
It's a motion.
Like if you look at the ocean, what do you see?
Waves.
No.
It's water.
You see?
You see how stupid the scientists are?
They tell you everything is a wave.
Well, no.
A wave of what?
Anyway.
So learn about the ether.
Learn about external input.
And these things, once you, let me just say it this way, just to sum this part up, this interjection, because you're on a good roll there regarding, because you can share more about the younger culture than I can.
But when you establish that there's an external force, cosmic censorship, i.e. everything else that we don't see tangible that affects us, our ability to see or not see something, how does that happen?
You will never really figure it out right now.
Later on we will, post-resurrection.
But do you understand its characteristics?
So like you were bringing up, all those descriptions you gave were basically out of Japan, but there are video games that come out of America, or is it that the video game market right now is really Korea, Japan, and America, and you can't tell the difference anymore?
Well, the market is global.
But Japan has…
Oh, yes.
There are, okay.
There are studios.
I believe so, yeah.
So you have the major studios, obviously, that spearhead a lot of things.
But with the video games, the way it works is that you have publishers, and the publishers really, they have all the money, and they're sort of the main powerhouse.
And then you have the developers and the studios, and a lot of them are independent, and the publishers will pay the studios to make the game.
So it's like, we'll give you a contract to make a game for a certain console.
Right, right.
So you've got a bunch of geeks in a room underground, in their basement, making these things for years.
Yeah, I got you.
Writing the code for it.
Yeah, okay.
Right.
And of course, that was more 30 years ago.
Now, the geeks are sort of running things in Silicon Valley, and they have their…
They have glass towers.
Yeah.
They have a better standing.
Okay, got you.
But a lot of stuff still does come out of Japan.
I mean, they own Nintendo, which is one of the big console guys.
They obviously own…
They put out the anime stuff, largely.
A lot of the classic video game brands still do attach themselves to Japan and come out of there.
So there's something in Japan that I have not been able to identify, not having been there.
I can't speak the language, but it's very clear.
A lot of the fantasy sci-fi stuff took its origins from there, starting in the 60s.
The Japanese are to Asia as the Greeks are to Europe.
What I mean by that is if you…
Look how different language, culture, and all that is, right?
Right.
Japan is sort of an anomaly, Asian anomaly.
Most…
The ignorant people don't see it that way, but it's very different.
Yeah.
And all the Asians…
You could deal with Asians of any country in Asia, even the Pacific Rim.
The moment you bring up Japan, it's like, oh yeah, that's like someone from Mars, you know?
Or I really like them or I really don't like them, whether you're speaking to a Malaysian, Chinese, Korean, or whatever.
If you're speaking to a Korean and you bring up Malaysian, okay.
But if you're speaking to a Korean and you bring up Japan, all of a sudden there's a strong sentiment that comes up, either positive or negative.
So go ahead.
Yeah.
What was I going to say?
Japan, something, something.
It got plugged out of my mind.
No, Japan, you were saying that it's still coming out of Japan.
They're very powerful, regardless of the independent studios or international community.
Even like goddess religion stuff.
Like it's very clear to me, the sort of goddess religion artifacts that exist in that culture.
But it's interesting because the traditional Japanese Shinto culture, it doesn't seem to reflect that.
It's very…
The contours for that are well-defined.
The sort of borderline aesthetic…
That's monism.
Monism in a way, which…
In a way, I would define a lot of the stuff we talk about.
Monism is that there's the God source and then there's everything else, and you ain't it.
Where everything else kind of blurs it around, but anyway.
Monism, if you were to define it…
Now, monotheism, which is stupid.
There's no such thing as monotheism.
That's like saying Santa Claus.
Monism is where you have the source and then everything else, and everything else is not part of that source, which is very scriptural, by the way.
So a pot is not the potter.
The bread is not the baker.
So there's a little bit of wisdom in monism, but what people think of it is…
Anyway, there is wisdom in Buddhism.
There is wisdom in the Hindu culture.
There's no such thing as Hinduism, which overlaps.
There is wisdom in Shinto.
There's no wisdom in Christianity, by the way.
Sorry, I'll go out on a limb and say that for the hundredth time.
There's no wisdom in a lot of Judaism and all their sects.
So let me just put it that way.
There's a lot of wisdom to be found in a lot of the stripped-down rits of the ancient world, but none to be…
And by the way, there's no wisdom to be found in any of the organizations now, like modern Shinto, modern Buddhism, and all that.
Those are just morons.
But I'm just saying, I'm talking about the rit now, right?
The script.
There is wisdom in the ancient Greek writings.
You know, what's interesting about Scripture, it delineates the culture of…
Two cultures are mentioned more in terms of knowledge than any other.
A little bit of Egypt, but mostly it's the Hellenes, the Greeks, and the Hebrews, right?
And just, I think I've mentioned this before, the Hebrews relied culturally and traditionally to get their knowledge and wisdom by revelation, by direct conveyance from an angelic being, from the Godhead.
Where the Greeks do it by deduction and philosophy through observation, right?
Looking for commonalities, you know?
Like, you know, the Phi, the relationship 1.116, you know, all that.
They try to find it within the creation itself.
So there's a lot of wisdom in all that.
Obviously, you know, if you're going to get a direct revelation from the Godhead through an angel, obviously that trumps the rest.
But the culture, basically, of the Judaic mindset is you get wisdom delivered, conveyed to you from an angel, through prophets, even though they hate it when they get it because they kill the prophets, right?
And the Greek side is you get wisdom by philosophy or by observing.
And there's wisdom in both, obviously.
But I would take the latter.
I would take it by revelation because it comes more direct.
But nonetheless, this is what's going on.
I just summed up 5,000 years worth of history, or maybe less.
Actually, let's say 2,500 years of thinking.
Indeed.
But to go back to what you were going to say about the Japanese, where are they getting it from now?
So, anyway.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, like the goddess religion thing, there seems to be two.
I'm speaking in very general terms.
This is just from observation.
There seems to be two parallel cultures going on in Japan.
And maybe even in China, you can sort of see it developing there.
You have the sort of traditional Shinto Japanese culture, and its spin-offs, and its sort of connection to what people call Buddhism, even though they're different things.
Yeah, they're not the same at all.
Go ahead.
And then you have this new wave, sort of post-1970s, 80s Japan, where young people are adhering to this video game anime culture that really does a good job of turning their brains to mush and turning them into morons.
It makes them very receptive to this sort of New Age way of thinking.
Believe in yourself.
Follow your dreams.
Be accepting of everything.
Don't be too critical.
And this sort of nonsense.
And these things exist side by side, and I don't really see there being...
But hold on.
All these New Age people, including them, they're being set up for the Antichrist.
Because it's going to be so easy for this guy to come on the scene and switch all that.
Yeah.
Because it's not a competing mindset.
It's a completely different mindset.
It's always easier to get someone out of one mindset into a completely other than to a competing mindset.
Right.
So, go ahead.
Yeah, so...
There's laying the groundwork ahead of time, isn't there?
Yes.
Yeah.
Yes, cosmically, I mean, it's obviously part of the setup.
That is the most God's-eye-view way of looking at it.
But once you start looking at it a little closer, I think it becomes interesting to delineate exactly what mechanisms are being used to enforce that.
And in this case, it's the video game culture and the anime culture.
And I mean, you do have a few North American powerhouses.
You have Blizzard Entertainment, which is a video game company in California.
They made sort of things that almost everybody's heard of.
World of Warcraft, Diablo, these very big online games that kids play for like eight hours straight type of things.
But still, Japan is a powerhouse.
Yeah, I just thought it was interesting what the guy wrote in the email because I didn't recognize that.
I figured you'd appreciate the details of the email.
It was Greek to me.
Well, actually not Greek, but you know what I mean.
I don't know any of that stuff at all, the names and all that.
But I figured you'd appreciate the detail of the email and that someone else is seeing the detail here.
Sure.
So, yeah, sort of moving back to what we were talking about.
I mean, aside from Egypt coming into riches or learning how to maximize their potential and what they have further along.
If you look at Ezekiel 29 and 30, it speaks of additional Egyptian related events.
It's a bit harder for me to conclude what's being said, though.
I have to look at it a bit more.
But Ezekiel 30, for the day is near.
Even the day of Yahweh is near.
It is a day of the clouds, the time of the nations.
The sword will come upon Mitzrayim and great anguish shall be in Cush.
And when the slain fall in Mitzrayim and they take away their wealth and her foundations are broken down.
So along with this downfall of Egypt and Cush, Ethiopia, it mentions an entire string of nations that generally seem to stretch out west and south of Egypt.
Like we've mentioned before, Ezekiel chapter 30, verse 5, Cush and Put and Lut and all the mixed people and Cub and the sons of the land.
The covenant shall fall with them by the sword and them being Egypt.
So looking at that, we know about Cush.
We know about Put, because that's Libya.
Then we have the nation of Lut.
I've had a hard time identifying them because you can go two ways with that.
Either you can take Lut as stemming from the actual guy, Lut, who was a son of Shem, grandson of Noah.
Or you can take it as a nation that stems from Lutim, who is a son of Mitzrayim.
So we know that these nations generally come from actual people that have the same name.
But you have two people here that are sort of similar names, Lut and Lutim.
In almost all the commentary that I look at, and I think that they're taking their cue from Josephus, they go with the Lut origin.
Which points to various Anatolian Turkish people, particularly the Lydians.
They're Semites, I should say, right?
Yeah.
This sort of Iron Age, what they call the Iron Age Kingdom of Western Asia Minor.
You have the Book of Jubilees also, when it describes how the world was divided between Noah's sons and grandsons.
It says that Lut received the mountain of Ashur, and all appertaining to them, until it reaches the Great Sea, and until it reaches the east of Ashur, his brother.
I just put in a search on Lut on a map.
And an older map has it as Beth Dagon, Yehud, Anu, Lut, Bonabreg, Afik.
It's not too far from the Great Sea, about 15-20 kilometers.
Hmm, the Mediterranean.
Yes.
Yeah.
So it's Beth Dagon, Jaffa.
So Tel Aviv, it's just, let's say, 10 miles or 15 kilometers west and slightly south of modern Tel Aviv, which makes sense.
Right?
Yeah.
Changing the names of places destroys the information.
So, if it's not there now, and I don't know where this reference is, but let's just visit it and see.
Ludum, Genesis, yeah.
Ludum and Lut are different.
Right.
The Semitic Lut.
That would be son of, not Mithrim, the other one, I forget.
Son of Shem.
Yeah, right.
According to Herodotus, Leto was the first king.
Argos, okay, there's a lot of stuff here.
Not recognizable as Semitic, but it is.
Okay, so if we put in something like that and we don't see much, and it's going to be a prominent or semi-prominent feature in the future, what does that mean?
It means there's going to be, what, a revival of this, right?
So something to look for.
I mean, I sort of, I don't, Jubilees is obviously not canonical, but if it's offering up something and then you search for something that sort of agrees with it, I don't feel like it's, it shouldn't be discarded.
So saying that Lud received the mountains of Ashore up until the Great Sea, you know, we know that the old Assyrian Empire of 2000 BC, and not even just that, the Neo-Assyrian Empire of the 7th century, they extended all the way north into the Caucasus mountain area, so is that what's meant by the mountains of Asshore?
I don't really know, I think it's possible.
I think a revival is in order, I will know more, but it needs to be looked at.
You know, speaking of the Assyrian people, you know, they're the most discounted force, even though they were not as prominent historically known in its time.
Well, actually they were.
They were.
For 400 years they were, but they've been discounted.
You know, where do you think Nebuchadnezzar came from?
Wasn't he an Assyrian general?
The senior?
Oh, the first or the second?
The first.
Oh, I haven't looked into that.
The earliest.
Yeah, look into it.
I'm just throwing this out there.
I haven't looked into it in over a decade, but if you study, you know, obviously the Book of Daniel is pertinent, but the senior, the first Nebuchadnezzar, how did he come about?
Now, you'll find this historically that he was an Assyrian that, you know, he turned on his own people.
He got enough support, defeated them from memory here.
He turned, he was an Assyrian general, you know, like a military force should have top three generals, let's say.
You know, imagine one of them gets three quarters of the force, turns around on the other two, and then goes and then sets up his own deal later on.
So, and settled, obviously, what we call Babylon or settled, you know, another place.
Still exercising influence over what?
The whole world.
So, I just want to throw that in there, not to complicate, but to extend the perception of what we think when we bring up, you know, let's say someone like Nebuchadnezzar.
I need to re-examine all that as well.
So, when you say Nebuchadnezzar I, you mean the father of the second one?
Uh-huh.
Right.
The earliest historical record of that name shows him, I believe, from memory as, you know, described, as I just described.
I guess the only thing that I feel like, so let's not confuse one, two things.
So, we have Nebuchadnezzar II and he has a father, but his father is not Nebuchadnezzar I.
He's an Assyrian by name of Nabopolazar, some weird pronunciation, Nabopolazar.
And then you have the actual Nebuchadnezzar I, which is a completely different guy from hundreds of years before that.
Right.
So, Nebuchadnezzar I is around 1000 BC or 1100 BC.
And then you have Nebuchadnezzar II, which is in the 6th, 7th century.
Right.
So, his father, yes, was an Assyrian, but he's a different guy.
He's not Nebuchadnezzar I.
Yeah, we're talking about a big stretch in time, right?
Yeah.
But yeah, Nabopolazar is an Assyrian.
That's interesting.
That's why I say these, I've been crying, you know, watch Assyria, watch Assyria.
Well, no, there's a million things to watch, not a million, but quantifiably there's at least several dozen things that need to be examined.
And I've been trying to underscore the importance of, in reverse here, how Assyrians have been discounted.
And how there's going to be a big bait and switch on that, where the spiritual, meaning where people lay their faith in, will be Judean, even though the characters behind it will be, you know, not Judean.
So, here's an interesting way to talk about future events.
Israel will increase in prominence.
I'll say the word, I don't like to use it because it doesn't really hold true merit.
The Jews will be in the news every day, all the way to the end.
I assure you that, for sure.
I'll stake anything on it.
What you call, what the world at large calls the Jews will be in the news every day till kingdom come.
Okay?
And how they're going to be in the news is the same and more intense, right?
More concentrated.
But what's going to change is the way the people are going to view them.
You see?
And I'll just leave it like that for now.
All this, you know, that's why, you know, strong steam, you know, I use that as a remark, a negative remark in a way.
But you're going to see the influence of Israel at large, whether it's geographic, political, spiritual, religious, the people increasing in magnitude as time goes on, all the way to kingdom come.
But the powers behind it, that interest or that noteworthiness will change from being, you know, those people and other people.
You know, as the Caesarian, the quote unquote, instead of or Antichrist.
You know, by the way, let me just say it this way.
When the Antichrist is in power, people are not going to say, oh, look at the Caesarian.
I don't think I've discussed it in too much detail because I don't have that much detail that I could give in terms of temporal, you know.
You know, like, oh, watch, this will happen first and then this will happen next exactly this way when this guy is here, you know.
No, but I'm giving you more of a generality of how the perception at large will be.
And you have roughly two or three more prime ministers before this takes place.
I think I've discussed that before as well.
This changed.
And I'll go on record.
I'm the only one that has ever brought up that analogy ever, anywhere, to watch the prime ministers in the first chapter of Isaiah.
Oh, let's give the Greek a big hand.
Yeah, get a gold star.
But anyway, that has to be watched as well and considered as part of the temporal nature of this information.
I mean, how, you know, how objective can you be?
Never enough, right?
You can't be too objective.
So the quest is to try to be as objective as possible.
And you know you're going to fall short occasionally.
But the thing is you have to keep persisting the objectivity of it.
Define objective.
Without subjectivity.
In other words, you know what, also, it's like defining agapi.
What is agapi?
It's one of the primary words that are translated as love from the Greek.
You really can't translate agapi.
There are words in Greek that have no translation, right, just like Hebrew.
There are words that have no translation.
They can be directly translated to another word.
Agapi means doing the right thing even though you don't feel like it.
When you know that something is right, like, for example, to have love is like someone calls you at 3 o'clock in the morning and then they say, well, I'm going to the airport in the middle of the night.
Can you please walk my dog?
And if you're like, well, the dog needs to be walked.
It's the right thing to do.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning.
I'll get up and come over.
That's, you see, where if you don't have agapi, you'll say, oh, well, you know, it's too bad.
The dog will have to wait.
You know, it's 3 in the morning, dude.
You see?
So when you put that stuff aside, it's agapi.
So when you put the problem with objectivity is like people, if people don't like, here's the, let me just describe it in a tiptoe, roundabout way.
You ever talk to someone and say, well, I don't like that, so it can't be true?
That's the opposite of objectivity.
If people don't like the information, they will not even consider it.
Because here's the thing.
There's more to this at work than we believe or can want to admit to ourselves.
And this is a thing about objectivity.
And I'll tell you, this is how scoundrelous and how evil people are on the planet right now.
Recently I was watching something about the fake moon landings, right?
And some guy said that he brought this up to a professor.
You know, there's over 30,000 pieces of evidence, which most, you know, like, you know, NASA has destroyed, by the way, all of their reference material on the Apollo missions, because they don't want anyone looking at it.
Anyway, he had a discussion with a college professor in physics who believed in the moon landings occurred.
And he showed him, you know, this, let's say, a binder of all the evidence that there's no way it could have.
And the college professor stopped.
This is a college professor now, entitled class.
And he said that even if one of the astronauts went on national TV and admitted the moon landings were fake, I would still believe they went to the moon.
So, when you discuss objectivity, that's why I brought up the word love, because part of objectivity is doing the right thing, the word agape, right?
So, when you're not objective, are you doing the wrong thing?
Not necessarily, right?
No.
But in this case, we're discussing objectivity.
Let me just put it, I'll go on a limb, maybe not.
Most people are not capable, I've said this before, I shouldn't say it like that.
Yes, most people are not capable of being objective.
Just like a fish is not capable of climbing a tree at this point.
Well, there might be a fish that can climb a tree, but you see what I mean?
It's as far-fetched as that.
You know, like wisdom and knowledge is a prize in its own right.
You know, if you have that wisdom and knowledge and you have persistence and you can put up with all the filth in the world, then you can become very wealthy, right?
Obviously, by taking advantage of all the morons.
That's what's called marketing.
But if you prize wisdom and knowledge above all, you don't have to do that.
You'll be happy with just most basic food, clothing and shelter and comforts.
Unless you want to deal with all the filth, meaning humans, people.
Not all of them are filthy, but as a general, you could go to a landfill, not everything is completely filthy, but it's a landfill, yes.
To be surprised that a landfill is filthy, you are an idiot.
To actually think that humanity is not filthy and disgusting, you are an idiot.
So anyway, I decided to throw that in there.
Was that objective or subjective?
Hmm, I'm going to leave that for another time.
I think that was pretty damn objective, but anyway.
Now, that would sound very subjective to someone else, wouldn't it?
But I'm telling you, that's objective.
So you see, these are various things on objectivity.
It goes along hand in hand with love.
When you read about the gods, the paramount thing is love, isn't it?
Did he say objectivity?
No.
It's love, especially when you read what's called the New Testament, which you shouldn't read it because you're not going to understand anything in it.
I'm talking about the public at large, right?
Or you're going to think it's something else.
You know, there are still idiots out in the world that talk about there's a different god of the Old Testament than there is of the New Testament.
You know, this is how stupid people are.
And what was it, just three minutes ago, I just gave you what's going on?
So maybe, Sam, to define objectivity, I would use the word agape, which is almost untranslatable.
It just means it's usually translated as love, but it's a type of love where you do the right thing, you know what the right thing is, and you do it regardless of how you feel, right?
Where you have also philia, which is, you know, friendship, brotherly friendship, close friendship.
And then you have erotos, which is erotic, lustful, carnal.
So objective is also the least carnal, right?
Yeah, it helps somewhat.
If you don't have supreme command over your own emotionalism, you cannot be objective, by the way.
If you are always driving a car on an icy road and you don't know how to handle it, there's no way you're going to be objective.
You know, if you're stuck in emotionalism, you cannot be objective, unless it happens by accident or happenstance, or at the point of a gun.
I think I just gave the analogy of the professor who admitted that even if the astronauts went on television and admitted they'd never landed on the moon, he would still believe they did.
That goes beyond being objective or subjective, that is insanity.
How many times have you heard me say, dealing with the public, you want to deal with crazy people?
What do you think all these police, military, judges, generals, presidents, doctors, professors, lawyers, it is no different than going to a planet and coming back later and saying, what the hell happened here?
Well, they took all the people out of the insane asylum and made them police, lawyers, judges, professors, doctors, psychologists.
Yeah, that would make total sense.
And the people love them.
All of them, not some of them.
Now, there are some in those fields that I mentioned, professors, police, judges, lawyers, doctors, that are not insane, that are pretty rational, but you know what?
They don't last very long.
And when they do get all the training and they finally hit something like a bat across the teeth, they see what's going on, they look for an exit strategy, they usually last only a few months or a few years, max.
So if you were to make a general statement that they're all basically insane, that's pretty accurate.
But there is a small group in there that passes through.
This is planet Earth.
This goes back to that thing that Sam brought up before about the conditioning of a generation.
I mean, look at how many generations have been conditioned already with that hive mentality.
And there's various different shades of hive, but it all comes back to that same…
But why are they conditioned, Bruce?
Is it really conditioning or is it a precept of the law being applied?
And what precept of the law would be applied?
Think about it.
It'll take a second pause.
I'm going to go get some more coffee in the office and see if the Wi-Fi works.
Okay, your point, Bruce, was that they're being conditioned, and I'm saying that it's the application of a certain precept.
I wouldn't say the law directly, but I would say that it's a precept that you find in Scripture, which is, you know, I would say the law.
What's being applied?
The sins of the fathers get put on for how many generations, right?
Right.
The sins of the fathers get put on as many as three to four generations.
Now, you could break that.
That's right.
So are they really being brainwashed or is it the sins of their parents being put on?
And they're just bringing it into acceptance.
Do you see the objectivity there using Scripture as a reference?
See, when I see people being brainwashed, what kind of evil stalk did you come from?
Well, usually people, you know, I'll give you an example.
Speaking out in public, they say, oh, they're brainwashed.
I'm like, yeah, you might say they're brainwashed, but I say what kind of evil stalk did they come from?
Right, right.
You see?
I don't know.
Does that make sense?
Yes, it does.
Does that help?
But you can break that.
It tells you how to break that in Scripture.
Are you familiar with what I just brought up, Sam, about the brainwashing?
Does that make sense to you?
The sins of the fathers stuff I know about, but it's been a long time since I looked at it.
But I do know that.
But it does, you know, after the third or fourth generation, I mean, it does get lifted.
Mm-hmm.
But if they've been bred and groomed to do the same thing after the fourth generation, if they're doing the same thing that was done four generations ago, guess what happens?
It starts all over again.
Yeah.
It's not a vicious cycle.
It tells you how to break it.
If you vow to not be like them, right, you break it right there.
You could be the first generation.
Yeah.
But you don't have any autonomy to do anything anyway, because it's all external.
It's all external.
But remember, there's going to be a big, I'm suggesting, inferring there's going to be a big surprise on how people are going to find out later how much free will they really had.
And others are going to be really disappointed to see how much free will they didn't have.
So what do you know about the ether?
Ether meaning, you know, you don't know, like the bear.
We don't know what a bear is, but we know enough about it, right?
So the point here is this.
Later on at the resurrection, let me just repeat this.
Some people will be surprised and disappointed to find out how much free will they really had.
And others will be surprised and disappointed to find out how much lack of free will they really had.
So it depends on the mindset, doesn't it?
It depends on the spirit.
You know, like your spirit is dwelling in you by it being animated by your body.
But it's not really in your body, is it?
No, it really all comes down to that, doesn't it?
The spirit.
Mm-hmm.
No?
Again, the cruise ship analogy works well.
Look at some of these modern cruise ships.
You know, some of them have been turned into floating cities for wealthy people who don't know that property taxes, you know, how to deal with that, right?
By the way, if most of these wealthy people have Harvard attorney graduates as their consultants, they don't know that property taxes are only paid on properties that are for profit.
I've said this many times before.
You could look at any code book in the world, except maybe for a subject like England.
But in America, all the cities and states and jurisdictions, it tells you very clearly that non-profits are exempt from property taxes.
So let me ask you, where you sleep, shit, eat, fuck, and do all this other stuff, is that for profit?
What are you going to do in paying property taxes?
Anyway, because you have Harvard law school attorneys telling you you're feeding you.
All right, so back to the cruise ship analogy.
I just had to throw that in there because it's pertinent.
When you're on a cruise ship, you know everyone on the ship is going to a certain destination from point A to point B, let's say, but you have a lot of free will on the cruise ship.
But do you?
Well, it depends on what ticket you bought, right?
First class you might have a little bit more, right, than steerage.
I don't think they have steerage anymore.
Here's the other thing.
Can you jump off the cruise ship and get on a lifeboat?
Here's another concept with the thing.
Can the cruise ship be hijacked or boarded by pirates?
Yeah, true.
Yeah, you see all the possibilities with the cruise ship analogy?
Do you think the Earth, when you read about these demonic spirits or malevolent spirits coming down the Earth with great wrath, does that sound like you're about to be pirated on a planetary level?
It certainly does.
Mm-hmm.
Surprise.
Hmm.
It's worth contemplating.
It brings a whole new look at things.
Did we lose the group?
No, I'm here.
Well, I just got a message.
I think it was Seth.
He put in, look at Ezekiel 1.8, is it?
I need to put on some reading glasses about bearing, just barely, 18, bearing the sin.
The soul of the sinner doth die and not bear the iniquity of the father.
And he just told the father bear the iniquity of the son.
So that seems to go counter to what I just said.
It shall be upon him, and the wickedness of the wicked shall be upon him.
I think that might be post this situation.
But anyway, that could be looked at.
Ezekiel 18, Seth put that in there.
It seems to be contradictory.
But in direct contradiction, if it's viewed in the same temporal space, right, same time.
You know, here's the interesting thing about the Book of Ezekiel.
Do you know how much of that is really post-millennial kingdom, post-kingdom come?
A lot of it.
A lot of people misinterpret many of the things.
I'm not saying Seth is here by dropping that in.
But I would suggest that many of the things that are precepts that were given to Moses.
In other words, what you see in the first five books still applies today.
A lot of the prophetic writings apply.
Many of the prophetic writings contain information that applied to the post-first resurrection period, right?
And they get mixed up.
Or just before it.
Yeah, like the very end or the very beginning of the gods being on earth.
I mean, he's looking at Ezekiel.
But the stuff that you're talking about is in Exodus where he's still talking to the Israelites.
You shall not worship these other gods.
Or, you know, for I am a jealous Elohim visiting the iniquity of the fathers and the children of the third and fourth generations of those who hate me.
So that's kind of a specific thing.
Well, what I'm suggesting here is up until the next temple is built and desecrated.
I think the abomination of desolation is a form of desecration.
Everything applies still.
That's in the first five books of Moses.
And by the way, throughout history, up until maybe, I'd say, the last 500 years.
If you mention the biblical text, it was just the first five books of Moses.
Especially the past 2,000 years.
Very few people knew of all the other writings.
Because they were held, whether canonized or not, they were held by certain people as, you know, occulted writings.
But the first five books of Moses were not occulted or hidden.
Up until, you know, the later translations.
You know, 500 years ago.
It's kind of ironic to say it that way.
I mean, they read the scroll of Isaiah in the synagogue and things like this.
The rabbis had access.
Yeah, they did.
Right.
But I'm saying the world at large, you know.
Septuagint was the first five books of Moses.
The other Greek translations were done much later.
You know, to satisfy, quote unquote, Jews living in non, you know, Egypt, Greece, and other places in the world.
Anyway.
So, this, by the way, this concept of the law is a, not from a Christian sense.
Well, they don't have, I shouldn't bring it up there.
People think it's arcane.
What's in the law, by the way, I'm just, this is another way of saying it.
In the first five books is the scriptural rationale.
It's the primer.
It's the cipher.
It's the thing that you stand on.
When you see something in scripture that seems anomalous or just kind of like whacked out compared to the rationale that's used in the world.
That means that it has to do something with the law that you don't know about.
And when you understand the law, you'll say, oh, I see why this comment is brought up this way.
You see?
Think of it that way.
And the reason why you should do the law, and that, you know, whoever you is, is when it comes to food, you're going to listen to some whacked out scientist that tells you red meat is bad now and then tells you red meat's okay later.
Or tells you you have calories or this and that and the other.
Nah.
You've got to have a basis of law.
Some whacked out attorney or something.
Anyway.
Yeah, we're kind of, this question is nice.
We're kind of far away from Libya and Egypt and stuff like that.
I'll get back on that.
But we're not.
But here's the interesting part.
I mentioned the first five books, right?
Do you know when they left out of Egypt, right?
We're still on the topic of Egypt.
You know, it was the whole world that was liberated.
Do you know that I'm suggesting here if you go look at when they left Egypt, right, and the slavery, you know, the exodus, you'll see I think more than once mentioned the whole world left.
Meaning it was a, as if, I'm not going to go out and say that this is how it was, but there was a, as if the whole world was enslaved to Egypt.
There was a time of political subjugation that changed, you know, throughout the whole world, known world.
It says a mixed multitude went up with them.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
And it represented a breaking of a certain, what do you call when you have a period of something, you know.
Bondage.
Yeah, yeah.
It was the thing to do.
I mean, it seems like the Israel side of paradigm were a model for other places, which we don't know much about other than the, you know, the Mycenaeans and the Minoans and all that.
So, and their cultures were devastated during that time period, during that century, if not maybe 20 years of that exodus also with natural disasters and other things.
And, you know, immigration problems, I should say.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I know that.
Because you have two types of invaders.
You have an invader that comes to your shores in embattlement gear, you know, battleships, armed soldiers.
Then you have another type of invader that comes to your shores with their wagons and all their belongings and their families and their little children.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
What you got there, a bag of chips?
Crisps?
Sponge cake.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, all right.
So Egypt and Libya, the way I would sum all that up is within the same degree, other than the specifics mentioned about the interest of Egypt with the Antichrist and the Mycenaeans, the battles.
Because there's a leader of Egypt there that's a woman also, a daughter, right, from what I recall later on in another book.
So we're going to look for prominence of a political leader in Egypt.
When you see a political leader in Egypt who is a woman, you know the time is nigh, as they say in King Jimmy, right, or in Old English.
But I would suggest the significance of the rest of the continent would be similar to the significance of the satellite nature of the Greek and the Persians.
I shouldn't say the Persians because the Persians are going to have a direct hand, very direct hand in the next seven years.
So, in other words, Turkey, when you – okay, let me just sum it up this way, maybe a little more clarity.
The way I would sum up as far as, you know, temporarily now, Egypt, Libya, you know, the northern half, upper half of Africa, if not the whole continent, would be the way I would sum up a loose union or a loose confederacy of Greece, Cyprus, and Turkey and the Balkans, some of the Balkan states, working in concert with the Middle East.
Directly and indirectly.
So, I would almost say that that whole southern Mediterranean rim will loosely and directly be supporting the Middle East Union.
Well, you know, we know the whole world is going to support it, but they will be, you know, tied in.
So, if you mess with one of them, it's like messing with the rest, right?
In other words, there's going to be a schism between the influence of the West as it is now in, you know, the southern Mediterranean rim or Africa in the future.
In other words, they'll be more tied in being influenced by this Middle East Union, just as Greece, Cyprus, and Turkey will be more influenced by the Middle East Union than they are right now with the West.
It sounds kind of like a lump, but it's not an amorphous lump.
It could be defined, you know.
But I am lumping it in, yeah, for sanity.
In other words, to have a healthy perspective on the situation.
What do I mean by healthy perspective?
One that is vitality.
In other words, no matter what's going on in Libya or Cyprus or Turkey or Greece or whatever is not as significant as what's going on in Iran, you know, Persia, Israel, Lebanon, Iraq, you know what I mean, Palestine, Philistines.
What's going on in Egypt, let's just bring in Egypt also into the fold here.
What to watch for to have a good sense of vitality and a good-natured sense on what's coming in prophecy and have a handle on prophecy.
Watch Egypt, Israel, Persia, Lebanon, Syria, Iran, right?
Watch those countries.
That is far more important than what's going on in Libya or Cyprus, right?
Does that help with focus?
I never said watch anything.
I'm just giving an observation on the nature of the role that they'll play.
Yeah, but I'm saying watch it.
Watch the core countries for sure.
I'll give you an example.
Back in 2011 when the NATO went in and just shot up Libya and they told everyone it was a revolution, well, there was no revolution at all.
It was quite the contrary.
Some people were getting in touch with me.
Look, sorry, that's Libya, man.
That's not Persia, Egypt, Israel, Syria, Lebanon, Iraq, Syria.
It's not that.
So it's peripheral.
Yes, it's important.
But it's not important scripturally.
Sure.
To have a handle on prophecy.
In other words, if you had a clock on the wall and instead of having numbers on the clock, you know, 1 through 12, you have events, right?
You know, prophetic events.
And it would be more than a 24-hour clock.
It would be like a 280-item clock, 300, 400-item clock.
There'd be some African nations on there.
We just said that before things, you know, come to an end.
They're going to be not the head, they're going to be the tail of Egypt.
If Egypt was a creature and it had a head and a tail, the head of Egypt would be facing, its chin would be on Israel, and its tail and its leg and its butt would be across the southern Mediterranean rim or the northern African continent.
Does that help with a clear picture?
Sure.
It's a comical picture.
Yeah.
You could cut off the tail or the leg, it'll live, but you can't cut off the head.
That's the main receptor.
So its head would be Egypt.
Well, if we were to come to a conclusion right now, I would say the head of the African continent will be Egypt, not Libya, not Morocco.
Yeah.
That's what we said.
Yeah, if we were to sum things up.
So watch Egypt.
And just like I interjected earlier, if you see a leadership in Egypt that is grooming a woman, especially a daughter of a current leader, to rise into prominence of power, the time is nigh.
Right?
That's how you say it, right?
So, yeah.
By the way, I did that when the thing was going on in the Arab Spring.
I was hunting around all these Egyptian political figures and who their families were and if they had any daughters that were definitely post-pubescent but in their 20 range or so that were being groomed for political leadership.
I didn't see any.
Even though they did have daughters, I didn't see any of them that were 20, 25, 30 or so within the age of being taken seriously.
I don't think a 20-year-old woman on the world scene would be taken seriously, but a 30-year-old would, you see.
And I didn't see anyone like that.
So, again, using scripture rationale, I just said, no, there's no one around to have said.
None of this Arab Spring stuff that happened seven years ago was set into motion what we deem as prophetic, you know, the dynamics of prophecy taking place.
But is it dynamic for prophecy to take place?
Yes, of course.
All of this stuff, even stuff that happened 500 years ago is involved.
These are shadows.
You know how an object casts a shadow?
We're looking at the shadow without the object.
It's almost like an aberration, what's still happening right now in the world scene.
But it doesn't, I mean, this does not take away about the subject at hand, which is Egypt and northern part of Africa and all the countries involved.
But there's still, the important things to lay down the foundation is the rise of this power in the Middle East around, guess what, a temple in Jerusalem.
So, to give you an example, if you, right now let's say we have a conversation, let's just say arbitrarily, and there's a world figure right now that's influencing the world and there is no temple, he's not the Antichrist.
Even if he's Assyrian.
Because there's no temple yet.
Right.
There's no Assyria yet, you see.
So I'm sticking with scripture, you know.
I know you are also.
But, yeah, what of North Africa would be, if I were to title this, would be what of North Africa, right?
No, I'm just pointing to that as being something that can be observed.
And that it is a part of the time markers that when that region gets taken over, we're very close to seeing this guy move into Jerusalem and make that his capital.
Oh, yeah.
Theoretically it has relevance, yeah.
This is 10 years from now.
Yeah, I'm not saying that it's something to look at now.
I'm just saying that it can be observed as having relevance.
Do you want to get into a little bit of what can be looked at right now?
I haven't really studied anything connected to that right now.
Over the past week, these things kind of go in week by week.
There's three things always when you look at scripture to look at.
One is to look at nature, what nature is doing.
Because one of the things that prophecy, Christ said there will be great earthquakes and great signs in the sky, which is nature, right?
We're not talking about a big LCD plasma TV, right?
So we're looking at a natural phenomenon or the way that nature is going to be behaving, right?
None of that yet.
The other thing to look at is, you know, watch Israel, what's going on there.
And that means also spiritually, because the gods consider that the most important place on earth.
You know, I'm talking about the God of the Bible, not the other religions and stuff.
And the other thing to look at is the people's mindset towards the gods.
Now, each one of those shares a huge study.
We could discuss, you know, things that are happening on earth.
That's many, many hours to discuss.
You know, because that also involves the animal kingdom.
And I think in previous sonic events, I brought up salient points on that.
The point about Israel and what the gods consider to be a center, watch that, obviously.
And the mindset of humanity, of course, that has to be watched.
And what the mindset of humanity is right now is still, if you go out on the street, and this is important, I know that they don't matter, they really don't, not to me and not to the gods.
And they shouldn't, you know, the public at large is, you know, even if you want to know how to feel, whether you feel good or feel bad about how you view people, take yourself out of it and look at how the leaders of the people view them.
And don't sidetrack yourself and say, well, they're puppets and they're corrupt.
No, no, no, no.
It can't be that way for thousands of years.
The leaders of the people don't care about their own people.
Why should you?
I'm not saying that you should be cruel and nasty and thieving.
You should always be impeccable.
Forget about the masses.
They're finished.
They're just a blob, like the movie with Steve McQueen, The Blob.
Their own people, their own leaderships don't care about them at all.
So there's not much.
I had to throw that in there because it's very important to what I'm going to say next.
If you go out and speak to these people that no one cares about, they don't even care about their own children.
But anyway, ask them about the gods.
What reaction do you think you're going to get?
Either some stupid religion or I don't care, I don't know, or maybe one out of 10,000 I really want to know.
This is important.
That attitude will change.
Watch how that attitude changes.
That's what I mean about the mindset of the people.
In the future, I know it sounds kind of bizarre right now, people are going to take an interest in the quote-unquote gods in a very rational way, not the way they are right now.
That's part of prophecy.
Indirectly, there is no verse.
Greek, show me the verse where it says that.
The other thing is, of course, watch Israel.
That's the epicenter.
Not because of people, because obviously there are people in Russia, they think the epicenter is Moscow, Korea, they think it's Seoul.
Everyone thinks Tokyo and Japan.
No, I'm talking about what the gods think.
Watch what's going on in Jerusalem or Israel at large.
You know what else is another thing that we haven't gotten into that you might want to study maybe in the future or whatever, bring this up?
The fate of the Palestinians or the modern-day Philistines.
Very, very important.
I think in one of the books, I don't know if it's Jeremiah or Ezekiel or somewhere, that there's a reconciliation between quote-unquote Israel and Judah and the modern-day Philistines to the point where you cannot discern them apart.
They are almost acting as brothers.
It sounds insane when you look at the current situation, right?
Are you familiar with these verses that I just brought up?
I haven't studied them, but I know of them.
Okay, so the fate of the modern-day Palestinian or modern-day Philistine is very, very interesting because believe it or not, they are destroyed, by the way, when that kingdom come, right?
They are destroyed, if you remember the verses about that utterly, right?
But before that time, they act in unison with Israel.