and greetings folks and how are you folks tonight and we got Greek and Sam
online hi greetings everyone this is a ritual of rituals every week for the I
guess the anti pranking and let's inform some idiots on this planet about things
that they were in front of them that they never see anyway I don't know what
else we do we do how are you Sam I'm doing quite fine okay good it's on your
mind tonight uh-huh there's always things on my mind but specifically for
streaming purposes I guess we'll look at some things that I've been trying to
figure out this week and maybe you have something you want to bring up on your
own accord I will say that my week generally does consist of the familiar
to most people nine to five so studying has to kind of take a backseat I wish it
wasn't like that but like they say I'm so happy to get home after work that I
forget how pissed off I was all day so no wonder I keep going back right but
the people listening might know about work but I don't think they know about
studying mmm so and it take that whichever way you want to so good but I
do only have fortunately or unfortunately one sort of topic of
attention for this stream and after that I'll just have miscellaneous questions
that I tuck away for a rainy day or a Skype call with the Greek so I've been
thinking about the sort of coming religious abandonment that's the people
are going to be manifesting when things start to change based on what's
outlined in some of the minor prophets we can deduce that the world will soon
experience some kind of a reformation and spiritual understandings and they'll
abandon their religions and ultimately ancient history and these scriptures
will be held in the highest esteem and then once that happens everybody
realizes that contemporary religion is based on a mixture of paganism
Hellenism and ancient Greek philosophy and ignorance yes which is paganism
yeah that's right it's funny when people say I'm proud to be a pagan I'm
like you're stupid you just admitted to being stupid and I even you know when I
was doing the sonic events with Ocelli I was like you just admitted you're an
idiot that's okay next subject you know so and if people people not aware of the
gravity of what they're saying obviously when it comes to those things I want to
throw in an item there because I've been pondering this for over a decade it
doesn't say for how long they're going to leave their religions and acknowledge
the most high that there will be a more temporal let's say more permanent
situation of that in the future after the mop-up crew see I don't like calling it
the second coming or end times or all that because no one even knows what
those things mean I mean I know what they mean but when you tell people
phrases like that they just they glaze over you know like a donut so I just call
it the mop-up crew because they can attach that people are always
complaining about stuff and say oh it's not perfect it's not a fair world so when
you say mop-up crew they can attach that to their idiotic worldview whatever it
is pagan or they're just learning or they're not want to learn you see what
I mean so so when this acknowledgement I call it more of an acknowledgement than
the change of the world religions because remember when the mop-up crew comes when
they perform what they are going to do it has to be lawful because the logic
behind that is there there will be I'd ever read anywhere that they're gonna be
sniveling humans about why they did it obviously there's gonna be a lot of
contention about the situation but not about that so it has to be done when
it's lawful so how much does like a Catholic or Mormon or a Jew or Christian
or average pagan have to admit acknowledge the most high and the right
thing for how long it's not that they have to admit it and that's it
be all end all it's you know as a condition it just has to be admitted you
see it's like when when someone is in court for sentencing how long do they
have to admit that they're guilty they just have to say it right it's just a
passing moment it's a momentary thing so I'm not suggesting that the abandonment
of all these the pagan Catholicism and pagan whatever you see in the world is
going to be an absolute abandonment because there are places in scripture
that do state that they even after they acknowledge they go back to how they
were before and even worse I'm just paraphrasing right mm-hmm so I just want
to throw that in as an initial comment and what they're going to bring what I
suggest is going to be worse is they're going to do arrow duels and you know
which is basically temple prostitution overt sacrificing and all this other
stuff so so continue yeah as far as that goes I can definitely see there being
various subsections of people with varying degrees of responses to what's
happening you'll have people that will probably throw themselves headlong into
abandoning their religious convictions because they would have been set up that
way I mean it doesn't take much examination to realize there's a whole
lot of fraud being perpetrated and some people will want to get away from that
real quick and maybe some 80 year old Catholic lady that really felt like
Jesus is our Savior is probably going to come back and try and do some kind of a
syncretism between acknowledging the Most High and her old Catholic stuff
this probably be probably be a range of things and by the way I just want to throw
in since you brought that around I had once done a small restoration project
because old people like that do accumulate a lot of stuff and she got
stuffed in a nursing home and the only thing left was this little tiny piece
of furniture I restored it for it was about an 80 year old piece and I told
her the truth and she was in shock about everything and she was in her 80s
and this is over a decade ago and she was like oh I better find out more
about this and she was a very unique example of the human condition
regardless of her age but now that since you brought up the old Catholic lady I
have actual first-hand experience with one so good okay so it is positive but
usually the group as a whole is finished when you think of humanity and
wholesale it's like you know in certain archaeology and
architecture courses they take the the whole class for a tour at the landfill
because the best stuff you'll find in archaeology is at a landfill and
architects also like to look at landfills because it tells you a lot
about the culture so basically when you are about this is a the earth and
people are part of a spiritual landfill at the moment you see what I mean it's
all garbage so it doesn't take much they're still going to be in the landfill
even when they acknowledge but but go ahead I don't want to go off on too much
on what really is going on now let's just stay on the on the point about the
religion what else is on there about what else you got about it well it's
kind of clear that the prime prediction for all this is in Zechariah 12 and 13
so more specifically 12 10 to 13 6 so you would forget about the chapter
markers because that's just stuff the King James translators have put in there
arbitrarily but you have a sort of continuous account from 12 10 to almost
14 so right I shall pour on the house of David in the inhabitants of Jerusalem a
spirit of favor and prayers and they shall look upon me whom they have
pierced and they shall mourn for him as one mourns for his only son it's worth
noting noted noticing I think that the prophecy is concerning not only
Israelites but it says all the inhabitants of Jerusalem so I'm
guessing no matter who they are as far as race cultural religion right back to
geographic thing right back to the geography of things yes so if the whole
the whole population is going to have some kind of a spiritual rejuvenation to
understand and accept the truth and then I'm guessing that that will reverberate
around the world through the television the internet mass media and things like
that yeah so yeah people will begin to abandon what they previously right
whether it's momentary or daily or weekly for a period it's going to be for
a time just like they you know like if you bring up 9-11 right now anyone I was
15 years ago or people have a curiosity and the interesting thing about 9-11 is
if you brought up what happened the day or week of there were too much in the
shock to listen so either way whether you tell them when it's happening or
just after it happened or much later they're not going to get it but they're
going to be in some state like that if you know what I mean when they abandon
their religions you know I like using 9-11 it's a perfect metaphor for that
because it's sort of supernatural you know how can you take 200,000 tons of
steel and turn it into dust in eight seconds that's supernatural but it's not
but because of people's ignorance they they brush it away it's like oh no big
deal you see so this is going to be within that realm I suggest there it
won't be in so much that realm in the place in and in and near in about the
place of Jerusalem because I would suggest in order for a temple edifice to
be put together you can't build it on a cemetery over dead bodies that are
buried you know when even though whether you know it or not a temple will not be
allowed to be buried or built over a burial place right even if you even if
you you have to be absolutely sure that there are no bodies buried underneath
that edifice and what and you know how they you know how they do that they they
keep scraping all the every all the loose dirt until they get down to what
bedrock so there's some guy out there he's been a pretty good biblical
scholar for several decades he says oh it's going to be on the Mount of Olives
and you know I'm not going to say who it is you know who I'm talking about
right they they still have remnants of some guy that proponents of their work
Christians of course they're schizophrenic because they expound
Christianity but they say away with Christians do or bad okay all right so
schizophrenic so they say it's going to be built on the Mount of Olives oh really
so you're gonna scrape it down to bedrock and what do you see when you look
at the Mount of Olives except if you go on Google Earth you other than a
couple of apartments a couple of falafel places and and some small businesses
what is it what is it known for right cemeteries so so okay I'm giving a
little deep more detail than I need for the point the point is when you see a
dedication like a Hanukkah right to the temple you can't have churches and mosques
and you know all that pagan crap has to go you know the via de la Rosa and all
that crap that they have there you know that the a skepulous you know that that
Jesus stuff that has to be cleared out of there that's going to be the stuff to
really watch as your precursor to what you're doing with the topic at hand is
because it wouldn't be lawful in other words when you see the prediction or the
assumption and a strong presumption that there'll be a temple in the near future
will it be a lawful or unlawful one well I'll be lawful in order I just gave you
the requirements for it to be what you know for the temple will be lawful you
can't have pagan temples like churches yes if you listening for the first time
churches a pagan temple mosques are pagan temples so how are they going to
clear are they going to clear out all that filth and junk out of Jerusalem
well that's something to watch for I think it's going to be done using
natural either an earthquake there's someone wrote that there might be a
tsunami coming in well I'll be one hell of a tsunami or it might just be man
that does it in a fire or a riot kind of fervor that's been done before where
buildings have been burned down and tore down in a riot type situation so I'm just
stating these things as facts based on the requirements of certain things that
are viewed as facts right right so as a result the inhabitants whether they're
Jews or Muslims or Christians so-called they will presumably banish idolatry and
paganism from the region and it's also says in the prophecy that Yahweh himself
will rid the area of evil spirits would formerly been in that area who caused
these antagonisms and things to prevail and it shall be in that day that I cut
off the names of the idols from the earth and they shall be remembered no
more and I shall also remove the prophets and the unclean spirits from
the earth so there is a sort of more primary reason why you can't really get
anything done in Jerusalem at the moment because there's a spiritual
underpinning right in other words all that spiritual underpinning is based on
the law basically preconditions conditions and requirements for for
certain things to take place most people are not familiar with that by the way so
they think they've been so duped about spirituality think oh it's in your
heart or what you believe in they don't understand even though they see a
physical brick-and-mortar or pragmatic substantive representation of that you
know through iconography and whatever pagan crap they're doing they think it's
solely non-material but here we're I'm suggesting I think what you brought up
also Yahweh clearing the place out it's also you can't clear the spirits out and
leave the building you know what I mean so and also just one other thought it
like in Europe you have a lot of churches in America there's a lot of
churches when it happens there what do you think is going to happen to the ones
everywhere else I'm not saying that it will but I'm just that'll be quite a day
I think I've mentioned before the Vatican will be a discotheque they
already have all the sodomites and the cocaine in there all they got to do is
put up some ball and some lights and it anyway good well actually the Vatican is
interesting because they would have to probably turn on themselves that's
interesting and they already are but like violently I don't know if the
priesthood I don't know if the state Italian state will come in and take the
moderates they'll blow themselves up I don't know well they're a city-state
like Washington DC and the city of London and you know they'd have to ask
for help yeah and they might it depends it's gonna be you know it you know how
they say may you live in interesting times it's gonna be so interesting but
I'm suggesting and I've been on the record for many years saying when these
things happen no matter how extreme no one's gonna really notice anyway because
of the cosmic censorship they're gonna be led to it being okay and the metaphor
there as you know how many times have you I've got on the record saying if you
took a newspaper and sent it back in a time machine you know a newspaper from
today or last week or last year send it back 50 or 100 years it would completely
and it was known it would stop the entire society and they would say we
have to stop everything so these things don't happen so I think you've also said
things to the effect in the past that people it's gonna come a time globally
will people like the rabbis and priests and preachers and imams and things of
that nature will be shown to be false teachers and the prophecy specifically
does talk about that they will be so ashamed of their previous positions that
they'll pretend to have been something else like farmers or something right man
of the light working the land yeah and when I remember if you look at that
closely maybe this is not the right time to do it and that's right not the
right time for me to bring it up because I haven't looked at that many years but
that is a twofold thing that happens twice by the way in other words I think
it was in Isaiah and someone else's something similar to that but if you in
other words they will they will initially state that and then they will
go back to it and then it either after the you know the first resurrection
because most people think you know when the mop-up crew comes it's going to be
hunky-dory right it's not it's going to be pretty crappy on earth for at least
70 years if not more so but you'll be taken care of whoever you is so there'll
be a time then as well you see but anyway continue and it just let's just
bring this up as something to revisit in the future because I have to get all my
in a row to present that yeah my studying hasn't been thorough enough to
have details on that but I've seen it because you have the same similar things
being said in Isaiah 25 27 and it toggles back and forth and sometimes it
seems to be talking about this period and then other times it will say in that
day and usually in that day is millennial kingdom cleanup and it's
saying some similar things then so you kind of get confused like what's it
talking about which way it's the exact time right well you'll know that well
either way you know there is a time coming that's to expect that whether it's
a single fold expression of that condition or a dual fold expression of
that condition so specifically and it shall be when one prophesies again that
his father and mother who brought him forth shall say to him you shall not live
because you have spoken falsehoods in the name of Yahweh and his father and
mother who brought him forth shall pierce him through when he prophesied
that's interesting and it shall be in that day that the prophet shall be
ashamed and everyone of his vision when he prophesied and not shall not put on a
hairy robe to deceive but shall say I am no prophet I am a farmer for a man sold
me as a slave in my youth and one shall say to him what are these wounds on your
hands and he shall say because I was wounded at home by those who love me
I'm not sure about that last bit what they're saying there but piercing is
well you have to you have to take it this way you know what's if you've
spoken falsely against Yahweh it's a form of blasphemy or blasphemy in itself
like you know yeah first degree second degree third degree right and that's
capital punishment but because it's a high level you're pierced in other words
instead of being just stoned be usually when there was a stoning they beat you
up right or cut your kill I don't want to get into cut your Achilles tendon so you
can't run I mean there's a lot of if you want to there's not much on the
internet by the way but there's a lot of historical stuff on how stoning was done
through the ages right and make a long story short here real short it was
always death by stoning but when you were pierced it showed that you had no more
free will to move meaning that you were pinned down to something you see or it
was usually a tree or a stake or something that you can you know it's
going to be difficult to drive a nail through someone into stone so you need
some kind of a cellulose type material or something you can you know drive usually
wood is the best material to nail into right I mean you can come up with
certain modern composites that you can nail into but wood is still the best so
it was typically a tree and usually when it was a big show they nailed you
to a cross beam and then they put a rope on that and they put the rope over a
branch and lynched it up they pulled you up at a good height right and then when
you got to the finished height they tied off the rope and then they nailed your
feet so you wouldn't dangle I just gave you a description of how the Messiah was
and with two others on the same tree left and right so but but in the case of
Stephen they didn't do that they just don't know they just stoned him out
right yeah in other words they threw him a pretty good beating and then stoned
him on the spot he wasn't pierced right and Paul was not pierced either they just
don't mm-hmm yeah usually to get pierced you you are it's a more formal display
of your crime where with Paul and Stephen it was okay we had enough for
this asshole you know so it would be just like now or even not even so much
go to the Western movies in the u.s. and they just shot you right you were in the
bar you had a fight and they shot you right there or outside where when it was
more formal it was a firing squad where you were actually tied to a pole with a
bag over your head but either way you're shot right you see the analogy
when it's an official execution by firing you were tied to a stake with a
bag you know you've seen that you've heard of it or seen the depictions of
that where many people were shot because of the group you know had enough of this
guy run in his mouth right so this is a little more formal it seems or it seems
like the people are taking the law into their own hands it seems versus taking
it to a priest so this is one of the fine points in the scripture where it
needs to be read in context and move further along but you know a lot of the
things that we just I just mentioned the past few minutes I've said before but I
think I threw in a little more detail so whether you apply it to what we're
discussing right now in Zachariah or just the general concept of how
executions capital punishment was done I think it's it's all right to say what
I just said so okay go ahead that's fine so I'm guessing then that the end of
this sort of versus saying that these guys will have been people will have
attempted to kill them or stone them but they will have failed and that's why
they have these hand piercings and then when they're asked about it they're
gonna lie and say well I was wounded at home I don't know why you would say I
was wounded at home by those who love me well who's speaking there who's
speaking there is an interesting thing it's a farmer guy yeah yeah I know that
it's it's but who is speaking really I mean you know how when you look at the
Psalms I'm not suggesting this I need to go back and look I'd like to do a study
on the book of Zechariah I'm glad you're bringing it up but you know when you read
the Psalms a lot of people have done studies on the Psalms like well this is
the Christ speaking through David right or it's the psalmist because there's a
what five or six or seven psalmists in there so so we need to look at just the
condition right now that you're bringing up and you know who's you know who's
saying yeah that's it that's an interesting thing to look at you know is
it the Christ speaking through there you know is he the one that's speaking
against Yahweh no so that has to be examined the translation needs to be
examined yeah but we know that it's the former pastor Ramon that's me so far
yeah so far because remember the Christ in in historically was considered to be
one of these even though he wasn't right if you read a historical accounts
outside of Scripture they paint him in a very negative light as you know a
negative spiritual character there is history in Scripture by the way most
people think it's all this stuff but there is the history that the gods are
concerned with you won't find iPhones and airplanes and trains and vaccines in
there actually you will find vaccines indirectly but anyway do we have an
exact time when this will happen as far as you know yeah after after 2025 yeah
and I know not an exact date but a time after this said this is after the
seven-year period is over yeah and when this seven-year period is over there
will be without a shadow of a doubt you will see that coming like just like you
would see you know the weather coming if you had access to you know weather
maps right this is this is forecasting with accuracy so this is the seven-year
period that's going to set everyone up in a Hollywood style fashion mind
control the I saw someone in chat I just want to NLP neuro linguistic
programming this is people talk about brainwashing you know from intelligence
agencies government religion whatever any authority brainwashes the public oh
you ain't seen nothing yet talk about brainwashing but at the same time
there's going to be expansion of the consciousness meaning you know what you
think about what you know into this direction of what's lawful what's you
know proper and changes yeah because remember as things come more and more
further after the 2025 2026 period no one's complaining about being deceived
you ever notice that so because the propaganda is so strong but it's also
backed up it's not pure propaganda because pure propaganda is just that
it's going to be backed up by substance and signs and visions and testimony of
these things and visual you know you know YouTube's on it right so yeah let me
just throw this in again I've said it maybe a thousand times that you're being
played folks you're being played but you're not being played by some scumbag
whatever attorney or mobster or punk you're being played by the gods so don't
feel bad but you're being played so in other words you're being set up to be
punked and it's well-deserved by the way so okay good so once people begin
learning these things as we've said they'll be predictably upset that they
haven't comprehended how simple in plain the truth is compared to the
traditional stuff that they've been fed and I would imagine that there would be
a fallout I mean I don't I haven't been to any of the Asian countries but it'll
be interesting to see for example how things would unfold there horribly
horribly for the monks and the religious authorities yeah but anyway people are
not familiar what they do to when the Asians get upset but I kind of respect
them for that like you know you could look this up if there's a corrupt
policeman in the name you know it's not like America the Western world they just
complain and the attorney that the cop is working for laughs at everybody no no
they know they find out where this guy lives and they pull him out of his house
and beat him to death right so you could look this up don't don't you know in Asia
so yeah they're gonna be what they're going to be dipped dipped and dived for
just like a lot of white people are non-white non-asians let's say you know I
don't know if you're born there and you're white or you're an Asian I guess
so but a lot of non the the stupidity of ancestral worship you know people say oh
I asked my I heard this white guy actually from Sweden he's saying that
you know I'm looking for help from my dead parents and I'm like you're an
idiot you know and all this you know you know this the typicals you know
religious stuff that comes out of Asia there's a lot of quote-unquote white
people or non Asians that have fallen for that stupidity too but they're they're
living in a different culture in a Western culture they're not going to
react like the Asians will in their culture so they will climb the Himalayas
and grab those monks and throw them off the cliffs yes they will so so yeah I
mean the follow-up for the Joel Osteen's and the ayatollahs of the world won't be
so nice but what will be understood is the fact that the religious leaders have
been very ignorant of what's in their professed text not just in terms of
pushing traditions like Christmas or Ramadan but you also have things like
Christians essentially teaching that the spirit is immortal when it says
very clearly in 1st Timothy that only God is immortal or Yahweh is immortal
right and they can't even define the spirit or the soul they interchange it
that's yeah so now we're going to talk about crazy people which is okay I'm
okay with it because Christians are just insane that's a that's easy to
surmise and it doesn't mean if you're insane you cannot ever be sane you can
but you you know if you talk crazy shit believe in crazy shit and don't want to
look up what you you know whatever you're you're crazy right it's pretty
simple doesn't mean that it's a terminal so the leaders of these people are
going to be held at a higher responsibility obviously and the
intention is not to dwell overly on that but there is an aspect of it that should
be looked at the fact that the on sort of the what they call the Jewish or the
Islamic side people are very ignorant of their own history of Jerusalem and they
don't even for example know where the Temple of Solomon was built or stood so
I'm right and the reason specifically though isn't I mean yeah you could say
that they're stupid or that they're crazy specifically though it's because
as Isaiah says in chapter 29 for Yahweh has poured out on you the spirit of deep
sleep and has covered your eyes the prophets and he has covered your head
the seers and the entire vision of you is like the words of a book that is
sealed which men gave to one who knows books saying read this please and he
said I'm unable to read it for it is sealed and the book is given to one who
does not know books saying read this please and he said I have not known
books or basically I can't read which is kind of reminiscent of Greek speak
right or vice versa yeah I can't read it because I'm illiterate or I can't read
it because I'm blind yeah they have a spirit of deception that's been placed
on them which is why they don't know anything that's right that's right it
doesn't mean that you have to be and once you're aware of it you can wrestle
with it by the way and I mean that literally in your mind you know so
correct me if I'm wrong because as far as the temple stuff goes I have not had
enough time to look into it but I believe that the original temples were
situated on the southeastern ridge of the plateau that Jerusalem is on yeah
which is Ernest Martin and there's three other people in the 20th century who
came up with that it's not just Ernest Martin by the way but he's he's done the
most work on it and I could pull up their names by if you give me some time I
looked at these notes I did about five years ago on literary proofs or literary
apologetics on where the temple was and you know that was discussed as early as
the 1920s so okay yeah it was there for the simple reason that I figured out it
was there on my own initially without the details that after studying these
other men was through the prop the two prophecies that state Jerusalem be
plowed like a field and not one stone will be like left upon another and also
the third thing is that everything I was taught was a lie so and also the first
thing that I came up with to read on a on the temple was when I what's the
first thing if you want to look at a historical account of that time you're
going to run across our good friend Joe Josephus right and what did Josephus
write in one of his works he's been to Egypt he saw the temples and they're
nothing as an engineering marvel compared minimal compared to the
structure at the temple now when you look at that pile of rocks they call the
temple does does that look more astounding than the temple than the
pyramids of Giza no way not at all so there must have been something there
that was so far more interesting you see
absolutely so um in that case as far as a location that would have been where
the city of David was next to Mount Zion with the which is being on when you say
city of David that would be like the size of your average city park right now
and I'm not talking about the big parks talking like you know maybe a would be a
modern Cartesian square block or two you know because you could put a hundred
houses on a square block you know all around four sides let's say right so
when we say these things they're very small like Jerusalem is what not even 20
acres 30 acres you know or hectares of 15 hectares or you can it's very small
but good so yeah but before it so on when the city in order to destroy the
city of David it would take no low no less than or no more than a hundred or
two hundred people with pry bars that are about as you know a little more than
waist-high and a couple of donkeys and maybe 24 hours
hmm right and a simple a zippo you know what a zippo is right lighter cigarette
lighter okay no it doesn't seem like a size sizable camp but yeah so its
absence is no is there's no big deal it was our construction it could be
rebuilt in a month and the current religious authority seemed to be quite
unequated with that as well as the prophecies of the destruction of Mount
Zion and not Ophel where the temples were located which would have happened I
think in sometime in the Simon the Maccabee era last part in the second
century BC so that particular destruction you can find that in Isaiah
29 but what's also stated is that Yahweh would cause them all to be blinded so
that they would sort of forget about it and for 2,000 for 2,000 years right so
um the particular verses pertaining to this is woe to Ariel woe to Ariel the
city where David dwelt and year to year let the festivals come around I shall
distress Ariel and there shall be mourning and sorrow and it shall be to
me as Ariel Isaiah 29 so what it seems to be addressing here is that Yahweh is
going to personally bring about some kind of a distress to Ariel and I guess
you would have to ask what is Ariel and what what I found is that it's a
symbolic name for both Jerusalem and the altar itself a burnt offering in the
temple sometimes the temple itself there seems to be an overlap but Ezekiel
does make it clear in chapter 43 that what Ariel is the altar because it says
the aerial or the altar of L is 12 cubits by 12 cubits and as describing
the dimensions and what it actually says is the aerial the aerial 12 long by 12
wide and I believe aerial is derived from the word are you are you meaning
lion so the altar literally means the line of L every L and that seems to be
it's a metaphor for perhaps the Holy of Holies or his central location because it
also denotes a place of fire or a place of cleansing but continue yeah so
basically what he's saying is that he's gonna put Jerusalem and the temple upon
the altar of burned offerings so that the city and the temple will become an area
and that would be destroyed in a similar manner that the altar flames consume
sacrifices seems to be what it is and then the following verse shows Yahweh
marshalling some kind of siege and other destroying machines against the city of
David in the temple I shall encamp against you all around and I shall lay
siege against you with a mound and I shall raise siege works against you so
on and so forth and then it talks about the city being destroyed and then
everything in that area will be lowered to the ground and submerged into the
bedrock until there's nothing left and I think we can see overlaps with Simon
the Hasmonean events in the second century BC because I think that there
were Gentiles Syrian Gentiles who had been living in the city of David for some
couple of decades and that created a conflict between the Judeans trying to
use the temple and these Gentiles and then if you see the destruction of the
area as Yahweh evicting these strangers then that's a fulfillment of that
prophecy because they do get kicked out and it was it was also voluntarily
dismantled and put back together because it was I think in Isaiah it was inhabited
by evil spirits right they were summoned meaning on the lower parts you
know right oh yeah I think there's and you know there's stories about a pig
being sacrificed their stories I mean you know left and right about it but but
either way there was definitely cosmic censorship and but these events did
happen and the temple is not what people you know are told politically it is or
religiously mm-hmm today right so the specific verses the multitude of your
strangers that is to say Zion strangers or the city of David strangers shall be
small like dust and the multitude of the terrible ones shall be as chaff that
passes away and it shall be in an instant suddenly thou shall be visited
by Yahweh with thunder and an earthquake and great noise and storm and tempest
and flames of devouring fire and I think that we do there is some historical
records of an earthquake hitting Jerusalem at that point and also a fire
being the city being torched with fire soon after that so you can also see that
as being a continuation of that prophecy fulfillment it wasn't I don't know if it
was as big as the earthquake that happened the time of Isaiah in that you
read about in Amos that is brought up in other places as well but it was more
local but I have run into articles that were written about historical I haven't
seen the historical you know we know we're more direct actual history but
just articles about the weather in the time period then the earthquakes were
happening all through the first millennium there one report is you know a
along the Jordan Valley there was an earthquake and a schism opened up and
fire was coming out of it for 40 years you know I mean does that sound like an
exaggeration yes but nonetheless it's not good
yeah I've also read that at a later time the waters of the Gihon spring became
quite bitter to drink and later showed up would speculate that it was inhabited by
demons because they couldn't use water for anything so that would also be in
line with the prophecy about familiar spirits speaking from the ground and
occupying the region which is yeah Isaiah 29 4 or 5 or something and your
voice shall be like that of a medium out of the ground and your speech shall
whisper out the dust so yeah and also be aware folks this is a repeat of this
currently you know and when I go out into public I see it literally I see
people speaking and they don't know what they're saying but I'm not talking just
like you know some trashy thing or whatever I'm talking about like someone
who's a university astronomer and I'm not even part of the conversation to and
to instigate a little Greek you wrote in the wrong way so here's the thing it
was two people talking me and I was out of the way listening so imagine if I
went in there holy crap I didn't you know so right and like I said before
Isaiah 25 repeats a lot of this stuff that you have these walled cities that
will be brought down made into turn into dust and he lays the exalted city low
and so on and I think the city of David was at one point higher than even the
temple mount it was pretty elevated so you could say that that's being referred
to there also because they cut it down to the bedrock and actually submerged it
so all of this is probably what is eventually going to be understood once
this rejuvenation comes to Jerusalem and the censorship that the Jews and the
Muslims you have regarding the temple I mean that's intriguing it's an
intriguing showcase of how hopeless human beings are in the face of
external input because the temple never seems to be central to their way of life
the Judeans whether they were living in the region or whether they were living
abroad whether they were righteous or heretical whether they were secular or
following the law or whether they were young or old didn't really matter so it
would seem inconceivable that you know just a few years of Babylonian captivity
or problems at any other period of time when the temples were not operating
normally would have allowed the whole nation to forget where it stood for
almost 800 years but not only did the Israelites forget but even the Arabs
forgot because the temple was an international thing like everybody
knew where it was as a political group they did but there's always been
certain individuals that had gone to Jerusalem on a pilgrimage and did not go
up to that Fort Antola where they call the Dome of the Rock they went down by
the Gihon Spring there's always records of people know this is the other thing
when we speak about these things you know even cosmic censorship it's in
wholesale terms but not everyone you see but those those that are not the
everyone's are such a small group it's insignificant it's almost like not
having might as well say that they don't even exist that's how minor they
are there's always a witness by the way if you know what I mean right you even
if you don't know about it right that's why you know I tell people you know if
someone says I'm the only one who does that well there's just someone else you
just haven't heard of because typically there's a duplicity in this this thing
we call existence you know you know there's there's always going to be I
shouldn't say that in a way for sure but there's there's more than one you even
though you're just hearing one yeah it has been known but you know what do you
do you live in a community that says the temple is up here and you say no it's
not you'll be ostracized yeah but fortunately now you people can work a
job or a job and make enough to go about their own personal life with less
personal interaction I mean with less interaction with others that about their
personal life right I mean like one perfect thing would be to live in an area
and work out of the house or where you live so you don't have to interact with
these scumbags but that sounds rather antisocial Greek well you know what
you know everybody's got their own perspective on it I guess but I did that
once it was nice yeah it is it is it's quite cool actually we're a deserted
island and then they come to rescue you're like no we throw rocks at them go
home leave me alone leave me alone they're like no you got to come with us
because the attorneys can't get you from here well that's about all that I
have on this topic I mean it's fairly straightforward as far as just reading
the prophecies it's interesting like I said that they haven't picked up on it I
mean like you said there's always going to be select individuals or smaller
groups and I know that the rabbis have their sort of secrets that they keep I'm
sure that to some extent they know about it but it's not openly acknowledged I
think even if you read the the targums and the midrash they don't really
address this prophecy they're explicit in any explicit way it's just touched
upon lightly but they don't explain anything so even in their own yeah it's
it's just glossed over because if they looked at it they know that the temple
was not the domes rock but oh yeah oh yeah that's and it is quite well known I
think I've read brought up this story before I was once in California I was
speaking to a former Merced guy who was in the IDF and his I'm not going to give
I don't think well I'll give more detail his when his dad was a rabbi and when
his dad died 30,000 people came to the funeral so he was a popular rabbi right
and when I explained to him where the temple was he started crying and I
thought it was because of a quote-unquote religious faithful you
know revelatory moment of acknowledgement right and I said I'm
sorry it's so emotional to you he says well let me tell you why it's emotional
to me he says because there have been soldiers in the IDF Air Force that were
ready to do a suicide run with an f-16 jet into the temple of the mount to
destroy it to bring about you know apocalyptic you know a change and we had
to go and shoot them down and and he knew some of those guys that did that so
in other words because they're people are being lied to where it is you have
these suicidal types in the military that have access to it by the way if you
you know you people say about what do we do about chemtrail planes well it's up
to the mill you some if you have a true patriot in the US Air Force to go up
there and take one of those planes down I don't mean shoot it down but bring it
down you know what I mean but you they don't exist right it's America whatever
but he had mentioned to me that there were people in the Israeli military that
were planning on doing suicide runs on the temple mount what they call a temple
mount to cleanse it your change the condition there and they were taken up
by their own people that's why he was emotional about it it seemed like the
information of it not being the temple at all was secondary to his own personal
grief of that situation which is not discussed by the way this you don't hear
oh yeah we had to kill some Israeli IDF because they were planning on blowing up
the temple mount you know that doesn't quite make the news if you know what I
mean so I wanted to share that with in this sonic I think I have before so
that's an aspect of the grief it can cause right if you have a religious
zealot now their zealoty and their fervor is misdirected it's a waste of
time again isn't it where if they actually these religious zealots knew
where the temple was they would say well holy crap we can build it at any time
all we got it I think I think it's either a heritage site now or it's owned
by some Palestinian farmers or people I think but I think it's a heritage site
though meaning it's it's not considered to be under private ownership you know
but you know they know what to do the guy go if it's owned by a private
Palestinian the guy goes to sleep he wakes up dead you know that's that's how
these things work you know what I mean this is the world that you know he slips
on a banana peel or dies in a car accident you know these things are
strange how how human life is not regarded by the gods you know the gods
any God has no problem with taking out people for even no reason so that we
that we can see this is something people have to keep in the back of their minds
you're we're all expendable yeah they offer protection until your job is done
for them and then when you're done you're disposed of or dispatched to the
resurrection when I the reason why I say dispatch the resurrection because when
you're dead you have no consciousness so there might be a magneto dielectric
perception when you die that you hover over your body for a few seconds when
whatever demons are oppressing you or following you around grab that field and
push it around and you could see for a moment but then it's lights out or bright
light which is the ATP in the imploding in the body which is what keeps cells
going you know phosphates so anyway there's anyway that's just a counter a
little bit of the stupidity of the new age stuff well I'm good on this topic
unless there's something else you want to look at I'm kind of depleted
otherwise Oh except for some miscellaneous things here or there
speaking of looking at I brought up to someone earlier this is a total
lascivious talking about in my early days you know 60s and 70s an old man
gave me a World War two memorabilia and what was in there was put pin-up girls
if anyone remembers the concept of a pin-up girl giving the soldiers and one
of them was postcards and pinups of Virginia Bell so you guys look up
Virginia Bell and I brought this up to someone earlier here today we were
talking about you know World War two you know 1940s 1950s eras pinups so that's
something to look at what anyway it's nothing new you know what I mean by the
pinups you know they send soldiers a pretty girl those usually soft dick you
know if you know so anything to look at no there's always other than the
constant random stupidity on the it's easy to banter on these constant random
stupidity on the rectangle but you know what the newspapers are even worse and
the periodicals are even worse so you know print I think food clothing and
shelter is still the should be the paramount pursuit of upping the quality
of those things and it's not a trivial pursuit by the way and make make busy
time until your time is over otherwise and you know there's a lot to discuss on
food clothing and shelter and health and upping the quality of that
consistently I mean you know how in scripture it said that Christ did so
many things he filled so many books right you could fill all the books I mean
we can discuss from now till 2025 without stopping except for drinking
water on how to up food of clothing and shelter right that seems to be an
interesting thing always to discuss another thing to discuss is what's
coming with more detail and I'm always hesitant on doing I'd like to be more
redundant at this point because I don't I think that the the stuff that I brought
up is light years or miles ahead of anything else there's no reason to go
into more detail but there will be a reason to go into more detail in the
near future when I myself personally get more information from what's how it's
going to come you know what I mean so instead of giving out a myriad of
details now that might need some adjustment in the next year or two in
terms of the you know imparting the information of the details I'd rather
wait because there's going to be an opening up of certain quote-unquote
books and knowledge in this area to give more detail on so the only other thing I
would say about what's coming is if you are a student of prophecy which most
people hate that but most people you get a lot of lip service on they want to
learn and study but most people you know that's you know how you know you
know how I why I say that that most people actually hate finding out the
truth it doesn't matter what they say look at what they what what they do and
there's almost other than you and maybe one other that I don't see anyone really
studying or really putting something and this is not to disparage those that are
not I haven't you know haven't displayed it but I don't see much develop even on
the rectangle if you go on the rectangle and look up prophecy or biblical studies
it's still the same garbage that's always been on there so I think do you
want to be a garbage you know pick up crew you know like you ever see the guys
in parks with the bag and the spike and they pick up all the litter or do you
want to find some clean ground and start doing some pretty good study you know I
think the second is always best but and I don't think the time for that is still
yet to go into deeper study and then of course the book of Revelation is still
off-hands publicly I probably will always be I would like to pursue the
book of Zechariah in concert with of course you have to harmonize it to the
rest of scripture in concert though with the book of Daniel which by the way the
book of Daniel doesn't really come into play until after 2025 2027 even do you
know what I mean because it's the it's the last dynamic because if you read the
book of Daniel it's very dynamic you know what I mean and the dynamics don't
start until that time period you know the dynamic attributes of what they call
the Antichrist or instead of Christ yeah he's 20 years old right now yeah so if
you want to if you want to go to every world database and find every Assyrian
male that was born between 1997 in the year 2000 that would cover all of them
you could pin it you could find them pretty wouldn't be too hard I'm not
talking about remember that movie The Omen you know let's go find me you know
the son of Satan he's not the son of Satan by the way so anyway that's an
interesting thing of research look around for an exceptional 20 year old
Assyrians on the internet I don't know Facebook Twitter whatever website you
got some whiz kid kind of thing you know I'm using the term kid literally here
you know I mean or you know he's going to be a very upstanding individual
actually not a kid actually you might want to call him human he's probably in
the media right now and you don't even know it who this leader will be and the
reason I'm bringing this up is not to create a you know an air of intrigue
around this character but just to show you how there is no dynamics until after
that that relate to the book of Daniel after 2025 2027 around there in you know
and when I use those years they start in the spring like for example 2018 hasn't
really started yet right I mean starting soon it starts in the spring right so and
this is an interesting time period also watch for very this is I'm gonna I'll go
on I didn't want to I was thinking I've been researching this now for about six
months and I'm gonna go on the line and say it look for very rapid military
movements known as aggressive movements this year starting in the spring and
going till next spring or in and around the area of Israel you know what I mean
by that is like false flags assassinations political moves political
changes quite possibly I wouldn't say more than 50-50 the monarchy and Jordan
will be expelled around this time I wouldn't say that could happen even in
the next you know seven years from now but that would be an interesting thing
and the reason I'm bringing this up again is a few weeks ago there was an
article of the monarchy and Jordan had to expel his members of his family for
forming a violent coup against him right you could look this up it didn't
make you know front-page news but it was in the Jordanian Times I think or
whatever I'm on whatever is the name of the paper in Arabic so this is a year of
right now I would look for very rapid changes things that don't make sense what
I mean about false flags you know the Illuminati Illuminati's right and the
Freemasons and these guys guess what who's bidding they can't do anything
unless they're allowed to do it by various spiritual elements that are you
know taking marching orders from the most high so and what I mean by a false
flag is do you remember there was a Palestinian and alleged Palestinian
vest suicide bomber about five or six years ago blew themselves up it wasn't
in Jerusalem but nearby I think in a tour bus on a busy street you said well
you know well Greek that happens all the time they were not really haven't been
any lately like that but why when I say false flag is the reports that came out
from boots on the ground there was a shop owner about 20 or 30 meters
downstreet from that explosion and when the security came around he they came in
and guess that collected body parts right because they had come through the
window but those body parts were frozen solid so what so okay for those of you
that need for me to piece it together for you no pun intended they loaded up
the bus with frozen cadavers and blew it up you get it anyway so who's they I
don't know was there a suicide bomber or not I don't know but I could tell you
from boots on the ground report was a frozen forearm and a frozen tibia came
through the window frozen solid and that doesn't happen in summer you know or
late spring Israel you know you don't have people walking around hard as rock
so so even even though that obviously was a false flag of some sort it did have a
political effect so don't mind the false flag aspect what I'm saying is watch out
for all of it right and even if it's shown to be a false like it still has a
political impact like give another commentary like right now they're
saying Netanyahu might be indicted by the police right I just saw that is yeah
that's completely the police have no authority to do that by the way it's
such a joke but you know everyone buys it because you know how I know everyone
buys it because no one knows the law the police don't work for the police don't
have any power like that even in Israel but that's what they're putting out
there because it's time for him to go it could be the tooth fairy is indicting
him and everyone would say yes he's being indicted he's a bad guy by the
tooth who's indicted tooth fairy but it doesn't matter even if you see so what I
mean how ridiculous is please can't indict anybody they're an agency they
work for the attorney but but that's what they're putting out and that's you
know so what it doesn't matter if it's you see how you know I mean anyway you
know this is a giving example you know you have a lot of people coming out in
the community now called whistleblowers you know of course of them
most of them are fake but you know how you know you got a genuine wish little
government whistleblower one of their first things and I thought the first
thing on the early in their impartment of what their purpose of speaking as
they call everyone and anyone working in their agency an idiot or stupid I'm
serious if you start saying here I'm a whistleblower from this agency or that
agency and they're doing this if they're they're not real but when you know you
got a real one when he says yeah I work for this agency and they're all a bunch
of idiots and you know if they didn't have guns and it's such bad things it
would be laughable right yeah okay yeah there so there you got how you have a
good testimony there and and I'm saying this from first-hand experience I've run
into guys you know various agencies and when you sit down so I said they're all
a bunch of idiots you didn't say some of them it's just like if you know people
in the military army Air Force Marines whatever that are not just grunts you
know like officers if you've ever read I've known people who had relatives and
they write lettered back letters back whether it's from Afghanistan Iraq or
where have you and they said there were their their own men are more dangerous
than the enemy and their own men are killing more of his own men than the
enemy is every time and what you don't hear about that so anyway so I'm just
saying it because it's true no it's verifiable it's fine I just have one
last sort of biblical related thing because it's certain things I don't know
I guess it tickles certain sensibilities I've brought up the
Leviathan thing before and you gave a little bit of exposition on it we
couldn't really nail anything down specifically maybe it has a horn maybe
it doesn't but then I saw it in a different place when I'm reading up on
this Isaiah Zachariah prophecy more suit it's maybe a little more supernatural
than we thought right but go ahead well I don't know exactly what it is I mean
you come across in Isaiah 27 I was fishing around and just randomly came
across it in that day Yahweh shall visit with his sword hard great and steadfast
upon the Leviathan the fugitive serpent the torturous serpent and he will kill
the monster which is in the sea so what does this have to do with some random
sea monster because now it's almost speaking of it like it's the Nakash
using the word Nakash what do you know about Greek mythology and the sea
monster and what do you know about Canaanite mythology and the sea monster
what do you know about there are no accounts of Israelites going to the sea
as if they were almost didn't they're afraid of it the Danites did yeah they
did but you didn't see other you know you didn't see them as a group there
were on foot 99% of the time and 94% of them 99% of the time right let's see 90
yeah 93% of them 99% of the time are on foot unless they're walking on water no
pun intended yeah and what do you know about the the
God of the Canaanite God of the sea think about it actually not much do a
live search it sounds like you're in front of the rectangle I'm not I'm ready
to go outside for a moment and come back in I shouldn't lose reception but what
was there a Canaanite God of the sea I think it starts with a T or an A I think
it starts with a T this is gonna require some research yeah we're talking about
gods you know now or so we're you know are we crazy because we're talking about
things we can't see right now you know anyway I have a God called yeah God of
the sea yeah that's that's the one yeah you know come after your ass very
aggressive at the at a certain time period especially during the time of
Abraham and that such it was very aggressive I don't have any images
well I don't think anyone does and if they are they're contrived well it seems
as if Yahweh doesn't like him very much and I'm guessing I don't think Yahweh
likes anyone anymore but anyway no it takes a lot to please him at this point
because he's imagine someone that you like is standing in a landfill do you
really want to spend time looking at them you know it's like come on get out
of there already you know he doesn't have a lot of gods that he points out by
name and says that he has an issue I think Moloch is one but I don't think he
ever says he's gonna kill Moloch personally he does not saying no no hold
on a second I'm not saying that Yom is Leviathan and vice versa or any but I'm
just saying it is pretty flippin interesting to look at the condition you
know what I mean so what else Leviathan comes up about four times in scripture
five but he's always he's always painted as something undesirable that has to be
conquered yes so I don't yeah it's all very vague information but um you know
yeah for now it is vague mm-hmm but what I find I you know I can't it's hard to
reconcile this idea of the Nakash in Genesis being anthropomorphic but then
you're calling the Leviathan Nakash and that's not anthropomorphic presumably
right so you can't have it be both ways Nakash has to be of a certain is
apparently a certain species of Elohim it'd be nice to establish what that is
you can't have it be well Nakash is also isn't Nakash somewhere also translated
as divination or sorcery in the Old Testament in context in that context
well here's the interesting thing you know there's a certain arrogance about
living in this time period right now when I say arrogance I mean it goes back
to like that when the founding of the modern religions that we that are around
Islam modern Judaism and Christianity there's an arrogance instilled in that
right mm-hmm I'm not talking about the
stupidity of it I'm talking about the arrogance now you see what I mean the
pride and arrogance of it so the I think that that persistence of that pride and
arrogance and stupidity you know at tag it along you know it's it's okay to be I
don't know anyway like stupid people don't know they're stupid right but to
proud people know they're proud I would suggest that yes I would suggest that as
as time goes on we're gonna get a little more information on this and and you
know what you're ready I'll even go out on a limb and say this we might even get
manifestation of it so I mean there's always been very prominent snake worship
cults in most countries as far as go stretching back to ancient times so
there's something to trigger if something does manifest well the snake
was associated with the breath in ancient Egypt right I shouldn't say right
like it was wholeheartedly but if you study I don't even like to go in on
Egypt ology because it's such a fine line you know because it's such rubbish that's
out there it was associated with various aspects of life and more
specifically the what they call what we call the soul or the breath right that's
why you saw it on the Pharaoh's headdresses and things like that it was
not in certain Native Americans also associated with that they were I think
in Egyptian hieroglyphics a snake is written as the footless one you know but
you know by the way I'm just going to give a private thing I meditate on off
and you know what what I'm going to say sorry about that water there what I'm
going to say I'm we do a sonic event and I'm like who the hell cares no one
really wants to hear this stuff you know and on the other hand they say they do
but they you know it's like let's what should we talk about right that's this
is like a diversion now right but what should we talk about right so so and the
thing is there's lots to talk about but it really you know it really I think
giving people a heads-up is always the best way to give information you know
heads-up means what's coming next week what's coming next month what's coming
next year and also how to put things that have happened in perspective and is
defining Egypt a logical terms of a necessity I wouldn't say so at all unless
it matters you know it's poignant to something we're discussing I'll put it
even to this point that most of Scripture which I've gone publicly and
said many times has nothing to do with most people anyway getting into a lot of
the fine points without constantly being redundant about the overall story that
has a lot to do with everyone because their feet are on the ground that kind of
pertinence you see is another view of it so you know the concept of having a
reference you know commensurability Scripture is commensurable in almost
every other aspect of what they call mythology religion but except for the
ones that are completely diaposed you know like when they tell you you
die you go to heaven and I'm not talking about that I'm talking about certain
prophecies you know when you hear about the fifth the flood myth right you know
they call it the flood story every culture has one when you talk about end
times every culture you know says good people are going to be treated badly
good will be evil evil will be considered good there's going to be a
schism between male and female there's going to be a cleanup period you know
every culture has that you know so that's what's commensurable and just you
know commensurable meaning like if you say foot and yards they're commensurable
by inches or if you say meters and centimeters is commensurable by
millimeters in other words is a common denominator common divider Scripture is
a common divider for all things and those commensurable things those things
that can be shown that do affect everyone on the planet I think are of the
utmost importance importance to discuss but I will suggest also that the gods in
Scripture and the Most High are having their own little private wars that we
are not given a lot of information about and I mean that literally you know
when I say a private war right a war and that doesn't mean a hot war hop doesn't
you know when I said you could have you could be in a state of war and in
Stacey's also where nothing is going on yeah sure they are yeah so yeah so now
now we're good now we're gonna have to get nosy are we to find out about the
Leviathan yeah I mean you would have to look at some kind of a reference
material for you have to look at everything and then have find a good
reference to explain everything you have to look at every single sea monster
sea god sea creature that would be within that realm that range of size and
description everything and then what are you using as your reference is of course
the obvious Scripture right and archaeology good archaeology is is a good
is a good reference by the way that's where you really got to look at the
pictures folks when you when you do archaeology look at the pictures don't
read with these morons right I mean you could but you better have a very high
level of discernment look for pictures we know he's in the Mediterranean
somewhere because that's where the abyss is but beyond that I don't know I'm
guessing that is pretty significant is there under is there an underwater cave
that goes from the Mediterranean to one of the inland rivers you think hmm let's
just say I never said that let's bring that up in another time or maybe I will
in the future if I get more information on it so but these are just things that
you want in other words you know when you throw something like that statement
out there I just did I think it should actually have a relaxing effect on the
mind for rationality right you know I shouldn't stress anyone out there
shouldn't the only stress you should have is stress itself anyway whatever
that means so anyway the theme was you brought up good
never Zachariah I was about to say because I cried I did suggest in the
past that that is a pivotal book for studying understanding these times I
mean pivoting pivotal meaning that a lot of things are gonna rotate you know
there's gonna be a lot of movement and the only one explain you won't be able
to explain why these things are happening geopolitically and locally in
that part of the world or it possibly your neighborhood unless you understand
the things that are going to be coming listed in the book of Zachariah and then
after that most likely later on will be more things listed in the book of Daniel
and Revelation when she actually I won't I'll just say if you study the book
Revelation most of it happens in one day so you know most of the dynamics that
occur on earth let me just say most of it you know because you know most of it
is actual dictation right you know like a third but it's like a third party
dictation it's like you're watching someone receiving dictation that's what
most of it is but the actual dynamics on earth happened one day so once it starts
you won't have a lot I mean it's just in a day's work right you know what I mean
so it'll happen quick you know in other words it's like have you ever had a
dislocated shoulder or known anyone who has when the arm comes out of the socket
enough what they do is they they sit you down and say okay you're gonna go
see the doctor and before you see the doctor these two orderlies are going to
help you out these big guys and they say listen we're gonna pull your arm back on
three so you're you're in pain and then they're like one two boom and they pull
your arm on two not on three because they know on three you're gonna tighten
up right you're expecting it they pull it a little sooner you see what I mean
if you tell someone I'm going to pull this part of your body that hurts on
three guess what happens when the number three comes you cringe you tighten up
you flex you right but if I tell you I'm gonna pull it on three and I pull it on
one and a half or two you didn't see it coming did you so yeah most of the
idiots that are alive today are not going to see anything any of the stuff
we've ever discussed coming at all on this planet they can't so I hate to tell
people this but I people born in the past few hundred years because it goes by
generation you're born here to be target practice for the gods I'm sorry you're
not mentioned at all you're mentioned in the most negative possible light it's
like breeding it's like breeding creatures to be blown up no different
than except for a very small group which is listed out how it's going to be
done separated it's just like a movie set you ever see movie sets when they
spend all this time before CG building them you spent weeks and months building
them and just to blow them up in five minutes don't take it personally though
see if you got some other punk human doing it yeah you might want to take it
personally get out of the get out of the situation but when the gods are doing it
now you ain't going nowhere and that's the positive stuff you don't want to
hear me say the note the negative stuff is keep that to myself I was I'm not
gonna tell you what I really think you've heard that before so don't take it
personally how can you not take it personally well you'll see later food
clothing shelter is there any progress on finding about finding out about this
thing regarding the satellite geo imagery emissions that can locate where
the four Eden rivers were you know I have to go back and look at that again
but there has been information coming up and going away and I don't is there
anything on the rectangle about that by the way I haven't looked into it really
did we mention that publicly or do you and I do it in a private it was public
that was from a discussion I've had with someone that worked in geophysics you
know oil companies and mineral companies they've been putting information
together so much for the past you know 75 80 years since of airplane flight and
by the way when you're in airplanes photographing the earth to use what's
called stereo photography right it's a two cameras and when you view the print
you view through a stereoscope you know and gives you a 3d image very important
so it's very different than looking at images on the internet or whatever
yeah and this is these are things that are being bounced around and I hear that
it was shut down once their biblical references came up in other words you
know study into that area so let's let's just say that's a field of study
that needs to be continued right and we'll see if we can bring up if I can on
my end work on that in the future so I guess moving away from sort of biblical
things you talk a bit more about how the food market works in general like when
you mention how the fish is always going to be two years or one year old right
kept in storage the typical fish you know the stuff that people buy in the
market not all fish but you know the you know what what do people eat
halibut salmon tuna those are them and whitefish flounder those are the main
staple you know when you ask someone you know fish most Americans use it fishes
fish they can't even discern you know those types of fish you know like the
ones you get at the fast-food stores and restaurants yeah what they do is in
order to keep the market stable is you have inventory to meet demand so you can
you can do you know commodities markets work on that they look at charts of how
what the demand has been on a particular item and in order to keep it stable they
have extra on background you know so most most of these fish from what was
this from someone in the industry that told me that that you when you go out to
eat or in the store the typical you know commercial fish that is already two
years old you know it's a season and also with fruit as well apples can be
stored in nitrogen for over a year right leafy greens obviously not but certain
things like certain citrus certain hard you know fleshy fruits like apples and
pears and things can be over a year old and they're and they're gotten from all
over the world put in storehouses and then put on the market accordingly you
know as as they would be expected what does that do for the efficacy and
vitality of the food not much so yeah the veg believe it or not there's more
veg sold than meat on the food market you know non-meat you know you know so
that is really the focus of when you speaking of food supply how that is
controlled it's not good by the way but it's good enough to keep you alive
no one on the meat front yeah meat is pretty pretty sketchy that that on the
meat front here to give an example how that works back in the 80s there was a
red meat scare you know like red meat was bad for you and then I think there
was some kind of a boycott with or internal transportation issue or
something but red meat cow meat bovine got a bad rap so the slaughter rate and
the meat being animals being slaughtered for their meat went down drastically but
the the demand for leather goods did not so the leather good supply was
supplied by the animal being slaughtered for meat and the leather going to the
leather side of the economy right but when the cows were let's say stop being
slaughtered at a high rate guess what happened to the leather the demand
stayed up but the supply went down so if anyone remembers in the 1980s if you
bought a leather jacket that was a hundred bucks all of a sudden next year
it's 200 bucks or leather shoes right that were made from cow you know the
price of all these things jumped up so there's certain things that can't be
controlled like that you know when they're tied in hand in hand like for
example if just to put it more simply restating the whole thing if people
decided not to eat cow meat or bovine meat that's fine but they also have to
decide that they no longer have a demand for what leather right the skin
of the animal you can't say you or we're going to diminish the demand of the
flesh and the muscles of the animal but we want to keep the the demand for its
hide up well now you're going to be slaughtering cows for their hide and
what that created was a big boom in research of synthetic leathers if you go
on the market today there are some even synthetic petard leathers that unless
you really know leather or look at the back very closely you can fool your
average person with it you know what I mean so that's one thing that the plant
world will have a hard time substituting for is a leather type material you can
achieve it using composites you know plant fibers with resins right so that's
an aspect of the food market that is rarely discussed you know when you have
a by-product that is in demand and the main product does not it drives a
synthetic market doesn't it you can have a breathable synthetic leather it does
exist it's not on the market I think as it could be like for example you know
like Ferrari got it got into one point the exotic car manufacturer where they
actually started ranches on their own to breed cows that were not contained by
barbed wire because if you've been around cows you know they'll be eating
grass and they'll lean up against barbed wire and they'll cut themselves and they
don't mind it too much but when their hide is harvested you see the scar on
the hide and when you're putting together a 200-300,000 whatever car you
don't you know you want perfect leather so they actually got into that aspect of
it now the the aspect of food I'd never really like going on record to say I'm a
vegetarian but it is most the most noble diet
noble versus base would be to eat a plant-based diet and like I say I've
been saying for a decade and more a decade and a half what's 2003 that's a
that's 15 years right so it's more than a decade so what they call 2003 this the
scriptures indirectly promotes a vegetarian diet not directly but
indirectly right what I mean by that it doesn't say be vegetarian or eat only
plants even though it does state I have the plants for as your food it doesn't
say only and also in Leviticus it does state that if you touch the flesh of a
dead animal you're unclean if you put a chicken sandwich to your mouth or a goat
sandwich goat roti or whatever is that the flesh of a dead animal yes it is you
so it doesn't say directly but indirectly it's it's about as strong as
it gets right so that's why I would say the most noble diet to have and I'll go
on record to say is to eat that vegetable matter and noble but more
specifically I mean if we're just gonna be practical because most people can't
understand scripture what you're talking about anyway why does the plant diet
offer a higher quality and volume of nutrition I would suggest that you have
to have you know I've said the scripture is about the written by the
gods to the gods and we just happen to get it so you know it's given to us
also you know as a CC car you know we know someone CC's it's been forwarded to
us that's how you one would view it and there's very high level of science in
there what the gods consider to be clean or unclean or tomorrow to me you know
which is not clean right is is within their obviousness there's a certain you
ever notice certain things in scripture it's it's do's and don'ts have an
obviousness heir to them you know and if you ask why it's like well it's if you
have to ask why it's not for you I usually say you know that's why you know
the legalistic part of scripture starts out in Genesis he made this and it was
good he made this it was good in the land separated this it was good he made
the animals it was good but then you know people get to the part where the
laws and the behavior oh and that's not good right you see so it's it's a it's a
contrast on the human character as well but other than saying that about
scripture if you look at what science gleans around nutrition you let's say
protein you know a slab of meat might give you 30 or 40 grams of protein and a
vegetable serving might only give you seven or eight and people think well then
if I want protein I need to eat meat but what science doesn't tell you is in
terms of biocompatibility only four or five grams of that protein if not less
of the meat is compatible and about seven or eight grams of the vegetable is
biocompatible so where are you going to get more protein now the plant but the
meats gonna transmute anyway so what's compatibility about compatibility means
what how the body reacts to it give you another example I knew guys sold life
insurance back 20 years ago so and when you agree to get on that they send you a
postcard you're supposed to prick your finger and there's like dots on there
and put two blood samples and send it in so I test you for AIDS right and I said
you know I know these people here go talk to him selling life insurance as
well you know I warned them about you anyway if they're dumb enough to go for
it that's between you and them and I said all these people will beat will have
AIDS even though they had don't have AIDS I said I said how are you gonna do
that so you'll see so what when these people did this blood test thing for the
life insurance thing I told him go to a steakhouse if especially if you eat meat
and eat a really rare steak I mean if you like rare steak it's even better but
get it like really rare and he don't eat a good sized portion of it and then wait
about two hours and then do a blood test and you're gonna come in as like a
possibility you know very strong you know like they want to test you again
that you might have AIDS right because when you eat that meat within a few hours
if you do what's called an AIDS test you're gonna show a mild to strong
positive that you have AIDS even though you don't you know because of the
mitochondria junk that's put in the blood right so I was just messing with
them but it was a good it was a good point it's provable what I just told
you if you know in the past 20 years they probably changed the criteria of
that because they're looking for viruses that don't exist so they
whenever you perpetrate a fraud like electrons or viruses or protons or or
you know whatever you have to keep changing it to keep your victims off
balance right you can change the criteria of how you define it so anyway
yeah just pass this through the body I had a conversation today out in the
market with a so-called person worked in a one of these health food stores I
said pull up a image of the intestines you know from the lumen all the way to
the wall and all that and they looked at it and I said okay now I want you to pull
up an image of a steel belted radial tire or cross-section and they looked at
it and they're like they look alike I said yes that's right you're the first
person that ever came across and said yes they look alike how much absorbing does
a steel belted radial truck tire do none intended you can when you look at in a
human intestine or animal intestine there is absolutely no intention of
absorption there as a matter of fact if it does happen you will die of sepsis or
get sepsis in a in a way you see so you know the the other thing of it is Sam
what do you see with your eye and your perception with a clear mind right you
let me give you an example you ask most people in the Western world especially
children where does milk come from or meat come from you know what they say
comes from the store they don't know what it's like to have a pet animal and
a pet cow or a pet goat or a pet chicken and kill it and eat it your appetite
goes down really fast when you're not used to it and even when you're used to
it you don't do it often it's funny over here there's a there's a fast-food
place in America and it's called chick something I'm not gonna fi LA whatever
and and I call it the born-again chicken sandwiches because they you know they
pride themselves and being closed on Sunday they're boarding and Christians
right I said oh you're gonna go get a boarding and you want one of these says
someone wants offer is that I don't want a boarding and chicken sandwich you know
I mean but anyway they don't know what they're doing and you know but anyway I
just had to throw that in there as a little dig perhaps you want a boarding
and chicken sandwich you see how ridiculous yeah hopefully it's in season
you want to eat seasonally because the body works optimally right if you can
actually it's not about if you can you should it's one of those things that you
almost cannot you should not elect as being optional you should avoid things
that don't grow within the cross latitude in other words if it comes from
across the world that place where it comes from is it does that place have
the same climate and weather as you do and if it does you'd be safe but the best
is to eat locally that's why you can kiss mankind goodbye because most of the
markets are international until that goes away with you well the only way
international markets will go away as with disaster and catastrophe right you
know the ability to ship things goes away and that's not going to happen
post cleanup post mop-up yeah there are foods that can mentally slow you down
yes I mean like have a permanent effect on your mental processes as far as being
able to think and recall and fluidity of thought yes logical sequences I have
a I have a test for that very simple and anyone can do this at any age I used to
do it with younger people because believe it or not as time goes on you'll
notice most of the health complaints are coming from younger people right more
more and more before you eat something write your name you know or the name
sign it or or however you write whether it's in print or script have a meal and
wait five or ten minutes after the meal and write your name again but on a
separate piece of paper and then compare the two you know we could wait a half
hour than wait an hour and you'll notice that let's say you have some junk food
you know stuff that's offered at the market today and you eat it and you
write your name and you'll notice sometimes that you know it's not being
written as you're writing it you know it's screwed up that's how negative the
effect can be you see and what that's a motor skill test right you know from the
mind to the hand by the way that's a whole other thing to discuss by the way
you know how you see in scripture the arm is you know of Yahweh and this and
that you know does the you know that does your hand ever do anything that your
mind doesn't want it to do does the body do anything that the brain doesn't
want it to do you know what I mean so so when you read those things you know
anyway that is a very simple motor skill test you know you'd think certain
athletes would well they do athletes are very picky about what they eat
specifically on how it reacts to themselves like sometimes if you're
around athletes and you offer something even though it is considered a
good food they may not want it because and yes and why is I don't like the way
I feel when I do that right they know that it messes up their motor skills so
the easiest way to see that as motor skills like give you an example six year
old girl eight year old boy 13 year old girl all in the same room having sweet
snacks chocolate milk ask them to write their name all right they can write at
that age and and then have the snacks wait 15 minutes and what the interesting
thing was they couldn't even write it across the line it was like it was
ruled paper it went down it went across a little bit then it went down on a 45
degree angle I mean that's how critical it was with these small people so
imagine people going to junk food even you know born-again chicken sandwiches
through a drive-thru they're eating this crap and and they're behind the
wheel which is a 5,000 pound you know or 2,500 or kilo missile on rubber tires
right I mean the reason I ask is from personal I guess observation of
something that would have transpired because when I was a kid I had a
certain way of being able to think and then once I graduated high school and
left the third world country that I was living in and came back to the West
something changed quite noticeably and of course at that point I wouldn't connect
it to the food but there's a certain fluidity of thought that when I was 15
16 just doesn't exist anymore I guess I would have to trace it to
something in the food but even when I was a teenager living where I was living we
ate junk food it was powdered milk it was you know Oreos and whatnot alongside
whatever local food that we were eating but for some reason the effect became
more pronounced when I moved back to the West oh yeah the gods the gods have a
funny way of doing stuff like that you know think of it this way if you have an
organism living on a planet and it's living on the planet because of food and
water and air you want to mess around with them you what you don't have to
mess around with them you just mess around with their food water and air
don't you right yeah I mean that's that's how you get rid of a monster you
don't by the way fight it you starve it or poison it you know through its food
supply so you got seven and a half billion monsters walking around potential
monsters the gods are like oh yeah these guys they won't even see it coming they
don't even know what's going on and they never will well I mean not until you
know never when I say never I mean and within the ever within the ever if it
doesn't happen then it's never you know I mean and I've reiterated this in the
last sonic event if you got problems in your life it's not you it's people
around you by the way if you if you know the truth yeah so but if you go back to
their ways and you know like all these self-help gurus you know just wake up
and say oh I'm so glad for all the things that I got and everyone around me
bullshit well go back to that and you'll see everything will start getting
better for you right because now you're in accord so the hardest thing about
finding out the truth is how do you live with the morons around you gracefully
right and that's something I've never really gotten into too much but that is
also something that is absolutely necessary to be able to do which is
actually you'll be expending twice the energy because on one side you're
running the program of reality real reality and then the other one you have
to project the program of stupidity because of the people around you by the
way I have an interesting letter to read in a little bit which might be
interesting unless you have any other thoughts on on that I got a letter in
the mail it's actually a lawsuit and I'm going to read it I think would be I was
going to scan it and post it up but I'd rather just read it I mean it'd be
interesting and I want to say a lawsuit it's it's it's formal you know you will
I'll keep it anonymous but I'll use the initials instead how's that yes and it's
regarding sonic events by the way oh so whoever is bringing it to you listens
to Greek speak yep that's fine yeah and I think there'll be you know let me see
if I could bring this up I was I didn't really think about it when I got it a
few days ago I was thinking oh this will be interesting to read then I just kind
of forgot about it till just now I'm gonna keep it anonymous which is not that
difficult you know when you look at a lawsuit how it's printed out it's got
the case on the left and all the other details and all this other stuff one two
yeah it's two and a half pages or two pages okay here we go you ready the
court is in the court of public opinion via internet radio broadcasts worldwide
that's the court and the plaintiff I'm gonna just call CP well it is real or
fake no it's it's real we've had a tracking label it's gotten in the mail
we're gonna keep order for here I don't hear I'm gonna Bruce are you still
there oh yeah I'm here okay I'm gonna put on the camera and can you see this I
don't disbelieve it I just don't see how you see that do you see that I'm
looking yes I need to enlarge my thing it's a bit small you see that yeah I do
see that yeah and it's signed right okay I'm gonna show you how to cover here do
you see that yeah okay all right so I'm yeah I'm not making this up yeah I might
I might do I might do some just leave some of the personal stuff out and take
some scans and put it up there maybe you'll put it up Bruce but it's in the
opinion via internet radio broadcasts worldwide CP the plaintiff versus the
Greek claimant and the case is over number episode number nine Ocelli and
the Greek February 2nd 2017 in caps underscored objections by plaintiff
regarding comment made by claimant about all surface-dwelling earth inhabitants
aka space eaters of the earth comes now the plaintiff CP and respectively
respectfully states as follows all caps objection I hereby object to the
statement made by the claimant on the American Freedom Radio broadcast
February 2nd 2017 here the Chuck Ocelli show on episode 9 of Ocelli and the
Greek statement of facts claimant made the following statement on internet
broadcast via American Freedom Radio quote that's why I tell people everyone
you've ever known everyone you know and everyone you will meet as a moron and
I've been telling this to people for more than a decade and no one's
rebutted it so now you know legally it stands the Greek spoken by the Greek on
Ocelli and the Greek to 9 2017 while that may be true that from the time of
birth until some 36 years after the fact the plaintiff could not be considered
quote a moron spiritually speaking but he has since demonstrated through much
study observation and practice of scriptural law and is no longer a quote
moron that being said the plaintiff does agree that through the observation the
majority which is 99.99999% of the space eaters inhabiting planet earth do
indeed have the mental capacity of a 12 year old child has since grown beyond
that to one of approximately 21 years of age even though the plaintiff is
significantly older the plaintiff has matured demonstratively beyond the
spiritual quote moron through maturation and objective engagement of historical
study and observation of not only his own behavior but that of his immediate
surroundings as well as a significant number of years of scriptural study and
practice albeit he has since realized that the versions of KGV of scripture
quote he has engaged in tremendously inadequate when utilizing original
languages of preservation through interlinear comparison where for CP
praise and demands but the historical record reflected the Greek statement no
longer stands unrebutted be that the plaintiff's historical record reflect
that he is indeed matured beyond the mental state of eight or twelve year old
child see the plaintiff intends to continually mature beyond that of a 21
year old earth inhabitant to that of a mature and lawful man reflecting his
papal age which shall not be revealed in this objection sign CP pro se litigant
such-and-such and so certificate of service this is to certify that a true
and exact copy of the foregoing instrument has been sent via United
States mail postage space to the Greek blah blah blah on this 31st day of
January papal subject calendar lawfully 31st day of the 11th month year yet to be
lawfully determined CP signed so in that case I will demur and state that we
do have a viable objection and we can't and somehow state the facts herein as
being accepted as fact and we and and properly rebutted so that's one out of
over a decade so there you go and there's quite an effort made I mean look
is it a gag you know Bruce I showed you know is it a joke no it's not it's this
is a proper statement because why because now we have what of it a written
record of it and a sonic record of it isn't that interesting so the let the
record stand as such that this has been rebutted and it stands until further
changes are admitted or other admissions but so far all the admissions and
evidence provided grant an exception with this particular man known as CP and by
the way thank you for your continuing support CP and your diligence and I
figured you wouldn't mind me reading Senate it reading this out if you are
listening you call in if you want but either way I just I thought that would
be an interesting little thing to throw in good for CP I mean it is self
analysis though well whatever it is I thought it would be apropos to to read
read it because it is done properly it's more than yeah in other words it's self
and out but it was also addressing you see the whole the whole issue which was
what I had said it was done properly you like that Bruce yes I did Greek it
was most interesting what I might do is just scan it using one of those silly
pads actually they I was told you don't even need one of these flatbed scanners
anymore because that iPad thing does just as good right yeah they're not too
bad not too bad yeah pretty close and and I'll just take off some of the
personal info on both sides and I'll put it on an imager thing maybe that does
that work well for you yes that does imagery you could capture it and maybe
convenience what's that at your convenience yeah I'll do and then I think
that would be something you might like to put up in images thing I will
certainly put it up yeah all right I'm not near the rectangle now I am in the
office actually but let's see is there anything going on in chat getting hit up
on Skype as well let's see not really what's anything else you want to add or
take away Bruce or Sam no I was I I've been taken away by your discussions
again you and you and Sam both
but what's this a study on socialist countries that you came across with for
the doctor said that when it says that when the doctors want to strike them
mortgages were empty yeah they did oh I look it up is there anything left of it
online no I don't even know what to search for what's this what's this put
it when the morgues morgues morgues are empty when hospitals shut down or when
doctors doc put in doctor strike morgues empty I don't know how your keywords I
guess how browsers work yep the more more the most recent one which was about a
decade and a half or so ago was done by an Israeli group believe it or not from
what I remember and by the way folks things that are on the rectangle do get
taken down and scrubbed I've had people I've sent links to things that I thought
were interesting a couple of years ago since computer guy says oh I'll find it
and he gets he never got back to me I got back to me says oh no yeah it was
scrubbed so but there is a socialized medicine and by the way one thing you
don't hear about much is strikes and boycotts and things like that unless
it's a political thing you know so and here's the thing about the Americans
I've been you know ever since the election this is not just the Americans
but you know each society is slightly different just like you Sam mentioned
you were in a third world country and you know whatever change you notice a
change these morons here they don't understand what's going on in a big
level they're always questioning America and they've got you know their new
president now whatever not disparaging him because they're all none of them
weren't any good ever and they shouldn't be because obviously they don't
understand they're trying to break this natural or cultural cycle you ever heard
what I mean by that is you know what goes around comes around right so the
this country here known as the American states it was started by violence and
disease from foreigners right there was a proclamation that King George did that
really pissed off that what they call the founding fathers of America that
proclamation was a no more expansion past the Mississippi or the colonies to
preserve the not the native people right and George Washington all those
guys like screw that we're gonna go genocide them all which they did now
they'll say well they're still Native Americans but there's so few that if you
say they were all killed it's pretty pretty close but anyway this country
here was settled by violence and disease by spreading disease and violence how do
you think it's going to end I don't know
disease and violence maybe so I don't know about protecting American values
and this and that because I just laid it out for you folks and unfortunately yes
I am here but now we're in the situation where it doesn't matter where you go
which country you go to because now it's global but I think within the global
scheme you'll have these little micro turnovers you know what I mean by like
what goes around comes around personally like for example look at Israel and
scripture says I will bring you back I will once again make you right what goes
around comes around kind of thing well how do you think the Americans are going
to end up in the Canadians and those guys anyway this is not a political
statement this is a universal statement meaning all-encompassing right so yeah
so these morons here you know go ahead you can have your born-again chicken
sandwiches in your stupid bowls and all that other stuff but it's good that they
don't see it coming even when it's happening they'll deny it and of course
you have the mop-up crew so anyway also you've mentioned and I have to look into
it because I think it's it's an extensive topic but the Renaissance was a
movement which effectively shut down any worthwhile spiritual developments in
favor of this sort of inward-looking new age based it's all about you the
individual follow your feelings blah blah blah somewhat expand on that
somewhat the Renaissance was the start of the military-industrial complex you've
heard of that term right now when you say industry most people think like you
know weaving looms and coal mines and I know industry meaning banking because
most industries work hand-in-hand with the financers right so the banking
industry controls it just means an overt but no I shouldn't say overt not a non
overt actually the opposite commercial development with the bankers are in
control of everything right if you look at major history it's been you know like
for example war you know that all wars are bankers wars right you've heard of
that right well you know country developments of countries and industry
is based on the banking and behind it and the real battle is with the finances
and with the banking and that's what came out of the Renaissance predominantly
and really what it was is a recentralization of the papal power you
know from the Emperor and vice versa you know a little struggle going back and
forth you know and to answer the question about the individual that's the
divide and conquer you know you get everyone to focus on the individual on
themselves only and then you've got them all pigeonhole don't you and you that's
how that you know by the way and when you've got everyone focusing on what
they're going to do you take them out one by one and instill fear or instill
hope or however you're going to do whatever your end goal is oh that was
the Renaissance was not a Renaissance at all it's Renaissance was like after
9-11 the terrorism thing you know what terrorism what Renaissance but as far as
the individual thing I mean that also has a polarity to it where there's also
this sort of leftist group mentality that we see quite prevalent today with
identity politics where people are forcing themselves to identify as group
members and then doubling down on that group identity along lines of say race
or class or whatever yeah on one hand you have individual focus but then yeah
they're suckers yeah they're just suckers and and Gustave Le Bon if you
ask any of those people why they're doing it and you look at what they
reference as the core belief it hardly resembles that at all but yet they're
doing it but look the expect the race war or the race conflict to increase
because especially in what they call the American states is because it was a race
war when the country started essentially right magazines and newspapers were sold
based on the how much of a headcount they had on Indians right but do we do
we know specifically weddings well I guess you said the banks but because I'm
trying to figure out what the institutions are that are there that
were pushing that at the time because what you're presented with is often some
philosopher or some Leonardo da Vinci character who's pontificating about I
don't know the benefits of individualism but then behind that you
would have the machinations that are actually putting into effect what what
they want and I don't really know where to find that repeat that well as far as
the Renaissance you have the most front-facing aspect of that is the
artistic like Leonardo da Vinci and whatever is being done in Vienna by
certain individuals but then as far as what's actually taking place
ideologically to shift mass mass consciousness that's being pushed
somewhere else and I'm trying to find what institutions are sort of
responsible for that the banks and the universities yeah universities became
quite popular the church became popular all those things are malevolent by the
way in intent and in and in practice all right you know people were back you
know University I mean people have figured out now I think especially in
the past 30 years universities a joke only the the weakest minds actually
think there's anything to be gotten out of there they're well endowed you know
with laboratories and things like that devices you know tools grunt work so it
it's not taking that seriously but if you went against university politics and
education you know more than 150 years ago or a hundred years ago your life was
at stake you know or your livelihood was now it's not so much because I
everything everyone realizes an unspoken joke right but that was just as
dangerous as speaking out against as it was the church and if by the way if you
read up on you know the persecutions that were done on people that wanted a
translation of the biblical text or went against the Christian dogma or the
Christian tradition the it was always that not what they were doing was wrong
the ones that were persecuted was because they were disrupting a thousand
years of tradition you know it you know and that's that's also the rise with
people that the the what they call the bar association or the legal society
came into prominence as it is today back then because right now everyone
misses the point and it's actually been illustrated in the American news a year
ago when Trump said we're going to stop immigration and some like district judge
said no and he stops it so they're telling you the attorneys are running
the country right not the president right if you go to a doctor he says well
I can't legally do that well so the attorneys running the hospital now if you
go to the university why legally can't teach that well so the attorneys are
running the university now right you go to the restaurant well I can't serve
legally serve that also the attorneys are running your restaurant now I'm gonna
keep going right I knew a fellow out of England he was an attorney I said what
do you do he says he said I edit medical textbooks and I'm like what do you know
about medicine is nothing very little so how the hell are you editing them
think about it and what is an attorney a Satanist right I mean it's an
adversary so everybody loves it you know that's what they want I still hear
these idiots on the rectangle occasionally we want justice oh yeah
really you're a fucking moron anyway excuse the medical term there but the
Renaissance is an interesting thing only because I mean when when is the period
of the Renaissance classified as a 15th century with 13 1400s 1500s and it was
already you know call it the pre Victorian it was pre Baroque get a
Baroque it's a Baroque but anyway that was the what would you say what would you
when you say I would say 14 1500s what for Renaissance right 13 14 that's
they want to start late 1300s and then into the 1700s yeah that's when
everything started like Christopher Columbus discovered America by the way
if you guys want to turn your head inside out you know we spoke about the
Minoans before briefly or the Keftari I think they're mentioned in Deuteronomy
how they were even just right yeah you know we slaughtered them too right they
kind of got in the way that's a Chaldean term Keftari for Minoan or from the
island of Crete by the way they're a very prominent culture Mycenae as well
and everyone only knows about the Egyptians there on that time period but
do you know that they had mined over a million tons when you deal with metal by
the way million tons is not a lot even though if you drop it on your foot it
will break your toe right Bruce or you know but a million tons in mining terms
is not much but it is a million tons from the Minoans had mined that much
copper native copper from Michigan we're talking about 2000 BC 1500 BC
where's Michigan Great Lakes area of the States that's six thousand miles away
yeah and it's it's the evidence is irrefutable but no one wants to look go
online and look up Minoans mining copper in Michigan I mean they're finding
thousands of artifacts and bodies buried and by the way with isotopes you
know you can check the isotope of any metal and you'll know where it came
from because the isotope of the copper from Michigan is different than the
isotope of the copper anywhere else right so basically the copper that was
used and what they call their idiotic Bronze Age was fueled by the Americans
by the Americas you find it look Minoan copper from Michigan in America what is
that that this is this is roughly 1500 1600 BC what does that do for your
history what you know you don't necessarily put a million tons in a
backpack and swim across the Atlantic no you don't I mean yeah we're talking
about seafaring lines what I mean by a line is you know when you're going out
right you'll see other ships coming and you wave right right right you get it
it's not like oh are we gonna make it no you are as a matter of fact when you're
going there's you'll see other ships coming you might stop for a minute and
share things too you know and islands on there are islands in the Atlantic by the
way on the way out right so you know it's when you tell people crossing the
Atlantic they go that big body of water no there are islands out there you could
look really close on Google Earth and there's plenty of places to stop from
Europe to the States you know Bruce guys Sam we feel exactly you could look I
mean where's Bermuda you know I mean that Bermuda but Bahamas and other
places and whatever maybe I'm not using the right terms but you'll see there's
lots of little places to stop so one dead snack right now Center if I
remember correctly yep so they have a hard time but you see I shouldn't say a
hard time no one's having a hard time because everyone knows everyone who's
anyone knows that these universities are they won't hire you unless you're an
idiot now it is possible to be an idiot and be have a talent at one thing and you
obviously will be compensated for doing that thing well but generally they don't
hire people that are competent you know individuals I mean I have never met
anyone in any university system or any professor any academic that I would
invite over for dinner even though I have in the past I wouldn't do it anymore
because they're all the same pretty much they're there to brainwash your children
and the youth but they do it voluntarily no one's putting a gun to anyone's head
and the ones that are not there for that don't last in the system very long at
all year two years three years five years tops and then they just leave and
discussed all of them that are competent so if you say that these people are
incompetent and you could say even evil is pretty pretty accurate description of
them it's in your face the real history of discovery or the real history of how
the earth was pretty much covered and navigated by anyone and everyone at any
time in history and why am I saying this because during the Renaissance you
have Christopher Columbus by the way as they tout right coming over now by the
way you know there is an argument was an argument about the origin of Christopher
Columbus and you know there are various places in Italy that have plaques this
is where he was born right he was financed by Spain and with blessings of
you know the powers that be but you know if you go to the island of Chios there's
a little humble house and they have a little plaque very on very not well
known at all is this is where Christopher Columbus was born it's a
Greek and you know if you're French by the way when you sign your name you sign
it in front you know French right or when you're when you're Arabic you sign it in
Arabic when you're right now how many Pete how many Greeks sign their name in
Greek just about all of them right now if you go on the rectangle I don't know
if it's up maybe it is go find Christopher Columbus a signature is that
in Roman English