Greetings, folks.
How are you all tonight?
And Greek, how are you doing tonight, sir?
Greetings, everyone who cares to listen and hear things.
Doing okay, as usual.
I'm gonna grab some coffee and smoke, so I'll go back over there and see if there's anything going on in chat.
And if that's not cringeworthy, and like Sam says, and we'll maybe do a little short sonic.
It might be really short if Sam doesn't come on.
Unless you got any ideas, Bruce?
I don't.
I'm fresh out of ideas.
I was just scanning through the chat today and got my little self some nourishment on the Hebrew language, which I found very refreshing and very enlightened with.
And that was given to us by one Thomas, and I'm very thankful for that.
What an eye-opener.
Oh, okay.
I was a delight to get those little things.
What was it?
It was a rabbi teaching the video on the DNA of Hebrew.
I hope he didn't say there's DNA in Hebrew.
No, no, no.
He was, I guess, dissecting the...
Yes, it is.
Yeah, but you gotta also listen to what rabbis say, but they, in other words, and also watch what they do, and they're two very different things.
You know, I don't know enough about the man.
They say, do as they do, not do as they do.
Yeah, the rabbis will never...
Here's an interesting thing.
Rabbis generally, they don't last long if they tell people the truth.
Does that make any sense?
Just like lawyers and doctors, right?
Yeah, it does, yeah.
And again, I'm always astounded by that.
Yeah, so what they do, they have a story, a spiel, as they say in Yiddish, for the public, and then what they've discovered and how little they know is another spiel.
And I'm speaking from experience, but that's okay.
I have a feeling I'm a little more advanced than you guys are, unfortunately or fortunately, and you'll figure out more stuff.
I mean, you do bring a lot to the table and certainly give a lot to ponder on and chew on later, and I'm thankful for that.
You know, even small little bits and pieces, I go a long way in helping to understand this, and for me that's an enlightenment, and I need that, clearly.
I think we all do.
Well, you mentioned, yes, but it varies again, and you mentioned, let's go back to what you were saying earlier, this was a video presentation done by a rabbi on the DNA of Hebrew.
Right.
Is that about right?
Okay, so that's basically suggesting the origins of what's in it, right?
Dissecting words, the numerals of the words, the meanings of the word, taking it apart letter by letter, adding things up.
I mean, there were some things that just were absolutely, you know, I took for granted when reading.
Okay, good.
Now, the reason why we, let me just bring us back down to earth, because this is, I assure you, that was not in that text, the presentation.
The significance of anyone considering what is held within technical aspects, or the communicative aspects of the Hebrew language, usually bears its significance on what's called the Old Testament, or scriptures, you know, what's been preserved in that language, right?
That's why anyone would see that that language has any notable bearing on knowing what it's about, right?
So, whether you know Hebrew, or English, or whatever language, can you communicate, and is what's being communicated, the information held within the Scripture being communicated to you?
Because if you don't understand something, it's not the information, it's you, right?
Like, for example, if you, right, so if you sit down, if you go to like a computer programming convention, and they have a one-hour lecture on C++, or COBOL, or whatever all this other stuff, old or new is, and you don't understand a dang thing, it's not the information, it's you, right?
You don't have the training, you don't know how to, right, you don't know what's being communicated.
So, my point is this, if you sat that rabbi down, not surely, but if you bet, this is a really good bet, and ask him to explain the scriptures to you, do you think he can?
And I would bet that he can't, outside of a religious, whatever, you know, dogma he's been showing.
So, my whole point of bringing these things up is, is the communication coming through?
You know, it's kind of like, you know, you got an 18-volt cordless power drill with a battery pack, 18-volt DC, and you got a socket on the wall that's 110 50 cycle AC.
You're with me, right?
So, when the battery on the 18-volt cordless drill starts to run down, you know that you somehow need to get the power from 115 or 110 AC, 120 AC, into that battery pack.
How do you do it?
You got a charger, right?
And the charger's got its own, it takes the AC 120 into DC 18 or like, you know, 19 and a half volt to charge, right?
Do you see my point?
Right, yes.
And this is what's going on with what's been held in ancient texts.
Can you convert it?
Or not convert it in a way where you change it, but get it so it's usable for what you're using, right?
Right, right.
And it's going to be an interesting road trying to get that mindset, you know.
It's all about mindset.
Yeah.
And you know, let's just play around a little bit.
I call it dicking around with this stuff.
You know, it means you can't take it seriously, but you're playing around with it, you know.
Playing with your thing.
So, what it is, is very simple.
You know, you got mindset, which means, well, you know, it's not subject matter, it's mindset, right?
Regardless of subject matter.
And then you've got weak mindset, strong mindset.
Then you've got mastermind set, right?
Right.
Think about that, right?
You've got the various aspects to it.
Which would go along with growth, I would think, huh?
Yeah, but you could grow crooked.
Yeah.
You could grow in the wrong direction, like a tree.
Unfortunately, based on people's decision-making ability, they make decisions that they can't change, believe it or not, you know.
Well, look at what happened with Christianity, you know.
Well, that was rotten from the beginning, because when I say beginning, that's, you know, 500 to a thousand AD.
There was really no such thing prior to that, other than various groups that couldn't be defined.
Yeah, it's just, but so it is, you know, the term Jewish was not used in common vernacular until about the late 17th or 18th century.
That was a fairly new development, you know, like African American, you know.
Right.
That was not used.
There was another one that was thrown in a chat about Jesus, and people trying to understand Jewish people when it came to the word Jesus.
And that was an interesting little, I guess, 10-20 minute documentary.
Well, you know, that's a real easy one to fix.
There's no such thing.
That's a fiction.
Right.
It's fiat.
There's no such thing as Jesus, yeah, as they say, you know, the Christian, they go blank.
But then again, there, you know, if you look at Christianity as a movement, look at the sci-fi convention movements.
You ever see, remember this, even if you haven't been to one, which I have not, the Star Trek conventions and the Star Wars conventions.
These people take these things very seriously, even though they're fiction.
And they've got, you know, a billion and a half, two billion strong.
So remember, the point is, it's not how many, it's the quality of what's going on.
Look at McDonald's and look at, you know, all the stuff, the information that's put out there.
Look at the rectangle, the dumpster.
What's on the rectangle, you know, other than a, you know, weather map and whatever you can glean from reference material, but otherwise there's not much on there.
I don't know if you guys remember the old pocket reference.
I found one the other day.
It was a little, the navy blue.
It's got about 400 pages, real fine print.
It's got every, you know, conversion chart and melting points of metals and freezing points and gases.
Do you remember those little references?
Yeah, yeah.
I used to saw them until a few years ago.
I used to see them at the checkout near the, you know, point of sale item at the hardware stores.
Yeah, they're quick buys.
Yeah, I don't see them anymore.
No, a little piece of nostalgia.
Yeah, I'm not even gonna get into slide rule and all that either, because slide rule is a mindset.
Slide rule is a mindset, by the way.
It is, it is.
Yeah, so, you know, here's an interesting thing, just to throw around.
I guess people like to talk about Scripture.
I like to talk about Scripture, but there's a lot more to talk about that matters as well from us, you know, from just being a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant.
But there's like a thought of the minute, you know.
I wouldn't say thought of the day, but thought of the minute.
There is a certain book at the end of the compile, what they call the Bible, and it says that Satan, you know, the adversary comes to the earth with great wrath, you know, woe to the inhabitants of the earth, right?
You, you, does that ring, you know, do you recall something like that?
Yes, I do.
Hmm.
All right, let's take a three-second pause there.
Okay, so you recall it.
It's pretty common, you know.
It'd be hard to find anyone who hasn't, who says they haven't, has even studied a little bit they've heard of it, right?
Okay.
Where does it show that the people complain about that?
901.
Yep, they don't mind it at all, because he's giving them, he's doing what?
He's accommodating them.
When you have a school bus full of second graders, and they're all yelling, we want ice cream, and the teacher and the bus driver say, okay, next right, we're gonna go to the ice cream store.
You think any of those children are going to be complaining?
Unless, you know, of course they can't make the transaction.
So what's going on is humanity's being watched on their level of free will, you know, what they want to do while they're on the ship, and they're being accommodated.
You ever hear of cryptocurrency?
Oh yeah.
You ever hear of freedom of religion?
You ever hear of freedom of speech?
You ever hear about, you know, voting secretly?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, where do you think those things are inspired from?
You ever hear of vaccines, chemtrails, on and on and on?
There was another one that was brought in there this morning, I believe, by one lady of CHAT, wanted to talk about viruses and flu and a couple other things.
It's a medical fiction, basically, and there have been many medical fictions.
Manufactured by our unknowns, I guess you would call them.
The Rockefeller Institute, there was a group out of France that took care of the Europeans.
The Asians have sort of, you know, the Asians are the drones.
They just do, they believe in, you know, whatever the authority says we do.
Not all of them, but the great majority.
I mean, just like the rest of the world.
But they, they're the servile mentality.
They don't question it.
So they don't get bombarded with a lot of that free will steering about, like the Westerners do.
They don't have the propaganda machine as elaborate as the Westerners do.
They don't need it, right?
Because they focus on food, clothing, and shelter.
If you know people from Asia, all the way from the Pacific Rim to mainland China, and even Japan and all that, they have a sense of statism or authoritatism, that it's there to serve a function, and our function is to work within, you know, a certain framework of what we understand as our, you know, food, clothing, shelter.
Where the Westerners have somehow been given this idea that they can do whatever they want.
You know, they have this concept of, I don't know, we don't call it freedom and liberty, and they could choose to do whatever they want.
You know what I mean?
Like, for example, you know, they can have a Midwestern farmer, you know, and if the boy, young child says, I want to grow up to be a doctor, no one's going to complain.
Alright son, just make sure you study well, and we'll send you to a good school if we can afford it.
That's the response to that, right?
Most likely.
Unless, you know, the next summer, you know, when, you know, there's a new tractor, and it's like, what's the new tractor for?
To make sure you stay on the farm, right?
That's for you.
Well, there's that response also, but in Asia, if you come from a certain group or whatever, and you say that, that's like, you know, we're just going to ignore that, right?
So, until it became more Western to a certain degree, and of course, you have, you know, the idea of, I don't know how much of an underground market there is, but there's a lot of Asian people from, I've met quite a few actually, quite a few, meaning like 30 or 40 or 50 in the past couple of decades.
They come over here, they're washing dishes, and they phone back saying that if you come here, you'll make enough money to live like a king, right?
Right.
It's just different, right?
So, you know, there's an interesting cultural aspect to many of these things.
Just like, for example, if you go to the continent of Africa, in some suburban or semi-developed, you know, areas, even cities, you'll see buildings half-finished, and they're sitting there for like, you know, 10, 20 years, and you're like, what the hell, you know?
And well, they don't believe in getting low construction loans, so if they save up enough money, they'll put some of the bricks down and build the shell, and then like, if they have enough money in five or ten years, they'll put the windows in.
You know what I mean?
It's not like here, where, you know, well, let's just get a construction loan and build it all in one, you know, go, right?
Right.
Yeah, so you got to understand a little bit of the culture, but now it's all being, now, let's go back, you know, everyone is being accommodated by these demonic forces.
So what, you know, what do you want?
Because you're going to be accommodated as long as it's in line with what you've been raised to believe in, is what you should want, which is, that goes back to the mindset.
And the society you're in, I would think, also, plays a big part, you know, what the economy is like.
Well, there's the mindset, you see how the triggers work, you know, like, okay, let's say when you said the society, how it works, let's use the computer as a metaphor.
Would you say that everyone who has, like, a Microsoft computer is in the same, all those computers are in the same society?
They use Windows and, right, Microsoft's operating system, right?
No matter where they are, there's that computer culture society, whether, how far or how close they are, if it runs a Microsoft operating system, that's pretty much that Microsoft society, right?
So what happens is, even though they're all in the same society, they all break down and have different problems and catch different viruses and are susceptible and use different ways, each machine, typically.
Many of them can be used the same, but typically you can't say that they're all going to have the same problems, right?
Right.
So, and a lot of them is hardware based also.
So, I mean, not a lot, but often.
Let's go with people.
I'll give you an example.
I won't use names here.
If I use names, you folks might know who it is.
I made a phone call to a particular place and I got a receptionist and it got bumped up to a secretary and I started having a conversation.
This was regarding medicine and research.
And I brought up a few terms, you know, he says, well, you know, they're not available, but, you know, I'll take your query, I'll take some notes on it, and I'll move it along.
I said, oh, wow, I've never had that, because usually when you get a secretary, they say, I'll give you a name, they'll call you back, and that's it, right?
Right.
Very rarely do they say, I'll take, you know, give me a synopsis on what you want to know and I'll take notes on it and refer that as well.
I mean, that's really, that's a pretty cool, I mean, you really feel like you're being obliged, right?
So, I got a few things and then I paused because it got real quiet and I said, well, what do you think about that so far?
She goes, I don't know, I'm not technical.
I'm not a technical person, the secretary said.
I said, really?
Oh, okay, interesting.
So, because this happens often, and I explained, I said, can I make a personal comment, you know, don't take offense, but can I just give you what I've discovered with many people that say that?
She goes, oh, sure.
So, at some point in your life during your
youth, there was someone within the area, either family or social, that said
they're not technical and all the other people either applauded it and said
that's fine and they were still respected or still accepted and you
looked at that and you said, well, you know, being tech, you know, that's, I
have to discipline myself to learn technical things, let's say, and this
person here is respected and liked by others and they say that they don't like
technical stuff and they get away with it.
You know what?
I'm going to use that line the rest of my life.
Does that make any sense, what I just said?
Oh, yeah.
The same way that people say, oh, I want to talk about, you ever hear about, oh, I'm not religious, you know, no, no, I don't want to talk about God, I'm not religious.
It's not that they're not religious, of course they are, you know, if they wake up in the morning and brush their teeth or, you know, doing anything regularly, they don't know what that means, but what happened with them also, at some point in their life, they recognized that people that were still liked and respected said that and got away with it, and they said, I'm going to use that line.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, that does make sense, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so anybody who benefit from this, email me for contact information, it's 150 bucks an hour for a PsycheVal there, there you go.
You know, it's funny, I had a guy once, he used to do these Skype calls, these group calls, and he says, oh, I said, why do you keep coming here?
You never say anything.
He says, oh, man, I got a really good deal from a psychotherapist, and you know, I pay like half because it was a friend of the family, but I get more out of listening to you than them, and I'm like, oh, I'm gonna stop right here, you got to send me your contact information so I could send you a bill, but anyway, that's just a joke.
So, all right, I'm going to move
from this, I'm just doing some weather work, I hate to say, right, say or not say,
yeah, actually, if anyone's interested, I'm aiming pretty much north from the
southwest, you go to any weather map, you'll see there's a huge swath, go to a
24-hour one, and you'll see what's going on, it's pretty interesting, and
then the idea is to reverse it, so you know, half the weathermen get fired
because all of their forecasts won't work.
I'd be grateful for a warmer weather.
Yeah, we could do that, that's actually, we could do that, you know,
once back, there was someone in Chicago, an investor type, it says there's a big
snowstorm coming in four days, if you could stop that, I believe it, and we
stopped, it was sunny, it went up 20 degrees, and they were really
enthralled, but after, skeptical again, it was like, oh, I gotta keep doing it, it
doesn't work that way, you know, so, Sam, there we go, Sam, we're on with Bruce,
and so, what's going on, Sam, anything you want to talk about, I'll just
share with everyone, you know, there's no subject of study for tonight,
other than just getting, you know, some, you can either save our breath to cool
our porridge, or blow balloons, or whatever, but there's really not much to
talk about, is there, tonight?
Well, I mean, initially, that wasn't the case, but we can bounce around, I suppose.
I guess I had a general question that I've been
walking around with in my head, and I've had some encounters with people where
you try to talk to them about their perspective on things, and these are just
sort of, I don't know, regular people, for lack of a better word, like young people
in their early 20s that don't really have much direction, and they're just
doing whatever, and when you try to have a conversation with them about, say, the
ideal interplay between being objective and subjective, because when you try to
objectify things, there's this trendy mindset currently, which I guess you
could say is some kind of an offshoot from the New Age, where people want to be
very feelings-driven, and want their sensory experiences to sort of dictate
the direction of their lives, and when you try to suggest that they should be a
bit more rational, they associate this with some kind of, um, what's the bad guy
in the Stanley Kubrick movie?
Dr. Strangelove, evil, overly cold, not very warm, projecting, and they seem to have a hard time getting over that image, and I try to sort of show that the objective and the subjective can go hand in hand, that you do have to have some kind of a metric to measure what you're seeing in the world, whilst at the same time, sure, you can go out and be sort of engaged in emotional pursuits also.
So my question is sort of, how would the Greek, using Greek speak, sort of show that interplay as being the ideal, rather than having it swing to one extreme?
Okay, let's go back piece by piece.
The crux of the matter is the younger people, twenty-somethings objectifying, right?
Maybe they don't know how to objectify, because it was never simplified.
I would suggest that the easiest way to define objectification, other than it's the absence of subjectivity, is whether it's a concept or a physical thing, is to start by understanding its origin, right?
So like, for example, can mankind be objectified when we have, let's say, creationism versus evolution?
And I put the verses there because it's still viewed that way.
And then there's the attempt to harmonize them.
Well, yes, because if, let's just look at the origin of the creation myth or story or declaration, because I gave you the ways it's viewed, and then let's just look at where evolution came from, that whole concept, its origins.
And now we can start objectifying the information, right?
But the problem with, you want to do what they call psychoanalysis of young people, is very simple.
Well, they're small people, they were just recently children, and now their stature has increased, so they're not so small, but their minds are still small, just like their parents.
I think you've heard me discuss that people stop developing at eight or nine years old, but this is not good to tell them, because they think...
But the evaluation of these young people is that, especially this generation right now, has realized, even though it's difficult for them to elaborate or communicate it, is that the old people are fools.
They've been lied to, and the stuff that the old people do and believe too is rubbish.
You get it?
Okay, but then now they're in a conflict, because wherever they go to get
edification, it's usually an older person, like a college professor, or, you know,
the talking heads on TV, or church, or wherever they go, or, you know, they're
told to usually garner information from other people, and, you know, that know,
they're in the know, and they tend to be older, so you got a little bit of a
problem.
That's why I think you and I once had a conversation, and one of the best ways, and I'm not really for it, but I wouldn't disagree, or I would say, I would agree, but not strongly, is that the best way to get through to young people is through video games, music, and that culture that they adhere to as being, you know, something that they find happiness in.
You know what I mean?
So that's why very often it's said, imagine making an objective film about subject matter.
Okay, what does that mean?
Well, let's actually make a, you know, there's a Bible-themed films.
Let's just do, let's make a film that's in scripture.
You know, that'll, you know, let's do a Ten Commandments movie, how it really went down, right, with Moses being 80 years old, and the tablets being, like, really small in his hand, and, you know, with them walking on an ice bridge, let's say, right, because it was really cold out, which was a miracle for it to freeze like that, you know.
So anyway, you know, the older demographic, if you're 21 and older, you're going to lose it.
They're not going to be able to stand it, but the 21 and younger are going to love it, right.
They will, from personal experience, I'll tell you, young people do, quote-unquote, resonate with the truth much better than older people do, as a general group.
Yeah, that's understood.
And they're not going to get it from the older people.
But what I'm talking about is more of a linguistical methodology for making a case, because you'll talk to these young people, or at least I will, and you can't really get them to see what you're trying to say about objectivity.
Like, they're very stuck in this feelings-driven way of thinking, where if you try to put that down, they feel like you're demonizing it, and they don't even know why they have to be rational about anything.
Yeah, if they don't like something, they'll just say, that's an opinion, that's why I don't like it, it's not the truth, yeah.
Well, that's the problem, that's the armoring, you know, Wilhelm Reich talked about armoring, and I gave a mild example of it earlier, how people latch on to catchphrases they carry for the rest of their lives, because it gives them a feeling that they could get away from a certain discipline, right.
And accomplishment, yes.
Right, so, yeah, well, let's just look at it several ways.
One way, let's go back to Scripture, these people that we're discussing, these younger people, are not viewed favorably in Scripture, right?
This last generation is probably the most wicked group of people to ever walk on this planet, right?
And we're like, well, how could that be?
You know, well, we'll find out.
Okay, so that's a big thing to consider, right?
Yeah, I would suggest the ones born after 1998, or specifically the ones born after 2003, 2004, right, those would be in the last generation more specifically, you know.
Yeah, but their vessels for that.
Sure, sure, but that doesn't mean that you can't talk to one of them and get them to do something.
No, I think the whole group niche can be, if you talk to one of them, you can talk to all of them, and vice versa, right?
And then there's the more specific side.
The other way I would, the way I approach young people is by questioning.
Like, for example, today I was out doing commerce, and I noticed the clerk was within the range that you were discussing, young 20s.
I mean, actually, if I told you they looked like 13, but they were really around 20, 22, around there, you know what I mean?
So, and I handed them the notes, and they gave me the number.
I said, here are the notes.
I hope you get money for it someday.
And they kind of gave me like the stare for half a second.
And I said, well, do you know the serial numbers on the money?
She goes, what?
I said, the serial numbers on the money.
You know where they come from?
They're like, no, I said birth certificates.
And they're like, really?
I said, does Does that sound morally correct to you?
Have you ever heard that before?
He goes, no, that doesn't sound morally correct to me at all.
So right there you're asking several questions and you're actually providing within the answer the issue of morality.
She didn't understand what you said though, that's just a pat answer.
Yeah, but it's a start.
No, but that's not good enough.
I mean, I'm talking about how do you present objectivity as being desirable, not throwing like little crumbs.
That's like telling people they have to like something.
Well, no, it's not saying that they have to, but that it is advisable that they would at least inquire into it.
Oh, that's a different thing.
Yeah, now you've become their attorney though.
No, I'm not their attorney.
I know, I know.
I'm an attorney for what I'm saying.
Yeah, yeah.
See, I've been, just from personal experience, I've done it one-on-one and I've done it in groups.
And with both you have to use a very high sense of discernment of the group.
You have to put every aspect of what you know, what's called profiling and stereotyping at its highest and best use.
Like if you see a guy who's 20 years old with jet black hair, black fingernails and a duster coat dragging on the ground with work boots and he looks like Eddie Munster, you're not going to say the same thing to them.
Because I've seen them, those creatures walking around.
Oh, yeah.
And if you see, you know, a Latin or black dude with a baseball cap to the side, you know, dragging knuckles on the ground with his pants all the way down, it's different, you know.
So, and then you got the preppy white boy, you know, that's different too.
Yeah, but what you're saying about different is just the tone of how you approach them.
I'm talking about the content.
Anybody can adjust their tone that has some sense.
Let's tone the content also to a certain degree.
Content also.
That's really a big question.
But that can be adjusted when you think about how would you address a mixed multitude of people at once.
No, no, I'm talking about one-on-one, not a mixed multitude.
One-on-one, you have to use every profiling, stereotypical, prejudiced thing you can imagine at its highest and best use.
In other words, all those things that I tell you are not politic, you get it?
Yeah, I don't mean be stereotypical and profile on a loose and nonsensical way.
You almost have to be a bit of a shrink, you know, just to get in their head and feel them out and know where they're going and where they came from.
Yeah, but you can see it depends.
If you could read what they call the spirit through the eyes, that's a really good one.
I'll give you an example.
These sodomite types or lesbian types, once you get a point, they're very easy.
Because when you look at their eyes, their eyes look like plastic.
They have no light coming out of it at all.
They have no glint.
It looks like they're mannequins.
It's really interesting.
I've been showing people that and they're like, yeah, that's real interesting.
I say, yeah, well, there's a spirit that's working in that, right?
All this stuff has a spiritual counterpart to it.
But how would you communicate it, Sam?
Again, it's so highly specialized.
It sounds like what you're saying is not…
In other words, what you're saying, Sam, is how do you objectify being objective?
How do you objectify imparting an objective reality to someone?
Yes, and also how do you objectify that to them as they're looking back at you?
Because you're trying to give them something that they can then make sense of and establish as being valuable.
Timing is important as well.
If they've got to get somewhere and they're not really listening to you, it doesn't matter what you say.
No, well, here's two different scenarios.
So, one, I'm talking to a certain girl.
She's 20, and the conversation goes relatively well.
I'd say, you know, 7 out of 10.
She's receptive.
She's listening.
She's interested.
She's asking questions.
She actually has to go take a smoke, and she's like, why don't you come with me so we can continue the conversation?
And then even when I don't go with her because I'm working, she comes back and says, let's keep talking about what we were talking about before.
But then, you know, the next day when I show up, there's hardly any exchange of words at all.
And you can tell that, like, the spark has sort of died down or the spark of curiosity has died down.
And I know that I'm not going to meet her the next day because she's going to be gone from the city.
So clearly she's not feeling any kind of stress or urgency enough to establish a permanent connection, like give me your phone number or let's be friends on Facebook.
So I might never see her again.
But I know that for a brief moment, she had this sort of lucid realization of something that was pertinent, and then maybe it died down later.
I count that as a success because it shows that rhetorically I was able to establish something.
But then in another situation, you come up to somebody who is exactly the same age, same gender.
And they're essentially antithetical to everything that you're saying, not in a violent way or aggressive way because I'm being diplomatic.
But you can see that they don't really want to continue in that subject.
And then they say, well, I have to go to the bathroom.
And then they come back and change the subject so that we end up going somewhere else.
OK.
I'd say the first one, Sam, I think you might have given just enough that maybe later on they might pick it up.
But that second one sounds like a lost cause.
Yeah.
This is either one.
If it's the same gender, Sam, just remember this.
All right.
Candy is dandy, but liquor is quicker.
But anyway, that's an old saying.
Bruce is old enough to probably know that, right?
But anyway.
I mean, it comes down to what I'm seeing as being skill.
Because I had the skill to deal with whatever the mindset or the spirit was behind the first girl.
And with the second girl, it was a completely different armory.
OK, let's get ghetto.
Ghetto means you got game.
You got game, man.
You ain't got no game.
Anyway.
What?
Jesus.
I'm just joking, yo.
But anyway.
That's why I said back in the days, was it the 50s, 60s, there was a saying, candy is dandy, but liquor is quicker.
Liquor is quicker.
Yeah.
No, I would suggest it's mindset.
And regardless of what you're talking about, if the mindset's not there, it doesn't matter.
Like, you know, in Greek-speak, we cover every subject under the sun, right?
And ones that are not even under the sun, let's say, allegedly.
So the thing is, it's a mindset that allows one to do that, right?
You're presuming.
Like, when I do Greek-speak, let's say I go on, let's say, something like a Ridiculous Freeman interview, I try to set the mindset immediately.
And right away I know it's OK if there's 1,000 people listening.
If we lose 995, it's OK.
And the mindset's already set that up.
So when I, let's say, give an example, this sounds like, you know, you and I now are playing table tennis, right, back and forth with this conversation, because it's going to be very personal aspects that have to come up.
I like to address the mindset.
And within that address, I also tell people, within a few words or somehow, that most people don't want to talk about this because it's uncomfortable.
But, you see, so instead of making it seem like what we're saying within this framework of objectivity, let's say, is going to be all peaches, peachy keen, and roses, and rosy, and all that, try to let them know right away this is, you know, what did they do with the gangster rap albums after, was it Ice-T, F the Police, all that.
You've got to put the explicit lyrics sticker on the CDs and, remember?
Yeah, so you've got to let them know that there's an explicit lyrics and explicit thought forms on this conversation.
So anyway, that's one way.
Well, there is a facet of pop culture which has sort of valorated or valorized a sort of thinking.
You may have heard it.
It's sort of trendy right now.
It's called wokeness.
So it's this idea of being aware or being awake of what's, quote, unquote, actually happening.
It doesn't really extend further than, say, sort of benign conspiracy theories like be aware that there's GMOs in the marketplace or be aware that the government lies or things like this.
But it's still this idea that you want to be keyed into certain knowledge that the masses are oblivious to because they're stupid.
So you're the one who's not stupid and therefore you're woke.
So you can use that sort of thing to make inroads into a conversation by appealing to people's sense of wanting to be special or there's self-exceptionalism by touching on the mindset and suggesting that, well, have you considered this?
And they'll find that to be interesting.
I'm going to stop you right there because if we went back 500 years ago and told anyone that the government lies and the church is full of crap and the drugs are bad or whatever, whether they're legal or illegal, people will agree.
They know that.
It's always been that way.
The government always lies.
So how about one suggestion would be do you know how people say the government lies and they do and how this is so?
That's because they're accommodating the mindset of the people.
There's a difference there, a big difference.
To expect that the government is not going to lie, if we went back 4,000 years, any time in history, except for certain people that were supposed to be lawful, the government didn't lie.
For example, if you go to Scripture, I'll get back on the subject real quick, there was no secrets from the people.
There were sequestered places where not everyone can go.
Let's say the high priest can only go at a certain time, but there were no secrets.
So what's happening now is the people have been let down to a belief and have been groomed and bred.
Now, you can groom something out of someone, but you can't unbreed something out of someone.
So they've been bred and groomed into a certain way where everything, there isn't all-out chaos, where everyone's just killing each other at random because they're being accommodated.
For example, that's why I always say that, maybe you haven't heard me say this, but I'll say it.
When there's something to be acquired, I won't say I can't afford that.
I'll say I don't want to afford that.
Because how many times have you heard people working, flipping burgers at minimum wage, and they want a brand-new car, and they get it.
They'll get enough for the deposit, they'll get someone to co-sign, they'll get a loan, and then in two years they have a brand-new car.
You're like, wait a second, that's like a three-year salary, how'd you do that?
Because they wanted to afford it, even though they couldn't.
So instead of saying I can't afford that, say I don't want to afford that, past, present, future.
Or another way is that doesn't accommodate me.
Instead of I don't like it, or I don't want it, that doesn't accommodate me.
Actually, let me just bounce around a little bit here.
I had a conversation with someone over a decade ago, and I was talking about legal stuff.
And I said, look, man, it's all contract.
I saw him about a year later, and he says, Greek, you were right.
I said, what happened?
He says, well, they wanted to give me 30 days in jail.
And I told the judge that sentencing, I told him that I can't do that.
And the judge says, why?
I says, because that doesn't benefit me.
And the judge stopped and said, then what does?
He says that I have this case dismissed, and I don't do any time in jail at all.
And the judge says, okay, how about a $500 fine and 30 hours community service?
He says, yeah, fine, I'll do that.
So let me back up here.
The judge wanted him to do 30 days in jail agreeing with the prosecutor, right?
This was over, like, signing paper.
Like, they charged him for being a false notary or something, and he wasn't.
Anyway, to make a long story short and just focusing on the matter here, when he objected to the 30 days in jail, it was because, you know, he needs to work to pay his rent, and he had a child or whatever.
So he can't be gone for 30 days, you know.
So when the judge says, why don't you object to the 30 days, it's because it doesn't benefit me.
And the judge says, okay, then how about this then?
Do you see my point?
So when you're having a conversation, even on a layman level, when you're dealing with people, either social or from an edifying point of view, like if someone brings you somebody, let's say you tell something to someone and they can't explain it like you, they'll actually bring them to you and say, hey, Sam, why don't you tell them what you told me because you could say it better, right?
That's a possibility, right?
When that happens and when there's a communication, why are people listening?
You know, is it because if they hear the information they'll be better, you know, financially, stature-wise, you know, status-wise, or what?
Is it going to alleviate a fear that they have?
Is it going to satisfy a curiosity?
You know, how is it accommodating or benefiting them?
So, you know, like Sun Tzu said, you know, the art of war, one of the reasons it was essential to compile this is because he thought about what all people have in common is personal gain, the desire for personal gain.
You see?
So how does it benefit anyone?
I'll give you a reason why.
The reason why I did Greek speak is very simple.
It's because no one else was saying these things, and most of them were blaringly obvious.
I mean, it's just so obvious.
It's like the 800-pound gorilla in the room filing, clipping his toenails.
You know, that's how obvious, you know.
So I had to say it from that point of view.
I never went out and said, well, this is going to benefit anyone.
On the contrary, I said this is going to break up.
If you try to decide to go down this road with even half the subjects discussed with Greek speak, I assure you, it will break up your family, you won't have any friends, and you're going to have a miserable time.
But at least you'll have a miserable time being happy you know the truth.
Let me say that again.
You'll have a miserable time being happy that you know the truth.
Amen.
Sure, but that kind of thing pertains more to sort of these closed intimate relationships between family members where there are certain expectations of how people should act and things are a little more sensitive.
Whereas if you're going to run into a stranger, you have the ability to sort of create the lay of the land on the fly if you respect whatever the dynamics are between your personality and their personality.
And as far as what you said about personal gain, I feel like everybody wants to have a narrative that they can use to contextualize their experiences.
Otherwise they end up becoming apathetic or misled or deceived or there's a cognitive dissonance because they can't understand the world around them.
Well, hold on.
Most people are living under the presumption that other people care about what they have to say.
And I think I've mentioned this before.
From public speaking, I'd look at people and I'm wondering if they're really listening or they're just waiting for me to shut up and sit down so they can get the microphone and say what they have to say.
Well, I think about that occasionally.
And what I keep coming to is that if what you have to say is interesting enough that it captivates them, then it does tame down that desire to then jump up and speak.
So what I'm trying to find out is how can you create a presentation of this objective mindset in a way that is captivating to people?
Simple.
You've got to be on the fly.
Do you have to be a surface bear?
Maybe, but at least you're getting somewhere.
Well, yeah, the surface bear, I've thrown that out there a couple of times.
I never explained it fully, but I could another time or maybe later.
But it's very simple.
I can only, for expediting, review what I've said.
If you've ever heard Greek speak, especially, like I said, when I do like a ridiculous Freeman thing or whatever else, I'll come out and I'll mention timekeeping.
Why?
Because that's the most obvious that most people will encounter that.
Most people will encounter, let's say, the money system or currency, but they don't think about it.
But most people will think more about time than they think about the money system.
So there's a certain order.
There's a bringing up the obvious and why and how it can be considered for what it is versus what the person might think personally about it.
And that goes back to what you're saying.
Now you have to find people that want to be objective.
Just like I said earlier, if I do get an interview and there's a thousand people listening, I make sure in the first 30 seconds that I lose 99% of the audience.
Yeah, but that's because you have the luxury of choosing 10% of the audience because you even have an audience to begin with.
But if you're talking to one person, that is your skills versus their censorship.
And what is the level of your skill and your rhetorical presentation?
Well, the level then, again, is you need to figure out who you're talking to really well and get into their desire, which is common.
If they're uncomfortable, they want to be comfortable.
If they're hungry, they want to eat.
If they're stupid, they usually don't know they're stupid, so they don't want to learn.
You see?
You know, stupid people don't know that they're stupid, by the way.
You know how I know that?
I go talk to a professor, ask him if he's stupid, and he'll say, no, I'm not stupid.
I tell these idiots usually, I said, you know that if you knew the truth, you'd be fired in like a week, right?
Not a truth in general, you know, like some kind of altruistic truth.
You know, I'm talking about the specific field that they're studying, even if it's the anal glands of the Moroccan housefly.
A misunderstood subject.
Right.
So, again, it's very specific, but I would say if I was speaking to a plebeian, you know, just someone out on the street, it might be a little harsh, but generally when you're walking about and running into people, they are so far gone that when I use the term space heater, I mean it.
They're just taking up space and giving off heat.
Yeah, but this is just, I mean, at the end of the day, we can choose to not reject that view, and it shouldn't be rejected because it is pointing to enough truth.
But it is pejorative, ultimately, to say that they're space heaters, even if they are space heaters, because you can reach one person.
You know, Sam.
So do you have the skills to do that?
Look, it's winter season here.
I reach for a space heater occasionally.
Do you get it?
Because it's cold, space heater warms up.
Okay, so if you need a body, you know.
Usually when the Greek gets stuck, he starts making jokes.
No, it's not about being stuck.
It's a matter of, you know, it's too open-ended.
I think it's personal.
Let's go back to the interviews.
Usually when someone wants to interview the Greek, I look at the rest of the stuff that they're doing, and I know, you know, I see the response that they've gotten on the rest of the stuff, and I see the mindset of the people that are coming repeatedly because the chances.
Let's say I get interviewed by someone who's got 10 YouTubes.
The chances of each of the 10 YouTubes being watched by individual people that have not repeated is very slim.
They're usually repeats.
So I get to see the mindset, right?
So you could use that concept with people that you know or even don't know.
You know, if you see someone out.
You're doing an analysis ahead of time.
Yeah, yeah.
And most people right now, just like at any time other than right now, what's so interesting right now is that the, believe it or not, people are not so concerned about food, clothing, and shelter as much as they used to be because they don't have to interact with it as much.
Specifically.
In other words, you could work a certain job or a job that has nothing to do with food, clothing, and shelter, and what you get, the money that's ordered up with the paycheck, you know, pay to the order of, you're ordering money.
You used to get food, clothing, shelter, where years ago, no matter what you did in society, you had to invest a certain amount of time in food, clothing, and shelter.
You didn't buy a shirt.
You didn't buy a coat.
You had to know someone or make it yourself, let's say.
Or, you know, you didn't buy a meal.
You had to make it.
And shelter, you also had to modify or make.
So now people are totally removed in most cases from that in most parts of the world where they can pretty much think they can do whatever they want to get those things.
There was a bartering going on back then, you know.
You were in touch with other people.
You knew other people.
One way or another, if you had to have a shirt made, you were two people away from having it done.
Well, gold was the currency of the elite, the monarchs, and the lords.
Silver was the currency of the common man, and barter was the currency of the poor.
Yeah.
So whenever you hear bartering, by the way, that's poor, the poor classes.
The common classes, meaning the society at large used silver.
That's why if you remember pre-1960s American coins, whether they were dimes, nickels, quarters, half dollars, were made of what, Bruce?
You remember?
Silver, mostly.
Right, yeah.
So that was common.
And then you had the gold certificates.
You know, whenever you got a 50 note that said, you know, at any Federal Reserve Bank, exchange it for what?
Gold.
When it was 20 or $10 notes, it was exchanged for what?
Silver.
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, Seth just mentioned that he will call in in about 10 minutes or so.
Oh, okay.
So long.
Yeah, anybody else wants to call in, that's fine.
We don't have any subject matter tonight that we're hammering out.
And if you'd like to bring up a subject and call in, you know, welcome to do so.
Sure.
The point that Sam is bringing up is an interesting thing.
And I've mentioned loosely to I think Sam personally and other people about that general roundabout subject.
How do you communicate this to other people or, you know, why is there mixed reaction on this?
And ultimately, there's something that I've been speaking of called cosmic censorship, right?
And another thing that I've mentioned is our thoughts are externally garnered, right?
We receive and communicate.
So just like in the computer, when you have a port or something, you know, that the information coming in or out is controlled via that port or that program.
In other words, when you're addressing someone, whether it's known to you, so the person is well-known or just unfamiliar or just vaguely acquainted with them, you're not just speaking to them directly.
You're speaking to what's controlling them on the other side.
Yeah, but you can't just presume that they don't have any agency of their own because certain facets of their mind.
Yeah.
They do.
That's why it's demanded and commanded that we are disciplined and educated, right, throughout the years, right?
And what that does is the discipline and the education and the edification that we have as people within a culture and also individually is how do we free will handle that situation without knowing it.
I'll give you an example of how that works so simply.
You've heard me discuss lymphology and the biological vacuum.
And they're both very different, but I bring up lymphology because it's closer to the reality than the allopathic medicine, you know, that you're just chemical dump, right?
Okay.
So if you burn, bruise, break, what do I say?
Squeeze it.
And I don't mean just squeeze it.
I mean methodically go into a regimen where you have extreme constriction that relieves within an interim, so you have to maintain circulation and maintain that squeeze to produce a biological vacuum or retain that so it heals very quickly, anywhere from five to 100 times faster than normal.
So when you bring up that point, it's like, oh, okay, why does that make sense to most people?
Because you ever see someone bump their nose or their elbow?
What's the first thing they do?
They grab it and they hold on to it, don't they, right?
You ever see someone?
Bump my elbow.
What do they do?
They put their hand on it.
Grab that bugger and hold on to it tight, yeah.
Yeah, and you're like, hey, what are you doing?
Oh, I just bumped my elbow.
And if you were doing a storyboard for a film, someone who just came around the corner, bumped their elbow, how would you cast the actor?
How would you direct the actor?
You would have the actor, let's say, if he bumps his left elbow, have his right arm facing to the left with his hand cupping the elbow.
Wouldn't you see that in the scene, let's say, to make it realistic?
Or if someone just got punched in the nose, you would have them coming around the corner as an actor.
Wouldn't you direct them to put their hands on their nose while they're telling the other actor, I just got punched in the nose, you see?
And doesn't that seem very logical and rational to everyone, that's the normal thing to do?
Okay, so when you give a piece of information which is reactionary also, what is normal for them to do?
Well, they have to contemplate it or ignore it because they have that choice.
I mean, yes, I do understand how the censorship works on their end.
I'm just trying to find an offensive with which I can pierce that.
And like I said, it's some kind of a skill that I haven't quite nailed down.
Sure, sure.
One thing that I would do on that is when you, you know, the concept of a mirror, right, is to send a reflection and that's the general, you know, back to the source.
So one thing that I would suggest is public speaking because you will learn more about your delivery when you're doing public speaking.
I'll give you an example.
Let's just say the first time I got on radio on AFR, it was to co-host the Vinnie Eastwood show and have Trevor James Constable as a guest, right?
And I was just by myself.
I knew I was just alone because Trevor wasn't even on the line yet.
And the moment they said you're on, it was like I was just in the room with a microphone.
I was facing a proverbial black hole and I felt like I was going to fall into it, right?
I didn't know.
I just all of a sudden realized this giant abyss of silence, right?
If you ever speak publicly to a small audience, when I would mean like five to ten or more people, and you present yourself to speak and they all go quiet and they're listening, ready, focusing on you, there is a moment there, whether it's a short moment or a long moment, where you're like, uh, okay.
What you're noticing is a vacuum that happens there.
You see, Bruce is saying you've experienced that, right, Bruce?
Oh, yeah.
And this is natural and normal.
And all the speech classes in the world, because there are speech classes, by the way, some better vocational schools give them in the lower grades, let's say in high school, and there are speech, you know, how to present things publicly.
None of those help.
I mean, they could tell you how to set up the subject matter, how to address a crowd, but nothing can help you with that.
You know, I think being a people person really, really helps.
You know, interchanging with people all day long gives you kind of a skill to read them really quick and kind of wrap your head around where they're at and then opening.
If you get that opportunity.
And, Sam, I empathize with you 100%.
I've been in that spot where I've tried very carefully and articulate, you know, articulate, bring my point across, and I really do empathize with where you struggle from.
And it's a tricky course.
You really have to read on the fly.
But, Bruce, how would you say that's changed at all, or does it change?
I think this is what we're trying to maybe impart to Sam.
I think every person is different.
And for me, it's like dropping a seed.
I throw it out there.
If they come back, great.
If they don't, you know, I try.
In some cases, that's great, too.
Yeah.
I'm just joking.
Well, it's acceptable, you know.
Yeah.
It has to be.
But what I wanted to ask you, Bruce, on this is when I was explaining how the vacuum, you know, shows up when you first do public speaking, you said, yeah, you've noticed that.
But do you notice that that's changed at all the more you do it?
Yes.
Yes, I believe so.
I believe so.
A little more outspoken, not timid, certainly not mic-shy.
I've been in front of a mic before many times.
Well, let's say there's no mic and you're in front of people.
It's the same thing.
No, that would be a different thing.
Well, no.
No, it wouldn't be.
I've been there.
I've played in front of people.
So I think in that respect, no, I wouldn't feel intimidated.
All right.
As long as you don't play with yourself in front of people, you'll be fine.
Exactly.
Okay.
Yeah, you know, there's many aspects to it.
I think eventually it's public speaking.
And eventually you're going to discover whether you're addressing one person or many when you're comfortable.
The same, you're pretty much you've got what they call the gift of gab, or now you can gab, you know.
Yep, you're ready to fly.
Yeah.
I've found that most people can't communicate, period.
I'll give you an example.
Very often I hear people in conversation and they'll give all the adjectives and the point that is salient or that needs to be conveyed is given in the end.
And it kind of labors the listener.
And that comes from, I can not wholly blame, but the concept of when someone says they saw a movie, you know, the spoiler concept, I don't want to know what happens.
So that develops a framework where people just keep creating, you know, like, you know, I went to the store today, you know, the store that I usually go to and so and so and so and so and they were out of this.
Well, okay.
Well, why don't you say they were out of this at the store first, right?
In other words, give the important stuff first, right?
Give the spoiler first when you're communicating.
Give the important stuff first.
Don't follow the social norm, which is, oh, I don't want to know what happens.
I want to watch it for myself, you know, a TV show or the movies or a book.
Where if you know anyone that works in film, by the way, or in the creative arts and performance, they want to know the end first.
They want to know how it ends.
And that's how they judge the whole thing.
They're like, okay, great.
So the rest is film.
They know that.
But the common person somehow has been groomed to not want to know what happens until the show is over.
You ever notice that?
Yeah, but if you tell them, like for some people they go, like if you go and you watch Scream and you don't know what Scream is and you're watching it and you're enjoying what you're seeing for the first hour, if you had been told that it ends with the bad guy getting stabbed 50 times and dismembered, you might not have watched it.
But now you're stuck and you want to see how it ends.
So exactly, people are stuck.
People, they are stuck, yes.
Now, stuck can mean different things.
If you're working in a mine, you don't want to get stuck.
You know, they have gears that if you throw your hard hat in there, it crushes it like a piece of tissue paper.
So it depends on the situation.
And there is a big machine that's grinding people, and they're not going to get stuck in it.
They're just going to get ground and spit out.
Here's another example.
If I know I have to get to the point with someone, when they give me a date, you know, I say, that's a work schedule, you know, you can't keep time with that.
You ever notice weekend, weekend, weekend, weekday?
That's the Pope's work schedule.
And some people just, huh?
And other people are like, holy crap.
Say no more.
I got it.
You notice I said some people?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's always been a one out of a million scenario, by the way.
You know, what was it, 7,000 have not bowed their knee to ball is an interesting thing.
That speaks volumes.
It's different.
It is different, but it's a one out of a million situation.
Yeah, but is it a one out of a million because of them or because of you?
Well, that has to be determined, like Bruce and I were talking about earlier.
Mm-hmm.
It's because of them.
They are a certain way.
It's always them.
But here's the thing.
The crux in Greek speak is this.
I don't say it often enough.
If the situation's screwed up, it's not you.
It's them.
How do I know?
Because they tell everyone it's you that's doing it, not them.
No, it's backwards.
All the psychologists, psychiatrists, self-help gurus say it's you.
No, it's them.
You are in a fucked up, sorry, medical term there, world.
So when stuff goes bad, it's not you.
It's them.
Yes, it is them.
And I got scripture and ancient writs to back me up 100% on that.
So you can even have the elite, the modern-day elite, Illuminatis or whatever you want to call them, Freemasons or whatever.
They know it's them, the people.
The whole society's screwed up.
Yeah, but the Freemasons and the Illuminati, they themselves are stupid.
Yeah, I know that.
So because they're stupid, they can't offer any kind of – and I'm not saying that you could really do a remedy because God's doing it.
But they can't even offer anything in the semblance of a remedy.
Whereas what I'm saying is what adjustments do I have to make to myself so at least I can make a bulletproof presentation?
Publicly?
Yeah.
Publicly, you should appear impeccably.
You should wear good clothing and have impeccable appearance, first of all, because this way it's difficult for people to judge you on fashion.
In other words, if you can always appear unfashionable but impeccable, meaning like you're not following any trends, people will listen.
Like giving an example on that, Bruce, you're with me on this, I think.
I remember growing up and I was pretty young in the 60s and 70s and I always heard this thing about hippies.
And whenever I remember going out in public, if I saw a guy with long hair, I said, oh, that's what they're talking about.
Right?
You remember?
The hippies in the 60s and 70s, they were talking, it doesn't matter what you said or what you did, if you were classified as a hippie, forget it.
That's it.
Remember that?
Yeah.
So I didn't know really exactly what that meant until I saw it happening.
And I was like, oh, that's no big deal.
That's just the way they wear their hair and their dress and the way they speak.
What does that have to do with…
But they were ostracized before you got, you see.
There were pot smokers, all sorts of things wrapped up into that.
Anti-war people, everything was wrapped up into the word hippie.
Yeah.
It was undesirable.
Like if you brought home a hippie, it didn't matter what they…
It was a fashion trend, though, because obviously there's no such thing.
It's a fashion, right?
Right.
So you want to be unfashionable but acceptable.
The other thing is timing.
If someone's late for work, they're not going to listen.
If they're ready to go to work, they're not going to listen.
But unless you live at a job or work, you live at a job.
You guys are right.
Most of you are waking hours.
If you're at what they call a job or a yob where the boss lets everyone punch in and go to the movies, then you can talk, you know, especially if the boss allows you to – if the boss wants to hear, the rest will follow.
I don't know.
Again, you notice we're getting very personal.
When I go in public, I always wear a dressy button-down shirt, an Oxford type.
It's usually no less than a $50 or $80 shirt.
It's not a cheap shirt and khakis.
And good-looking shoes usually when I'm out in public if I can.
So right away, I stand out in a crowd.
It's like, where does this guy wear an expensive dress shirt?
Usually, there's a professional type that looks like that.
So I don't know.
I mean that's a good place to start.
I know if I didn't – if I was trendy, I was walking by a mall the other day and I saw $100 jeans in the window with holes in them, rips in them.
I wouldn't – if you paid me $100, I wouldn't wear those in public, let's say, not buy them.
I mean so we're dealing with a very superficial aspect, but your appearance is very important, first of all.
The second thing is the setting is very important.
And the third thing is can you give an important point immediately?
The other thing is how would you put yourself in a situation that you know you would be definitely rejected and see how long you can maintain yourself there?
Again, didn't they have game shows like that in the 70s, Bruce, where they put – see how long someone could be before they get dunked or something like that?
What was it?
Yeah, you had a few of them out there.
Yeah, an endurance kind of thing, but it was a prank kind of endurance.
It was mostly a prank, yeah.
Yeah, go into a situation where you know you're going to be kicked out and see how – you know you're going to be kicked out in the end, but see how long you can keep it going.
In other words, you know the audience is going to be unfriendly to you.
So in other words, if you can get an unfriendly audience to listen, want to listen to you, can you imagine what a friendly audience would do?
Yeah, I mean these sort of things, they do address the issue in a sort of roundabout way, which is not ineffective, but I guess the only way to actually get down to what would work is to find yourself in the practical situation and make adjustments on the fly.
You know, it's an interesting thing if you really take that seriously.
I was thinking of experimenting with this before, going to what they call a Craigslist or putting out flyers to do a public speaking engagement.
I know places that would allow me to do a public speaking engagement.
You'll see very often there are some restaurants that have speaking engagement whatever, and they don't charge you to do it because they want the customers.
They have an area in the back.
What's your slowest night?
You know, our slowest night is Wednesday night because of those damn Christian Bible studies.
All right, okay.
Well, Wednesday night, I'll need an area for 20 people to sit down and do a speech here.
Okay, great.
That's, you know, they've got to order something.
You know, it's 20 potential plates.
And set something like that up and go speak about something and see if you can do that and do it little by little.
And you're going to notice that you're going to get a spirit of speaking.
There is a spirit behind speaking, by the way, publicly.
There's a spirit behind everything.
And those people that we're told are so savage Native Americans and all that are not.
You know, they have totems to everything you can imagine.
I agree.
Seth is mentioning that he was trying to call.
Yeah, he was.
And because if I let him in, it would have put this one on hold.
Ah, okay.
He was just calling in.
Yeah.
Let's see if we can get him online then.
I could add him to a group call.
Yeah, add him in.
Yeah.
Let's see if he has anything to add or take away.
Let's see if this works now.
Public speaking is essentially public speaking.
It doesn't matter how many people you're addressing.
Or even private speaking is the same.
And there is a spirit behind that, ultimately.
I think you and I, Sam, have discussed that when something happens or doesn't happen, the primal elements or the gods either allow it or disallow it, right?
Mm-hmm.
This is one of the hardest things for fleshy humans to comprehend and live with constantly, is that there is a spiritual element behind anything and everything we can experience.
I especially prove that when I speak to the, quote, unquote, religious leader types, whether it's a rabbi, an imam, or a priest, or a minister, whenever you bring up something like an emergency or financial, they'll say, oh, that has nothing to do with God.
They actually say that.
They profess that with their own mouth, right?
So this is the type of spiritual leadership that's out in the world, which is, you know, the opposite.
Let's see, do we have Seth?
Yes.
Am I audible?
Yeah, low but audible.
Yes, you're there.
I can fix the lowness.
Yes, do that.
And on the mic, too.
Yeah, go ahead.
All right.
Is that better?
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
The mic is echoing.
Somebody's echoing.
I'll fix that.
It's speakers, maybe.
So we're discussing public speaking, Seth.
Anything you want to throw in there with Sam about speaking publicly?
I think you brought up discussions that you've had with people.
I know you told us about the academic at the bar scene several times, and perhaps things that happened personal or whatever.
But anything you want to say about what Sam has been asking, if you've been listening?
Yeah, absolutely, actually.
I missed the last, like, maybe three minutes of the conversation.
Oh, that's fine.
But I was going to – public speaking, Sam was asking more about speaking one-on-one to a person, and in one sense I suppose that is public speaking, if it's, you know, with a relative stranger.
But I would say that in talking about the objectivity and the subjectivity is kind of you have to realize who your audience is, whether that's one person or, you know, a multitude of people.
And beyond that, let them change the subject and pull apart whatever subject they turn to.
Etymology makes that a very easy thing to do because any subject that's spoken about they speak about with words.
And so, you know, a common one is, well, that's nice, but what about people move on using the word nice.
And as I'm sure everyone's well aware, nice has a very interesting etymology, especially being that it's used colloquially to describe something that is pleasant.
You know, that's not the intent of that word.
That's not what that word means.
It means silly or stupid.
Right.
I think about three-quarters of the words that people use commonly looked up etymologically will probably differ in meaning to how they think they're being used.
I'd say three-quarters because I've been looking at that.
I've put etymology down, but 50% to 75% is conservative, that about 50% to 75% of the words that people use are not aware of what their etymological meaning is.
So that would be an easy place to grab their attention if they so cared.
That's the point, if they're not empathetic, right?
And if you can take the perspective that, you know, all things are connected one way or another, then juxtaposition from one subject to another doesn't really occur.
If we're discussing the all, then we're discussing the all.
And then it just becomes, well, how can you describe your observations in a manner in which the person that is listening hears?
And even if they don't understand, they have the possibility for comprehension.
Well, speaking of possibilities, I want to throw this in real quick, and then we'll just jump back on the various things on the possibilities.
Do you know that there's a spiritual counterpart to these actions?
And do you know that there is more than an eventuality, or more than, I'm sorry, more than a presumption that when someone is listening to you, or let's say finding out what you have to say interesting enough for them, that they were brought to you, you didn't bring them to yourself, in other words?
In other words, it's happening somewhere else as well, right?
In other words, it was meant for them to hear that, right?
So one way is to ask for those that are ready to hear it, and it's meant for them to hear it, then just, you know, how do we randomly stamp these things out?
Right.
Now we're getting more into the woo-woo spiritual side of things, which is, you know, believe it or not, it's the core.
Yes, but this is known.
Like, we're not, we can't just continue, I mean, there's a certain sphere of one's consciousness that should be aware of that, but you can't just continuously defer to the sense of the fate of what we have been dealt.
Like, what are you going to do?
You have a level of skill, that level of skill can be improved, and it can give tangible results.
Like, that's what I want to see.
What is the result that you are asking for?
I'm not here to overcome the spirit of the world or convert people.
No.
I'm just here to see my results.
What I'm saying is there are billions and trillions of spirits at work here.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean that I cannot achieve a result that is satisfying for myself, because I was never trying to convert the person anyway.
I already gave the example of the girl that I felt, that was a 7 out of 10.
She's gone, I won't see her again.
Don't care.
But I got what I wanted out of that.
I'm not going to get what I want from other people.
Well, okay.
Then how would you read that from a primal perspective, from primacy?
That was one that was just sent by.
That's fine.
That's like when you're on a raft going down a river.
You see one rock, here's another rock, or this is the rock that sinks your raft, or this is the rock that you tie to.
I mean, I don't know.
You want to view it from a philosophical point of view, it could be viewed that way also.
You're going to pass through many people.
Just be happy that when you do pass through many people, no one wants to kill you, because they have that potential of violence also, verbal and physical.
We're talking about earth now, right?
So now it's a numbers game, isn't it, if you want to look at it that way.
In other words, in the beginning maybe I was saying you have to change what you're saying.
No, you don't have to change what you're saying.
You say the same thing.
And is it tonality?
Possibly.
Is it timing?
But ultimately there's a primacy to it.
And the primacy is it's those that are meant to hear it are going to hear it.
And you could ask for that.
And you could tap into that aspect of reality, where there's a primal reality that controls this reality, to maybe give you the fine points.
And is it time to bring those that are maybe.
Maybe now?
I'm hearing a lot of maybes.
Yeah, well, maybe this is what I mean by maybe.
You don't know for sure if within the area that you physically can reach, and even acoustically through the Internet or the rectangle, how many people are ready to listen to what you have to say.
A hundred?
A thousand?
A million?
Ten?
Fifteen?
Ask to have those brought to you when you're ready to do it.
That harkens back to the is it what you say or is it how you say it, which is a bad question because it's both.
It's when you say it and who's backing you up to say it.
Greek has an echo.
It's Seth.
There's going to be some kind of hum with him.
If you mute out when you're not speaking, we're okay.
When you speak, it comes on, it's fine.
Hey, I'm cool with the subject.
I feel like I'll have to review what's been said and think about things a bit more.
Well, hold on before you're cool with the subject.
You can do an overt, outward, dynamic demonstration of the subject matter by simply seeing how many people you can organize by communication.
I'm going to be speaking on A, B, C, and D on this certain day.
See how many people show up.
Then that's going to temper your metal and see if no one shows up, how you feel about it, or if 100 people show up, how you feel about it.
The less you're attached about what they do, the better you'll be at what you do.
There's a marketing aspect to this too.
You know that typically businesses, meaning individuals that start businesses, let's say, that are very specific on one thing tend to be more lucrative than those that are general.
For example, a plumbing contractor will probably be more lucrative business than a general handyman.
The more specific you get, the more lucrative.
If you, let's say, opened a plumbing store that just sold washers or faucet handles, chances are you might even be more lucrative than the regular plumber who is more lucrative than the general practitioner, handyman, you see.
Sam, can I ask you a question?
What is the result that you were after in the public conversation?
You said that you got the result that you were after once, and then another time you gave an example where you didn't, and I heard those.
But what would you say the result that you were seeking?
What is it you were trying to take away or give in these conversations?
It's an endeavor on my part to create sort of a unilateral presentation that is unrebuttable in its content because it addresses things that are objective in a way that also explains those things using metrics that people can understand.
So I'm not so much interested in having a back and forth so much as I am in showing something that stands on the merit of what it is in and of itself.
And that doesn't really require that, you know, the person that I'm talking to likes it per se or even that they remember it, but just that they acknowledge it in the moment.
And some people obviously don't do even that because of censorship, but it could also be because your presentation is not suitable.
It's not adequate.
They find it grating, or you're just not being efficient with your words or your body language or some other intangible.
So I'm out to improve my own ability to make that presentation, and I measure that by how accepting they are of what's being said.
I've got to interject comically here.
This is a planet of censored assholes, basically.
So if you're looking for that, it ain't going to work out too well for you.
I don't know.
I mean, says the guy who goes on radio and when he talks, people just shut up and listen?
Yeah, well, here's the other aspect to it.
Like Seth, when I used to go on, when he was doing thing on Revolution Radio, I used to basically say, look, I'm not here to have a conversation.
I'm here to throw rocks, and occasionally someone would say, Greek, you've been talking for 20 minutes.
The rest of us have to want to say something to us.
I said, I don't care.
What the hell could you possibly say?
Now, that's what I just said sounds really crass and awful to most, but that's the truth.
Is that what you want to tell people?
No.
That's the truth.
Sorry.
I'm not using those words.
Yeah, right.
So what brought that up is it's unrebuttable, but to who?
You know, you can tell a rock that the elephant is really a banana.
He's not going to rebut that because it's a rock.
It doesn't care about that.
So, yeah, what do you tell anyone that is a part of a society that has no idea what's going to be happening to them in the next decade and a half and what they're going to fall for and what they're set up for?
What do you tell someone like that?
What do you tell people on the Titanic, or which was the Olympic, let's say, that this ship is going to hit the bottom tomorrow night?
What do you tell them?
And you're on there with them, too.
Yeah, where do you begin?
Yeah.
Well, you tell them that the boat's going to sink.
Well, they'll lock you up in a cage if you say that too much.
Yeah, it depends on your presentation.
Well, that's what Sam is trying to say.
Thank you.
That's what I was trying to get.
That's what Sam is asking for.
How do you present that, right?
Well, and just to be clear, I'm asking, or I was asking, not so much anymore.
I kind of feel like we're going in circles.
The specifics of the nuances of a presentation that is at its most effective or the closest thing to a template that you could establish for that, because obviously I already know how to make some kind of a presentation and make headway, but it's about making it hyper-efficient.
And, you know, ironically, perhaps it's not even something that you could give an answer for because if you could, then it wouldn't be hyper-specific.
It would be general.
So maybe this isn't kind of a pointless thing to talk about.
Well, the thing is, no, it's not, because here, I had some communication with someone recently who does a lot of interviews and stuff like that.
They have YouTubes and all that crap.
And I said, how about having, how about, you know, all your guests, they talk about all these different subjects and whistleblowers and all that stuff, but I've listened to some of your stuff and I've never gone away with anything I could use right away.
How about discussing about something or anything that to whoever is hearing, they could use, they could walk away and they could use it.
They could use that information to improve their lives, their pathetic, miserable lives.
Let me just add that as a footnote, what's left of it.
So you see, dare anyone go on the rectangle anywhere, even the medical people, and watch as many presentations or read as many presentations as you can and tell me what you walk away with that you could use right now or you can apply either immediately if needed.
Nothing.
There's almost nothing like that.
Don't get sick in the United States?
Yeah, either way.
It doesn't matter.
Any subject.
What can you get a presentation on, whatever subject it is, and walk away feeling that you can apply something there immediately?
And I'm not talking about a how-to video like replacing a water pump on an LG Trom washing machine or something like that.
I'm just talking about what is generally referred to as conversational stuff.
And that's the easiest way to get through to people.
Food, clothing, shelter, personal gain and fear.
Personal gain is how are they going to go to bed or wake up tomorrow knowing that they gained a little bit more financial whatever.
I guess a skinny person, weight, if they want to do that.
Or shed some fear.
How do they shed some fear is another way.
Food, clothing, shelter, what they call money, what they call their fears or phobias.
The ultimate thing, believe it or not, it might sound kind of petty, it's not as health.
Most people are, because there's so much fear attached to health, that's why it's gotten so.
Anyway, it's a long, I've never really given the background on what I've discovered on this.
There's so few people left on the planet today that understand how to keep a body healthy or how to make a body healthy.
And that's because they've always had so much fear of that subject and understanding the conditions of society that's ruled by malevolent entities.
The fear gets to a point where now anything will do and that anything now became the opposite of what they should be doing.
But not to kill them directly, but to keep them vulnerable.
Proof of that is, like today I was out at the shops and there was people discussing buying tropical fruit.
And it's still cold, it's still the end of winter, but a couple of people, I said, I gave them the lowdown, this is going to change your body chemistry to the tropics.
And two people were like, wow.
And one person was like, oh, I'm allergic to that anyway.
And I said, by the way, there were no allergies 50 years ago.
And just walked away.
So, do you want to interject?
I was going to say you can just share information is one way of doing it.
Another way, Greek, that I've observed you communicating with others is simply asking questions and uncommon questions, questions that are not generally asked like, well, who tells you what day it is?
Where do you get your, what is food?
These simple questions like that are not presented.
Very simple questions with relatively simple answers, realistically.
But at the same time, those questions are so very uncommon that when you present someone with something that is unexpected, it almost produces like a hiccup in their train of thought.
So where even if someone was simply waiting for their turn to speak or their chance to share their ideas or their experience, you can derail that almost completely just with simple, simple questions.
Yeah, like children ask where babies come from, but adults never ask where credit comes from.
I mean, yeah, that's one way.
But you also, I think opposite of Sam, I'm not attached to it.
When I run into someone, I know they're an asshole.
I never said any words.
I presume it 99%.
The only time I'll get involved with them personally is if they absolutely, positively reached out or needed some help, that was obvious.
Otherwise, they could go about whatever.
I've completely separated myself from what other people are interested in or what their needs and wants are, and that allows me to be objective.
So, for example, when they go into a political fervor over something, I look at it and I'm like, okay, the subject matter is all wrong.
This is really stupid.
And for them to take it so seriously, that makes them even worse.
So you're in a really – well, you, whoever is listening, if you really become objective, you will find humanity be repugnant, which is another word for disgusting.
That's why I always tell little children, if you're not disgusted with people, you're not paying attention.
And adults standing there, they didn't say, how dare you say that to the children.
They were in agreement.
They didn't.
They didn't say, how dare you tell that to them.
They were like, yeah, okay, that's pretty much right.
Isn't that funny?
You would expect them to freak out over it, right?
I have two small children that I talk to – I have two sons that I talk to with regularity.
And they are of an age where they both ask questions and like to share what they have learned.
And I find myself very, very often explaining that the people that are telling them these things have no idea what they're talking about.
I'm like, yes, in this – in what is being shared, what you're talking about is true – not true.
It's not a word I would use actually.
It is accurate, but there's no precision here.
What is being discussed is their guessing, and they're basing their guesses upon guesses that have been – scientific theory is that.
It's all theory because no one is – it's baseless.
It's based upon emptiness.
Well, all of it is fiction.
And so explaining to two small children the fiction and seeing it blossom, I suppose, the realization that what is being – these people that we present as authorities of information, be them a school teacher or a scientist or a faceless nobody behind a YouTube video, that none of them have any concept of what is real because this concept of what is real has not been presented to them.
Well, if they get a handle on religion, which means what you do regularly, that's why religion is very important because you get your – what you – the reason why you do what you do from your god, and that's been totally watered down and eliminated now from society completely.
When they understand that as children, they don't have to go around telling everyone they're using the word wrong, but you essentially get that from the parents first, and then the parents had gotten it from a god.
So whether you know there's a god or not, you're still, as a child, functioning in the religious manner because the parents are doing it.
That is a key aspect to – I don't know.
You want to talk about creation, right?
Because none of the stuff that the scientists, like you're mentioning with the theories, add up.
Mathematically, it doesn't work.
So ultimately, it was made by another group that we know only what they want us to know about them and settle into that and go on from there.
That's why I always discuss – not always, but I bring up the hypocrisy of what is going on and the stupidity.
But you see, also, another thing that's kind of harsh is that this is not only a grooming, a programming.
It's bred into people, just like a water dog and a bird dog.
You get a water dog in the backyard with a bird dog.
One has been bred to be in the water.
If there's a swimming pool, he's jumping in, and you ask him, why did you jump in the water?
I don't know.
I wanted to.
And the other bird dog is chasing birds.
Why are you chasing?
Why do you want to jump up the tree?
I don't know.
It's just what I feel like I have to do.
It's kind of a little late to breed that out of them.
So humans right now have been bred into this nastiness, and you want to find the ones where it's not bred into them.
You know what I mean?
But on the same token, or the other side of the same coin, is that, as you've illustrated in the past better than I'm going to right now, is that if a dog is raised by apes, it's still going to behave as a dog, whereas if a human is raised by apes, it's going to act like an ape.
Whereas humanity, or mankind, is much more susceptible to its environment and its information and how it uses that information.
And what I mean by the breeding, it's actually the downbreeding of humanity also.
They've lost robustness, and they're actually physically weak.
Physically weak.
Well, they call them descendants instead of ascendants, right?
Yeah, perhaps.
I'll give you an example.
After the 1950s, they introduced bovine milk to Korea, south and north.
It wasn't customary for them to incorporate that in their diet to children.
And within one generation, the adults were 20 to 30 percent larger because of the bovine milk.
And the girls started menstruating earlier.
Yeah, perhaps.
Yeah, I remember that study.
Yeah, there's a Japanese anthropologist who did this in the 50s and 60s.
So the average person living on the Korean peninsula was 5'4", and within one generation, the average height was 5'7", 5'8", for male, and for men.
And they attribute it directly to the bovine.
So what I mean by the breeding is that right now the chemical constituents and the toxins and the poor water quality and all that have changed the human body, just like if you had a radio that had good reception, if you opened it and started tweaking some of the values on the resistors and capacitors and inductors, it won't have that good reception anymore.
I think that's a perfect analogy right there.
We have breeded ourselves so poorly.
Here's an example.
This is a striking example, and it may or may not be pertinent, but Wal-Mart phenomenon.
When I had first gone into a Wal-Mart, I was astounded at the level of – I'd call them Wal-Martians, right?
Where did these people come from?
Most of them looked deformed and just like strange creatures, anthropomorphic obviously, but they don't look like fit humans to me.
After a while I was thinking, where were all these people, because there's not just one or two, we're talking thousands.
Where were all these people before Wal-Mart landed on planet Earth?
Where were they hiding?
I mean, I was out in public, I was at various places like Sears and J.C. Penney's or the movies.
I didn't see so many malformed creatures like that.
Where did they come from?
Were they always there, or did they come through some kind of vortex, wormhole, when Wal-Mart opened up?
I know, it sounds kind of crazy.
I think about that sometimes when I'm wondering, am I living in some kind of a stepped reality here?
So I tie all that back to speaking to people.
It's still shocking.
I haven't been everywhere in the United States, but wherever I go, I know I'm going to see a freak show if I go to a Wal-Mart, whether it's the employees or the customers.
And such a freak show did not exist prior to that.
Now, I don't like using corporate brand names like McDonald's and Wal-Mart and all that other stuff, but sometimes it has to be brought out because it's very specific.
Well, I think one of the things that I noticed was the girth, just the sheer girth of people in general.
It struck me.
Well, just like you're saying, the girth there, Bruce, I just want to bring this up real quick.
The first thing that came up in a millisecond was, you know that when you have a society that's quote-unquote have an obesity problem, that's because they're malnourished.
In other words, they're eating enough in quantity, but the body is not recognizing it as food and it's producing this store because it's in a crisis mode.
I could go along with that.
If you go to places like France, for example, where they eat tremendous amounts of protein, animal protein and fat, right, and wine and cigarettes and all that.
And by the way, you can light up a cigarette in a Paris restaurant, no problem, right?
Right.
Or a bar.
Okay.
And when I tell you the French, do you think of people with girth like you mentioned here earlier?
No, God no.
God no.
But they eat more quote-unquote fatty foods than here.
Yeah.
But see, the difference is there's no…
I think I mentioned to you, I've been in the Midwest and several, all the way from people living in a trailer to people living in a six-bathroom, five-bedroom house, McMansion.
And if I sat and ate with them for a couple of days, I felt sick.
And this is how they ate normally.
Imagine that.
So these people, you know, I used to say publicly, Americans, most American children have never had real bread or real cheese or real milk in their entire…
Or people, most Americans never had real bread or real milk or real cheese in their entire life.
They're going to go from cradle to grave not knowing what real bread tastes like or real milk or real, you see, cheese.
Yeah.
So that's what I mean about the breeding aspect.
The grooming aspect is what Seth brought up, external input.
What kind of external input are they getting?
And unfortunately, where Sam is…
Yeah, well, is it a horror to who?
They seem to be enjoying it.
The Observer.
Could you imagine a horror film being billed as a comedy?
I don't know.
Is that what's going on?
So where Sam is…
Sam, how Western would you say where you are and, you know, I'm not…
You're not in America, let's say.
So let's say how Western would you say it is and Americanized?
Pretty Americanized or still retain non-American culture?
Pretty Americanized.
Yeah, see, that's…
Is that okay?
All right, pretty Americanized.
I'd say ugly Americanized, but let me just put it this way.
Is that a positive or a negative?
I mean…
It's hard to say.
But personally, it's something that one is accustomed to seeing to the point of being apathetic towards it.
Now, how far West can you go before you start going East again?
America, right?
Yeah, no kidding, yeah.
You know, I had an interesting treat a while back.
Once in a while, we'll go and listen to radio stations from another country.
And I'm always amazed at how Americanized the music is in different areas and then some that just retain their own stuff and that's it.
It's few.
Okay, so mankind is sent out from the West going to the East, then he comes back to the West and keeps going West.
Just looking at the directions here.
Anyway, I think public speaking is when you meet someone.
Just to go back to what Sam brought up, if you just meet someone and you're in the early parts of acquaintanceship, let's say, it is no different than being a general public interchanger.
Obviously, the dynamic changes when you have multiple people listening.
But I would suggest that the question at heart is public speaking, whether it's to one or 500 or 1,000, if you're vaguely, especially if they're not acquainted at all with the subject matter, then you could be in a prison cell with someone, it's still public speaking if they're not acquainted at all, and if they don't know you either.
So I think it's the same rules.
Each time you test yourself.
Right.
I think going in front of more than one person at a time is best, and then asking for feedback.
I'll give you an example.
Have you guys ever heard of boiler room high-pressure telephone sales telemarketing?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Well, I've experienced that.
To make the story kind of short, there's a construction material catalog, and the first day there, they said, okay, here's a list of Dun & Bradstreet cards.
These are companies listed on Dun & Bradstreet, and their phone numbers are on there.
And you go ahead, and it's your first day here, and just start calling them.
You can only sell them extension cords.
I'm like, wait a second, there's like 300 items here.
Yeah, but you can only sell extension cords.
Only extension cords, right?
I'm like, okay, I'll play along with this, right?
Not everything in the catalog, right?
Because you think in everything in the catalog you're going to make a sale, right?
Right.
And the next guy that was there the first day says, you can only sell yellow marker tape.
That's it.
It's only one item.
You know, when you go to a construction catalog, it has all those things in there.
So one thing for the whole week.
So anyway, I'm sitting there.
I'm like, okay, fine.
Well, at the end of the second day, not the first day, they bring me in after everybody leaves, and there's another guy waiting outside, and they hit a button, and they have – they prerecorded me speaking to people, and they were – two of the guys were – they said, why did you say that?
Your pauses are too long.
They had recorded what I was saying and then criticizing it to me.
Yeah.
I didn't know any of this was going to happen.
And they said, we don't do this with everyone, but you have – you got what it takes, right?
And I'm like, no, no, no.
Actually, as a matter of fact, I got what it takes, but not with you guys.
You guys are insane.
But I sold $700 – what they call dollars' worth of extension cords in two days.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, it was nice.
I didn't mean it that way, but – But they wanted me to stay, and I was like, no, no.
You guys are crazy.
But you know what?
After I left there, after I got my sense of normalcy back – because it was traumatizing to go sit down, and they start playing a recording of what you've been saying all day, and you're like, holy shit, I didn't know it was being recorded.
This is like listening to your own voice.
That's when I realized I don't want to listen to pre-recorded stuff I say.
But, okay, so what they were doing is they were criticizing what you were – you see what I mean?
The trauma – but once this trauma wore off, after a few months, in retrospect, I thought about it, and I was like, what a crazy situation.
But I learned a lot because I never had anyone come back and criticize how I spoke, right?
So I'll keep that in the back of the mind.
That's helped me tremendously.
Well, it made me realize I don't want to hear myself recorded.
I don't like the way I sound, number one.
Number two, maybe it's like a repulsion of some – two similar polarities repelling.
We all have that.
And the other thing was that when – the reason these guys were doing high-pressure sales is because they were trying to maximize efficiency, right?
They were not calling people to have conversations.
The purpose of the call was to make a profit, was to maximize that, right?
Anyway, I'll be back in about 30 seconds or so.
Okay.
Well, greetings, salutations.
Thanks for allowing me to join the conversation.
Oh, you're more than welcome, more than welcome.
Sam, are you still with us?
Yes, I'm still here.
I'm just a bit slow because I'm tired.
Okay.
Remember, Sam, you can only talk about extension cords.
I like the orange ones.
Well, the blue ones with the lighted end, which tells you that they're engaged.
I've seen orange ones like that as well.
In different lengths, yeah, yeah.
50-foot, I've found to be very useful, although it can be laborious to drag around.
100 feet is always something.
I've got milk crates.
Actually, I got the milk crates by permission.
You know, most people have milk crates you're not supposed to have, right?
But with 100-foot, 10-gauge cords, you try to carry it 100 feet, you're tired, right?
It's really heavy.
Because at a young age, I found out that if you use an under-gauged wire on a motor, you eventually ruin that motor, right?
All right.
Very valuable as well.
Those are the cables that when I was doing the carpentry, which involved setting up and moving a lot of tools and powering those tools from varying distances, one of the things that always got locked up very, very thoroughly was the extension cables.
Because the heavy gauge and their copper, and copper is valuable, and people will steal what is not tied down, as they say.
Well, now they have a thing here where they only get bare copper at the salvage yard.
So, the crackheads have to sit there and strip all this insulation off.
I've seen or at least been told that they'll just burn it off, throw it all in a fire, burn it off, rinse the carbonation off.
They've had places where people would rob the house if it's been sitting idle for a while and just strip the copper out of it.
Okay.
Now, about wrapping extension.
One of the things is, Bruce, wrapping or Seth or even Sam, wrapping an extension cord, any kind of cord, and pulling it apart, you get tangles, right?
Right.
When you work at a TV studio, some of those cables are very expensive because they carry both audio and video.
If you've ever been in a TV studio, if you stand on one, I mean, everyone yells at you, right?
Immediately.
Yeah, and you have to wrap them a certain way.
Do you guys know about the over and under when you coil up a long cord?
I'm familiar with it, but admittedly not adept.
Well, look, maybe there's a YouTube video on how to wrap the coil over.
That's one of the things they train you when you wrap up your coils.
You go over and under.
If anyone wants to look it up, I don't know if there's anything on the rectangle about it.
Basically, as you bring the cable into the coiled section with your palm facing where you're wrapping it, you grab it, palm facing the opposite direction, bring it in, right?
You keep rotating the way you grab it, so palm facing the loop, then palm facing opposite the loop.
So when you pull it apart, it kind of acts like a coil.
So you have, instead of it being stacked, it's an intermittent stack, you know?
Anyway, I don't know if I gave a great visual on that.
It's a great idea.
Yeah, it does, yeah, and you don't get tangles.
So, again, back to communicating this.
100 foot sneaks is what I learned on.
Well, yeah.
100 foot, I like the 50, 25 or whatever sounds, 25 is really short.
50 is pretty good.
100 gets a little long.
It is long.
On the 100 footer that I've got here that I like to use, I went to a Granger and I bought the real heavy-duty male-female plug and I spliced it into 250s, you know?
So I could use, now I have, you know, but I still store it as 100 because 250s are more useful than a 100 footer, I think.
Also, at the middle junction, you could put a junction box, right?
Yep, and you could put all your phantom if you want.
Yep, all stuff coming off of it.
But essentially, I just want to go back to the general discussion.
Who are you communicating to?
You're communicating to a society of people that are set up by the gods to be basically slaughtered at a rate of 90% slaughter, kill rate, right?
Okay, that doesn't sound good, right?
I mean, whether, you know, whether you want to be apathetic to the cause of whichever one, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't sound good statistically or anything.
That's the truth of the matter.
The second aspect is we know, based on the writ, that these people won't know what's happening to them when it's happening, so they have to be that oblivious to it.
Let me just ask you, if you just did a general statistical informational exchange with anyone in the galaxy saying that these people in about a decade and a half are going to be slaughtered at a rate of 90%, 10% survival, and they're not going to be aware of it, what the hell else is more important to be able to get across to these idiots?
It seems like all the other subject matter just fades away, doesn't it?
I mean, the last thing you want to do is go around and say, you morons are going to be slaughtered at a rate of 90% in a decade and a half.
You know what they're going to do to you, right?
They're going to be in a padded cell with a lollipop, right?
You know, as you said that, I was thinking about the slaughterhouse and the cow.
You know, the dumb animal.
We've been reduced to such a dumb species.
Well, no, you're not really that dumb.
You're being deceived.
Okay, yes.
But statistically, yeah, you are.
Because the fact is that you are going to be slaughtered at a rate of 90%.
Slaughter, right?
Yeah, so in essence, just like if you go to a...
Okay, Bruce, I'll grant you that for sure.
If you go to a ranch and say that these cattle within the next year will be slaughtered at a rate of 90%, we would all say, yeah, pretty much.
That's about right.
Maybe more.
Yeah, so from that, yeah, I could see that.
But in essence, humans are not even animals, by the way.
Right?
I think Seth brought up the point earlier.
They come with downloads.
Like, for example, I've got some kittens, and they were eating, and after they ate, they all in unison licked their paws and wiped their brow in unison.
Perfect unison, like the greatest choreographer couldn't do it.
And I mentioned to someone else nearby, I said, who taught them how to do that?
Who taught them how to do that?
No one.
Download.
They came with that download.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So the humans, they don't have a download, or men doesn't have a download very much.
And literally, you ever heard the expression, they don't even know how to wipe their butt?
Literally, I think that had to be taught.
And if you look at history, by the way, when they divide all the ages, you know, Stone Age, Bronze Age, Iron Age, they fail to tell you how many a mixture of all those tools they find all the time, aged all the time, right?
It was either a stone society, you know, litho-based, bronze-based, or iron-based.
And I just want to throw this in there, because there's no such thing as a Stone Age or a caveman, you know.
There's no such thing as a Bronze Age or an Iron Age.
It wasn't either, you know, was it an iron-based society?
Like isn't this called an information-based society now, right?
So what does that mean?
Is that better than Stone Age?
I don't know.
Right?
So, yeah, this is absurd.
Now, the reason I brought this up is recently reading an article, and they were pushing that they did find iron Egyptian tools during the Bronze Age in Egypt.
But those were very special, because they only made them from meteorites.
So they're starting to find dating that all these things coexisted at the same time, and they give these stupid excuses.
Dates are constantly being pushed back as well, specifically within the last year.
It seems every other week or so, even in the accepted realms of archaeology and things like that, they are accepting the fringes and whatnot.
They are beginning to push back the dates of the different lands being inhabited, levels of technology.
They push back like older?
Yeah, absolutely.
The same way they do with the age of the earth as they do.
How old is the earth 50 years ago versus how old it is now?
It's aging at 1.2 million years per year now.
We're beginning to see more of that with human artifacts and with the availability of the internet and mass dissemination of information, not without censorship, but with it being easier to divulge lots of information than it is to sequester a small piece of information.
Recently I've seen an uptick in what would 20 years ago be considered fringe or conspiracy-oriented archaeologists.
A lot of it is being reinforced by current archaeological finds and things like that.
They have to keep their victims unbalanced.
Get them to believe it's this old and whatever.
I'm just going to step away for a second.
I'll be right back.
I have to go get something.
Okay.
There was someone brought up in chat asked if there was going to be anything scripturally discussed.
I'm paraphrasing.
One question I had, and it's a very large and succinct all at the same time, I suppose, is possible extrapolation on the commandments listed in Exodus 34.
I mentioned probably unadvisedly that I found just in reading through the Interlinear, I noted eight different commandments.
There was a bit of chuckling because it's referred to as the Ten Commandments.
Why it's referred to as the Ten Commandments is because the Disney movie and the religious – that's how it is presented is these Ten Commandments.
The Ten Commandments that are spoken of and commonly colloquially spoken of are not the ones that were actually memorialized in stone.
So clarification on that, and it's very possible that I smashed some commandments together in taking my count because it appeared that a couple of the commandments were actually just clarifying a singular one.
That in specific being giving the first fruits of the womb and your children to Yahweh.
So any extrapolation you would like to offer, I would greatly.
I haven't looked at it, and stuff like that, I'd like for you guys to come up with it.
And I've in the past given hints maybe in chat on how to come up with good research in scripture.
My focus is going to be on prophecy, on Revelation, the book of Zechariah, the book of Daniel, Genesis.
I don't see, as a matter of fact, on a cursory examination, I see 12 commandments written on the stone.
Can I share the eight, and then you can correct, perhaps?
It seems rote.
Which two are missing?
How about that?
The one involving the breaking of the neck, as I saw that as being an extrapolation or explanation or clarification of the first or his, and don't send them empty-handed.
Ransoming the donkey with a lamb were you to break the donkey's neck, right?
Right.
That's one commandment.
It could be two, where you ransom.
In other words, the commandment is you ransom a donkey with a lamb.
Which donkey and what lamb?
Well, that would be a lot of lamb being given up for a lot of donkeys if Abraham had 4,000-something asses, right?
Right.
That's a lot of lambs being given up for that, for example.
But it's the first, right?
What I've gone down to explain when it came to work I like to do on that, it doesn't mean that I don't want to do work on it.
Definitely, if I'm asked to do something regarding that and I see that it's necessary, I'll do it.
But what I've always explained to people is what they're told in Exodus 20 as the commandments, because they didn't go up to the mount where Moses was to go up to get the commandments,
the no shoes, no shirt, no service, say don't touch this mountain and do these things,
those are misinterpreted and portrayed as those were written on the stones as you see them memorialized on these things that look like tombstones, right?
Right.
So those were oral commands to a mob or a group of people that resembled basically Mitsriites, because they were not discernible from the Egyptians in terms of those things at that point.
Right, they were brought out of the society that they were a part of.
Right, and they acted and behaved accordingly.
So if you look at those oral commands in Exodus 20, each one was to counteract something that was part of the culture of Egypt.
Right.