But, you know, if you go to the island of Chios, there's a little humble house, and they have a little plaque, very not well-known at all.
This is where Christopher Columbus was born.
It's a Greek.
And, you know, if you're French, by the way, when you sign your name, you sign it in French, you know, French, right?
Or when you're Arabic, you sign it in Arabic, right?
Now, how many Greeks sign their name in Greek?
Just about all of them, right?
Now, if you go on the rectangle, I don't know if it's up, maybe it is, go find Christopher Columbus's signature.
Is that in Roman English, or Roman Italian, or Roman, or is it in Greek script?
It's in Greek.
You know, so...
Oh, boy.
I'm not saying you should go out and convince or debate this topic, because evidence means nothing, right?
But Christopher Columbus signed his name in Greek.
You know why?
Because he was Italian.
See how stupid things are?
Did you find this, by the way?
Is there anything on the rectangle about this?
Okay, so this is what...
I'm being sarcastic, because this is what the Renaissance is doing, and still is today.
Versus what I'm counting, you know.
Are you familiar with any of this, Bruce?
The copper from Michigan?
No, that actually was a rather a bit of a surprise, and I am definitely going to check on that, along with the other one that you were just mentioning.
Yeah, yeah, so this is all products of the Renaissance, all this bullshit, by the way.
Wow.
You know, that people think, you know, it's good.
I'm showing you that you can go a little bit deeper.
Which I fully intend on doing.
I'm back on the copper from Michigan and Ohio, and all the settlements.
I mean, there's the Tucson artifacts also.
There is artifacts all over the New Mexico, Roman settlements, and Minoan settlements, and it's not just finding something that's debatable.
It's rock-solid, you know what I mean?
And backed up by science, and it's ignored.
The Mormons got involved in this a hundred years ago, and they got approached.
What is this?
The Minoan civilization here?
They got involved in the archaeology of it, and they got approached, and they shut it all down, and they said they're all fakes.
Hmm, but anyway, that's politically what you're supposed to do, right?
Like the Mormons aren't fakes themselves, but anyway, so that's another little bit of study, too.
The reason I brought up the Minoan copper in Michigan, it's not like one of these things that are debatable.
It is like, I mean, it's like a B-52.
You know, it's like you said, an airplane crashed on my street today, right?
On the street that I live on, and you're like, are you sure?
It's a B-52.
Yes, I'm sure, right?
Yeah, you can't miss it.
It's so big that it'll crush you.
Yeah.
So, why am I bringing this up?
Because this is contrary to what you've been taught, still taught today out of the Renaissance.
Just like, for example, let's go back to American politics.
The crap that they're espousing in the political scene right now is the same crap that they were doing in the 1950s and 40s in America, and people are buying it.
They fall for it over and over and over again.
Find anything, Sam, on Christopher Columbus's signature being Greek or Minoan copper?
I know there's stuff on the internet in the chat.
There was a link.
Yeah, I found the signature stuff.
It's a combination of Greek and Latin.
First part being Greek, second part being Latin.
Either way, there's some interesting stuff to be, the reason I'm bringing these things up, if I had, if I settled in my mind a little bit, I'll bring up more stuff to counter the teachings of the Renaissance.
So, when you bring up the Renaissance, just like you said of the individual and the leftist groups and all that, it's really the teachings of the Renaissance, you know.
Now, whenever there is a financial boom, there is always a boom in art, whether it's music or, you know, pictographic or sculpture.
They tend to subsidize the artistic community, right?
Yes.
Yeah, I mean you could see the Arabic or Arabesque influence in Da Vinci.
You could see Michelangelo didn't do it all on his own.
It's just like a plumber.
You ever call a plumber?
Fix something in the house or clear a drain?
Yep, if you ever do that, watch what's going on very carefully.
What happens is the truck pulls up, it says plumbing, whatever, Joe's plumbing, and there's two guys in the truck.
The plumber comes out, he greets you, and while he's greeting you, the plumber's helper loads up the tools.
They both come in the house, the plumber's helper gets into all the sewage and gets all whatever, clears the drain while the plumber's talking to you, plugs in the machine.
Plumber's helper cleans up, puts the tools back in the truck, and the plumber writes you the bill.
Did you get the picture of what's going on here?
It's just like a hospital.
Everybody, the doctor, the doctor.
You ever go watch what's going in the hospital?
Who's doing all the work, the majority of the work?
The nurses, right?
The plumber's helper does all the work.
Do you think Michelangelo stood there with chisels and hammers for weeks on end carving all that stuff?
Or did he direct it and write the bill?
Was he, here's the other thing, was Michelangelo well-versed in scripture, which was a problem with the Pope?
Yep, how do we know?
Look at some of the sculpture that he did.
He went wrong, terribly wrong, on the one where he has the Christ depicted after his death taken down off the cross with the mother holding him.
That's totally wrong.
Because if you did a sculpture of that, it would be very simple.
You would have the mother, let's say the woman, holding something that looked like a skeleton from the front, all the bones revealed, with shards of flesh hanging, eye sockets open, no face on it at all.
The head would probably be twice the size of a normal head.
The abdomen would be twice the size of a normal abdomen, with shards of flesh everywhere, like ripped newspaper.
It wouldn't look anything like that.
That's why, you know, how do you know the Shroud of Turin is a fraud?
It should take you 0.3 seconds, not 0.5 seconds.
Just look at it.
It's not someone who's been stoned to death, and neither is it based on the haircut.
Yeah, he has long hair.
Yeah, it should take 0.3 seconds.
If it takes you three quarters of a second to call it a fraud, you're slow.
Right?
Yeah, I'm being sarcastic, because it's well-deserved.
And how many morons do you think are still debating its authenticity, or how many morons even worse believe in that it is authentic?
So, there's going to be reckoning on all this stuff, and right now, this is the only place in the world you could hear this kind of talk, by the way, on these really ultra-minor, thanks to Bruce, recordings, and the Greek, and Sam coming across, and whoever else does.
It's kind of sad, but at least you can be happy that you're hearing it.
There are other people that know this, but I assure you, no one's saying it.
All in one wholesale, one-stop shop, you know.
This is the truth.
I shouldn't say truth, but because that's where it's been bandied around.
This is like a convenience store, you know, of I wish it were a store at some point.
I need to get cigarettes and coffee, and then fortunately and unfortunately, I have good taste in tobacco and coffee, so anyway, someone asked me, Greek, you're not taking out hurricanes anymore?
I said, no, because no one even wants to buy me a Starbucks coffee for it.
Not that I would drink that stuff, because some people that like coffee have a Starbucks, and they're like, oh, I get all jittery.
I don't feel good.
I said, it's because it's over-harvested.
When you over-harvest coffee, it gets this strange caffeine quality, and you know what I mean by poking at it too much?
Like back in the old days, the growers, you know, with the hemp, you know how they made it stronger?
They just kept poking the plant, and it developed THC as a defense mechanism, right?
I don't know.
Bruce might be old enough to remember those days.
Oh, yeah.
That's how you did it.
You kept pruning it, so it would...
Anyway, now I think that I heard recently from someone that the stuff is so strong now, it's almost hallucinogenic.
I don't know.
I don't touch this stuff, because if I ever do, I remember maybe a decade ago taking a toque off of some, yes, an admission of guilt, not really, and I was waiting for it to wear off.
I just didn't like the way it felt at all.
So...
I don't...
and that's one of the things that I don't get, you know what I mean?
Smoking weed or whatever.
I don't get it.
Escapism.
What's that?
Escapism, because, you know, apparently life sucks or something.
Yeah, whatever.
I don't know.
I think it's a...
yeah, it's...
let's just say it's an acquired state.
You know, like an acquired taste, but an acquired state.
I mean, it's better than putting knitting needles in your eyes, but, you know...
Speaking of drugs and such, I think at one point you said that the 60s counterculture was an intelligent psyop, actually.
Absolutely.
But for what, though?
Oh, how do you destroy a generation, little by little?
Now they don't have to do it anymore because they got smartphones to do it for them.
Yeah, but what do...
What do idiot intelligence folks need to know that for?
To know what?
About how to destroy a generation.
What do they care?
Oh, why not?
See, the whole thing was the condition...
You know, people think America is so stable.
It's extremely unstable because it's a supermarket to the world.
This is one thing people will never get, when I say never within their ever...
America or the States is not really a country.
As they think it's 50 little individual countries or 48, and it's not even that.
It's a marketplace.
Why do you think you have so many attorneys and so many prisons here?
You know, when you go to a big mall, if you're caught shoplifting, they have a little holding cell in there.
Are you familiar with that?
Bruce, have you ever heard of that?
Yeah, they have a little prison in the in the shopping mall, believe it or not.
A detention.
Detention, yeah.
So, this is...
America is not a country.
It never will be.
Who's an American?
You live on a street.
You got a guy born in India.
I'm American.
A guy born in Spain.
Yeah, right.
Sure you are.
You can't define it.
It's a big supermarket, but imagine instead of the customers going home, they sleep in the supermarket.
You see?
So it's very interesting.
I think George Carlin summed it up.
Shopping mall from one end to the other.
Sea to shining sea.
And you're all given a credit line to use it, and the attorneys are like, no, the attorneys will do anything to make sure that you guys never find out how the money system works.
That was another interesting subject to look at.
The churches, how they are tax exempt.
There's no usury fee.
Taxes are just a fee.
Right, exactly, a usury fee.
I don't think it's usury.
I'll tell you why.
Because you have two systems.
If you really comprehend Title 12, Section 411, because it's written on an eighth grade level, and most people can't comprehend it because it is on an eighth grade because they can only comprehend third grade or less, it says that you're not authorized to use Federal Reserve notes, right?
Right.
Okay, but then it tells you, because you're not, you could use them to make a demand for lawful money, but are you ever going to get lawful money?
No.
Because of the democratic consensus.
Correct.
Everyone has decided.
That's why nothing is ever going to happen with the Fed, because everyone's endorsing it with their signature.
I was at Ocelli once.
I went in with my endorsement.
I had to change the subject.
I was like, oh boy, this is not the right, you know, venue to discuss it on Ocelli the Greek.
I think it has to be done on a separate way alone or someone else who can understand it.
The taxing is not there to do anything other than to regulate the money supply.
Right?
And also it has another, in other words, you just pull it out of the system.
Because why do you have to do that?
Because you have something called inflation.
So, which inflation is a tax also.
Give you an example.
In 1920, a car was about 2000 bucks.
1930, a car was about 2000 bucks.
1940, a car was about 2000 bucks.
1950, a car was around 2000 bucks.
1960, it started to go up to 33,000.
So in 1910, if you put 2000 bucks in a jar and buried it and you woke up in 1940, can you buy a car with it?
Yes.
You know what I mean?
You didn't have inflation as much.
But now if you put whatever a car is, you put it away.
I mean, I went a couple of years ago, someone was talking, when I get a pickup truck and he left, he says, he wants 60,000 bucks for a pickup truck.
It's like, you're joking.
So it should be like 10 or 12.
So if you put 10 or 12,000 bucks away 10 years ago, can you buy a pickup truck?
No.
So that is a tax.
In a fiat money system, you're taxed at a rate of about 90%.
Meaning if you figure out all the taxes, which include utilities, whatever earnings you have, 90% of it goes out to you, you know, for your average By the way, the average, I think, salary in America is 61,000 a year, right?
So if you're not making 61,000 or more, you're in the poverty level, by the way.
Okay.
Which is roughly 1,200 a week.
So.
But Title 12, Section 401 is really simple.
Let me just give an example, a simple example.
A guy works at an auto parts store.
Okay.
And he, it was a national chain.
And he tells the boss, like, I'm using Title 12, Section 411, don't do any more deductions.
Oh, no, no, you're crazy.
You're one of those tax protesters.
They go up and down through legal, nothing happens.
Okay, so.
They're doing direct deposit in his bank account.
He can't get out of it.
He said, we won't give you a check.
What do you do?
This is what I just explained is a scenario for most people in the job market today, right?
They get direct deposit.
Okay, so what do you do?
Well, what he did was, you close the bank account.
And then when they try to do direct deposit, it bounces back.
And they come to you and they say, hey, listen, we tried to give you your paycheck, but it bounced back.
He says, yeah, you know, I can't have that account anymore.
Then guess what they did?
They had to give him a check now.
Because initially they said, no, no checks.
So you have to go beyond what they're telling you and be proactive.
So he closes the account.
Check bounces back to the corporate and they say, well, we're holding your checks now.
We can't do that.
We have to give it to you.
Well, cut me a check, asshole.
And what they did was they cut him a check, right?
So, you know, where it says pay to the order of, that's clear evidence that whenever you use anything that says pay to the order of, you're ordering up money.
Remember how I explained how it works?
Right.
When you write somebody a check, it gives the illusion that it was taken from one account to the other.
It wasn't.
But anyway, so he gets the check and on the back he writes lawful money only 12 USC 411 and signs it with a semicolon between the first and last name.
If you just do it exactly like it is on the driver's license or any ID that you have, it's fine.
Lawful money only 12 USC 411.
And every time he did that, he did a photocopy of the check.
And if you have a photocopy machine at home, by the way, and you don't want to do a lot, you can send the same piece of paper if you just reposition the check and it'll print it further down.
You know what I mean?
Anyway.
Or you could scan it.
So at the end of the year, it comes time to do a 1040 the next year.
So what he does is he writes down all the amount that they deducted and he has no income and all the amount that deducted should come back all of it because there's no income because he's making a demand for lawful money.
And where they tell you to sign the 1040, he just wrote see exhibit A.
And exhibit A is copies of all of the endorsements on the back of the checks that you wrote lawful money only USC 12 411.
And you put a little letter in there say these are all the instruments that you know about right?
And these are all your salary and this is all true.
Well, about not like a month later, like most people, but like four days later, he gets the check for the entire amount back.
Everything, no questions asked from the IRS.
You just take it to your boss and say, see, I got it all back and they don't care.
So you're going to have to wait.
It's not like this return stuff, you know, well, how much are deductible and you know, anyway, I just gave you one example of how it works because you're not going to get lawful money.
So at least at this point, see the IRS knows it, but the IRS agents don't know it.
Why?
Because then they want to do it, right?
Because they're getting taxed, right?
I've been to an IRS office where a guy gave $150 to make payment and they didn't want to take the cash and finally, they came out with a clipboard and they wrote 50 and they wrote the serial number and I said, well, you're doing that because if you don't document it that way, this office creates a tax liability and she was like, holy shit, where you come from?
You're not one of these space heaters, you know?
So anyone that complains about that should just do a little bit of research that when you're using something that you buy somewhat, when you're not authorized to use something, can you say that you're also being prohibited from using it?
Somewhat.
It's an indirect way of saying it, right?
If you're not authorized to go somewhere and you go there now, aren't you following through on a prohibition of some sort?
Okay, so when you're using something you're not authorized to use or prohibited stuff and all that, is there a penalty for that?
That you have to return something?
Yes.
So nowhere in the U.S. 12 U.S.C. 411 doesn't say that you're ever going to, they have to give you lawful money, it just says you have to evidence the demand.
Right.
How are you going to pay taxes when there's, you're not authorized to use
the money that,
and taxes don't pay for, look, go to any CAF or Comprehensive Annual Financial Report of any town in the U.S.
They'll tell you, they'll say, well, we spend 3 million to the police, 5 million to the courts, this million to this, wait a minute,
wait a second, when you go to the courts, the city's,
the accounting says that we're spending 3 million a month to keep the courts open,
but you know, they give you no listing on how much the courts take in and fees and penalties.
Where does that go?
Oh, 3 million, 5 million a month for the police.
Where's all the money, don't the police write tickets for fines all the time?
Where does that, where does that go?
You know, there's no accounting for any of that?
And how many people are bringing this up?
Someone says, well, this guy does a video.
No, that guy's an idiot.
I looked at what he says.
He's not bringing up anything.
Come on, people, this is planet Earth.
I'm not saying wake up because you don't want to wake up in it.
You know, better to be asleep.
If you could sleep on a picket fence, you'll be happy here.
You know what I mean?
You know, on the edge of a picket fence, fall asleep.
If you're comfortable, I mean, that's the only way you're going to be happy.
Because if you don't know what's going on, you're always going to bitch and whine on how they took your paycheck or you paid this fine or whatever.
But if you do know what's going on, you're not going to be happy because you can say, how can all these people be morons?
Except for the one that sent me the legal rebuttal, of course, CP.
Thank you, Chris, for doing that, by the way.
Do you see, I hope, Bruce, does that clear up Title 12, Section 411 a little bit more?
It does, yes.
Anyone can do it.
But if you're accepting direct deposit or use credit cards or PayPal or all that, you see, I was going to start a PayPal thing and I got back and forth with them.
They wouldn't let me do any conditional responses.
And I found out that they could run it through any clearinghouse they want.
So when the money goes from terminal to terminal computer, I can't get in there and say demand for lawful money.
So there's no way that you can do a PayPal lawfully.
I don't see it.
At the end result, when money comes into your hand, could you not document that as the money received?
Yes, you can.
But in the middle, if they decide to stop it, you have no recourse.
And that happens.
But it's digital at that point, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's digital when it comes in.
But you have to state that it's lawful right before it lands.
And you can't.
Only after the fact.
It's totally unlawful.
So if you're using PayPal, you're using debit cards, you could probably do it with a debit card if on the bank account you have on the signature card.
Now, if you go to a Wells Fargo or Bank of America and sign up for a bank account, they do it with a digital pen, just sign here.
Well, you know how many times when you return something at a hardware store, they ask you to sign with a digital pen?
Do you think that you don't think they're going to put that signature in inventory and use it on other stuff?
Right.
They do.
Now, I'm not going to say who does and for sure, because I don't know and I don't care to know.
I just want them to go away when the mop-up crew comes.
But if you think that you are signing digital pads and that's all it's for, you're an idiot.
They're putting that shit on contracts that you don't know.
Here's proof of it, indirect proof.
Wells Fargo, if you remember, about a year or two ago, they got in trouble because they opened up about two million credit card accounts for people who didn't even know that those accounts existed, right?
Right.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, I do remember.
Well, what does it take to open a credit card account?
A signature, doesn't it?
Where did they get those signatures?
From all those signatures they have on a warehouse, whenever those idiots sign those signature pads.
So if you're going to open a bank account, say you want it on paper, you're not going to sign the signature thing and then just tell the guy, go to the back, pull up the thing and hit control P and print it out for me, please.
And then just do, when you sign it, lawful money only, type 12 USC, and then sign the name and then it's on record.
And you're starting with your bank account that way or the bank account that way at least.
There's going to be fraud going on the whole time.
When you, let's say, have a thousand bucks in the bank, if you take out a hundred, if you withdraw it in cash, that's one way to affirm that it is a clean withdrawal.
But when you get a check and you deposit, even with lawful money, it's not being taken out of the company that you work for account.
It's being created there on the spot.
That kind of fraud, you can't stop.
Because that's just how it works.
I think you guys remember me.
You know, Sam, let's go over it real quick.
If I write a check to you, Bruce, for a hundred dollars, or let's say, Bruce, you write a check to me for a hundred dollars.
You send it to me in the mail.
It's a check now.
And I get it in the mail.
I take it and I say, oh, a hundred dollar check from Bruce.
I go to the bank.
I give it to the teller.
She looks at the front.
She sees your signature.
She looks at the back.
She doesn't see.
She goes, I can't use this.
Well, because I didn't endorse the back, right?
Correct.
When I endorsed the back, I asked her, can you use it now?
I used to screw around with them that way.
And she said, yeah, I could use it now.
And the only thing banks have in their inventory is transaction numbers.
So they bring up the next transaction number.
They put your information in.
And because there's two signatures on the check, she creates the hundred dollars right there.
Not out of thin air, based on the requirements that they are told that they can create this hundred dollars.
Now she has the information on Bruce's bank.
And this bank that I use calls Bruce's bank and says, we did the thing.
Because you know how the Mothra also talks.
You know that thing you told me about the thing?
Oh, that thing?
Yeah.
What about that thing?
It wasn't so good, that thing.
Oh, the thing.
Right.
You get it?
So anyway, the bank that I'm using calls Bruce's bank and says, we did the thing for a hundred bucks.
So now Bruce's bank takes the hundred bucks out of the account that he sees, puts it into another account under his name that he doesn't see.
So when you go to the account that you do see, Bruce, it shows that the hundred dollars are taken out.
And because you don't know what's going on, you say, oh, the Greek cashed the check.
They took it out from my account.
That's why, right?
Right.
That's not what's going on at all.
It's still in your name at the bank.
Then it sits there and the bank says, this is an abandoned funds.
And then they file an abandoned form, abandoned funds.
Then they wait a little bit.
Then they file a claim form.
And now you know how the bankers get their money, their personal money, credits, because they're not allowed to create it on their own either.
They have to finagle.
So one thing you can do is put, let's say, a thousand bucks in the bank, go spend it all.
At the end of the month, give the bank the statement.
There'll be a thousand dollars at the beginning.
The bottom would be zero.
Give the bank statement with a claimant form.
Say, I want to claim all those funds I just spent.
Uh-oh.
Watch what happens.
And it goes right to legal.
You don't go to the teller because she's a complete idiot.
How do I know she's an idiot?
Because if she wasn't, she wouldn't be a teller.
It's very simple.
I mean, it's mathematical.
So watch what happens.
Oh, you want to see a show and every, you know, and you're all, all of you using this stuff are being defrauded.
You cannot escape it.
You cannot escape it at this point.
You're finished.
Now, you know, even on this little stream, you know, I just lost $9,000.
That's 99% of the people, right?
So if there's 20 people listening, like only one quarter of one person's brain got what I just said.
So that's why I don't get into this stuff too much.
And I'm not belittling or berating the people on the stream.
Say, yes, you are Greek, but, you know, sorry, that's the truth.
Most of you, whoever's listening, this is not going to get it.
That's how simple it is.
And that's how censored that, you know, the people on this planet are.
You get it?
You could just say no or yes, it doesn't matter.
This stuff is one of the core subjects of the cosmic censorship.
Understanding how the money system works.
Why?
Because you know why the money system is 100% fraud right now?
Because the gods are doing it, not because man is doing it.
You know how I know that?
Because if they pulled such a fraud on you and you weren't censored, it would have been uncovered within a few days or a few weeks and stopped.
But because it's been going on for over 50 or 75 years and you can't even explain, the simplest explanation, still people don't get it.
That's absolute proof of cosmic censorship.
Just like you were stating earlier with Isaiah.
You know, close their minds and their eyes and their ears and everything.
Now, am I special or anything?
Not at all.
I'm in a really tough situation to be around such stupidity and censorship.
Am I any less censored?
Not necessarily.
But regarding this topic, yeah, I'm less censored for sure.
That's obvious.
But as a whole, am I less censored?
I don't know.
And it doesn't matter.
Because I'm here with y'all.
And you're never going to understand the money system based on the ever that you have left.
That's an assurance.
What will happen as things wrap up, there'll be an inkling or an impression or an inspiration to stop using it.
And then it'll fall apart.
You see.
But if you, anyway, back to anyone listening to this, if you wrap your mind around Title 12, Section 411, all you got to do is make a demand.
And then just say, hey, look, you want to tax me on this or you want this?
Give me some lawful money first.
You see?
Lawful just means it has to be based on something.
Ultimately, even now, people don't understand money.
And you have these idiots.
But there's this one guy, someone's, I get, fortunately, I don't get berated whoever sent me the links.
This guy, he's really popular.
I mean, he, this moron, his initials are JW.
Ocelli has interviewed him a couple of times and asked me, I said, this guy's a total moron.
He, this guy, he's got huge following, right?
I mean, you can just look at the thing, the statistics.
And to show you how piss poor the humans are.
He's predicted the collapse of the dollar no less than 50 times in the past four years.
And he gives dates and it never comes and he still gets more followers.
And never once does he bring up it's a credit-based economy.
You're supposed to be an expert on gold and silver or something.
Laughable, laughable, space heater stuff.
Are you a 900 watt space heater or a 600 watt space heater?
Is your cord kinked or is your switch broken?
It's deplorable.
I mean, the gods must be just laughing.
I shouldn't say laughing their ass off, but they must be like, this place stinks.
And you know what?
It does say it stinks to high heaven, doesn't it?
Somewhere in there, Sam, if you could back me up on that maybe.
Yes, it does.
Their stench comes up.
Yeah.
So money you'll never understand within the ever that's left.
You'll never understand how the human body works ever with the ever that's left.
Right?
Most likely you're probably never going to understand scripture in the ever that's left.
You're just going to understand enough that it's lawful for the mop-up crew to come.
You see?
Kind of like a traffic ticket.
Most people don't read those things.
If you read it, it's open wide.
What makes a traffic ticket lawful is that you did what?
You endorsed it.
You signed it.
They don't care.
They don't watch.
You try to read it.
They're going to get mad.
Just sign it.
You ever see people with contracts buying a car or something?
They think they're buying a car.
Just sign it.
Don't read it.
Yeah, you're never going to understand within the ever that you have left.
You're not going to understand anything.
The only thing I understand is that are you experiencing pain, comfort?
Is your stomach growling?
Let me put something in it so it's not on my thirsty.
Let me drink something wet so I'm not thirsty.
Some stupid stuff on the rectangle or tv.
Yeah, you're not going to get anything.
Now the reason I'm saying it this way is because you're never going to understand anything that is going to make a viable change in the civilization that you live in.
Ever.
In the ever that's left.
Ever ever it will be because you're going to be ruled with an iron fist and an iron rod.
Which you're being people who talk about a police state and all this other stuff and not so much now about termination of the population growth.
Yeah, all that's going to happen, but it's not going to be done by man.
And when the mop-up crew comes, you know, you're going to be ruled with a very heavy hand.
I hope no one is under the delusion that they're not.
Right?
You're going to be ruled with an extremely heavy hand, but it's going to be benevolent.
There's not going to be any lying.
You're not going to have attorneys.
I assure you there will be no attorneys.
You're not going to have little scumbag priests and ministers and pastors.
Right?
You're not going to have supreme court justices.
There isn't going to be no justice.
That's for sure.
No goddess religion.
Right?
You're not going to have vaccines.
You're not going to have the doctors that you have now.
You'll be well-versed, taught to be well-versed in the human body.
Yep.
It's going to be quite interesting.
So none of this Greek speak applies, by the way, to this society, and it shouldn't.
Why?
Well, first of all, hardly anyone understands what's being said.
And it's not because I'm smarter than everyone or anyone listening at all.
If you don't understand it, how the hell are you going to implement it or meditate on it?
Meditate means to grab a thought or a concept and think about it over and over and over.
Very often, I hate to think about what's going on between the ears of the people listening to Greek speak.
They grab on to, and just from reading emails occasionally and other things, I see they just grab on to one or two words.
Oh, I know this word and I know that word.
Maybe if I piece them together, that's what he said.
No, that's not what I said.
You know.
But at least, Bruce, you're archiving these, and somewhere along the line, someone will come along and actually listen to this and figure out what's being said.
Now, I'm being sarcastic because deservingly so.
I know there are people that hear this and know it.
They can get it.
What I'm saying is even if there are or there aren't, it doesn't make any difference.
Things are going to happen the way they're going to happen and for good reason and well-deserved, by the way.
You could take it up with the gods later.
I'm sure you'll have plenty of time for them to listen, but I think there's going to be a change of heart and a change of mind in the future later on when things are overt.
That's the other thing.
Do you ever get the feeling, Sam and Bruce, that this past 6,000 years has been about secrets?
It's all secrets.
But the majority of the secrets, not all of them, but a majority, meaning more than half, if not three-quarter, are in plain sight.
Then the leftover, let's say the quarter that's left over, if you divide that in half, half of them are so hidden and cryptic that you probably will never figure out in this situation, and the other bit will be figured out.
To make things lawful, by anyone.
And what I mean by figured out, right now, that many of the things that have been deeply hidden by the gods can be shown and you still won't recognize them as such, as something that has been hidden and uncovered.
So it's quite interesting.
I keep saying it's quite interesting, because the focus, although it sounds like a trivial pursuit, on food, clothing, and shelter, and then, of course, within that, hopefully you will have good company, even if it's an animal friend or whatever, and good interactions, and you'll be conservative with what you've been given, and use it as best and highest use.
And that's all that's really that can be done.
The rest of it is just whatever free will you want to exercise in that direction.
Like, for example, there could be someone that could really be into Greek speak and also be into American football.
I can't see that the two are reckoned, but it is possible, but unlikely.
I think it's actually an impossibility, but who am I to say it's really an impossibility?
It is possible.
Wait, what?
Based on what?
Why?
Well, let's just say, forget about Greek speak for a moment, is it possible for someone to be studying scripture, objectively, and how, you know, the real scripture, and be a big football fan into sports?
Is it possible?
Yes.
I'm not seeing it.
I'm not seeing it either, but it is possible.
Why?
Why are you not seeing it?
Not that I'm into it.
I hate American football.
Or any sport.
For the reason, very simple reason, is because eventually when you're into sports, it's a very social thing.
And you're going to be interacting with others.
And if you look at your average...
You can watch it on TV.
Yes, you can watch it on TV.
That's what I mean.
It could be possible.
But then how much of it can you watch?
You see, so in other words, what I'm saying, though, even though it's food, clothing, and shelter, there's a myriad of interests that you can incorporate, but those are really minimal.
That's personal.
That's the personal aspect, you know?
Mm-hmm You know, that's like years ago when you used to go to a fine tailor for a suit.
They ask that if you're a man, they ask you, how does your stuff hang on the left or the right?
Because they make an adjustment for it, right?
You know, whatever.
So, I mean, who's to say how it should hang?
That's my lascivious comment for the day, by the way.
Maybe the second one.
Third.
Third, okay.
Yeah.
You carnal people out there, you can blush or run or yell or whatever.
Fine.
So, and I hate it when people call it your junk because it ain't junk.
So, nonetheless, I think I'm good for today.
I'm gonna have to retire soon.
Yeah, and thanks for doing this, Bruce.
Oh, no, no problem.
No problem.
Yeah, and one of these days I'll tell everyone what I really think.
I remember one of your discussions quite fondly.
Well, you know, then that was discussion was about how to fix.
You can fix anything.
It's just that.
And everything, yeah.
But the thing is that people aren't gonna like it.
Well, then don't ask me to fix it.
No, they're not.
No, no, they're not.
And I think what I told you was very objective.
I think you were being soft, actually, that night.
Yeah, right.
It still ends up, in other words, it still ends up.
It still ends up not being pretty.
Well, yeah, you're gonna lose, to fix it, you're gonna lose about three quarters of the population instead of 90 to 90.
Just on the first couple of minutes.
Yeah.
Well, the better, I mean, I'm not saying you could do it better than the gods, but for sure, three quarters of people gotta go.
I'll go on the record for saying that.
That's without a doubt.
The gods are going to eliminate 95% of y'all.
But for sure, what I see so far, three quarters can't be around it to make the world a better place because they're seared.
You cannot change them.
It's just like when you work at the foundry and you're pouring, let's say, pawls for a sailboat pin, right?
You know what a pawl is, right?
Looks like a rod with a hook on it.
And if the mold is no good, in other words, if the metal casts out, it has to be melted again and cast again.
In other words, most people are cast into just pure evil and they don't even know it.
And they don't want to know it and you can't change them.
And it's not because I say it, it's because they say it.
And I used to hear people say, by the way, maybe Bruce, you might have heard of it living here.
I'll defend to the death what you believe in for your right or some stupid stuff that people say, right?
Yeah, I do recall that.
You better stop saying I'll defend to the death because one of these days you might be accommodated.
And it ain't worth dying for.
It's some stupid shit.
Freedom of speech, freedom of religion, all that stuff.
That's some real dumb shit.
None of that shit.
Right, so, oh no, or, yeah.
Yeah, that's some dumb stuff, man.
And yeah, but here's the thing, they will be accommodated.
And they're not, yeah.
Yeah, that's one of the examples that I can give.
And you can even see the evil that's in the little children.
They're raised into that.
Right.
So, and the gods have a pretty good solution for that.
They're going to turn all these young people, especially that were born 1998 up until around 2005 and so.
Oh, yeah, you're going to see what they're going to start doing.
Not now, but much later.
Yeah.
You're not going to say, do it for the children anymore.
So, it's not them.
They're just being used at this point.
It will be interesting to see how those cloakalism does it.
And they're in that little bit that are left.
The majority of them are just a representative sample of the scumbags on the planet now.
But they're going to be ruled and rearranged by the gods, which no man can do.
You know what I mean?
No, no one can do it.
You're going to have to have supernatural, ultra-natural and dino-natural beings to do it.
It ain't going to happen.
There's no, it's really, really bad.
It's, yeah, but it's not so bad if you don't know that it's bad.
Does that make any sense?
It's not so bad if you don't know how bad it is.
If you know, if you just go out to objectify and learn on your own, objectively what's going on, it's really bad.
I don't recommend anyone do that.
I recommend focusing on how to improve your food, clothing and sheltering.
So well, Greek, how come you're talking about these things?
Well, because it's not that I have to get them off my chest.
It's just that it's kind of sublime to see how no one else is discussing them so simply.
It's just retarded.
So yeah, you don't want to know.
Well, here's the other thing.
You're going to have to learn how to weave and loom and create happiness.
People try to, you ever say they want to find happiness?
We're under a rock?
Are you thinking you're going to pick it out of your belly button or someone else's belly button?
No, no, no, no.
You're going to have to learn how to create it once you find the truth.
I don't even like to use that word, the truth.
Look at all the morons out there using it.
So yeah, it's really, really bad.
So I don't know.
What do we get?
What's that?
Another word that they destroyed.
And they don't even know what it means.
They have no reference.
Even here's the sad thing.
They're deceived about you know how I say if headquarters is full of deception, only deception can come in and go out of it.
So yes.
Yeah.
And the thing is they, it cannot be changed.
Not because it cannot be changed.
It's because they've decided that they don't want it changed.
So.
Yeah.
It's all about them.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna have to check out.
Sorry guys.
That's fine.
Let's uh, let's just say sorry for the whole thing.
And uh, thanks and sorry and thank you.
And we'll do it again maybe next week.
Thanks Bruce.
Hey guys.
Yes.
And uh, I want to thank you again and uh, all the uh, 20, what is it, 20 listeners tonight.
So a lot of people got an earful.
So I want to thank you both.
What's that?
That, that are hearing.
Yeah.
We don't know who's listening.
Correct.
And I want to thank you Sam and uh, Greek.
You uh, outdone yourselves again.
Well, so have you with your archiving skills there.
So um, everyone take care.
Thanks again.
Okay, be well both of you.
And be well everybody out there and you have a good night.
And we'll catch you next time.