And tonight we got myself and Greek.
Hey man.
All right.
And how are you doing tonight sir?
Oh doing okay actually I'm trying to get set up here so we can do the sonic event.
Really need some coffee and some smokes and kind of get it ready and talk about whatever.
See if anyone's got any questions and you know this is becoming an unregular regular thing.
Right.
So I don't know what are you writing.
It's good to know that we can that we can do this on the fly anytime we want.
And yeah that's good for that.
There's no rigorous scheduling and all that kind of stuff and if people want it you can always grab it off the server.
Right if it's how's that working by the way for everyone so far?
It seems to be going good no negative feedback other than that I mislabeled a couple of files so they weren't available but we remedied that straight away.
Okay.
Other than that nothing negative a lot of positive you know thankfulness and such which is always welcomed.
So that was a positive thing.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay good.
So what's on anybody's mind?
Anybody got anything they want to mull around or just do a little bit of Greek speak?
Seems that we just started and we got that 20 second or so delay.
Nothing yet appearing but whatever is on your mind is always welcomed.
Hmm.
I'll just start off with I had a
conversation with someone recently on a telephone bringing up a few things and
and it was like a little conference call and I got a little overheated about what
I was saying and they pretty much said well you're attacking our whole society
I'm like well I don't think that society is worth attacking you know I'm just
saying like what's what's wrong you know you people are always complaining you
know the typical human garbage you know that they talk about and I said well
look you don't even know how to keep time you don't know how the body works
you know you actually millions of you every day go sit down and get blood
pressure taken and none of you are the wiser to see that it's a prank right and
you're being pranked with told that your body absorbs oh your body absorbs stuff
and on and on and on you know how the money system works you know if everybody
says oh money's based on nothing so when they transfer money when you write
a check and it goes from one account to other how's it done what's really going
on I don't care I don't want to know one guy said it's really funny he says
basically thinks we're all just a bunch of animals I said well yeah pretty much
yeah and expect that they were thinking I was gonna defend that you know yeah
but you know that then that speaks poorly of the animals it's a very
strange animal and humans by the way or man kind womankind are not animals
that's another interesting thing that can be gone over it's something that
requires some thought not a lot of thought to see what what I just said is
true the other thing is that this is this environment meaning the the social
environment humanity at large there's no such thing as atheistic or secular
everything is based on some kind of deific model or archetype or really quick
you know for example you know if you have a secular which means not religious
and by the way all religions in the world bar none are pagan or atheist based you
know what there's no no real God there because they can't identify it right now
the ones that can identify gods are steeped in pagan ritual so this is the
almost without exception in terms of it from an organizational reality what is
going on on this planet and you combine that these various archetypal realities
that exist with the basic piss-poor human character that you see and that's a
cocktail for slow-moving disaster right but nonetheless when you go back to
nothing being secular like for example a scientist you know half the
terms that they use come from mythological gods or you know gods that
are dead you know if you heard like electron right that's you know or
volcano from the god Vulcan yeah so you know or what about the my favorite is
the idiots in the legal society the justice system that is the revived
goddess religion they don't know anything about law I don't wanna bring
this up is really funny someone was recently offering a law book collection
and says was my grandfather's law books and he practiced for almost 50 years and
they're all in perfect condition I said well of course they would be in perfect
condition because he never opened any of them he doesn't need to know what's in
there to practice law as an attorney all he needs to do is know how to accuse
people right anyway he's kind of a bad joke but it's true it's true yeah I dare
any you go to any doctor's office or law lawyer's office or attorney's office
and they have all these books you know I just take one off the shelf it's like
super crisp and clean they don't need those days of school and even then even
in school they don't they only touch the textbooks yeah which are whatever they
did your garbage now I was thinking by the way at one point of doing a
discussion which is somewhat of a loose study on how you're being pranked by the
medical system by looking at what instructions they give in their
universities like Harvard Med School and downstate medical not some local
community college I'm talking about I'm talking about you know the pinnacle and
also showing how you're being pranked by the legal society by going to you know
Yale Law School and all that in Princeton law and showing you their
curriculums very simple I was like yeah why am I doing this because all I do
with this is you know bring up a medical school university curriculum from
undergraduate to graduate just it just lists all the courses and it gives
course descriptions and the same with the medical the same with the scientists the
same with the physicists and you just look at all this and keep in the back
of your mind does what there is what they're giving in their curriculum as
part of the instruction institutional instruction to get what's called a
degree have any bearing on the field itself as we consider the field to be
and the answer to that is no no it doesn't so and it's very simple I mean
you know the common moron will say oh yes it is that's what you do and but I
said well look at it look what they're teaching this has nothing to do with the
human body live that's alive it's you know it's interesting to bounce around
to the medical idiots when you look at their curriculums and more on the
graduate level it's all cadaver dissection oh that's fine if you're
going to be working on cadavers your rest your life where you're not you get
and you're getting alive but you know this is it's a bad joke you know
somewhere in scripture it says it was a just to really hasten the quote here
it's let the dead bury the dead so just because we're walking around doesn't
really mean they're really alive and the medical community is trying to tell
you that and the same with the legal perfection of the profession the same
with most of the professions that people aspire to as being professional and what
does this surmise everything down to various levels of pranking and so that's
the that's the interesting part but the other interesting part is there's
nothing really secular what I mean by that is you know everything that you
look at in any language when you start going into the let's see what they call
the professional aspects or the sciences or the various disciplines you will see
the terms that are being used and the metaphors and and even the names are
based on ancient gods throughout you know and so how are they saying well I'm
secular and you know and I'm not religious well it's kind of like that's
the schizophrenic part that comes in when you're creating a so morticians mm-hmm
guys that guys that don't know shit and can alter your life within a second you
know with or without their stupidity and it just goes on worse yeah but
ultimately it'll be like no one put a gun to your head to go to them exactly
exactly yeah yeah but they put a gun to your head if you try to do what they
resemble you know if you give me an example if law wasn't let's just look at
it this way let's just side bend the secular there's no such thing as any
secular it's all really some kind of spiritual deific behind it we sidetracked
that for a second if the society let's say the authorities of any society were
concerned about being lawful wouldn't they teach law to everyone like in
scripture isn't there I think I don't know if it's an exodus or numbers or
Deuteronomy where they're told to put up some large pillars of stone and
plaster them and write the name the words of the law on it so as the people pass
through they all are aware of it because you know they're promoted right well
they used to know how much proclamations and oh that's a that's a long ritual yes
and now the the morons that are supposedly in the legislative body say
they don't even read it and why because it doesn't matter no you don't have to
read it you just have to know what they're telling you is going on on
television you know like you know a bunch of 19 Arab hijackers with box
cutters made the World Trade Center turn into dust right so I mean that's all you
need to know so I mean it's ridiculous so and then you go to the if there if
they wanted you to know about health or how the body works they would be
teaching that you would have buildings designed for that yeah yeah more than
the ones that are there to take care of you being sick you think that the
opposite would be true and they wouldn't be poisoning you through food
yeah right I think that's a whole different sector there the agricultural
community which has been inundated by corporations and all sorts of stuff was
that you beeping I go ahead and say something Bruce I'm saying I'm talking
one two three one two three four you got there we go there we go yep I got a copy
cuz I'm wireless so let's see if I figure better oh that was cute little
tones and it sounded like radar or echo did it okay
yeah thanks actually I'm doing a little bit of weather work and it tends to
really put a bubble around the area oh my oh you just you just want away there
yeah you all right how's that I'm much better
okay let's you know sudden one dead air and a couple little beeps and you're
gone that should be better okay yeah so these are the various basic basics of
examining a society you don't need to contemplate much on this earth right
now well even a slight meditation on the subject boy what an eye-opener after you
start really really taking a look around and just refreshing yourself on the
words and things boy what an eye-opener mm-hmm now here's another thing I want
to bring out which I haven't I think it'd be good to start speaking even more
plainly because you know the five or ten people listen to this already got
or I should say have established some foundation on on things so when I say
you know they're it's pranking they know what I'm referring to and things
like that so most of people listening this established a foundation on the
real reality versus the reality that people are told over and over which
doesn't exist so and from that point of view you see the contradictions you
know the and you know from being mild contradictions to just major lies that
are ridiculous because they're so in your face and no one really sees them
that it makes it just a ridiculous situation so now you have to manage how
you are going to think amongst the spiritual turmoil right this mind
turmoil right and let me just throw this in again you know the spirit is the mind
usually when you use the word mind it's what you're mindful I like to use the
word spirit which is the actual in the component of you but when I say mine
sometimes I mean that is what you're just focusing on at the moment like
being mindful of something right never see like I got to go mind this mind the
dog mind whatever so so it's still part of the spirit but the best way to be
mindful about you know how you're going to interact with all this stuff I have
found out and personally in the past decade believe it or not I'm gonna say
this it's gonna sound strange in the beginning and it might just but it might
if you let it sink in you'll see how it works okay are you still there Bruce yes
I was muted I was listening oh that's fine we're still on okay so how do you
make sense of all this craziness because you know it's not some let me just put
it again in perspective reassessing who was around you constantly you know
whether it's people at work pedestrians family members friends you know it
doesn't matter they they're you'll see that when you start operating on a core
level people are pretty much all the same whether they're related to you or
not and it went into what we're discussing here is when you grab a
foundation on what's really going on you'll see the turmoil and then you're
like how do I manage this you know and in my mind or spirit right and what
again just to repeat myself I'm going to just say this is how it's done and how
I've had great success with it very simple you must understand prophecy why
like in other words you must understand what comes next in all of this why
because if you're steeped in all of this ridiculousness and then you throw in
without even thinking about it you know it exists but you don't think about it
the the the possibility and probabilities of all the randomness you
know how many times you hear well you don't know you might just walk outside
and an asteroid hits you in the head or you might trip and fall you know you
right so yeah so when you when you factor in how ridiculous everyone is and
the randomness of everything you know it's very difficult to maintain peace
and harmony actually you have to work on it more than anything you know it's kind
of like a tightrope now between the insanity and non insanity so the easiest
way to manage that is to use to have a handle on what's coming in the future so
now when you see for example something in the news or what people are talking
about you knew it was coming already right you see so it's no big deal so you
start minimizing the randomness like for example if you lay out a whole bunch of
an ingredients and just mouth off you know profiteroles you know roast
potatoes and whatever whatever a whole bunch of dishes to an expert chef he's
like all right I'm gone all right I got it you know let's do it and he's pretty
much gonna enjoy it but if you go to like a common American whatever that you
used to microwaving food you put all the ingredients in your mouth off a bunch of
dishes to make that person is in extreme panic they don't know where to start
they don't even know basically how to turn the fire the heat on and so I mean
yes yeah they're gonna be they have no because it's totally outside of their
scope and and in both cases it's very similar the total clueless person who
can't prepare basically you know hard-boiled egg has to create a
knowledge base and even with the knowledge base they don't know how it's
going to turn out where the the skilled chef he's done it before and he sees
the you know if he they know that they have a sensibility and sensitivity on
their actions whatever they do will affect the outcome you see so and there's
an even flow to their way of doing it it's it's more graceful and finesse
it's like Tai Chi right they're not stressed they're happy about it versus
this guy that's just punching a bag or some such you know yeah oh exactly so to
just kind of sum things up what people will be seeing in the near future and
future is there's going to be a greater grasp of reality by the morons on this
planet and what I mean by that a greater grasp meaning of course like going back
to what we said earlier about nothing is secular right you go to a secular
scientist you could show him that 40 to 70 percent of all the terms and things
that he uses come out of old religious texts right and same with the attorneys
and doctors and all this other stuff so there's nothing secular there's a divine
aspect to us when I say about learning about more things and people will get a
grasp on this reality that means they're going to get a grasp of what the gods
are and their effect on humanity and all this in the real history of the gods
right so what that when and you know and then the next level after that is the
manifestation of man's final power base in the Middle East so now that sounds
like what Greek that's so general you know what does it have to do with me you
know going out and you know raising chickens or going to work as in the
warehouse or flying an airplane what does it have to do with that well it's
all interconnected and it's all and because the end results of this
particular society are going to be so compressed and rapid for rapid events
one after the other that you know you will see that everything and everyone no
matter what field or we're part of the world you're you know what field of
interest you have or work in or even just interested in or what part of the
world you're in or your nationality or religion or language you are all going
to begin to grasp a reasonable sense of your history your real history which you
cannot separate from those of the history of the gods right that's why
again there's nothing secular the gods have influenced and it's just people
denying it now you can take any particular vocation or condition that
anyone might have you know it doesn't matter what their sex is or their job
let's say or what part of the world they live they will all experience a
resurgence and a rediscovery and a discovery of the society of the gods and
how it affected this mankind you see no now they say that are you meaning this
in a point where to be kind of like more common around the water cooler kind of
thing or every no yes yes not exclusive or not necessarily just inclusive or
exclusive of anything outside the water cooler no I mean in the word on the
street the at the dinner table in the newspapers on the internet in the
movies somebody just a few days back sit down down where they were they were
starting to notice this a little more on their radio which I kind of found
interesting I was like hmm interesting tidbit there yeah no years years ago and
I used to do roundtables with Seth this is years ago all years four years ago or
so maybe more of a five or four roughly like around with 13 of 12 13 I was
saying there's gonna be more increase of the gods you know let's say the biblical
text in most of the audience being you know the Western Convention the
biblical text is you know pretty much what they consider to be you know when
you think of God thing right there's gonna be an increased discussion
increased looking in that direction not only in the subject matter well all of
the subject matter but also that the the the influence that it has on society
which hasn't started yet right because right now it's just like oh that's
religion put it aside you know we got to go to work right right so it's got
nothing to do with this so but none of it's going to be accurate is what I said
in the beginning very little accuracy but it doesn't matter you're looking in
that direction you see so this what's exciting about it is starting in the
next few months you're going to see that starting in earnest I mean you know
where it'll be whatever movement you see will be deep-rooted it won't be a fad or
a fashion that this is happening you see now now the the other thing is like I
said there's not going to be much accuracy let's just take it for example
or I'm reckoning around the 23rd of the 10th month if anyone's with me on that
I think roughly 23rd of the 10th month till noon and what they call this is the
pagan holiday of Christmas roughly for most of the world and it's a second
people say well you know it's secular really you know or religious this is a
time when the lines get blurred notice because so why are banks closed on it
you know what are they religious stuff you know it's not it's not Saturday in
Jerusalem because you know the Jews the Jews think Saturday is the Sabbath you
know consistently oh they've been for now and so so what's so it's just like for
example when it comes to elections the government all of a sudden says we have
to be lawful so for one day we'll try to follow the Constitution right you get it
you know when they do elections in government bring it right yeah any other
time you approach them so no no we don't go by those laws oh no no it's not
what it means but on the election day they say oh yeah yeah we're doing this
because it's constitutional one day right you know they try to be lawful yeah
I mean it's just you know it's just this is not a critique on any society now
what when you critique the earth right now is like a really bad greasy spoon at
the end of town if anyone greasy spoon just means like a place to go to eat like
a cafe or a diner and the food's not good yeah the reason why it's in
business is because of its location and you have no other choice right sorry
they're so hungry you're eat there so you know the whole place is bad but like
you know someone will say well did you have the pancakes there oh they're
terrible they're dry they have no flavor but did you have the meatloaf oh the
meatloaf is really bad right you know so you know you know that it's like how's
the coffee oh the coffee is horrendous it's even worse than the meatloaf it
should be you see so the place generally is bad and then within the place what's
on the menu there's various levels of disgust within it you see what I mean
right but but people still order it this is the society and planet earth so you
could say well yeah you know the earth is really bad you know like the
Americans oh yeah they're really like they're really off the rock like the
most ignorant crazy people in the world easy to say that and then runner-up
would probably be Canadians Australians and British in that order right but it
doesn't mean that that's perpetual or it's always has to be that way just
happens to be like the meatloaf right and then you could say well you know
this place is like this it's just this is like the you know Hitchhiker's Guide to
the Galaxy the restaurant at the end of the galaxy this is the greasy spoon
right now it is the nasty you know it's like where the suit the chicken soup and
the mop pot are on the floor next to each other you know I mean this is
planet earth so what do you do so the easiest to you know the thing is you
can't tell anyone what to do without knowing enough specifics right so I give
you an example of that you know like street sweeping sounds real basic but a
professional street sweeper has there are a lot of secrets to doing it well
give you an example like I knew someone who didn't maintenance contract to do
the casinos in Las Vegas and he had about 200 employees I mean he was making like
10 million 15 million a year just cleat maintaining parking lots you know
if there's a grease stain you steam clean it off you know and all this stuff
so I went out with there with these guys one night and just screwing around look
as oh yeah what are you doing you know his crew shows up and I said give me a
broom and he's like no no no you're doing it wrong you see this this parking
lot was roll when they rolled the asphalt they rolled it this way right front to
back here so you want to sweep along the line that they rolled the asphalt in
and I'm like what did you say I would have never thought of that no right no
you see I mean so it's like don't you know so most people say it's the green
yeah sort of like or go with the green yeah so so it's like even these guys
have their science and their expertise but when you say street sweeper even I
use it as an analogy of someone in the bottom you see so there's what how can
you say you know Greek what should I do well I don't know only you know what
you're doing so you know what you should do based on a certain foundation of
principles in other words if you know that you're being pranked right all
around you everyone around you is subject to it and you don't want to be
subject to it what do you do well easy you just figure out where it wins the
next time they're gonna offer you a chair with a thumbtack simple right and
but the thing is now when you're dealing with most of let's say established
institutions they offer you a chair let's say the legal society when they offer you
a chair you know this thumbtack and you're like oh I don't want to say they
pull out a gun and put it to your head and said sit on it so now it's the gun or
the thumbtack right so now you have to go higher than that you have to go to that
you have to understand why they're doing them how they're doing that and let's
say legal society medical society the politicians even even you know on
various car mechanics various fields you unfortunately have to know when
you're going to get involved in you have your everyday daily life and what you do
your regimen and then you need one of these morons you know one of these
specialists unfortunately you have to know what you want them to do so when
you go to a legal person or a medical person or a mechanical person
unfortunately or fortunately actually you know it's really fortunate when you
experience it and you do it you have to know what you want them to do and they're
simply just performing it you're that they're just the hands you're give on
the task yeah they're just doing the task and you're able to you know enough
about what you'd like for them to do that you can mentally manage it and
discuss it to the point where they can't get over on you or you know nothing
more nothing less just do this and get it done that's right and you right now
forthright about it or otherwise you'll don't eat you up really yes and I see
so-called intelligent people all around that I went to the doctor and you know
like oh really you know and then you watch them after two years and they're
being destroyed by negligence and whatever and even when they get in the
same attorneys or the mechanics or the contractors or whatever so so the point
is what the reason why society hasn't completely fall into shambles and by the
way if you don't think that it's possible for civilization or society
from the shambles you don't know any history but the reason why it hasn't at
this point is one reason is the gods are propping it up and also it's a
testament to the robustness of the human you know or the the spirit of people and
their ability to bounce back from you know bad situations and I'll give an
example again just to bounce around there was a study that was done by
someone years ago on socialist countries that have socialized medicine and when
the doctors would go on strike right doctors would actually go on strike the
hospitals would be essentially shut down and the morgues would be empty people
stop down yeah and the hospitals open up again and I say well it doesn't make any
sense of course it makes sense what you know just because the hospitals closed
no one's in the morgue what there aren't any car accidents yeah there aren't any
murder there aren't murders there aren't poison there aren't dying of old
age Judy's just suddenly stopped people stop dying exactly it's like if there
were no attorneys there would be no hardly anyone in prison right I mean
think about that it's the same thing you know if you didn't have mechanics cars
wouldn't break down why because they would build them so they didn't yep
right that's another situation I'm quite well versed and I do work with the
automotive quote-unquote people or the engine type people and what a bunch of
morons throughout I mean I mean you die but they're not any more moronic than
the medical community or the legal community or whatever
toilet paper certificates you know mm-hmm that's it they were trained to
do a task they did it well they picked they've got it score and by the way
click your chat on so you can kind of see some of this stuff you get some
interesting questions going through there oh do I okay let's see and by the
way the venue man went and gave a good analogy a gun tack when you were talking
about the thumbtack on the chair oh yeah that's right that's rather clever I just
see that it's open it okay great I see the day's questions hmm any truth to
monthly astrology signs and if so they start with the new moons astrology has
been kind of destroyed it's shifted between East and West and astrology right
now is like imagine taking a circuit board apart and what's the difference
between a tube amp and in a solid state well I see this analogy I'm getting is a
little different but don't take take the all the parts off a circuit board on
solder and put them in a bag and then just randomly dump the bag out and
solder everything back on do you expect it to work it could it might make smoke
and light maybe you don't know right so a little but there's a there's a cycle
it's been custom tailored now to sound plausible in you know when you go and
study let's say psychology 101 one of the things they do about horoscopes is
they write a horoscope and they hand it out they put everyone's name on it so
you think it's specifically done for you and then you know and they ask
everyone in the class to raise your hand if you feel it applies to you and just
about everyone raises their hand right and says well this is a custom-made you
know one for you others is that's why right and I say well I just want you to
look to the person behind you or next to you and just exchange the paper and it's
the same thing yeah everyone got the same horoscope it's a it's a legalized
you know thing back in the day and I'm talking way back the the accuracy of
these people back then where it was astounding they were articulate they
yes they were like Tai Chi they flowed and understood and now it's like you'd
say it's it's commercialized it's corrupted by God knows what
but well it is well wouldn't say God the gods are ready to you know do their
thing so but here's the other thing about astrology it just means basically
knowledge or words about where astronomy no most means the laws of the stars so
one is you know they've kind of shifted in between the purpose of prophecy I've
been saying this for a long time is to tell you the anomalies of thing you
know things that are anomalous things that are going to be happening outside
of the normal natural clockwork that you see in the skies in the earth and all
that you see so you could learn and many points in history you'll see that
there are astronomical references of course even now it should be used it is
the only lawful way to keep time right and because it's you know it's it's
lawful it's the anyone you know there's no use your patience do you see a
correlation between the prophecy and you know let's say stars and no different
no no because hear me I'm gonna say it again the purpose of prophecy is to
show you the anomalies that are not shown in the sky in the normal clockwork okay
let me give you a profit okay this is another metaphor it's a really easy way
let's say the sky and the sky movements moon Sun stars is like a clock on the
wall okay very reliable right just as it is now mechanically fixed to a certain
point mm-hmm and I tell you tomorrow you know that thing everyone says well we've
been counting on it for a really long time it'll probably work for a really
long time but I'm gonna say to you there's here's a prophecy tomorrow
someone's gonna walk in and shoot that clock well now what are you gonna keep
time with it's gonna be you know shrapnel right that's probably that's
the difference between prophecy and clockwork so what's the way it's way
outside the scope of anything that we often make up the normal mechanical
movements that you're used to like you rely on hmm and meditate on it I just
said something that I've been saying for over a decade and it just passes over
people's head and sometimes I'll say things that seem very minor and
insignificant those are the key points to Greek speak and no one comes back on
them you know and the reason why is because maybe it's so simple that I'll
say it again the purpose of prophecy is to impart the anomalies that will be
coming and the reason why they're anomalous is because they don't fit
within the normal day-to-day week-to-week month-to-month clockwork
that you're used to that you rely on give me an example like you're used to
planting and growing and sewing you know spring summer fall used to those
seasonal things that happen right you know you take out you put the snow
shovel away in the summer and you take it out in the fall or the winter right
this is normal you know you don't know big deal is normal stuff but what if I
were to tell you you're gonna have to take your snow shovel out in June
because it's gonna have snow up to the top of the door well it sounds pretty
ridiculous doesn't it right that sounds outside of the clockwork right right so
so the purpose of prophecy initially in other words initially what I mean is its
placement within a body of knowledge is to show you the anomalies and give it a
few examples of that like one example is when the the old man and the old woman
went to the temple in the New Testament for example to greet the Christ when
his parents brought him there for circumcision on being eight days old
right well how did they know to be there at that time and nobody's what there's
like millions of people going in and out of Jerusalem every day or that part of
the world because it was concentrated like New York City what no one else knew
no they didn't why those two people understood prophecy only two out of all
those millions of people at that time and just to recap I put it in the chat
recently if any I'm not going to give verses and all that because I'm not
into you know mouthing off the actual specifics in the text just like when you
discuss a film you don't say oh did you see the movie at one hour 42 minutes and
33 seconds no you either saw the movie and you know it or not you know well
what's interesting he was born when the parents were in transit right there were
moving around and the ones that witnessed that were shepherds only
shepherds and then there's an exodus to Egypt for two years I would say that go
back and check the text but these Magi which is a pretty accurate term by the
way but Easterners they didn't come and greet Christ until two years after he was
born in a house you know a house meaning like a quote-unquote residency
you know wasn't like a hotel or a motel or right right and then you know when
they came in a town to do this I mean they had the place was in you know it's
like the Bilderbergers coming into a town you know how they would shut it
down you know right people don't understand the the power of these guys
so and it's completely completely understated and erroneous just like for
example I say well wouldn't they tell you about the Christ the Christians or
that what do they show you what's the third their prominent symbols until you
meant until you mentioned that I never ever ever heard anything come close to
that and I think well so you know that was astounding it is yeah it was pretty
major and the thing is it doesn't have to go over and over because the purpose
of these accounts was to just put down on paper the facts have you ever read
for have you ever read for example or if anyone can consider reading what's
called an affidavit of evidence to be entered into a court case you know no
matter it's just like the few words that you were there at this time at this day
you saw this and you swear to it that's it it's not that it shocked you and you
couldn't sleep for a week or you didn't like the color sweatshirt he was wearing
or any you know I mean right the details are sparse if not none it you know sort
of time so yeah right detailed that's it open shut close now with with Seth
back in the day on the roundtable I did a two-hour explanation of what was going
on back then based on the entire you know what could be gleaned off of history
and understanding scripture understanding sociology at the time the
laws at the time and all that and then you know at this point I'd like to do
that again sometime in the future not tonight but I could just throw these
little tidbits in another tidbit is why were it why were they all in transit it
wasn't just his parents that were in transit it was the whole area was
transient or in transit for some reason when does this happen when does that
happen that happens during the Jubilee year doesn't it
right right because you give back property and you go and debts are
forgiven well you know when you know this period is coming up and when is it
done during the time of in-gathering when is the time of in-gathering so
seventh month and there was a lot of customs that went along with that oh yeah
yeah that are not reiterated that are not that are not in that what's called the
New Testament and because people are not aware of them there's no you know in
other words they could pull the wool over your eyes and say anything that's
what I was gonna say earlier the when you say the symbol of Christianity is a
guy nailed to a Roman cross with long hair wearing a diaper right that's that's
the symbol and that is completely non-biblical I was having a discussion
with someone recently if I were to do an archaeological dig I would go opposite
the Gihon Spring towards the east and then go vertically and you will find
there is a stone formation there which our house is built right now if you go
to Google you'll see there's like a in this when they did the Google Earth
photo there's a like apartments there like you know one single-story duplex
type stuff and there's like a rug and laundry hanging there you know it's
almost never when you put that picture up I think I still have that somewhere
if you if you zoom in you'll see there's like the current picture might have been
taken out of months ago there's laundry hanging in a laundry but someone's got a
rug drying that you know hanging there and all this other stuff that location
right there if you dug it up and you started understanding like alluvium and
how things you know you know over time how they were you want to take down how
they move and how things are buried over time or moved but you will do it that
basic geology if you keep digging down you'll come to a point where you will see
a tree stump basically or an area you see even when the tree totally decomposes
the soil there is slightly different right right it becomes clay in a vein
formation there might even be petrification what you will find in that
area is the base of an almond tree just the base and a lot of carbonization a
black layer and within that carbonization you'll probably find bone
fragments carbonized human bone fragments and other effects personal
effects burned probably burned leather satchels burned clothing bird sandals
burned personal effects maybe even some coinage maybe melted because what
happened was intensity yeah yeah yeah well in order to burn a tree and bodies
it usually it's a minimum to a two to four hour burn it was springtime so so
what you will find there is evidence of a tree that was burned with two people
that were burned on it the third was not burned he was put into a tomb right
that's gonna be one hell of an event by the way no one is discussing this type
of archaeology not at all but if I had unlimited time I would do it and funding
I would go and do that you know the way you do that is you you you go to the
properties there now you make them an offer they can't refuse so you can dig
underneath and get the permits and you'll find that I assure you and that
would have been the execution location of the Christ but not him he was because
he he was spared that burning right because they were like oh you know they
ran in haste to take the body down it was all in haste
oh yeah because you know as after they were declared dead the people started you
know doing all piling up all the stuff underneath personal belongings of the
two the robber and the thief and all that were with them right and and you know
starting a fire it doesn't happen immediately to take over an hour it
takes time yes preparation so this can be discovered now there's a focus on
archaeology that I would consider there's a focus on considering doing a
scriptural study someone I see T Bender put in what about the book of Daniel
being understood soon yes absolutely that is a one of the promises and if we are
in that time you will see an understanding in there and I've know
I've noticed personally the understanding of that book increasing
day-by-day for me I'd like to do a discussion on that I had once even though
I'm when I was doing the solo event someone called in a wonderful lady who's
been listening to Greek speak and actually been applying it and it helped
her out with some dream states and things like that quite well and she kept
asking about the book of Daniel and I gave I dropped a couple of tidbits on
some more understanding on the book of Daniel there and then I said that it
will be more soon and soon and soon meaning as time progresses not you know
one point now we understand it right it'll just keep opening up so and that
might I would say I would be right now I could do I mean that right now in this
sonic event but in the future I could easily do a four-hour explanation of the
book of Daniel but I would prefer to do something like that in a year or two or
three hmm because I think that'll be even more you know less gray area at
that point you know right now it's still before it was a blur now it's
pixelated but I got the image I'd like for it to be high it's not it's it's 240
P it's not 1080 you know right right no gotcha
or it's a charity clarity and sharpness focus yeah and I would suggest to anyone
unfortunately unless well of course there's a lot of good corn out there but
it's embedded with poo right or it's embedded in poo and unfortunately still
I tell people the best way to study scripture is don't bring anything from
the outside into it just pick it up and look at it but you really really have to
wring it out because there are things that are being given there that are so
simple I used to always say just because a statement is really short doesn't mean
it's not important right like someone falls off of a ship and screams help I'm
drowning what did he say that wasn't important it just two words it can't be
important right so and I'm not talking about doing it with desperation or you
know panic or or anything like that but yeah that is the book of Daniel for sure
I mean the the book of here's another one that I haven't brought up and
discussed much at all you ready this is a first I think or sort of a first at
least for the people listening book of Daniel yes here's another book you're
ready if you could wrap your mind around the book of Zechariah Zechariah's I've
discussed that book to some extent now that is really actually there's a couple
of key points major points in the book of Zechariah that are going to be
happening now soon next few years or so and those that's open for discussion
there's a lot of clarity on that national actually the analysis of that
is really good also I'm gonna mute um if you want to just entertain everyone
just for about three minutes I'll be right back I just have to run and do
something and I can't do it while I'm on okay gotcha be right back
all righty well that's interesting the upcoming tell you I'm curious just as
we're sitting here waiting I'm gonna throw some tunes in and be right with
you already and okay we're back there we go yeah it wasn't so bad so okay so so
yeah these things are of interest to me personally because I've been looking at
the prophetic aspect of this only because dividing any any information into
category right like this is a body of knowledge doesn't matter what it is
this is about this this is about that you know like a car manual you know this is
about the electrical system this is the engine this is the interior right all
right so when I started looking at the all of the ancient texts they all had
divisions they had history geography prophecy so on and so forth but the what
separates the scripture what's called the Bible and I don't mean and the
reason I use the Bible is because the audience understands what I mean by
that you know it hasn't been given all the caveats and the and the footnotes on
that already when you do a study on that what you will discover it is first-class
information but it is also timed temporal in many places it tells you
when you get to a certain time period then you know there'll be more
understanding on these matters so what's exciting about this time period is that
we are in that time period where these matters were to be understood so I think
there's much work to be done on that at least sonically in the near future but
at the same time here's the thing and I and I always tell people this there's an
old ghetto term yo how you living you know I mean like when someone's doing
something real crappy oh how you living you know you got a big tear in your couch
and your hole in your shoes and you don't know how to eat you know what I
mean how you know how can you live like that so how are you here's the here's the
thing I give the analogy if you're gonna go approach a king or something and
there's someone knocks on the door say Bruce we're gonna go see let's say the
president of a country and you're standing there in a holy t-shirt sweat
pants and flip-flops like oh let's go no you're probably like well we have to put
on you know our best definitely our cleanest dirty shirt or something right
our best clothing so if you're going to approach a body of information that
comes from the supreme being of the universe you think you're just gonna
eat whatever sleep whatever think whatever act whatever and you're gonna
get it nope I'm gonna have to put your discipline your whole you have to your
whole beam has to be within that has to and there's no margin of error and some
people will be able to achieve more than you know a higher quality of it but the
thing is are you striving to make it the best with what he's giving you what
you have is the point you see it's like when you go to McDonald's I remember
traveling the only thing was fast food and all that well the thing is you don't
eat what their places are known for you try to make the best possible choice you
know after a while I'd go and order let's say a particular sandwich and I
say we'll hold the meat patty just leave the lettuce the onions tomato and mayo
you're right and they're like no we can't do that we can't do that we don't
yeah so like I will just give me the patty and I toss it out you know if I
feel like someone's got a dog you know at the window I'll just give him a mask
and I keep the dog and he's like oh yeah you know or it's like the old Jack
Nicholson movies I want toast we don't serve toast so let me give me a tuna
fish sandwich on toast we can do that and he says but hold the tuna fish what
do you want me to do waitress right so but the waitress says well what do you
want me to do with the tuna fish and she goes put it between your legs I don't
care Jack Nicholson way you know that old Jersey psychopathic look that he
gives so yeah so there's many aspects to this make your best choices I mean
there's past couple of days I've been hitting up the chat with food choices
and all that that yeah I think would be a good schedule event I was thinking of
taking some notes and going down through that I'm not gonna do I think I'm just
going to ad-lib it or just go what runs off the top of the mind to a fine art
oh yeah I believe I do a certain point the best way to do it is to do a
syllabus sit down and say okay for you know for these few hours we're going to
talk about you know food selection you know based on season market
availability and basic preparation and you know basic recipes and then get into
more of the cultural aspect of food preparation which is actual recipes
themselves you know like hummus for example you know or hummus like they say
right what is that well it's mashed chickpeas lemon juice garlic and you
know sesame butter or tahina right tahini it's a delicious dip you know or
many many other that's just giving that one specific example or how to make
basic bread or how to do you know and and then focus around the find the best
of each culture right mm-hmm and and then why you know how to do proper slow
pot cooking how to really fry how to really and then that's another part of
it those are the more final detail you're celebrating a culture's history of fine
preparation of their delicacies yeah or their way of life you know like for
example yes you know what's interesting every culture has a handheld food what
we call a sandwich type thing yes like a roll or a piece you know you know
what's what's a hot dog or a hamburger or sandwich it's a roll with yeah you
know every culture has some kind of product around it yeah every culture has
something like that you know every culture has some kind of a hot pot soup
stew every culture has you see everyone's got some kind of you know your
way of preparing a certain type of genre of food you know bring that when
you bring that up I remember this Hmong lady who lived downstairs downstairs
for me and she made this it was like a dip and it had carrots and all and I'm
telling you you you would have died you're the taste buds were dancing with
the light it's the best way that I can I can I can put a minute well there's a
dip in certain a Punjab cultures and other cultures they make a dip a very
sweet pistachio I believe and carrot it's mostly sugar and you'll see it in
the middle of this of the plate so if you eat food that's too hot you take a
piece of that and it calms the heat down you know meaning not in temperature hot
but spicy hot spring oh I'm just thinking about it brings a joyful smile
well here's the irony of again which country in the world is known for having
20 feet of topsoil for thousands if not millions of acres the u.s. which country
has by hands down the most unhealthy and worst fed population in the world u.s.
most ill-prepared food I told you I was out in parts like New Mexico Colorado
Texas even Iowa place that I was sick staying with people eating what just for
two days what they ate I'm like you got to be joking
stream beans out of a can you know I mean everything was either canned or
frozen or just overcooked or cooked with a timer and there was no love in the
food and I don't mean everyone but everyone I stayed with for sure but
not even that it was you know that they have a saying in America like grandma
used to make I've been to many people's homes grandma's cooking tonight she's
cooking all day the food was crap not once but twice but every time as a Greek
get you pick yeah I like Greek you're too picky and I'm like yeah I mean like
I'd rather pick my nose and eat your food and it was it was yeah so that's
why I always tell people I always preferred living by the East Coast or
the West Coast because you had a good influx of Mediterranean and Asian
cultures you know if you go like in New York mass you know you have European
you know the immigrants you know great in California but once you go Midwest
forget it I mean yeah you go to places like in Kansas State of Kansas and I
would have great steaks you know and they love you know unclean foods but
that's it I mean so what and they're not mindful so the Americans are screwed that
way it's an interesting thing again about Americans I was discussing something you
know there's always a lot of you think there's some kind of God over the
agricultural market in this oh yeah but this is what it is you think you could
wipe out nearly an entire race of people and go unscathed you let you know
that so what I mean by that is I was talking about the someone's about the
controversy about the Holocaust and the Holocaust Museum with the Jews in
Europe no but I said well the Native Americans got it worse than them and
where's their Holocaust Museum right right much worse I think what is it only
one percent cruel oh yeah only one or the status around one or two percent of
surviving in Native Americans are pure blood yeah they're all mixed so they're
really been eliminated either from anyway so where's their Holocaust Museum
you know their their language is declining more and more every time so
yeah and this is just a point I mean you know I'm not focused on that whether
they get one or not at this point it doesn't matter it's all they have to
speak up for it yeah no big can be mature but what I mean is is the
Americans have said that yeah that's fine but no because it could materialize
is what I mean by that I mean it's sarcastic your con right I mean they're
trying to build that large what is it crazy horse monument you know it's good
twice yeah much more Dakotas so mm-hmm yeah but there's a yeah this is not a
rent this is pretty accurate Americans have the worst food and the worst
mindset on food generally speaking than anyone else in the world
we're not close to the British they are so but you know the British here's the
thing they're smaller and they have been overrun by foreigners for so many
years you know what is the if you go to England right now or foodie magazines
what is the national dish of England chicken tiki marcella you know some
chickens in my culture yeah so at least they put yeah but there you know they're
terrible also from an extent where you let's say you go to a place like New
York or California looking around for restaurants we're gonna see an English
food restaurant very rare yeah maybe maybe they'll do like a mock-up of an
English pub or something but you know heaven help you if you have to eat what
they eat you know you're eating fish and chips and well the minute you try to
make it mass anything it's already moving into some form of death yeah and
here's the thing also just to cover it myself again not really but cover but
I've always been saying that's white people food and no one ever has come
back to say that sounds racist because they know what I mean by that right it's
not racist you know I mean that could be could be any registry white people food
is white people food is the if you ever watched what they did to the food in
America from the 1930s on and it peaked around the 1970s all the convenience
foods you know you know what I mean right yeah it peaked around the 70s and
in the 80s it got more elaborate meaning in the 80s and they started freezing
croissants and things like that you know do you remember the corner do you
remember the corner stores mm-hmm yeah there well what stores now yeah right
and but the corner stores always had beautiful fresh everything you know you
know but here's the point and product coming in here and there but here's the
point even back then no matter how good the ingredients were these people didn't
know how to prepare it well at all I'm sorry right oh yeah I mean I've actually
won I was in a suburban place years ago I was doing an excursion staying with
some people I actually won an apple pie contest against a bunch of grandmas in
town Oh got the blue ribbon yeah oh and I'm not I'm not a baker so so so much
how grandma used to make you tell me grandma's cooking I'm going the other
way I'd rather eat at McDonald's because she don't know I mean unless she's from
Asia or Europe I'm sorry I mean I sound a little harsh and yeah so I mean now
you're getting into great-grandma territory and seeing if you can run
against them which were truly from the other side someone put in here ever
notice how people who eat a lot of fast-food start smelling like the food
you actually smell like all the food that you eat for example I've spoken to
military people when they go to places like Korea they can't stand being the
public spaces because they smell this fishy garlic smell and they can't they
can't smell stand the smell of the Americans because they have this bovine
fecal smell now what happens is when they stay there after a while and they
come here to America their family complains that they smell like garlic and
fish through their coming through their skin for a couple of weeks in our days
you see right so yeah gotta go somewhere
interesting that we would give it off you know it as we induce it into
ourselves and then it's just kind of lightly eliminated in a oxygen or sweat
or whatever oh yeah yeah 20 feet of topsoil yeah that's that's in initially
when they started doing the westward movement anymore you know the way we're
no no it was established to be around that much because they went out they
were doing the westward movement and they needed shelters you know they said
we're gonna settle here make a farm so they kept digging down looking for mud
to make clay brick and stuff and I couldn't find it so that's why when you
look at the old prairie dwellings are made of peat they had to make their
dwellings out of peat because they they kept digging and digging and digging and
digging and all they found was peat and topsoil so like shit we got to build our
abode out of that and he'd go look online peat houses as in moss right in
the Midwest back in the 19th century until they had a no you know established
enough of an area found maybe a an area where they could get some building
materials you know mm-hmm so yeah we covered just a few things and I just want
to say there's nothing secular you know you've heard the term don't listen to
what they say watch what they do you know right so ask people's experiences
but the thing is people are so dumbed up and so removed from reality even when
they're being tortured by a legal someone in the legal society or the
medical society they still think it's for their own good right so it's a single
masochist yeah they think it's fine you know I've seen been on this planet for
more than half a century now and I've seen Oh several dozen people deliberately
killed by doctors right yeah I mean deliberately on both sides and you know
and I watch it and it's a sick form of entertainment because I can't take it
seriously because you can't get involved it's like a pimp eating a pimp
beating up his girl you can't get involved in that fight because they're
both gonna turn up and I've seen that no so it's a really really sad thing you
when I hear about people going to the medical technicians or things it's a
snuff film in slow motion the same with the legal people so boy there was a
vision mm-hmm yeah yeah but anyway that's just this is believe it or not
with all this this crap that's going on now it's going to be viewed in a better
perspective much later when the gods put set things straight but the thing I
wanted to say about don't listen to what they say watch what they do and someone
put you will know them by their fruits one of the things that I've always tried
to do whenever especially I have a longer presence than just passing
through discussing things I always like to certain tidbits on how people can
make their lives better their brain whether it's just simple water
preparation or how to prepare a meal or ask a particular thing that might lead
to a better result or a better thought you see so so you actually have
something usable I like to be a sonic Swiss Army knife you know yes yes yeah
and at least leave people not just empty words development certainly gives you a
new perspective on things well it's it's it's good to read it on many of the
things I've noticed that it's it's a I think it's a renewed perspective yeah
because I started things I like to bring up give you an example we used to do
these Skype calls you know I used to have 10-15 people years ago and we used to be
on for hours sometimes we'd leave it on for 14 hours as a matter of fact there
was one that's left on perpetually right all you need is a one all you need is
the host to have a microphone and a camera or whatever hooked on to a
computer and he could go to you leave and leave it on anyone that's brought in
can be on so anyway used to be this guy coming on and he was dealing with you
know like venture capitalists inventors new ideas and things like that he would
come on and pontificate for minutes or half hour about this new thing and and
I'm like well wait a second here comes this guy again telling us about like a
new invention or a new appliance or new not appliance house appliance but
something that's going to you know make things easier or it's you know an
invention you know a doohickey or a gimmick or is something useful and I
said wait a second you know I've been listening to you for a while now and
everything that you're saying I'm gonna ask you can I go get that like oh no no
you can't get it it's only done by the government it's very expensive only this
one so what good is it what good is it if I can't yeah if I can't just go down to
the hardware store like 50 bucks get all the parts go out in the backyard
beat on it and make it in an hour or two or a day I don't want to know what why
are you telling me you know it sounds like it sounds like a mild pranking you
know just tell me what I can go and build right now and do whether it's the
best is stuff you have access to in your own immediate surroundings or even in
the bin you know yeah you know but none of this stuff so it's like ah and this
is what you're getting in your science by the way you know when you look at
science articles on the internet nanotechnology nothing behind it yeah
nothing you could do anything and you know it's interesting it shows you how
much pranking and how stupid people are they'll do these I've hyped up articles
and it's come this comes as new technological advancement it comes out
MIT and they show you like these 18 year olds in MIT doing it it's a prank you
never gonna that's not even real you know so it's it's it's just yeah it's
just bizarre so here's the thing if you're listening to my voice and you are
on this planet I really feel sorry for you as I do for anyone that's ever
passed through here but that's on a big cosmic level so it doesn't mean you need
to be leave live a sorry ass life and pathetic aspect of what is going around
you you can I wouldn't say rise above it because the last thing you want to do is
experience tall poppy syndrome in other words that means the nail that
sticks out gets hammered down right just like people say you got to stand up for
your rights I said that's fine but when they're fixing on busting people it
might be best for you to just sit down that day right I want to get out of the
way yeah mm-hmm so what does everyone have in common other you know they all
want I could use the different words here lasciviously or whatever but you
eat sleep you know go to the bathroom wash you know you make you know all
kinds of things during the day that might be part of your vocation or or what
you like to do and how do you make each one you know everyone shares those
things in common right unless you're you know paraplegic that's that's a very
small you know you have no functions yeah then that's a very small I'm
addressing those that are mobile and active what what do you have access to
and keep that in in perspective that you know you can make that immediately
better you know I used to for example discuss even what they call driving you
know I used to on Skype I told people listen when you're driving you on a
curved road do this when you adjust the seat you put make sure it's in this
position when you're accelerating and through it when you're going through a
turn this is how you do it and I've had everyone that was active in that come
back to me and say Greek I didn't think I'd get driving lessons over Skype but
all the techniques that you told me worked you see very simple because they
already had a car they were gonna drive anyway right right so and I learned this
from you know taking you know official or formal instructions on doing race car
driving and other things so and which is very scary because when I experienced
that I said wait a second these things that you're learning here should be
taught to everyone and these people out here driving don't know any of this that
makes them potentially very dangerous so I said well let me just try to impart
these skills to anyone just verbally you know so anything that's just an
example just sharing so you can make it a little bit better and of course find
your opiate you know the thing that numbs you out from all the
ridiculousness that's going on because I think some people have gotten fair
response that they've tried to approach others in any field and they don't want
to hear it that's the common thing and it's a very very very very very very to
the 10th power rare bird to find someone that is willing to listen and
it's even rarer for them to understand it and it's even more rare for them to
apply it yes and it's all very simple and whether I'm the only one saying
things the way they am right now I appear it appears that I am but I'd like
to see this type of more of this type of mindset being available to more people
just so you know the experience on this rock right now is just a little bit
better right better shoes make better walking right so that's pretty much it
and yeah so I mean that's uh I mean there's much much more to go and much
more to say we've been on for about an hour what do you think over 13 at the
moment okay so they got a little maybe they got
something a little bit more on the sonic mm-hmm yes so with some repetition so
let's just keep this unscheduled regular irregularity we'll see how things go
maybe yeah maybe in the near future there will be some investment on the
uncommon site and maybe something more formal but this seems to be trudging
along I did a little bit just to share some personal thoughts with everyone I
did a little bit of thinking that's it well you know stop being such a lazy
ass go ahead spend a couple of days on the uncommon site start you know some
more formal scheduling do you know various you know ways where people can
access maybe do videos you know bill I was building all this in my head and I'm
like what there's only like five people listen to this and apply it right
successfully right so it's not necessary I mean if you look on the internet you
know that you it's it's actually occasionally I'll do that I don't mean
need to mention names but in the alternative media and in the mainstream
media you have the big mainstream concerns right that you you know you look
up you know what right news or and the alternative and and and what's more
pathetic is the alternative feature yes and they're just as dumb and wasteful and
ignorant and just you just I listened to this past couple of weeks a little by
little I just leave it on the back while I'm beating on stuff and making
spark plugs and things I'm actually making a set of spark plugs I'm going to
be sending as a prototype for someone to work they're working there's silver
material in them so so I'm listening to the stuff on the internet and I'm like
you know I listened to this particular show for an hour you know someone did a
production and what did I get out of it nothing if you know what it well how
does it help me how can you know nothing I mean well oh yeah right you
know okay so this person said this but in you know I'm like what is wrong with
you people you know well I know it's about the same as the food you eat it and
you're still filled with emptiness you have no nutrition God knows what it does to
your God knows what it's doing otherwise internally can't be pretty I'm trying to
keep the criticism anonymous because I could start naming names of this guy
that guy that girl whatever certainly but it doesn't matter because it's all
of them they're all like that I'm not gonna sit and rain 25 million or 1
billion things on the internet it's all junk out there and there's a lot of good
corn but it's it's it's inside of poop and when is there going to be a more
sequestered you know just good corn somewhere so I don't know I don't think
that's ever really going to happen believe it or not but I think that I
think that when you when anyone does get the opportunity to be able to convey and
impart something that makes what someone is doing better immediately with what
they have available to them that's the ticket so with that set up you guys got
at least the nickels worth this time again and thanks thank you yes you're
welcome thanks for archiving this and we'll do it again soon
yes maybe just to let everyone know according to Sam his schedule is he's
off on what they call Tuesdays somewhere in Europe so maybe we'll get a lot of
good feedback because he's able to sit there like a little brat even though you
know he's pretty good guy and he's very well I call him a brat because a brat
gets focused on one thing and in it in it it doesn't seem like there's a lot of
leeway and that's good he's a good gent I like the fella yeah he brings a lot to
the table that's right that's right and it's in a brat like way which is
necessary because when you focus like that like he likes to focus on a theme
in a subject it gets it gets a lot done on that subject where it's in yes right
where myself you know I'm able to do this parallel thinking of so many things
at the same time and see the interconnectedness of these things and I
can't say everything at the same time so a lot you know so it's good to just
abandon most of the things that I the way I personally work and focus on the
way someone else would like things focused on and that's where Sam comes in
on that yes so that would be in what they call Tuesdays so if that could and
that happens to be the same day this is just conveniently placed for me that I'm
I'm well and can do such thing during the work week and so that's all good
that's all good yeah we'll see so that was just a real reference on these
irregular regular irregularities that happen exactly Sonic events correct so
okay so with that said hope you guys got at least a nickel's worth whatever the
exchange rate is wherever and oh by the way some people have been asking me
about a cryptocurrency anything like that and you know that's within this
sphere of Greek speak there's no reason to ask what I think of cryptocurrency
simply because the question to ask the person who's asking that question is
what is it lawful money and the answer to that is well it's right it's not so
it doesn't matter so it doesn't matter if it's dog poo or pig poo or cow poo
guess what it's still poo and believe it or not a certain amount of pig well
yeah and certain poo does fetch on the market you know for compost but others is
reviled and yeah so yeah just stuff to think about mindset folks all right well
be well thanks again Bruce yes you take care yes we will you take care now