Okay, so let's see.
Do you have Sam's contact?
Drag him back in or just go on.
I think he was still hooked.
Oh no, he is parted.
Okay.
Let's see if we can get him in here.
Let me bring him in.
Yeah, I just tried dragging him in.
I had a request from someone who wanted to call in and I mentioned Skype.
Oh my, I don't have Sam in my contact.
Oh, there he is.
Okay.
Got him?
Alrighty.
Hey Sam.
Hello.
So you had somebody in your contacts you say are Greek?
No, no.
I had a few people message that, actually one specifically a while back that wanted to call in.
Here's the interesting commentary on that also.
Most people have smart phones and if you have one, you can always download Skype and use that.
Now we have no preference for it.
You know, here's the interesting thing.
How many times do you hear about all these people complaining about the establishment and yet they pride themselves through their social media?
You know, you ever notice that?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, they'll get me on Twitter or Fecesbook or whatever, you know, and these are the people that are against talking New World Order, all this crap how, you know, we're being subjugated somehow.
Right, right.
You know, yeah, talk about morons, right?
I mean, anyway.
Yeah, yeah.
So who are you going to call in?
I ought to consider setting up on this end and get a telephone number hooked on Skype.
It isn't that costly.
Very simple to do.
Yeah, someone wanted to call in and join us, Sam, but they haven't.
So it's not much of an effort there because I'm presuming that person has a smart phone.
See, I don't have a smart phone.
I had one for a short time and I realized it was too subjective.
Like you can't use it without being subject to a certain mindset, believe it or not.
And if you're used to it, more power to you, but I can't get used to crap like that.
It's just like I can't get used to emotional garbage.
You ever get in a situation with someone and they're telling you it's all feeling, feeling, feeling, you don't get any background or anything that you could reference?
It's just like, you know, walk away, go see a shrink, go take some pills, you know?
So, I, I, me, me.
Yeah, they can't think beyond, yeah, yeah.
And also, don't be fooled, there's a lot of training that has been done by the establishment through academia.
So you, that's why you have dictionaries, how to pronounce words.
They don't know what any of the words mean.
But just to pronounce them, and they speak very, they sound smart.
You know, how many times I've heard a lot of morons say, oh, this person's smart.
I'm like, no, they sound smart.
There's a big difference.
You know, so they're presented very well.
It's just stupidity.
It's sad, but it's not sad.
I mean, the sadness has prevailed for thousands of years, but you still have wonderful access to wonderful things.
Let me give you an example.
I got, you know, the owners of a bakery, a high-end bakery that's gluten free, right, which is a joke, right?
And we got a box of cookies, and these cookies are like a dollar something each.
They're small cookies, and there's like 20-some-odd cookies in this little box.
All different flavors, very well prepared.
But there are people that still believe in that.
They don't even know what gluten is, first of all.
You know, it's like an elastic fiber in grain, right, in wheat.
And these idiots have told them, you know, the reason, they're the people that have, they bought into the wheat allergies.
It's a big thing.
Remember, it used to be other things before that?
Oh, yeah.
And no one is raising their hand and saying, could it be that the quality of the food is so low now that they can't acknowledge it, so they have to tell you it's a specific part of the food that's making you sick only?
I mean, this is how stupid people are.
Like, I think someone put a song in the people or shit.
They really are.
And then, by the way, just to bring it up even further, there's verses in scripture that talks about their bodies lying like shit, dung.
And when you see destruction happening, don't even pray for them.
How many times do you hear these morons saying pray for these people?
Like, why?
You know, why?
You know?
So anyway, that's not being mean-spirited or anything like that.
That's just actually being real about what's going on.
I mean, have you ever heard me discuss that there shouldn't be any organic food available?
Yeah, how that makes sense.
What kind of a sick society at large would accept that some of the food is being intentionally toxified and the other one is not, and you have to pay a premium for the one that's not?
What kind of a sick – well, I'll tell you.
Well, yeah, I don't have to tell you.
Yeah, just look around you.
The chances of anyone listening to my voice running into anyone that is of quality is so slim, you see?
Yeah.
This is the reality, but no one wants reality.
They just want to feel good about something.
Yeah, you want to feel good, just touch yourself.
Reach down there, grab it, and whatever, whatever you've got to do to make yourself feel better, because that's all you've got.
So, anyway, what else are we going to talk about?
Well, we were on the subject of Judas.
What I was saying was that I don't – I mean, there's nothing in the text that indicates that he's not acting of his own self-government other than that little possession bit, and I'm wondering how could he fulfill the prophecies about his betrayal unless he acted on his own free will?
To say that Satan made him do it in a literal sense and not even in this sort of Judeo-Christian figurative sense, I feel like that's really – I don't want to say underhanded, because it's not my place to have any which way opinion about it, but I'm trying to understand why the guy isn't doing it on his own then.
Well, there's several layers to that, but also if you remember in the piss-poor text that we get, that Christ basically addresses Satan to go do what he has to do.
Was it directed to Satan?
I don't know if it was Satan or Judas.
Have you ever heard me say that the rest of the entire Bible explains the Book of Revelation versus the other way around?
The entire Bible, yeah, I've heard you say that.
Because the Book of Revelation has primacy based on the first verse, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You ever notice how there's an outcry of certain beings in the Book of Revelation against those doing bad?
You ever notice how there's an outcry against Sodom and Gomorrah, remember?
You see how these things come up in Genesis that seem to have been directly taken out of Revelation?
I'm not suggesting anyone go read the Book of Revelation for the simple reason – I'm not saying don't read the Book of Revelation.
I'm not suggesting you read it, and the answer to that is why?
Because you're not going to understand anything in it.
Everyone?
No, not everyone, but just about everyone, no, you won't understand it.
I've not found anything that's true and correct on the rectangle about the Book of Revelation yet.
Other than, you know, the, or whatever.
I think you're right, it is Satan that he talks to, which is interesting.
Well, the interesting part, you know what the real interesting part is, that I strongly presume, if not more than that even, in the next seven years we might even have a real, in other words, a more factual text of what was memorialized in the New Testament.
Yeah, that might very well be so.
But what's it, I mean, usually what you find is that demon possession takes place in conjunction with some kind of physical trauma that gives some kind of a gateway of some sort.
Yeah, that's just typical.
But here, we're not seeing that with Judah at all.
He just, you know, dips his, what's the bread thing?
He puts his hand in the bread basket to pull out bread and then Satan enters into him.
Unleavened bread, yeah.
It's not like, you know what, I still have to interject, Sam.
Most people have the visuals from that, who's the guy who painted the Last Supper?
I forget the dude.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, I had, there was one of these alternative media guys, quite a few years ago, he got me on Skype.
He was doing this really long video to explain astrotheology on that painting of Da Vinci.
And I let him talk and talk and talk, and I said, he's been talking for 45 minutes, and I'm going to interject something.
I said, dude, you know, there is no Last Supper in the Bible, right?
You know, none of that stuff is biblical.
It's made up.
It's Christian, right?
He's like, oh, but I made the video already.
These are the people that you guys are looking to for information.
Oh, boy.
None of it is, yeah, so.
Yeah, it's quite interesting.
That was the Passach that they were doing, and it was a very interrupted way.
You know, the Passach is interruptive, you know, right?
You know what I mean?
Right?
So there's two levels to it.
For example, one level is, well, the bread is unleavened because they were ready to leave Egypt.
They didn't have time.
But the other thing is, doesn't leaven represent falling short or sin?
I don't even like to use the word sin because people don't even know what it means.
Missing the mark, right?
Okay, so which one is it?
Well, it's both.
Did Satan possess?
In other words, was Satan intervening in this situation for something to be done because of just that?
Or was it meant to go that way?
Remember, Abraham told his son on the way, the three-day walk to the sacrificial, right, with Abraham and Isaac.
It took him three days to get there.
Remember, he said, where's the site?
He says, well, you said the Elohim will provide one for us.
Remember?
The lamb for us, right?
Right?
Okay, so are we able to put all this together?
Some of it, for sure.
Other things are a bit harder.
Or it takes a bit more time.
Well, because, you know, here's the thing.
Most people have the desire to get as much detail about something that they're interested in as possible, right?
If you're interested in something, you want as much detail as you can get, humanly possible, let's say.
You know, not without the level of pain, but, you know.
And then there's other aspects of human desire to want to know about things that are important.
And that's kind of a joke, because if you look at most people that have careers, ask them about what their career or their profession is based on, they know very little.
So, but anyway, for let's say rational humans, which there's only a handful left on the planet, if you want to know more about something, the way you know more about it is by gleaning more detail.
And what I would broach to say to anyone is that the detail is there, it's just not in the way that you're used to seeing it.
Does that help?
Yeah.
But I mean, once you abandon that sort of viewpoint, you're on a completely different endeavor altogether anyway, so.
Well, that's with anything.
Once you find out anything about any subject, who are you going to go tell it to?
Look, if you really learn about electricity, you think you're going to go to some physics lab, even CERN, and talk to them about it?
Those guys are idiots.
You're finished.
You're stuck.
It doesn't matter what subject it is.
Once you start learning how the human body works, you think you're going to go talk to a medical technician?
You've got to be out of your mind.
No way.
So this is basically the discussions that we've been having, and 99% of Greek speak is a deep personal message for people to kind of say, hey, look, this is something you could prove on your own, any subject.
But you're kind of on your own with it, so make the best of it.
Can you imagine going into a church, right?
Let me give you an example.
Like I think the last sonic event we did, I brought up there's a ridiculous Bible museum.
They opened in Washington, D.C., some billionaire idiot, right?
How come he didn't invite the pope?
Well, two reasons.
One, because that whole Christian religion is so divided.
The other reason is the pope has nothing to do with the Bible, right?
And the Bible museum has nothing to do with the Bible.
It has to do with the American versions and the Gutenberg press.
Do you see how many levels of ridiculousness are here through the entire thing?
And he invested millions.
It doesn't matter.
Of credits, yeah.
Great, great.
Well, that's what I said earlier.
If you come out with a way to make a motor, which is not difficult to do, that just perpetually runs, not perpetually because there are other systems that break down within it, you're in big trouble.
If you figure out how the body works and you go around getting people out of ICU in 24 hours, you're in big trouble.
You see?
If you take cars and make them run pollution-free, you're in big trouble.
All the things that all these idiots on this planet are saying that they want with one side of their mouth, the other side of their mouth, they're ready to punish you for doing it.
That's called schizophrenia, isn't it?
Yes.
Torn mind.
Dual-minded.
Yeah.
So, one.
Go ahead.
No, when you read about all the destruction that's going to be brought on mankind because there's no other way to deal with mankind, the gods are, who's doing all that destruction?
The good guys or the bad guys?
Good guys.
Yeah.
And you're stuck down here with these idiots.
Yes, the most powerful guys.
Look, right now, if you get entangled in the legal society, they don't care about law.
They basically tell you, we have the guns, so we got you.
Right?
But I'll tell you what, the most powerful guys in the other realm does care about the law and does care about the right thing.
They're not some cult like you have over here.
You know what I mean?
I think it's interesting that what we're seeing is that it's lawful to make somebody do something that they don't want to do by putting another spirit into them and taking away their free will.
In order for something to be accomplished, yes.
Because that comes up constantly about the something needing to be accomplished.
Are you familiar with that in what they call the New Testament narrative?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
And why was it so important?
Do you know that there's an archetype to it in the lamp stand?
It was so important that it was done within that time period.
Right?
Because it's the center.
Number four.
And it's also important because we have, through agency and through unity, you know, like the concept of monotheism is ridiculous because that means there's only one God.
You could say ikhad or enatheism, which is ikhad means one, or enatheism, which means you only believe or you only have faith in one God.
Right?
So this is the manifestation of that coming on Earth.
He's taking a physical human body for this purpose, you know, of showing that to mankind what happens after you die.
That was the purpose, the sole purpose of the Christ coming here, by the way, as he did.
And, of course, when you're here doing that, you're going to do all the other things that were recorded.
And the whole thing is done in what?
Secret.
And it's a secret today.
And you have people, you have a billion plus people that are so sick and bizarre to say that they believe in a particular figure like that and they know nothing about it, you know, the situation or the figure themselves.
So anyway, you're on a planet with seven and a half, almost eight billion now, bizarre and sick individuals, minus a very tiny, tiny portion that could easily be gleaned and rendered as not being a part of that mentality.
So connected to what you said before about there being chaos on the other side, Christianity does sort of make the story of scripture all about individual self exceptionalism and, you know, the tribe of that religion.
But when you start to look at certain things about the Elohim and their society, certain things get uncovered that are interesting.
So in Revelation 12, there's this verse that talks about what's going on as far as the great dragon getting thrown out and such and the great dragon was thrown out that serpent of old called the devil and Satan who leaves all the world astray.
He was thrown to the earth and his messengers were thrown out with him and I heard a loud voice in heaven saying now have come the deliverance and the power and the reign of our Elohim and the authority of his Messiah for the accuser of our brothers who accused them before our Elohim day and night has been thrown out.
So often at times this is used to explain some kind of tribulation of the church, blah, blah, blah.
Satan was accusing the saints, yada, yada, assembly.
Yeah, right.
No circus in there.
Yeah, good.
But since we know that human spirits are disanimated when they die, the voice from heaven, which is that of an Elohim, it's not a human being because there are no human beings in heaven.
So the brethren that Satan has been accusing are not human beings at all.
There are other Elohim.
Yeah, I prefer not to get into the details of Revelation publicly at the moment.
I'll be glad to do that with you in the future in private, not now in the future, maybe a year or two from now if I'm still around for that.
Itchy.
It's an interesting thing for other people to think about.
He's accusing other Elohim, which means that they are fighting.
Here's an interesting thing that I've noticed, that just because someone looks adult doesn't mean that they necessarily are.
And one thing you'll find out when you're an adult raising children, I have not, but I should say that anyone could find this out, it's pretty obvious, is that one of the things that you always tell the immature is you're going to have to wait a few years for that.
That comes all the time, doesn't it?
Daddy, I want to ride a fire truck, I want to drive a car.
Well, you're going to have to wait a few years for that one.
And how fast do those years go by when you're in an immature mind state?
Really fast or really slow?
Actually, when you're younger, time seems to go by much slower, doesn't it, than when you're older?
And when you're older, like now I've been a few years past half a century, and I've realized that I wouldn't say the years go by like months or weeks or anything, but 15 years has gone by so fast, it went by only like a few seasons.
I can't say it was like weeks or months, because obviously I can count the months in between, there are many.
But it seems only like a few seasons, not many years.
So as you get older, what happens is you're no longer impressed by things.
See, when you're younger, time seems to go by slower, because you're still impressionable.
You're recording all of these events that are happening around you, and you're rationalizing them.
When you get older, you don't have to re-rationalize everything so much.
It depends on what you're trying to rationalize.
Because I've suggested that past the age of 12, most people are already completely shut down and fully indoctrinated, like automatons within the society.
They've even set up a subculture now, since maybe 50 or 60 years ago, maybe 50, I should say.
There is a subculture now set up within the culture called the kids' culture.
They have their own TV, their own movies, their own clothing, their own food, their own drink, their own schools.
Have you heard of that, Bruce, the kids' stuff?
Oh, yeah.
I remember when it started.
Yeah, in the 70s, I think.
Oh, I think, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, maybe late.
There was a little bit of that in the 50s, but I didn't really have that growing up, and I don't think you did.
No, no, no, no.
It's a subculture.
Late 60s, maybe?
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a subculture.
Like, when did McDonald's have their Happy Meals come out, right?
In the same run, Ronald McDonald really started coming and taking more precedence.
Yeah, and Sesame Street.
Yes.
Sesame Street and all that stuff.
The whole world is on.
So I'll tell you that right now, the subcultures are a big aspect.
For example, if you look at what's called social media, those are all subcultures, but are they really?
I mean, I don't think you're going to be counted as a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant here in the near future unless you have a social media account.
It's very possible.
Very, very possible.
Yeah, these are all subcultures.
So the subculture now, it's kind of like where the child becomes the parent.
Like Monsanto was from DuPont, and Monsanto is bigger than DuPont now.
So everything made was good, but now that everything that exists seems to be embarked with evil.
So there's more evil than good, right?
And in order to pass off evil, it has to appear as good, right?
Because like counterfeit money, you can't just get a crayon and write it on a paper towel.
They go through great pains and efforts to make something that's fake look like a fake Rolex or a fake Gucci bag, right?
Yeah, the manufacturer of these fake items go through great efforts, like the news, right?
The university, fake education.
It's the same buildings, but now all of a sudden it's all fake stuff.
I had a college professor once in a physics lab tell me there's no such thing as energy, it's electrons moving down the wire.
Yeah, this is pranking on a major, major level.
You know, on the last Sonic event, from what I remember, Sam, in closing, I think I was bringing up the book of Genesis.
And as time goes on, not out of desire, but just out of rhetorically saying it, I don't think I'm the one to get into explaining scripture on a consistent basis, even though people have that interest, I'll do it.
But I think what my forte is explaining on how people are being pranked and how to see through the cosmic censorship.
Not eliminate the cosmic censorship and being censorship free, but in essence the censorship as a fog.
You know, like navigating maritime vessels put a lot of effort into navigating the fog, don't they?
They have radar, fog lamps, lights, thorns, and they're aware of meteorological effects and things.
And that doesn't apply, because if I was in that situation, I could clear the fog using what I know about weather control.
But I'm just putting that in as a footnote, because I've had many people, even Ocelli before, who said, so Greek, you're not censored?
I mean, you know, it's like, oh boy, you know, how do you answer that, you know?
Is anybody home?
But anyway, the thing is, if you remember Bruce on the last, I don't know if I'm really the one to explain, I mean, doing the Genesis talks and all that and the biblical talks is fine.
And that is the subject, biblical stuff is really what I think about mostly.
But I don't really think I'm the one to go forward explaining that stuff.
Someone else has to rise to that occasion.
Or people can just study it themselves.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
You know, here's the interesting thing, thanks for saying that.
If you just clear the mind, and I've said this emphatically many times already, there is nothing that you know about anything biblical that you could bring to the text that will help you directly, only indirectly.
If you just approach the biblical text as any literary work that you would be quizzed on, tested on, or known for proficiency on, you'll get more than you've expected out of it, just by reading it.
But the minute you open up Exodus and say, oh, I saw this part in the movie with Cecil B.
DeMille, no, you just screwed yourself.
See?
Yeah.
And you have to read it several times, because there's clues that are given.
There's things that are seemingly open-ended that are tied and closed in other places.
So you're going to have to go through it once, just like when you download a computer program.
You download it, then you use it.
So you're going to have to download it by being familiar, reading it through.
And then you'll get to certain parts and say, oh, I see where these things need to be pieced together.
Eventually you'll see why it was done that way.
And then I also give the metaphor.
There used to be – well, for example, if you go – I use the metaphor of the waiting room, right?
And when you ever notice people in a waiting room, when they sit around and read magazines, they flip back to the front naturally?
They flip from the back to the front, yeah?
Now, I'm wondering in countries where they read from right to left, where the back would be the front, do they flip from the front to the back, from the left to the right?
I've never investigated that.
That might be interesting to know.
Yeah.
But in this case, that's a good advice.
Also, given the fact that Satan is shown to be an accuser not just here but on the other side, and probably primarily on the other side, that very much does line him up with the attorney function that we see paralleled in the legal society, if he spends his time calling out people for stuff that they may or may not have done.
Right, and using some lawful precedent, Scripture, and putting them in a situation where they have to get out of using some kind of tactic.
That's why the redemption is an important thing, where you don't have to go through that tactical mess.
Because literally, if you follow the text, we are being ransomed and redeemed.
Now, if you weren't held hostage or taken possession or ownership over by another, why would that be necessary?
I just want to throw this in.
Anyone who's listening to me, I'm really sorry for the conditions, not because I have anything to do with it really, but directly or indirectly, I would suggest even, of the conditions of the information that you guys have or humanity has through the rectangle and the academia.
It's just piss poor.
You're going to have to raise your inquisitiveness and discernment to really get the truth.
And the level of moroncy or idiocy is the norm.
Go anywhere, listen to anything, and it sounds good for a little while, and if you really know how to discern, you're going to say, oh boy, oh boy, I could see right through the bullshit and the stupidity and the plausibility.
Another thing that's interesting with this revelation bit, even though we haven't dug into it particularly deeply, but what can be seen is that if the adversary is clearly shown to be opposed to high-level entities on the other side to the point that when he's kicked out, they're all rejoicing that he's gone, then maybe you could say more incisively that he is the adversary of the Elohim and not necessarily humankind.
Because if things are primary on the other side, then they have an issue with him before we have an issue with him.
Yeah.
One thing that I like to give as an example is, given though it's an angelic being, the fighting over the body of the burial location of Moses being secret.
The answer was, you know, Yahweh rebuke you.
Not me rebuke you, but may the God of gods rebuke you.
You see.
But yet, in other conditions, in the book of Daniel, the angel comes and says, I may have had such a delay because I'm fighting the prince of Persia.
So, and one thing, he doesn't fight Satan.
He calls upon the higher power to do it as a form of rebuke.
But in another part, the same, I would suggest, angel is actually engaged in battle with another one of equal parity, let's say.
So, in this case, it seems like this adversary, Satan, is very powerful.
Or, it's best not to fight him.
It's just like the natural kingdom.
Aren't there some small venomous animals that are smaller in size than others that, you know, cower in their presence, right?
Right.
Like cobras.
I mean, how much does a cobra weigh at max?
You know, like three kilos, maybe?
A big one, four?
You know, any other, I mean, there's plenty of animals out there in the wilderness that could stomp on it, but they don't because of certain attributes.
And I'm not using that as a pun or a metaphor on the serpent thing either.
I'm just suggesting, you know, there's many animals like that.
Porcupine, skunks.
Pertaining to the archetype conversation of before, when you look through the text and you see these various templates or signifiers that are coming up,
like with the pitch and the arc and the pitch in the Moses basket thing,
I'm looking at the Moses and Aaron situation as seemingly being indicative of something because you had a function that was in one office
and then Moses and Aaron comes along and they split it into the king function with Moses and the priestly function with Aaron,
because Moses doesn't want to take on that task on his own.
Might the adversary in the Christ be a split of some kind of function?
Because they do seem to be tied to one another.
They're tied metaphorically through these events of the 7,000 years.
But other than that, I don't see them being tied, no.
Because one is begotten, the only begotten, meaning coming from by intent, and the other one is not.
And the other one is given a higher power than the other one.
One is considered to have primacy over the other.
Yeah, I don't see that connection.
But definitely I would say there is.
I think you and I once had a discussion.
Yes, there is a connection there, because if you look at it from a common denominator point of view, who sits on the throne of the earth right now?
Satan.
Who's going to sit on the same throne later?
Right?
You see?
So in other words, he's almost equal in that capacity in many ways, right?
Right.
You have said in the past that Satan lives in the atmosphere.
But where do you get that, apart from the prince of the powers of the air thing?
Well, the atmosphere, okay.
That's in boundary layer.
Well, look, you know, there are physical attributes to the spiritual realm on the earth.
Like underneath the Euphrates, there's angelic beings, right?
There's the prince of power of the sky, meaning, you know, our skies here.
There's attributes to water, you know, that are spiritual and physical, that go both ways.
You know, why would the demons be cast out of a jurisdiction and they go out and they come back to where there's water?
You know, remember reading that?
There are physical connections here, archetypes in the earth that retain and contain these beings.
Right.
I don't know why.
I mean, would he be, you know, and then there's also the rock.
You ever notice, for example, there's a rock metaphor is given through scripture as well, in a positive sense.
By the way, the capital punishment the spiritual world uses is what?
You know, stoning, lapidation.
I try to avoid those technical terms.
I try to keep it simple.
If you say lapidation, most people get lost.
Stoning.
What do you think a meteorite is?
A stone is?
Yeah.
I mean, duh.
Now, which one came first, the stoning commandment or the meteorite?
You know, I mean, I don't know.
Does it matter?
No, it's just that representation of the same thing.
It's a form of capital punishment.
There is this interesting bit in 1 Timothy 3, 5, where it says, For if a man does not know how to rule his own house, how shall he look after the assembly of Elohim?
Not a new convert, lest he become puffed up with pride and fall into the judgment of the devil.
So, is that an implication that Satan needs to be given specific jurisdiction over the Holy Ones through character flaws?
Like, if you're proud, then he can…
That sounds very Judeo-Christian.
It is, but hold on.
You know, I think historically, the New Testament has probably suffered the most out-of-context realization than anything else ever.
Well, you know, science and the rest of the stuff, too, is like that, too.
But if you look at what it really was intended for, it's not how it's being used.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
And actually what's being put out and how it's being explained is totally fake.
One thing that people don't understand, and they won't until the near future, this is a fact.
You can take it or leave it.
But, you know, if you don't like it, most people are not going to like what I'm about to say.
The whole commission, everything that you read about in the New Testament, I'm not talking Christian or biblical, ended in that first century, A.D. There's nothing left of it.
You're going to say, Greek, that sounds ridiculous because look at all these churches and religions.
Yeah, that has nothing to do with it.
Because the intent and the meaning of the purpose of what's called the New Testament and the Christ is lost by then.
What happened was there were enough people through oral tradition and knowledge of Scripture, mostly in the east of Israel.
Some had gone to Rome and Greece as well.
There was the Hellenic and the Roman aspect.
One of the primal things on their mind is what happens to you when you die and will we ever get proof of that?
And the Christ came to show what happens after you die, which is the resurrection.
Instead of depriving them of that knowledge, certain apostles or people were tasked to go out throughout the world and seek those that knew about this concept and let them know that it had been performed.
I don't see anything Christian about that.
I don't see any religious about it.
There's no church involved in that.
But now hold on a second.
Once you go out into public and you want to inform groups of people, whether small or large in various jurisdictions and geographic locations, isn't it best to set up a location where you do that in, like a meeting house or a group, where you start rehashing the evidence and all that, right?
Isn't that called an assembly to do that?
That's what went on then.
It's finished.
It's gone.
Everything that people have in their minds about the New Testament has nothing to do with what is really in the text itself at all.
None of that has been brought forward.
Now what happened is you have the fullness of the Gentiles.
And because they're all doing the same, there's no one to cry out against them.
Like years ago you heard about people being so God-awful that the surrounding people cried out against them.
Well, right now the entire society on the planet is God-awful.
Who's going to cry out against them?
You see?
Right.
When are the crazy people in the nuthouse going to cry out, get me out of this nuthouse?
These people are crazy.
They're all crazy, let's say.
I'm just saying as a generic metaphor.
So the character aspect, though, seems to give Satan an inroad into affecting these people.
As far as if you're proud, then he gets some kind of acclaim on you.
I'm not really understanding the technical side of that.
Well, the technical side, I explain, is very simple.
You can listen to it again on the recording.
The purposeful side of it is two sides of it.
For a high-level character like that to get involved, it's a fate element.
It's a prophetic element.
From a low-level intimate, it still is because, remember, you're on a cruise ship.
The ship is going from A to B, and what you do on that ship is limited.
But, yes, that's your free will.
You hear about people, let's say, let's go out extra-biblical or outside of the Bible for a moment.
People dabbling in the occulted, dark magic stuff.
Some of them come down with a possession thing or severe oppression.
You're not going to see that in Scripture.
Scripture just tells you don't dabble in magic, not because it doesn't work, but because it does work.
Because if magic was bunk, Scripture would tell you because it's bunk.
Very often it tells you the religions of man are bunk.
It's garbage.
It's worthless.
They'll tell you.
You notice that in Scripture?
Don't do this.
It's worthless.
The customs of the people are worthless.
It tells you why.
But in certain cases, don't do this.
Not because it's bunk, but because, you know, just don't do it.
Okay.
Let's move away from the Satan stuff.
It feels like perhaps we're putting too much emphasis on that.
Well, it's a very difficult thing to discuss because it's discussing the forest, right?
Where are you going to go within the society?
No, I'm not talking about nature now.
Man's society.
Where are you going to be Satan-free?
If I give you a minute to think about it or ten years, you're going to come back with the same answer.
You know what that answer is?
Nowhere.
The only time that you could probably get something like that is if they rebuild a temple or have a sanctuary dedicated to a specific God only.
You feeling me on that?
Yeah.
Sure.
I'll just bring up one more thing, and then I think I'll call it a day because I have my limits, too.
So the Zodiac is by no stretch, I think, an unimportant part of man's physical existence since it outlines the story of man's progression by marking the ages and events that have been pre-orchestrated.
And ancient civilizations, whether they were pagan or not, they kind of knew that, and they constructed monuments and artifacts that marked important time periods.
For example, if you look at the 10,500 BC marker where the recreation started, you can see certain things were constructed at that time, like Gobekli Tepli in Turkey.
And I could probably make a case that the Sphinx is actually from that period.
Also, I think we've talked about that, whether it was made before the recreation or after.
I could make a case that it was before or at that period.
So it was buried.
Yeah, it was buried.
By the way, just to interject something, you and I once had a discussion.
I started looking at some old notes about which pharaoh was for Moses, and it was Totonmos IV, the chariot pharaoh.
He's the one that also had a dream about uncovering the Sphinx because it was hidden under the sand.
And he was the one, and after him Egypt changed.
So it would be Totonmos IV that was the pharaoh during the Exodus.
He was the Exodus pharaoh in terms of history and dynastic.
If you're going to sift through all that, I just want to throw that out.
I put it in the chat once before, and there's not much about him, but yeah.
Right, so as I understand it, the ages, the change of the ages is visible from the Earth because of an astronomical phenomenon known as the precession, which is a change in the orientation of the rotational axis of the planet.
So the axis completes one revolution about 26,000 years at a rate of one degree every 72 years or so.
Allegedly.
Until it's knocked off its axis temporarily, radically, and then brought back.
And the Earth stops moving.
That's in the future though.
In the past, but go ahead.
When in the past?
Well, how does he hang the Earth?
It's in Job, if you look at it carefully.
Because there's a start.
It's not perpetual that the Earth hangs from nothing, right?
It was put there.
Well, before it was hanging from nothing, what was it hanging on?
The conditions were different.
Okay, that makes sense.
But can we nail down a time period for that?
No, yeah.
This is what I have to say about all time periods.
Other than the time period of your own pathetic life, I tell people, nothing else matters.
What really matters, if you want to go beyond your own pathetic life, 60, 70, 20 years, 50 years, 100 years, whatever it is, is get good, sound information that's been memorialized from the past.
You're going to go to scientists, you think they have good, sound information, or are they a bunch of liars and frauds?
Yeah, the entire group is liars and frauds, with some minimal exception.
Now, astrology has been relegated to junk by the people, just like the biblical stuff has been relegated to junk by the people.
Any field of study is good, but when people get their hands on it, they turn it into garbage.
So, I would stay away from the very large procession of time things, but I would not deny that there is a procession of symbolism in the sky, in the stars, via the constellations and other things, things that are dynamic, alignments and so on, and actual occurrences.
Those are good time keepers, but not in terms of time, but as event keepers.
Because scripture, by the way, does chronology through events, someone dying, someone being born, or just events.
And that's the main thing that is being censored by mankind.
One of the big agendas, even though they don't know it, the people that are in control, banking interests, because everyone is a suzerain to the bankers, right?
They're under control by the financial interests.
They don't know the truth, but they know that the truth can't get out.
This is the third time I'm saying this tonight.
The people that have power in this world don't know the truth as much as they could.
Scripture says they do know the truth and deny it.
That's why they're given up to certain ways.
But I would suggest that they don't look into it and study it enough to really know it, but they know it exists.
But what they do know even more is that it's important for you not to know it.
Do you get that?
Yeah.
Simple enough.
Yeah, it's like someone who doesn't know how to operate a chainsaw to cut down a tree, but he wants to make sure that someone who does, or could, doesn't cut down the tree either.
Right.
And the doctors are the same way.
Doctors don't want you to know about the body.
It's called job security.
How many times have you heard, mechanics don't want you to work at a car?
Yeah, it's a vicious, you're in a really bad vicious cycle, but you've been this way for a long time.
The thing to say about events is, I think I mentioned on the last Sonic event, is get used to searching archaeology.
You'll be, just put in archaeology in a search and hit past 24 hours or past week, because archaeologists are kind of slow in posting stuff.
You'll get a handle on it.
And do me a favor, right, because I've done this and I don't talk about it much.
Once you start finding interesting tidbits in archaeology, bookmark it.
Do me a favor, bookmark it.
And then do me another favor, when time goes by, a few months or more, maybe half a year, why don't you go back and click on that bookmark and tell me if it's still there.
I'm laughing facetiously.
Wow.
You know what a 404 is?
Yeah.
But what we can say about the current order of things is that the Zodiac is in the place that it's been for presumably quite some time, and that it's obviously relevant to the current dynamic.
And the Maserat also, yeah.
So as I understand it, the changes of the ages is something that we can observe, and the movement of the Earth's axis affects the position and the rising time of the constellations on what they call the spring equinox.
I'm not going to say that that's what it is, but what they call that.
So for about two millennia, each Zodiac constellation houses the rising of the sun on the so-called spring equinox, which signifies the age.
So I guess a simplistic and approximate breakdown of the ages since the period of around 11,000 B.C. or the Great Flood would be 10,000 B.C. to 8,000 B.C. is the age of Leo, which is pre-atomite destruction phase.
8,000 to 6,000 is the age of Cancer.
6,000 to 4,000 is the age of Gemini.
4,000 to 2,000 is the age of Taurus, which is pre-flood society.
2,000 to 1,000 B.C. is the age of Aries, which is Old Testament period.
And 1,000 to 2,000 is obviously the age of Pisces that we just went through.
And from 2,000 onwards is the age of Aquarius.
But Gemini would also be Old Testament also.
That's why you have so many twins in the Old Testament dualities, brotherly pairs.
I wouldn't say I've done this maybe in eight years, but I've gone out during the first month, the first moon, which is one thing that people are listening to lawful timekeeping.
You'll notice that the first and the seventh moons are the largest, but they're in different parts of the sky, right?
If you go out during that spring, which is the first moon when the cycle starts again, the morning prior to that moon rising, look in the east slightly to the south, you'll see Aquarius.
You'll see about 75 percent of it.
And you'll see Pisces also.
You'll see about 75 percent of Pisces.
In the east, yeah, and it's been more than 10 years.
You know like a child when he gets a new toy, it's like everything in his life revolves around that.
I've gone through phases where I was like, okay, now I'm doing lawful timekeeping.
I'm going to hammer that and get as much out of it as possible.
There's nothing wrong with that.
You do that when you do training in any field, right?
You do training.
It's a discipline.
You get it.
In other words, in the reason I said 10 years ago or more or roughly, you know, 06, 07, 08, let's say, if anyone's got any news on that, please share it.
But don't come around.
I mean, you can, but fortunately not much.
Look at this website.
Look at this link.
Look at this.
No, I want to hear from you.
Do a little bit of work.
I'd rather have genuine stuff.
I'm not saying that everything is crap, but you know how you're guilty until proven innocent, right?
You've heard of that?
Well, it's all crap until proven not to be.
So, no, but what you're bringing up, Sam, is extremely valid.
And yeah, it's one hell of a coincidence, isn't it, that the story of mankind is written in the stars?
And there's been a lot of research, by the way, on the parallax of stars.
You know, when you measure a star location in the winter, you know, since the Earth tilts its axis, let's say, for the summer, the star should also correspondingly have a different angle of parallax, right, because now the Earth has moved, right?
But when you do that, the stars don't change their angle, even though their position in the sky seems to.
There's a phenomenon that people just can't – the scientists just don't want to talk about it.
Just like if you look up on the Internet, I dare anyone, oh, why do your fingers and toes shrivel when you're putting water?
They have hundreds of links and people and scientists saying no one knows why that happens, right?
They tell you that all the time.
Or you ever notice whenever they bring up dinosaurs 60 million years ago, they make sure to say that every time.
That's propaganda.
It's like with 9-11.
Remember how they had a show that, you know, the Arab hijackers, Arab hijackers constantly.
It's propaganda.
So you can spot that when you see the – you know, there's this disingenuine thing that – I find that what most people have accepted to be true is disingenuous and of poor quality and of low quality and poor character.
So, you know, you're going to have to weed through all that stuff to get some really good corn.
But anyway, but if you want to study the parallax – So I'm going to go back to that.
So you know what?
As the Earth is moving, the entire universe is moving in unison with it as if there is no movement.
But you do see movement.
It's like a planetary scenario.
It's in unison, but it's not unitary per se because we know that the pole star or the load star changes.
So where the axis, the Earth's northbound axis is pointing now isn't where it was pointing, you know, thousands of years ago.
I forget the actual star that it's pointing at right now.
I'd have to look it up.
I think it's Polaris.
It's the north star right now.
And 3,000 BC, I think it was Thuban in the constellation of Draco.
So that does change.
Yeah.
You know, by the way, I'll just say this even though that's against better judgment.
You know, there is the first two chapters of Revelation is a star map.
I think you and I have spoken about it in private a little bit, regrettably so.
That's something that you can't just discuss a little bit and then run away from, you know what I mean?
But…
It's not that hidden, though.
Well, it ties into many other things, and it evolves, you know.
The word evolve means to open, unravel into many other aspects, you know.
By the way, this is a little hint.
Whenever there's a reference to the stars in Scripture, it's about an event.
It's not just the stars themselves, you know.
It's event-based.
Calendrical, it's a poor choice, but people understand that term.
You know…
You mentioned one time about how the stars unravel like a…
Scroll.
Yeah, like a scroll, yes.
Well, that just…
Well, that means that…
Well, okay, that's in code.
It's in the Book of Isaiah.
That's a code for a certain event, and I'll get into that in the future.
That has to do with…
You've heard of the pole shift?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, it has to do with where and how the pole shift is going to be with great specificity, and I'll get into that in the future.
Oh, my.
Okay.
That's why…
One thing, if you've listened to Greek speak before, and sadly to say I'm the only one saying these things like this, is that I've…
You know, on any interview, whatever I do, just to bring up…
You know, I like to bring up the…
How many times did the world was supposed to end in the past three years?
Financial collapse, meteors, government crackdowns, shutdowns.
How many times was it supposed to end?
Last year wasn't too bad.
I think twice last year, but the year before, it was like five times.
Right, right.
Yeah, and what do I always say?
Nah.
That ain't going to happen.
Why?
And I'll tell you why.
It's not like throwing dice.
And very often I say, well, we'll discuss this in the future.
Because why?
It'll make more sense then.
Right now it won't make any sense.
I'm still getting emails here and there about stuff that I said that I didn't say or stuff that I didn't say that I said, and it's like, what?
You know, so it's not too bad, though.
I mean, fortunately, the people that are communicating through email and Skype and even the chat tango are fairly rational and reasonable in the majority sense.
So, yeah.
But even then, there's more time that more water has to pass for other things to be discussed.
But I do want to thank and also thank, in a general sense, no one specific, about the timekeeping.
In the chat tango, when I do drop in from time to time, I look at it, and I would say the great majority of the people that do bring up timekeeping are in conjunction with what I'm able to perceive here.
So that's, you know, it's interesting.
You know, let's just put it this way, from an objective point of view, there are five or six or ten more people on the planet now than there were in the past that know how to do lawful timekeeping, which, by the way, is also taught in university astronomy, timekeeping.
But I think they get neuralized or, you know, any astronomical…
I think you dropped a link in one a few times about that one.
Yeah, and they do admit, but they do throw you off, just like attorneys and academics and doctors, they always throw you off.
They'll give you some, about, you know, sometimes 70% good information and then 30% poison to throw you off, you know, neuralize you.
You know, they'll tell you in all the academic stuff, the day is solar noon, right?
You remember reading that?
Oh, yes.
Solar noon, and they'll tell you that the moon rules the month, right?
They tell you that.
Yes, they do.
But they tell you there's no astronomical feature for the week.
Bullshit.
And then you go on to their stuff, and it's all academic horse crap.
It is, yeah.
Well, of course there's an astronomical feature for the week.
You have four quadrant-type phases for the moon.
You have full moon, half waning, dark moon, half waxing, full again.
So anyway, yeah, it's just a screwed up mess.
But look, enjoy good food, enjoy good drink, good conversation.
I hope we've indulged in some of it.
And keep yourself warm when it's cold and keep yourself cool when it's hot.
Cool head and warm feet, remember, because in nature the cold is rarefied and it rises, and the heat is densified and it descends.
Huh, what did he just say?
Yeah.
Keep your fluids or precious fluids, oils, liquids, in the dark and avoid as possible.
And make sure that you're drinking enough of it, too.
It's one thing to make the stuff, but it's another to get it into your body.
Yes, and if you don't have a good water source, getting it from fruit and vegetable is the best way.
You know, I dare anyone to take, if you eat fruits and vegetables as your diet, juice all of it, and look at how much juice, you know, a day's worth of fruit and vegetables.
Run it through a juicer, look how many glasses of liquid you get.
You see, that's already pre-filtered and it's charged, you see.
So, there's another aspect, if you can't get good water.
That's why if anyone, I remember if you're traveling internationally, oh, this water didn't affect me too bad.
And then you get like the worst sore throat you can imagine three days later, you know, because you're not used to the bugs there, you know, your body reproducing them, because they don't go into the body, your body reproduces them.
Right.
But you get into the habit of eating fruits and veggie, you know, so when you're traveling, don't drink the water like they say.
Eat lots of fruits and veg, because there's plenty of water in it that way.
But again, back to the fluids.
You know, I haven't gotten much response on it lately, but, you know, of course there's a quandary and a rarity and shortage of finding the proper shapes for water.
But, you know, you can go any secondhand store, whatever, furniture outlet or housewares outlet, and they have plant vases that generally are formed in that ovoid shape, you know.
And what you want to be is savvy enough to get a plant vase that is glass lined, you know, not the junk lined inside.
Don't get an unglazed one that says not for food use either and that has a narrow neck.
You know, not the vases that are really wide mouthed.
Those are fine too, because you might want to put a stopper or a cover on it.
And those are good home storage vessels, you know.
So they're not all that – there's not much of a shortage of it, I mean, if you look at it from that perspective, ovoid shaped vessels, right.
But strictly for water that has a good stopper and all that, yeah, of course there's a shortage.
Why would you want to provide people with the right geometry?
They're all blockheads anyway, square headed or square whatever.
So, well, look, in the future if there is memory of this, which I believe there is, you'll say that you lived during this time period and someone will pat you on the back.
Sure, that would be nice.
Well, it would be better than nice, I hope, yeah.
Well, they'll say what a nice – you'll say what a nice time it was.
Yeah.
Anyway, I think I'm good for this conversation.
I'll bring up the Zodiac stuff on a continuation tip next time.
Yeah, there's actually more to look into that.
And one thing about the Zodiac stuff, the Maserat has a different view on it, but it still has the same movement.
And it is lawful to look at the stars.
You know why?
Because anyone can reference it, and you'll find that all of the ancient information that's been memorialized on the stars is in unison.
What are you going to do, lie about where the moon is, lie about where the sun is?
You know what I mean?
So it is a good lawful reference point.
Another thing – well, we'll get into geography in the future.
I'll tell you a little thing that I've been looking at lately because it sparks back memories from doing the geophysics stuff.
You're aware how they use satellite geoimagery to look for minerals and things on the surface, right?
And what they do is they tweak the spectrum so it looks real funky, and as the spectrum changes, you know, it's unrealistic color.
It looks almost like rainbow colors on the Earth, but it's not.
That shows you where there's a preponderance of a certain mineral, you know, just by simply – you know, they'll look at Saudi Arabia, and they'll say, well, why is this bright blue band turquoise color here?
And, well, they'll dig around and find, well, there's this mineral over here.
You see there's like an emission spectrum, right?
But what they've – and I'm not – well, I'll just give a little spoiler of what I'm looking into.
I may not be successful as I've got to reach out and get some more critical information on it.
There is evidence – you know how we had discussion of the garden and how the river came out from the garden that divided into other rivers and the Gihong and the Euphrates, right?
Well, there's – through these geo-satellites, there is evidence of there was a main drop of water or a pool-type recession on the Earth where there are four branches and the Euphrates is still connected to it or part of the Euphrates because now the source of the Euphrates is a spring near Turkey and also runoff from certain mountain ranges.
But these are just things in the future.
I may not be successful in it, but we'll see if I could reach out and get some more critical information about – this would be the location of where the Garden of Eden was in relation to the Earth.
Do you see what I mean by this?
Through geophysical features where old rivers used to run.
And they know it.
A geophysicist will tell you there used to be a river here and now it's filled in through alluvial fill, which is decomposing of land that filled it in.
They could see that.
And zeolites are sources from deep river.
So anyway, that's an interesting study.
And I've been looking on the rectangle and there's nothing on there really.
But, I mean, who are you going to go tell to?
Oh, look, let's say we found where Noah's Ark is.
Who are you going to go tell?
Who are you going to talk to?
Who cares?
Yeah, exactly.
Well, that's the attitude.
Who cares?
Most of this stuff could be surmised.
Well, let's say you find where these rivers are flowing geophysically where they were at one point.
Who cares, right?
No, I mean, who cares about the other people that you supposedly want to talk to?
I don't want to talk to anybody.
Yeah, well, I don't either.
That's why I'm doing it electronically.
But here's the interesting thing.
But you know what this all means.
This is what I'm saying.
That's now.
It's temporal.
What I'm saying, it's not time yet.
Yeah, sure.
Right.
It's not time yet.
I mean, just look around.
These guys, these idiots are doing some kind of holiday right now.
Go talk to these savages what it means.
You want to talk about demonic oppression?
You know?
Well, look at their faces.
You want to see what evil looks like and worthlessness?
Speaking of that, when I was at the Yom, I had some lady come up to me, mid-60s, rather pepper pot kind.
And she comes up and she says, do you have an, what did she say?
I think Eastern Santa Claus or Western Santa, you know, from a different location.
Right, the non-fat one, yeah.
Right.
And I looked at her and I says, well, I'm really not familiar with any of that.
And could you be a little more specific?
And she had this dazed look in her eye, Greek.
I'm telling you, the emptiness of the stare, like she was dumbfounded and didn't know how to describe what it was that she was trying to come there for, or even if she had a purpose.
But it was actually, it kind of raised a hair on the back of my neck like, whoa, this is seriously screwed up.
Well, I'm glad that you can notice that, but I'm also sad that you noticed that, because I'm at the point where I can go anywhere and I see that.
If I go to the auto parts store, I see both the people behind the counter and the clients.
I agree, but this one was probably the most profound that just struck me so odd.
And I was like, wow, this is deep.
Yeah, humanity is, let's just leave it off like this.
If you don't believe what I'm saying, if you have a keen eye for biology and you're familiar with anthropomorphs, let me just be indirect like that.
Go watch some old black and white films of how people looked then, and then go look at the people that you see now, whether it's in television or not.
Look at the difference, and you tell me there's no degeneration there.
The old black and whites, you know?
Well, it's not even that they're black and white.
Go back even further.
That's a good marker.
Go look at photography and look at how robust.
The people had better displacement within this reality.
I have great difficulty with getting into deep observation or coinciding and relating with people, not because I have a difficulty with doing that.
It's just when I start examining their condition.
It's not that I'm much better, but I just wish I was around something better than what I see.
And I'm not talking about dregs and Walmart and all that.
I can navigate through all levels of society, and I see it throughout.
It's really sad.
And again, I just always bring it up.
If you look at even science fiction, when you go look for sages and masters, do you find them right there in the city, or do you have to go somewhere out in the cave in the mountain because they don't want to be around anybody?
And they're typically embittered, not because of their character as being as such, because they are able to perceive really what's going on.
And here's another interesting thing.
Humanity deserves the most compassion because we are the prize of creation.
But you know who I really feel bad for?
The animals.
Because they're extremely subjugated to humans.
They're not complaining, though.
Yeah, right.
Actually, thank you.
Someone sent me an email years ago.
I used to say beware of animal attacks being on the rise, not just as a coincidental thing, but an infliction of the natural kingdom kicking back to mankind.
And someone today sent me an email about some normal activities, things that were normal.
I think it was something with sea animals that were always around people, and all of a sudden they're starting to attack people now.
And someone could try to rationalize that and say, well, it's because their food is shortage.
Well, no, they don't see people as food or as territorial because the food shortages come and go on a seasonal level anyway.
So, yeah.
Even the animals, the spirits that are guiding them are like, yeah, these humans now, the mop-up crew is coming, so let's eke out.
Don't you want to kick them in the shins before you go anyway, Mr. Wolf?
Or Mr. B?
Or Mr. Whale?
Or Mr. Sea Lion?
Okay, guys, I think we've done okay.
People getting an earful, I think they're going to get more than a nickel's worth on this one also.
Oh, definitely, definitely.
Another wealth of information again.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And not to brag, but I still haven't shared more than 10% of what I found out in the past decade and a half.
I know I sound like an arrogant ass by saying that, but maybe a little bit of time goes on, I'll get to the 11%.
I look forward to it.
I look forward.
Yes, Greek, please bless us.
Yeah, right.
More information.
Yeah.
Definitely.
I don't know about that, but yeah.
Okay, well, we'll just keep it going somehow, and we'll see what develops, all right?
We certainly will.
You guys keep in touch.
I will.
Thanks again, Bruce, for doing all this, and thanks again, Sam.
No worries.
See you guys.
Be well, folks.
Talk to you guys later.
Good night.