Let's see, good evening everybody.
We got Greek, myself, and shortly Sam from the way it sounds.
Greetings Greek.
Greetings.
Okay, yeah, we'll do another sonic event, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's make sure everybody's happy on the board here.
Okay, we're good.
Okay, so we started speaking earlier about maybe any questions or anything like that.
I always have stuff to say if I get started.
So yeah, but either way, let's just get started on a few notions.
It's mid-season.
It's going about mid-season depending on where you are.
We just choose that notion carefully, mid-season.
So whatever season you're in right now, it's you're in the middle, approaching the middle of it.
So it just shows you, you know, if you got a perspective on time, how fast time, you know, events are moving.
The other thing is here for the majority of the people I'm reckoning are in the winter.
If anyone this year has done any, excuse me, on an experimental basis, eating seasonally, let's say, right, and found that it to be rewarding, you know, not eating foods that are derived or minimizing the intake of food that comes from or grown and harvested in warm climates, right?
I have found that personally.
And you know what's strange about that Greek is the way that it manifests itself in the individual if they're not eating within their longitude.
And you know, the nasal stuff, the flu, is there an actual, is that just the liver not being able to process this stuff?
You know, in other words, you're full of dung, shall we say?
Regarding what?
Well, if you're not eating lawfully, the body obviously reacts.
For instance, when I got sicker than a dog and I was guilty as charged on too much sugars and foods that just weren't in this climate.
So I guess I'm wondering why the human manifests that kind of behavior in itself, the nasal, the flu-like symptoms, all that.
Is that just us being full of dung?
No, I've gone into that before.
No, no, that's just whenever mucus is developed, that means the body is losing a vacuum condition.
It's losing a vacuum.
An analogy would be when you're looking at what they call a car, you see one of the tires are low.
Well, it's low because it's losing atmospheric difference, atmospheric potential, meaning the pressure in that tire should be high, and because it's not, it's sagging.
Now, the pressure in the body should be lower than the atmosphere, and when it starts to raise up, the pressure goes up, still in a vacuum, because the only time you lose complete vacuum is when you're dead.
If you lose vacuum in the body, you go into chemical decomposition.
So, no, that's like an example of that would be when an unborn infant is inside the mother's womb, what prevents it from falling out of the body?
You know, you have obviously a placenta and a lot of other stuff surrounding the development of that human, and it's called a mucus plug.
You could go look up the anatomy of a pregnant woman, and the child is, you know, it's all held up at the end of the uterus with what's called a mucus plug.
Why is it made, why is it mucus?
You see, no, eating seasonally is very simple.
It's just like the automobiles that are designed a certain way, like for a little while now, quite a few years, some of the better European cars and some of the better Japanese cars, the higher-end cars, when you go to tank up or fuel up, and you, what does it say on the thing?
It says 91 octane only.
You ever notice that?
Yeah, and the other cars are designed for 87 or 89.
Yeah, you're made from the earth, in case you haven't gotten that memo, right?
I mean, that's just a general statement.
Right, so there's a development process there that's involved.
Now, here's the thing.
There's two approaches to this.
One is, do you want to get pedantic into what's called, you know, find out all the science and everything there is to know about it, or do you want to know what just works right now, but more than just a ritual?
You know, like, for example, most people are using a car as a ritual.
They just know if they pull this lever and do this, the thing moves and they get to where they want to go, you know, a little bit more than that.
And I tend to save more of these, quote, unquote, deeper knowledge conversations for private, because in private, if anyone's ever had a private discussion with me, like eight hours is normal.
Right.
You know, and it's like, where do you find the time?
Well, I make the time.
So also, whenever you're doing even something like this, or the chatango or the website, you're dealing with the public.
Right.
And fortunately, I've never gotten anything negative really on the chatango.
Sometimes you're in there.
In person, I do get some negative comments, you know, and maybe off comments and things like that.
But everything's been very positive, not because I'm looking for that.
It's just like working in retail.
If you ask anybody in retail, what's really tough about being retail?
I'll give you all these reasons.
I look at them as though you're dealing with the public.
I'm like, yeah, basically, you know, and that means exactly the truth.
Yeah.
So this is a so this is still a very powerful.
And in other words, let's just say it this way.
The cults, CULT, a cult, it could define many ways, but I'm just using a normal definition.
You're being run by a series of cults right now society that have been normalized.
So you know, there was your all of your what you consider to be law is run by a secret cult.
And if you don't know that, so this is not a theory, this is actual fact, you're pretty naive.
Your food and your science and your schools and your medicine is also run by a cult.
Now, there's, you know, there's a level to that where you can see how they're not no one is doing what they're supposed to be doing.
That's according to what's memorialized in their own writings, right.
And, of course, you know, no one really cares, because obviously, these, everything is going the way it is, you know, your your spiritualists, you know, in other words, all of your religions, regardless of its Christian, Judaism, Islam, Hindu, Buddhist, and all the denominations therein are all cults, various cults.
In other words, it's there is a secret behind it.
And the secret is very simple.
These people are operating on plausibility, and a level of control that accommodates the masses.
That's all, it's very simple.
There's no knowledge that's necessary.
There's no technique, there's no law that's necessary.
In other words, if the people are partaking in their mechanistic you know, social things, you know, whether whether you're a street sweeper, or an attorney, or working in a bakery, or a mechanic or whatever, all you need to know is right now in this epoch, or this particular society, you're doing a particular thing every day by habit or by ritual or by desire or by necessity.
And you're not making waves, you know, there's not too much friction.
And you just move along.
And you just do every day do what you do today, you'll do it tomorrow.
You know, you have your little things here and there.
And it's just running that way.
So to have discussions about why things are the way they are, and how you can actually have more control over the things that personally influence you and that you could personally influence also outwardly, is very unpopular, and also misunderstood.
And the I'm going to bring Sam in here in a moment.
And the other thing is, there is no room for truth of anything outside of that truth, you see.
And the other thing, there's another thing also, that if stuff like Greek speak now, here's the thing I'm years ago, when I used to speak publicly, I always regretted it.
And now it's not that I like to speak it.
But you know, some time goes back or whatever.
And I'm like, what the hell is going on with these people on this planet?
What's wrong with you people?
You know, the stuff that you everything that you get involved in, no matter how esoteric or whatever sublime you think it is, there's a basic element to it.
And it's simple, there's a simple underlying current or a simple underlying principle or archetype to everything and no one is discussing these things.
So it's like, what's wrong with you, you know, inhabitants of the earth.
So, you know, I mean, there are people that know it.
They're not speaking.
Right?
And it doesn't mean because you're speaking, you don't know.
And if you don't know, you're not speaking.
Yes, that's, that's true.
In most cases, that's like a cliche that's used for stupid people.
And, you know, stupid people are very emotional.
But the thing is, if you do listen to Greek speak, it's going to take about, let's say three to six months for you to realize what you're hearing.
And anywhere between six months to three years to realize what's being said.
So it's very different to, oh, what happened this week?
You know, you only turn on these browsers and they're, and they're like, Oh, this is all you need to know about this, right?
And then next week you have the next thing.
Yeah, it's just ridiculous society.
But, but yeah, so that's a, that's a far cry from eating seasonally.
And also I've done more informational stuff about eating seasonally and all that with Seth.
I think this is common sense.
So if anyone wants to look up these things, and like I said, I think you've been listening to Greek speak for less than a year or so, Bruce?
Yes.
So you're past that initialization point.
Yeah.
Past the shock.
The initial.
Hey, Sam.
Hello.
Good evening, Sam.
I can hear your keyboard.
Put a towel under your keyboard or your cleanest dirty shirt or something.
Sorry, say that again.
You cut out for me.
Put something under your keyboard to damp it out.
Yeah, I don't really know what you mean.
The keyboard's part of the laptop.
Oh, then you got to throw, throw the whole thing away.
No, I'm just joking.
Yeah, you could dip, dip it out to put something underneath the laptop.
So it doesn't resonate against the hard surface.
And don't block the fan.
Anyway, how are you doing?
I'm doing well.
Just a little tired.
How are you guys?
Same, I guess.
A little tired.
I mean, I know what you want me to say.
We're streaming, so.
No, we're, that's fine.
There's only 10 people that are ever going to listen to this anyway, if that.
But no, we're just talking a little bit about here and there and, and the seasonality of things and whatever.
But the reason I announced to bring you in as well is because you messaged that you're available on what they call Tuesdays.
Do you know what day it is?
Anyone know roughly what it's, do you know, are you aware that it's roughly the 10th month?
You know, that's why it's called December, believe it or not.
And do you know that it's around the 18th day?
It started around noontime, so.
Fascinating.
What's so fascinating about that?
It's called sarcasm.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
It's kind of like, you know, if you're raised in the Christian,
what do you call it, thing and then the Gregorian calendar, even if you were excited about learning
lawful stuff, lawful just means you can measure it versus being told by a bunch of, you know,
psychopaths or whatever, or freaks or cultists, cult members being, in other words, if you have
someone that grew up in a cult from their parents were in a cult and their parents were in a cult,
and you want to get out of that cult, no matter how far you run away or how fast you run,
you can get out of the cult, but you can't get the cult out of the person.
You know, you can take the person out of the cult, but you can't.
Right.
So it takes six months to several years to see what really what's going on.
So, yeah, thanks for the encouragement.
No, but I think I'm past that stage.
It's just at a 3am in the morning when I haven't learned timekeeping yet.
I just have to try and be sarcastic to let that brush off.
Yeah, no, the time, it's not important.
Sure it is.
I'll get to that later, though.
But I do look into other things in my free time.
Yeah.
What do you feel like getting into?
Well, I figured we'd just continue from where we left off the last time.
I know that you've done a previous stream, but my mind is pretty much at the same place it was before, because I usually go into progression with these topics.
Okay.
So we're talking about the gods and the adversary and gleaning more.
Well, here's one thing.
Let me just start off this way.
There's one thing that, you know, you've heard me, one of the things that I like to do is discredit what people have in terms of the presumptiveness, the presumptive things that they have that they presume are facts and real or whatever, right?
Like the King James, King Jimmy, or all their biblical stuff.
And many times I've said that any inquisitive person that looks into, let's say, the biblical text as it's been delivered and handed out in society can invalidate it very rapidly, you know, as being an informational-based thing, right?
Now, the thing is, on what level do you want to look at it?
You have, obviously, to invalidate it, you're going to have to look at what it was supposed to be communicating.
And that's why I always suggest anyone that has an unabridged, which are very few and far in between, version of a Bible, read the introduction.
Do you have one?
It's about, they have about usually anywhere between 5 to 15 page introduction.
And if you read that introduction, you want to keep reading the rest of that piece of crap, you're an idiot.
You know, I mean, meaning as keeping that thing as a reference material, you know what I mean?
They flat out tell you what they're doing, right?
It's kind of like in Hollywood, you know, you ever watch these movies where the villain gets the victim and he's pointing the gun at him, he says, I'm going to shoot you because of this, and he's talking to him for five minutes.
I'm like, that's not how it happens in real life.
In real life, when someone wants to kill you, they do it quickly and they get out of there, right?
But in Hollywood, they stand there, right?
You know, like we'll pick any movie, they always do that, right?
Oh, I got you now, I'm going to make sure that it hurts.
Right.
That's stupid.
That's exactly what's going on with all of the, now because you have such poor text and poor reference material, what does that lead to?
Poor what?
Doctrine.
You want to know anything about poor doctrine?
You ever heard of Christmas?
Merry Christmas.
Right?
Look at the stuff, right?
It's ridiculous.
I'm not saying that you shouldn't do it.
I'm just saying you shouldn't do it if you know what's going on.
So, the interesting thing is, let's just take something really small.
Like, before we get into the text, you were talking about all this stuff about the gods and all this, but what we are talking about is based on what we know, based on what we see, based on this poor crap doctrine that we've been given from the ancient texts also, right?
Let's just take something simple.
If you look up the Strong's word for leprosy, right?
If you look up what they call leprosy, it's more of an old, well, it's actually Old and New Testament.
That word that's being used there, actually, it's one of these difficult words to pronounce.
I have to look it up myself.
I'm not even going to try it right now.
If you look it up, that's the same word that's used when something is in a necrotic state, like a stillborn baby, or Moses' errand sister.
Do you remember when she went up and the Elohim, Yahweh said, no, no, I speak to Moses directly.
I don't need you, basically.
And she got leprosy, it says, and she became white as snow.
She became white.
You know, Job talks about, it's mentioned in several places in scripture, this condition is mentioned.
It's not leprosy, as we know it.
Leprosy is where you're, you know, it's a condition where you have a flush of phagia, a thing where your limbs are falling off, and all this.
You know, this is a different condition.
This particular disease or condition is best rendered as a rapid necrotic state, like a necrosis comes in.
This is something that we're not familiar with today.
Would that be equivalent to the flesh-eating disease?
That would be more, no, it's not flesh-eating, because a child that's born stillborn doesn't have a flesh-eating disease, but they are pale gray color.
Okay.
It's as if, if you've ever seen anyone that's gone into shock, they, all of a sudden, they lose all their flesh, flesh tone, and they turn this, this pasty gray look.
Have you seen, have you ever experienced that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, I'm talking about the kind of shock that people die from if they're not treated, you know, out of it.
So, yeah, yeah.
So this is a condition that in today's society, what's been put out through this bad translations, bad versions, bad doctrine and imagery, there's something different going on here.
You know, that, well, let's say, does it pertain to, you know, that part of the world at that time?
Sure it does.
There's several things that pertain, because you notice when the patriarchs were, after the flood, you know, like Abraham's father and father-in-law, what they, they lived till 200 and something.
Abraham lived till 175.
So, you know, the life expectancy of man just didn't get cut off immediately after the flood.
There was a half life.
So, there was something in nature that was affecting it, that would rapidly withdrew or inflicted itself upon mankind where life span.
So there, in other words, there, there are things, if you're paying attention to the information, the conditions were different.
There are things that existed that were slightly different, you know.
And I'm not talking about, you know, like minor things that we adjust to today, like we say polio and all these other things that are misguided.
You know, we don't have that anymore or whatever.
But it could be something like that.
For example, an example, I brought up polio, because that's something that's completely misguided also.
There's no such thing.
That is a neurotoxin.
There was no polio before or after the spraying of pesticides, the new pesticides in the 20s and 30s and 40s, right?
I remember that when I was young.
Yeah, people were getting with the machines and spraying that big fog that went up and down the streets.
That's what caused polio.
Yeah, neurotoxins.
And then they stopped spraying and the doctor says, we'll take advantage of that and save the vaccine.
And we've isolated the bacteria or the pathogen.
They didn't really use the term virus back then.
That was not invented.
First started, they passed out the cubes with the polio vaccine on it.
All the kids.
Yeah, it's all a farce.
Yeah, this is a cult.
Yeah, if you if you ever, let me put it this way.
When you go see an attorney, an accountant, a doctor, a priest, a rabbi, a guru, you know, any mom, a psychiatrist, on and on and on and on.
And I'm telling you that these people are part of a cult.
Do you expect anyone to be part of a cult to give you rational activity or rational thinking or anything rational?
Or do you expect bizarre shit?
Right?
You expect bizarre shit.
And this is what they're doing.
Yeah.
And this is normal.
This is the norm.
You know, this is so.
So what to do?
Very simple.
To go back to the conversation.
It was very simple.
Just set yourself apart with Sam is when we have a conversation like that.
There's so many things to look at.
Let me just do a little more flexing.
Are you there, Sam?
Yes.
Okay.
When you're looking at these entities, let's use that term, you know, and delineating and trying to figure out who they are.
You know how they're really defined, by the way?
They're defined by their activities, just like people define themselves.
Well, I'm a street sweeper.
I'm a bus driver.
I'm a painter.
I'm a mechanic.
I'm a baker.
I'm a butcher.
You ever notice that people define themselves that way?
But essentially, they're human.
You know, if you cut them open, they're almost interchangeable based on blood type and other things.
These gods are not like that.
They actually are very different.
They're more different than we are.
Because, for example, you know, the difference between a carib and an angel is not the difference between, let's say, a black guy and a Chinaman.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm using like old Arizona talk here.
You know, if you ever, by the way, if you ever hang out with miners in Arizona or Colorado, Chinese people are called Chinamen.
So anyway, so you see what I mean?
There's a tremendous, but then again, they're also separated by what they do.
Because you can have a benevolent entity all of a sudden become malevolent based on his actions and intent.
All right.
The other thing you have to consider also is what is really going on?
What is really going on?
And I haven't stressed this in years ago, people used to ask me this.
I said, No, I don't want to talk about it.
But now I do.
Because I think there's at least five or 10 people out there that are beginning to get what's going on, you know, which is enough.
When you start studying the concept of the gods affecting humanity, that is a parallel society.
It's almost another universe, because it's intangible.
Now they can make themselves tangible to us, but we don't have control over that to some most most degrees, let's say.
Okay, there, but you see, and someone this is what I didn't talk about.
People say, Well, do the gods have a God?
Yes, they do.
And that is the God of the Bible, quote unquote.
That is the most high that is the one that you're reading about.
So when you reading about the most high Elohim Yahweh in the Bible, you have to keep in the in the back of your mind somewhere somehow, yes, you do have to do this, is that he is the God of the gods affecting us.
So he's like bypassing through.
So we have this entire society of the gods affecting humanity.
And when you read about what this head deity is doing, he's going through as a God, the realm of the gods, to us, you know, affecting things on earth.
Can you imagine that, you see, and this is the perspective.
That's why there's so little talk about, you know, General Motors factory in the US in the Bible, you won't find that.
That's why there's so little talk about the lightbulb.
That's either there's no talk about Hammurabi's code in the Bible.
You see that?
I hope that puts it in perspective.
What's going on, it's very, very limited, because what we're what that biblical text is supposed to be, is a message related to us from the God of the gods.
Now, unlike men, who, you know, are divided, well, I don't believe in that.
Oh, let's mythology or folklore fiction, you know, and they're divided, then you have the, you know, the atheists or the agnostics or whatever.
And then you have the idiots and all the various religious cults that believe this and believe that, right, which is, again, you know, whatever, the gods don't have that.
The gods know that they exist.
And they know that we exist.
And they know that they have a God, they don't have that atheistic.
In other words, if they have it, it hasn't been demonstrated in any literary form or intentional form anywhere.
You see?
So these are like, just basic things.
And then, of course, the other basic thing you have to remember is when you're reading the text, there's archetypes there.
Like, you know, how one archetype would be, you know, we try to visualize things vertically, and the things that are important in the God's realm, it's lateral, right?
It's left and right, inner circle, outer circle, not up and down within their realm, right?
And they communicate that to us in a certain degree.
So if you want to communicate with them, and be within their, like, act like you're in their group, you don't say, I want to go up and down, you say, I want to go in and out.
But when you talk about men, you're like, oh, I want to go, I'll be a high society or low society, right?
So it's different.
The other thing is, there's many things about archetypes that use, meaning these are things that result or are important, that repeat themselves.
Like one thing is like cutting something in half.
You know, you remember the sacrifice that Abraham and Yahweh cut in half.
And this is a covenant that he made with Abraham.
And he's, and you know, the whole onus is on the Elohim on this one.
Abraham is just sitting back, he doesn't have to do anything, right?
At that point, because this is after he already, right, brought Isaac and all that.
So you notice the cutting in half, and the only one that walks between it is the Elohim, man doesn't go between it.
Now, remember Solomon, with the women dispute over the child, he says, give me a sword so I can cut it in half.
Right?
Because there is a, there's a covenant there that was, I mean, shady.
So you're trying to develop a covenant, you know, like one woman saying this, the other woman saying that.
And when the covenant is formed, that decides who gets the child, right?
And that ends up in a backing out, just like the descendants of Abraham backed out.
Anyway, so you have all these parallels, you have the archetype of water, right?
You know, Moses is put in a basket covered with pitch.
Noah covers the ark with pitch.
By the way, that was an ark that Moses was put in, the same word, right?
So you have the water metaphor, again, that, you know, these archetypes keep coming up and up and up, right?
The side, the cutting in half, the water, the fire.
These are things that keep repeating themselves, and they're very, very little subtle variations that show up every time.
Do you get what I'm saying?
So, and they're happening all the time, you know, everywhere.
In almost every story, there's a recurring archetype, or alludes to one.
You know, it has to do with many of these little archetypes that are within the text.
So the problem that I also see is, if you haven't, if you're not familiar with the text, it's very difficult to discuss it.
The biggest misgiving that you can consider with any body of work is that it has, if it's not oral, it's literal, it has to be considered literally first.
You see, most people, like, for example, the biblical text doesn't get the respect of any other literary text.
Like, if you're reading, whether it's work of fiction, or work science, or work of history, the minute someone approaches the biblical text, oh, this is a religious thing.
Oh, this is something very, very important.
Oh, this is something, I know how it ends up, I saw the movie.
Oh, this is something.
See, it's not being viewed objectively at all, still today.
And, of course, because of the cultish nature of who people look up to, they don't know what's in the text either, I assure you on that.
But they know that it's important that you never find out what's in it.
Do you see my point?
Right.
Like, if you go to court, if you're dealing with law people, any law people, whether it's the law enforcement, which is anyway, or the attorneys, or the judges, or the legislature people, they don't know their own laws.
But they know it's important that you never find out what the laws are either.
The only thing you need to know is what we tell you, they say, and what's on TV, and obviously, what they don't say is what's on TV, and what they told you in school, and church, and whatever in the newspaper, you know, that's all you need to know.
So they actually, like, for example, use the legal cult, for example, and that's the whole thing, the attorney general, the judges, the police, the university professors that teach law, none of them know any law.
That's an assurance.
They have the appearance of knowing it.
But they know it's important that you don't know.
Now, how do you find out what the laws are?
Well, they're memorialized.
Because guess what?
You ever notice when people talk about laws, they're not a problem until they're what?
Passed, right?
Like, is it like passing gas?
Yeah, it seems like that.
No, no, they have to have the body of work memorialized in print.
And it's acknowledged as being considered insignificant, and from this date on, it's applied.
What's applied?
The passing of the gas, or the passing of what's memorialized on paper?
How many times have you heard these people pass in legislative bodies, and they don't read it?
They tell you, we don't read it, we don't need to read it, because we're going to go by plausibility, you see.
I'm telling you, there's no one in the legal side that knows any law at all.
Now, obviously, if they're putting a case together, and they have to go and try to embezzle funds or harass someone, they're going to look up some things and put it in the case and gives the appearance of it.
You see, this is very different.
This is the same now.
Let's say I'm giving you a mindset here that applies throughout.
The same thing.
They know that for X amount of years, if we cut people open and do this, they'll heal, and we could predict the way we're doing it, tell them two or three weeks.
And it works out that way, but they don't know why or what they're doing regarding that.
They just know that it's a ritual.
It's a business.
It's whatever.
Now, the same thing goes with these.
When you look at the biblical text, I can't see any other body of work that so much ignorance and inference has been applied to, or inference of ignorance has been applied to.
And it's an extremely difficult thing to speak on.
And the thing that's even more difficult is to go out and see how no one else is putting this stuff together in very, very simple terms, so anyone can just grasp it if they're interested.
That's the real sad part.
So, I mean, yeah, there's a lot of other researchers and people have done stuff, but it's like, come on, can't you speak about it on a neutral and an objective point of view that actually makes it dynamic for the listener and the user of the information?
You know, I think you and I, Sam, have discussed this.
Plenty of people have done good research, and they go back to this Christian cult, or this other cult, or whatever.
And it's like, ah, why did, you know, how do I, I have to listen to it, because the next thing they might say might be worth something, you know?
So I've learned to abandon all that stuff and use all those points that I just made to you.
And just keep in the back of your mind that the planet right now is overrun by these cult-type societies, which are at the top of every aspect of what you see called civilization, whether it's engineering, science, education, religion, legal, medical, these are all cult groups that are running it.
So, you take it, take it or leave it, you know?
No, it's fine.
Things should be that way, should it not?
Well, at this point, yeah.
It's the pinnacle of the story line, you know, of the biblical narrative, you know?
I mean, why?
Because it's the end.
It doesn't peak somewhere and then go down.
Right before it goes down, it peaks.
That's the interesting, that's another thing that's never really been discussed.
You know, I have an arc in a story line, like usually around the middle, it comes to a peak and many things are revealed or whatever, and you can see how the dynamics of that arc in the story line are going to push the rest of the story, right?
The scriptural stuff is all to wrap up this degenerative situation that humanity's in.
That does make sense.
However, what you mentioned about the leprosy thing, where do you get that from, that it's not leprosy and that it's something else?
Because I don't see that explicitly.
Yeah, what's the word that's being used?
It's S-H-something, I remember the letters in that.
Start researching that.
I think it's S-A-R-A, S-A-R-A.
S-A-R-A, thank you.
Yeah, S-A-R-A.
But it's pronounced similar to that.
But look around and see how that term keeps popping up, where you say, wait a second, that can't be leprosy then.
Look at the descriptions of it.
When someone was healed of it, it didn't say they were missing body parts, right?
Or they were disfigured from it, you see?
So look at this.
It's a very interesting...
In other words, is it important?
No, it's not important.
But is it important to see how we've misplaced that term in our minds?
Yes, that's very important.
And also the emotion.
Go ahead.
You brought up an interesting thing there, the word, and that kind of ties me into my question before about what's a good way to learn the letters, the meanings of each and every letter, so that it can help others, or even myself, just to...
This, this, and this means this, and it gives you another perspective on that particular...
Okay.
Yeah.
Etymology, or the basically root meaning of each letter, not root part of a word, but the letters themselves.
Yes.
Let me just give you a thing before I tell you.
You're on your own with that.
You just do some research on what Hebrew letters mean.
Actually, the internet is actually pretty good, because it doesn't get much better than that outside of any other convention, university or otherwise, or in print.
The reason why is, when you look up anything called New Testament, you're going to be bombarded with Christian garbage, like it or not.
Yeah.
Like it or not.
Okay, when you look up Hebrew meaning of words, you're going to be bombarded with Talmudic garbage, like it or not.
You know, occult Kabbalistic stuff, like it or not.
Okay.
You get it?
Yeah.
So you're on your own.
So in other words, if you could do research on the New Testament and filter out all the Christian crap...
Right.
You'll be able to research anywhere on anything and filter out all the Kabbalistic crap, the mystical.
I'm really with you on that, after trying it many different times, and I...
Frustration is the best way I can do it.
Are you familiar with picking edible corn out of poop?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, good.
You'll get it.
This is planet Earth.
Right.
You know what the term Kopra Faiyia is?
You don't want to do that.
Shit eaters.
Right.
So that's the best you're going to do on Earth right now.
I mean, look, and I always say this, there's still very pleasant things to do.
And if you can actually be around pleasant people, you're extremely fortunate.
I happen to be extremely fortunate in that way.
I hope you, whoever's listening is as well, because it doesn't be relevant if they're your relatives, parents, children, friends, neighbors, people are shit.
Right.
And if you don't like that, that's too bad.
That's the truth.
And you're not used to it.
So on the other hand, if you are around people that are genuinely better than that, you are truly in a good situation, right?
Then you have the food, clothing, shelter.
And this time I brought up the people first is because you could have good food, good clothing, good shelter, and guess who's going to mess it up for you?
Other people.
Yeah, yeah, you know, there's two types of people in the world, those that want to be left alone and those who won't leave them alone, right?
So and then you've got the other class, which is the majority of people are emotional.
They are so much into the censorship and the victim to censorship, which is nothing they can do about it.
And yes, sort of.
And they're so unrehabilitated that it has everything has to have some emotion behind it.
It has to be emotionally based.
How I feel, how you make other people feel.
Oh, I like the way it feels.
Oh, you know what I mean?
The garbage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, plenty of now, not that emotions or emotions can be very good.
And actually, they're necessary for the spirit to to function with ease in the body.
But when it's all emotion, it's rubbish.
And that's all you get out there, by the way, and out there, meaning in all of these cult like institutions and on the rectangle, it's it's all emotionally based.
You get you look for information.
It's emotionally based, you know?
Yeah.
While working where I work, I get to see my great abundance of of that particular thing.
And thank goodness for showers.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's it's all right.
The gods are going to take care of it, but they're going to do it within their their let's say their plan, their capabilities have to be used the way they decide to use them.
You know, the way they do them, the the the cleanup of civilization.
It is interesting to watch.
Oh, yeah, never, never a dull moment.
And the interesting thing about it, what makes the gods doing it so plausible is the level of brutality that's going to be put upon humanity will be accepted because most of it will appear to be of natural means.
So that's OK.
Sam, what else?
Do you want to you want to delve into anything else?
Have you woken up?
You know, we can pick up where we left off before.
So I think we stopped talking about this adversary.
We're in the middle of a discussion about that.
And I think one of the thoughts that I had right before we ended was this the actual wording of how we refer to him.
So Satan, when you look at the history of that word sort of throughout the English language, which isn't that long, and you try to trace it to earlier terms that they would have used before to refer to that entity.
I'm finding that the word Titan pops up a lot and that there seems to be this kind of connection between Titans and the Satan, the Hebrew word Satan.
There's obviously phonetic similarities.
If you look at the fact that Titan at one point was called Teton.
And, you know, there's some books on that.
I wouldn't necessarily recommend it.
But obviously, Alexander Hislop's The Two Babylons is a pretty famous one.
It gets some things right.
It gets a few things wrong.
But I thought I might just quote shortly from it.
The learned reader has no need of examples in proof of this frequent Chaldean transformation of the sh or se into te.
For the common reader, the following may be adduced.
You have the Hebrew word shekel, to weigh, which becomes tekel in Chaldean.
The Hebrew word shebar, to break, becomes tebar in Chaldean.
The Hebrew word seraphim in Chaldean becomes teraphim, and so on and so forth.
The Teton was actually known by the classic nations of antiquity to be Satan, or the spirit of wickedness.
And he goes on with that.
And there's other writers, like Irenaeus, the church father, who says, though the name Teton was originally derived from Chaldean, it became thoroughly naturalized in the Greek language, which is interesting to see that the word Titan doesn't even come from Greek.
Well, let me just interject something.
When you look at the bullshit education system on any level, they tell you that the language and alphabet started where?
In Phoenicia, which is just a blanket area in the Levant, you know what I mean?
So where did the Greeks come from?
Well, in other words, before Egypt, who was the sister nationality to the Greeks, if not the origin of the Greeks?
Phoenicia.
Cyprus.
Yeah, so it's kind of like the Latin countries in Europe.
But you have the sea, let's just say.
Yeah, but here, let me interject something else for people to mention.
This is important.
Just like I mentioned, when you read the God of what they call the Bible, that is not just that.
That is the God of the gods.
So you have the gods commissioned as such, and they control the physical reality that we experience at this time, and previous times also, meaning older times, days of old.
And if you were to go into their realm and walk down the street like you would here in any society and say, do you guys have a god?
And they would say, yes.
Their god is the god that we're reading about.
Keep that in mind.
It's sort of a difficult thing for people to ingest, meaning to get in, not ingest, meaning to joke about.
But to keep that in mind.
That's why there's so little information.
The narrative is almost stripped of detail, even though there's still a lot of detail in it, because of that.
Now, I wouldn't say totally because of that.
Because we have this God of the gods going through the society of the gods, and then coming here with this information.
By agency.
Now, let me ask you, this is another thing that people have to keep in mind.
When you go on the Stupid Rectangle, or you talk to other people, they talk about Satanists.
That is totally, completely erroneous.
What most people on the internet are referring to as Satanism is not.
What they're referring to in reality, and you could dissect this on your own, is the revival.
When you read about all these Satanic cults, all they are really is revived ancient balls or deities from ancient cultures, like Egypt and so on.
That's not Satanism.
Because if you look at the narrative, this entire realm was given to Satan.
Why do you start off in Genesis always reading, or throughout scripture, that man is in a really piss poor state?
Who would create something and deliberately put it in a piss poor state?
No, that's not what's going on.
What's going on is that there is a creation, and there is a deliberate handing over of consent and power and control to this adversary to do almost like I'm suggesting here, presumptually like in the book of Job.
He says, go do whatever to him, just don't kill him.
Right?
Kind of a parallel to that.
So don't take it personally, folks.
What's going on here is this adversary is following marching orders from his God, the Most High, or the God of Gods.
And this is his time period to do what he does.
By the way, is he given that authority prior to Genesis 2, or is it after when the fall comes that he takes over?
Because that's never...
Well, it's...
No, it is and it isn't.
It seems to be oscillating back and forth.
It seems to be just like a play where you have several acts, and there is the curtain drawn in between, and you have another, you know, and then it opens and there's a new act.
It seems to be done in a series of acts, if that makes sense.
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, I think you could somewhat conclusively say that he's in the picture by Genesis 1, 2, because they're in the garden, and the garden seems to have something to do with the Nakash as far as him having authority there.
Well, having authority and he...
We don't know if he was brought there, right, or sent there, or just happened to be there and commissioned.
Or, you know, I don't...
I'm not going to say this is by chance.
It's all by design, I'm going to say.
I'll venture to say that, even though it doesn't say I designed this for it to happen, but you do see that.
He's in...
The God of the gods, that we read about as the God of the Bible, seems to have, be in control of all things.
So, yeah, it's just, you know, here's the interesting thing that's very difficult.
Let me just interject this, and you heard me say it a lot of times, and it sounds futile.
Once you start to get a firm grip on anything, whether it's law, the Bible, health, how things work, real science, you know, real observation of nature, you know what I tell people?
I said, okay, good, you're getting a grasp.
Now, who are you going to go talk to about this?
Huh?
Can you tell me?
Who are you going to go tell this to?
Some moron?
You're on your own.
Yeah, tell it to yourself.
I mean, it's for your own sake that you don't...
No, it's a rhetorical question.
There's no answer.
There's no direct answer to it, because, obviously, you could already have established...
You know, the easiest thing is, for example, if you have children, and you're homeschooling them, well, you can...
You know, but then you put them in that same position, right?
They're going to go out in the world and talk to who?
Who are they going to talk to?
Huh?
Can you answer that?
No, you can't, because it's just a condition.
And the reason I brought that up, because it interjects exactly with what we're discussing with the adversary.
You know, these idiots on this planet going around saying, oh, these guys are Satanists.
Oh, really?
So Christianity, Judaism, Islam, Buddhism is not?
All of your colleges are not?
All of your governments are not?
Is that what you're trying to say?
Idiot?
This whole thing is under his auspices, right?
So I'm playing the devil's advocate, no pun intended.
It ain't that bad, is it?
Is it?
Or it is?
Think about it for a minute.
Well, you could still go out and take a windy walk in a rose garden.
You could still get good food if you really, really try.
By the way, I'll just interject something.
I was in a conversation with someone yesterday about acquiring food.
So you ever notice when you go into a conventional store, there's no smell or it doesn't smell good?
But when you go into like what they call organic or markets, whatever, there's a beautiful fragrance in the air.
You know, you ever notice that?
When you go into a health food store, it smells good.
And when you go into like a conventional, you know, I call white people market in America, if you go in the Midwest or anywhere like that, you know, there's no life there.
But it's still not that you could still make best choices.
So this is, I've given the analogy before with Ocelli.
Like I was traveling on the road for weeks at a time.
And, you know, on the road food, you get, you know, in America, it's terrible roadside food.
You got to make, you know, the big fast food chain.
So it's like McDonald's, McDonald's or McDonald's or McDonald's, right?
Well, you go in there and you try to make the best choice.
You know, I'll get some French fries and apple pie and a coffee maybe, right?
You don't go, oh, it's McDonald's.
I have to eat a Big Mac or a cheeseburger or something, you know, no.
Maybe I'll get a fish sandwich or something.
So no matter what situation you're put in, you could always make the best choice.
And sometimes the best choice is the way you behave.
So.
Pertaining to what you said about the Most High God, I think it's worth pointing out, that perhaps, well, not perhaps, but most likely why there's such an antagonism or disaffection for most people when it comes to understanding his place in the hierarchy, as far as being the God of the gods, is because he really doesn't seem to make any concrete appearances in the text itself.
He's always using a proxy.
So you can say that, well, he's creating a family and he's doing this, that and the third, but he really doesn't show up at all.
Why should he?
He's smart.
Look at it.
Look at everything.
You ever read about the things, there's certain rituals in scripture regarding the law and the priesthood that, you know, if a garment touches a piece of, you know, dead flesh, doesn't matter what it is, is that garment clean or unclean?
It's unclean, right?
So this is beyond, he's very, he's very smart and he's very specific.
And he sees things that the other gods don't see, by the way.
Right.
So there's archetypes there.
When you say that, did he see the division in the higher realm then?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, okay, so that...
The gods are, okay, the world of the gods is in a mess.
Simple.
You want to make it rhetorical?
Don't ask me how and why.
I'm just saying it rhetorical.
The heavenly realm, where all the gods are, is a total mess.
And they have a god that they look up to for order and design and power.
And that god that they look up to is the one that we're reading about in what they call the Bible.
And, but you can't mix this with the stupidity that's in the world again.
I mean, like, for example, you go to Christianity.
Oh, yeah, we got this rebellious son.
He's a total rebel.
And he comes over here and he says all of his father's laws are undone.
And, you know, but he's like his father, you know, schizophrenic, you know, son.
You know, if you listen to the religions of the world, especially Christianity, this J-E-S-U-S guy, you know, you got to lock him up, shoot him up with some Prozac because he's insane.
He's schizophrenic, you know?
Yeah.
So, I mean, this is what's being put in front of you.
The opposite.
I think I've talked about any situation in any condition of any field that man engages in is just absurd at this point, right?
You want to look at psychiatry, medicine, legal, science.
It's just absurd across the board.
So, why wouldn't your religious doctrines be absurd?
You see, so it's normal to be absurd.
So, again, of course he's going to do this all by proxy.
That's why, for example, when you read about the biblical Christ, which has nothing to do with the Christian and their 20,000 denominations or anything like that.
He came and he did everything in secret.
As a matter of fact, his identity is still secret today.
Everything about him is still a secret today.
But as time goes on, a certain group of people, which his physical stock came from, will be more and more interested in it.
And they're the ones that are holders of better records, you see?
And you will actually learn more about the biblical characters from the people of that lineage.
So, and you're only going to learn enough that when the kill shots come, you have enough that the kill shots are lawful, because they're not going to do the kill shots now, because no one knows anything.
So, later on, the gods don't want to say, well, look, you know, all these sniveling humans will say, we didn't know what was going on.
We were lied to by the attorneys, the doctors, the preachers, the professors.
They lied to us.
You know, so why did you come and take us out?
We were right there.
We had a chance to do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
They don't want to hear that.
So you're going to get enough correct and true information that when they do clean this situation up, and after the resurrection, no one will be able to say, well, we didn't have a chance.
You see how simple this is?
They have a last minute chance with getting better corn out of the poop.
Well, you're going to get enough corn, so you could say you didn't go hungry, right?
But some of it's actually going to be very fresh as well.
The analogy is like someone on death row.
If you go on death row anywhere in the world, and you ask everyone there, why are they there?
They'll tell you why.
But if you run into someone, and they don't know why they're on death row, they're going to take them off and run them through court all over again, and they have to acknowledge everything all along the way.
That's why when you go to anything lawful or legal, you have to acknowledge it.
You ever see some contracts where they make you initial on each page that you read it?
Oh, yeah.
So later on, you can't argue and say, well, I didn't read that page.
See?
So yeah, this is a very short thing.
All you have to know is certain key aspects of what, you know, certain lawful aspects of the gods, and that's it.
And all you really have to acknowledge is what you've been told that came before you actually really happened.
That's all.
And then you're actually, now it's time then after to, the mouth poop crew can come in.
So is there any of that information that exists out here now that it's so, what you're saying is it's just buried with so much poop.
But the truth is...
No, no, it exists.
You could, here, just pick up the King Jimmy or NIV or anything, and ask yourself, read an underbridged version.
They tell you everything that they're going to do to you in your mind in the introduction, right?
And then you're going to say, okay, this is no good.
So I better go find where they got it from.
And now it's easily accessible because of the electronic convention.
Very simple.
Look, let me give you another metaphor.
How many people are being arrested right now every minute or every hour for drug possession in the US?
It could be 5, 10 already since we brought it up.
How many people are sitting in jail?
Do you know that, and when you ask them, why am I being arrested or thrown in prison?
Because it's a criminal act, right?
To possess, you know, 20 tons of heroin or joint, anything in between, right?
Right.
It's a criminal act.
Well, haven't I given the code and the public law that shows that that's been decriminalized?
Yes, you have.
It's only civil now?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so...
I'm going to hold up.
Do you think, go ahead.
What exactly is the thing in that law, Public Law 98-473?
Is it that Section 1 is declassified because that offers up all the definitions?
So that's gone, or is it because the...
No, US, what it did was it repealed Title 184201, which is criminal...
No, what it did was it repealed criminal procedures.
And those criminal...
Hold on.
Those criminal procedures were applied to various titles, and one of them being Title 21, which is food, drugs, and narcotics.
But Title...
The repealed 4201 deals with the probation office.
It deals with Title 18 crimes and prosecution, yes.
No, but I mean, specifically, it's the...
That's the probation office, though.
Like the procedure for how to get somebody that's in jail on probation.
Right, right.
So if that's repealed, what does that have to do with food and drugs?
Because if you go read the public law, I gave the website on that, it applies to all of those other titles below it.
Scroll down.
And what is...
How do you...
If it repeals...
What is probation?
Probative...
Prohibitive activities, based on what?
There's no probation...
It's to prohibit.
You engage in prohibitive activities, it's criminal.
That's all been repealed.
Go read...
You see, it's very interesting.
You know, what's interesting with the link that I've dropped in before, it's the government publishing office, and their motto is informing America, right?
Go read...
Go read that it's the decriminalization of that.
It's the repealing of that.
Yeah, I'll just go read it again, because when I look at it...
You know, you guys called it 24, right?
Title 24?
No, no, 18.
Yeah, in other words, that has to do with prosecution and criminal acts.
And it applies to all those other titles as well.
Go ahead.
So there's a bunch of sections that have been repealed, and section one is one of them, and then section 4201 up to 4218.
Section one of title 18.
But what you're talking about is 4201 to 4218.
What I'm talking about is title 21.
There are various titles underneath that have also been repealed, according to that being repealed.
Okay.
Title 21 has to do with food, drugs, and narcotics.
And there's many other things in there too.
There's title 18 stuff.
There's title 30 stuff.
I mean, it goes all the way down through.
So what I'm trying to say here is they're going to give you the information, but is it clear?
Obviously not too clear, is it?
Because you have to go into the definition side of it, right?
Right.
And that's what we're talking about tonight.
You're trying to...
I think what you're...
The last time we spoke also, what we're speaking about tonight, is trying to define who this adversary is.
And that's a good thing.
I like that when we get into discussions about defining things, because you can't really use it unless it's defined.
Yeah.
Let's put the title, whatever it is.
I'll look into that again, because I had some trouble.
No, no, you should.
You should.
Did you ever pick up the link that I dropped in from the GPO, Government Publics, the Government Printing Office?
Yeah, I went to that site.
I looked through that stuff.
Yeah, that's right.
They do it very clearly.
I mean, it's not very clear, but they list all the titles that it affects underneath it.
But I was just trying to find a specific line that references that, or says that.
I dropped it into Skype.
Go ahead and find a specific line.
You know the concept of something being holographic, right?
If you put it in one specific line in scripture, for example, bounce back to that, all you have to do is redact that line, and you lost all the information.
But if you don't make it specific, and you put it throughout the entire context, you see it keeps showing up again, you see?
So the idea is that Title 18 is partly repealed, and that repeals Title 21.
The criminality of it.
Yeah, you could still be prosecuted civilly, though.
But civil prosecution is different.
Civil prosecution would be like a neighbor's dog bites you.
You go to the neighbor, and he doesn't want to do anything to make it right.
Now that's a civil action.
You don't go to jail for that, you know?
So the entirety of 21 is repealed?
You're dealing with out there.
All right, so let's say someone has a boat, and they're going from South America to the US, and it's full of white powder.
And here come the authorities, and they stop it.
And they're going to charge you with criminal.
No, no, no, no, it's civil.
So the people that stop them have to put a civil case.
Well, I'm upset.
You've done, you know, the Coast Guard official has to say, well, I got mental damage because he had this white powder.
So he has to go to, you see, it doesn't make any sense now.
The whole thing shows you what's going on.
You see, what they're actually doing, when it comes to narcotics and drugs, and all the other codes that you'll see there, is they're using libel, and admiralty, and seizure laws that have been in place for thousands of years, or really codified since the 1500s, you see?
So they'll probably take every, see, let me give you an example.
And you'll find this in older court cases.
When any authority or someone else comes and takes your stuff, right, what makes it your stuff?
Well, it's in your possession.
That's under admiralty.
The taking of stuff is admiralty.
Like, it could be, or maritime if it's in the ocean.
Like it or not.
Now, I don't like to get into that too much because it's been muddied up.
You know, when you go online, all these patriots, you know, we gotta, you know, restore the republic.
Really, if the republic was so good, why did you end up being a democracy?
You see, none of that stuff is worthwhile.
But the point here is very simple.
Everything is so muddied up right now that you just go along with it, you know, waste your time because you are gonna just, you take up your time until you don't have any more left.
Or figure out what's really going on and learn to set yourself apart from it.
And maybe figure out what the right thing to do is on the way.
Because let me just go back to one more thing.
This is what, this is the cult mentality that's really screwed humanity.
And there are various cults, like I mentioned earlier, every aspect of society.
When it comes to lawfulness or law, the concept of law, meaning morality, what you do and how you act, that comes from your God.
Your, I didn't say God, did I?
So, your God.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Let's get back to the Satan stuff.
So, just to quickly quote from Hislop again, because he has another interesting thing here.
Teton is just a Chaldean form of Shaitan, the very name by which the Satan has been called by time immemorial by devil worshippers in Kurdistan.
Which is also interesting, because you look into the Yazidi religion and they actually do worship the devil.
But they try to fudge with that and say, no, they don't, but they actually do.
The history of the Teton and his brethren is given by...
Go back under the Yazidis, the ones that worship the peacock.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah.
And they know that they're referring to that as Satan, a form of Satan.
But then when you try to talk to them about it, I just think it's funny that these try to fudge or try to divert the conversation.
Right.
But yeah, he's meant to represent Satan to them.
The history of Teton and his brethren as given by Homer and Hesiod.
Homer says that all of the gods of Tartarus were called Tetons in his Iliad book.
And Hesiod tells us that these Tetons have their dwelling in Tartarus also.
As in future tense.
Yeah, but they're equating the Tetons with the Satan in this case.
It's plausible, but it's rhetorically very different than the scriptural text.
But should it be denied?
No.
Should it be considered?
Yes.
How well or not it meshes with the biblical text, I would just say that the universal being that manages and controls and affects everything that we've ever come in touch with is this being, the adversary.
With intervention, of course.
There's a form of policing that is done also.
You ever heard of people have a guardian angel or they were saved from something that was malicious?
So there's an intertwining here of that.
Right.
And I'm just trying to point to that intertwining, not to say that there's a one-to-one ratio of correlation between the Titans and the Satan.
They're obviously different things.
Oh, yeah, there's many of them.
I would suggest to go back and consider that all the national borders were defined by these entities known of the sons of gods or the gods in basic form.
Basic form meaning from that society, right?
Not their god, not the most high god, but under their direction, under his direction.
I mean, yeah.
Also, interestingly, when you look at Etsy online, if you Google Titan for Etsy online, it says the name is perhaps from Tito, sun or day as in S-U-N, which probably is a loan word from a language of Asia minor.
So that sort of hammers to that point a bit.
So here we see that the word Titan could have originally been a way of designating the sun god.
Whoever the sun god is, he's obviously a key character in the spiritual hierarchy someplace.
Most major religions worship him in some form and there's a book called Christian Iconography by Adolf Hitler, which describes three different 10th century statues of Satan with a nimbus around his head.
So apparently that was an emphasis at one point in time that you could equate Satan with the sun god.
Though I wouldn't say that they're the same entity, but we don't really get much exposition about the sun.
No, there's a mixture.
There's a lot of mixing there.
There's a film, I forgot what it's called, the first lie Satan propagated was that he doesn't exist.
So I would suggest that's an interesting thing to lean on because true power is never really known.
And this is a dichotomy statement, meaning the true power on this planet is the adversary to mankind and the natural world.
And then there are other forces because there are other gods.
There are gods that come and bring sickness.
There are gods that bring death.
They each have their specific purpose.
But then you have the most high god that is allowing all of this by design of some kind that we are not given.
And it's fine.
It doesn't mean that because we don't know exactly, we shouldn't discuss it.
But I think that we know enough to lead what we can consider a more proper life.
And there's nothing wrong with waking up every day crying that you're on this planet.
Because that's actually a thing in scripture.
Also, not that you wake up every day crying that you're here.
But you know what I mean?
You and everyone you've ever heard of has been born, raised, and died in a battle zone, a spiritual battle zone.
So get over it.
And of course, there's the aspect of maturity.
Obviously, man is still, man as a whole, meaning woman also, is in an immature state spiritually.
But there are still people out there, believe it or not, in the world that have a woe-is-me attitude because of what's going on in their head.
And one of the first things that I did with Ocelli was called external input.
And I gave maybe a half a dozen examples on how if you're, let's say, out in the park or the beach and someone's playing jazz, on a radio, do you expect to open that radio and find a little jazz band in there?
Or are you going to see a whole bunch of circuitry that doesn't make any sense when you reference it directly to what you're hearing as being jazz music?
It would be the latter.
If you crack someone's head open or an animal that has a personality or anything, all you're going to see is all this quote unquote gray matter, right?
Because you're receiving and transmitting all external input.
And there's still people out there, believe it or not, they could listen to Greek-speak for the rest of their lives.
If I started speaking in 1940, which I wasn't around by, they'd still be thinking, woe-is-me because of what's going on in my P-brain.
That's part of the censorship.
They can't grasp.
Wilhelm Reich talked about the emotional armoring, that everything is coming from somewhere else and going to somewhere else, out.
There's nothing in you.
And that's another thing of the bad doctrine.
And the New Agers love it.
By the way, if you want to know something is really dumb, listen to the New Agers.
They borrow a lot of stuff from Christian doctrine.
You know, God is within you and all this other stuff that's not in the text.
That's very bad translation.
So, there's nothing in you.
It's all receiving and broadcasting.
That's very interesting.
When it comes to the subject of, say, possession, we can perhaps get into that later.
The vessel.
It's very simple.
Let's just say it real quick.
Most people are spiritually oppressed.
It's very rare to be spiritually possessed.
When a being possesses someone, what they do is they take over the metabolism and the body, which means the voice and everything else, and they put in dormancy the spirit.
They just turn it off.
So, when someone comes out of being possessed, they don't remember anything.
It's just as if they were churned off, like a fuse went off.
You know, when a fuse breaker goes off or something, everything that it was powering is off.
So, basically what happens is they throw the switch on your spirit.
Your spirit goes into complete unconsciousness, and then they hit another switch in real time.
You might pass out and come to with the other spirit now animating you.
Right.
I mean, since we're on this point of intersection, we might as well look at how these two different things interact with Satan on one hand, and then this possession thing.
So, you've stated multiple times that Satan will possess a certain human being for the first time in the form of the Antichrist.
Hold on.
Let me just interject.
He's about 20 years old right now.
So, go ahead.
I don't know if that's accurate at all, because, I mean, in Luke 22, we clearly see a statement to the effect that Satan possesses Judas, yet Satan entered into Judas, called Iscariot, being of the number of the 12.
And then he goes and talks to the chief priests and so on.
So, are we saying that Judas was unconscious during this, if it was a possession as it says?
I'm just giving as a rudimentary functional perspective.
No, in other words, I'm giving them the mechanism.
It can happen so fast that someone observing this will not see any unconsciousness, but the being that's being possessed is not conscious of it.
No.
Right.
So, then Judas is unconscious as he goes and talks to the chief priests.
Well, he had to be, because otherwise it would be both Satan and Judas together, both spirits in one body.
That's an interesting thing.
I mean, I don't see any part of the text where he kind of has any sort of self-reflection over what he's doing as if, well, I don't remember doing that.
It's, we're not really giving any insight into what his personal thoughts are.
Isn't it interesting how the entire biblical narrative, the entire thing is like that, where we find from our own human current perspective to lack the detail that we might think about as being important, lacking in the narrative.
And I'm telling you, there's several reasons for it being lacking.
And one of them was, it's a message coming from the gods of the gods.
And the other thing is, it's also we have a lot of social declinations that we're experiencing now.
A lot of the things that are what we consider to be normal, that we want to know now, are actually quite abnormal back then, or things that are not known anymore.
And for good reason, believe it or not.
Yeah.
But this possession, what's interesting about this Antichrist, or instead of Christ figure, is it seems to be perpetual after a certain time, you know, that when he gets possessed by, he remains in him, right?
That's why, you know, it states that Satan is also thrown in the lake of fire.
You see, because he's still there with the Antichrist.
Hmm.
So there's an interesting point on all this, regarding the psyche, which is the spirit.
And how do you say it?
You know, you know, the concept of biogenesis, life makes more life, you know, right?
You can't make life out of inorganic soup.
So the interesting thing of the mechanisms of the spirit, no matter how high up you go in the technological sense, also, let me give you an example.
If you're in a room right now with like, what they call Black Ops Lab, you know, a mile underground, and these guys get all the black budget funding, and they want to be able to take a spirit and play with it, you know, using, they're not going to use technology.
They're going to pull out a bunch of manuals and grimoires and things that are written on human skin, or parchment, or whatever that are centuries old.
I'm serious, even today.
Because you work with the spirit, the spirit is controlled by the spirit, just like life is controlled by life, or generated by life.
So don't believe that they're going to take someone's mind or spirit and put it in a machine, or take a machine and make it a spirit, unless a spirit wants to go into it, right?
Let me give you another example.
This is around the topic, it's sort of like bouncing around, maybe sounds like trivia.
There was a guy a while back, I heard of this before it got on The Rectangle, it got on The Rectangle for a little while.
He was a consultant to a pharmaceutical company, one of these big ones on the East Coast.
And he walked in one day real early in the morning, it was before dawn or so, and to get some start on some work.
And he noticed a light in one of the rooms, it might've been another floor or the same floor, and he went in there and he found all the high, you know, the high level people of the company doing like one of these dark magical seance type things, to evoke power.
No, I'm serious.
Yeah, yeah.
Why would they be doing that?
Yeah, why?
Because, you know, there's a very deep attachment to quote unquote pharmaceuticals and the spiritual reality, right?
And vice versa.
So, and it's right in front of everyone, they just don't see it.
And there's also references in biblical text about it, directly and indirectly.
So, I would suggest that matters of the spirit are controlled by the spirit and of the spirit, you see.
And good science in that realm, it will never be done in the current society because of that.
A perfect example is go to any psychologist or shrink, or psychologist or psychiatrist, and, you know, initialize the conversation, say, oh, so you're a spiritualist, you know, once they claim the profession.
They'll look at you and they're like, I don't know what that means.
I don't know what you're saying.
They don't even know what their own, the label of their own profession means.
Do you think you're going to get anything beyond that?
Oh my.
Do you know what one of the, because that's what psyche means, spirit.
Do you know that the, I think Freud, what a joker, talk about bizarre individual, just like most of them are, if you look at what they put in front of you.
When he was making his trip to the states to lecture on psychology, you know, one of the informal comments he made to people is we're going to America to bring this plague known as psychotherapy to them.
That's how naive, I mean, that's why, you know, if you've got great ideas, you'll find yourself wrestling a counter current in this society.
It doesn't matter if it's your own family, neighbor or the institutions, you know, like let's say you can figure out how to do magnetic and copper windings, you turn the motor on and it just keeps running, doesn't turn off.
That's a great thing, is it?
No, you're in a world of hurt now, because it goes contrary to what everyone believes and thinks how things should be.
But if you try to figure out something that'll cheat people, embezzle from people and hurt them, oh yeah, a lot of doors will open for you right away.
You know, Greek, I was just wondering here, it seems that we're coming up about an hour and a half, if we wouldn't mind taking a little pause, get ourself a beverage or so, give the throat a rest and let's see.
Five minutes or so.
Yeah, we'll come back at about 10 o'clock at my time here.
Okay, perfect, thanks.
Alrighty.
See you in a bit.
See you guys in a bit.
Bye-bye.
Okay, bye.