Here we go, we can go on, man.
Just the Greek.
And greeting folks, and we're live with the Greek.
And good evening.
Greetings.
How are you doing?
Doing okay.
Excellent.
And we're streaming.
This is the other, this is the backyard outhouse streams or whatever that Bruce has been running.
And I don't know if we've got, we have a new chat, so I would like mentioning that because people do ask, you know, I didn't know there was a new chat because they somehow bookmarked the Sonic events, right?
And they don't know there's another chat unless they hear me say it.
And the reason we left, eventually there was just a couple of trolls and one 40-year-old that lives at home with his mom just decided to hang around for a week and make everyone's life miserable.
So we started a new chat.
So if you're interested in that new chat, you email UncommonSenseRadio1 at gmail.com.
It's a numeric one and we'll tell you where it is.
So we normally, people come in and listen to these streams and we get quite a few, right Bruce?
Based on the server, based on- Yep.
Based on the server and activities, and it's been going strong and steady since that last event by the way.
And it has not let up, you know, you have your low areas like right, you know, in your very early morning hours, but after that it picks right up and it's been going since.
So that's good.
That means there's people paying attention.
And I'll give you a little highlight, Greg, I had a fellow over here last night for doing a repair on his laptop, he had a Windows 10, was locked out of it basically.
And I started talking to him about some of your stuff and I says, who was first black or who was the first president in the United States?
And this is a black gentleman by the way.
And I told him here, I got your laptop fixed, go ahead and type that in on Google.
And you know how they do those double takes?
This boy did a triple.
And you guys probably can't hear me yet.
I hear you just fine, how are you doing?
Okay, there we go.
Yeah, something, just a glitch on my end.
So we've mentioned in the chat we have someone else with us tonight and we'll bring them on if anyone else is familiar with Greek speak, you probably heard the early days with Ocelli and the Greek and no drum roll necessary, no applaud necessary.
Welcome, here comes Jersey in the house, Chuck Ocelli.
Chuck, how are you, man?
Oh, well, I'm about as well as can be expected.
My friend, yeah, I do have the Jersey accent, that's for sure.
I'll just pick it out, yeah.
No, it's okay.
Look, I bring it out of you too.
So we sound a little bit similar now and then.
Not at all.
Anyway, sorry.
Here I am.
Yes, indeed.
And good to be with you tonight.
Yeah, cool.
This is just like a set of, just imagine Skype calls that Bruce happens to put up on a server and whoever goes into chat accesses them and they've been getting out far and wide.
So the reason I brought you on might as well.
So you messaged tonight that you're doing some stuff.
You want to just tell everybody what you're doing.
I mean, you got, you're producing now on your own and you're doing the Ocelli effect, right?
It's still called the Ocelli effect, right?
So yeah.
Sure is.
Well, yeah, I was just letting you know.
But hey, we might as well let everybody who is listening know that, yeah, I'm now self-produced over there.
I have the 24-7 stream as well with, you know, things that I decide to load into it, which are generally just my shows.
But a bit of music as well.
I get stuff from independent artists who are not necessarily part of the corporate structure of things out there that I appreciate.
Friends of mine, things like that, play their music a little.
But mostly it's for my shows and I do my live events over there.
And now I'm actually handling, you know, the mixing, the board, everything independently, fully.
So it is a fully functional network.
I think of that scene in Star Wars.
This is a fully operational battle station.
So ocelli.com has now become exactly that.
So yeah, I'm really glad about it.
Thank you.
And hopefully you'll crest the tide of all the sewage of the independent media.
Need a good surfboard and ride away or ride on top of it.
Don't fall into it.
Yes, I do give advice.
But yeah, so how do people get to it?
The simplest way.
Simplest way?
Well, if you have one of those, what they allegedly call a smartphone, you can easily get it through one of those radio apps like TuneIn and you just look for Ocelli.
Pretty simple.
But if you wanted to go directly to my website, it's ocelli.com, spelled O-C-H-E-L-L-I, dot com, obviously.
Then you just go to listen live and like I said, the stream is there.
And according to that wind up toy they call a clock, at 8 p.m. on the eastern coast of the United States, guess what?
Every weekday, according to the Pope's work schedule, Monday through Friday, you can get me for two hours live and like I said, the stream does it the rest of the time.
So there you go.
Always believe it.
Get all the important stuff out as fast as possible in case life gets that short, right?
Exactly.
So okay, cool.
And basically, just a message, we don't really speak much and socialize and all that but
we did spend a lot of hours and not prenuptially either, meaning there was nothing there other
than we were showing up and doing it for two hours, and that's not the civiest, but showing
up and doing the audio stuff over at AFR and wherever else and for, I don't know, a combination
of at least 80 hours or 40 hours, more than that, let's see, 18 and 12, yeah, roughly
60 hours of stuff.
Easily.
Yeah, so 60 hours we did that we put out into this insanity known as the, I call it the internet or the stupid rectangle, right?
And believe it or not, a lot of people still use it as reference material for Greek-speak, you know what I mean?
So on that end, you did a lot of good work with me on that.
Thank you.
I use it as an introductory to help people get briefed on where to go and all this stuff.
And all those sonic events from back then are a very good stepping stone for people to get introduced to, have you ever really seen this?
Have you ever questioned it?
And it works very well.
Yeah, I find that it certainly has proven to be one of those things that I've done that causes people to begin to question a great many things.
You know, again, what did we start with?
The thing that is a constant concern, well, what day is it, you know?
And you notice, I still mention, by the way, at the top of every single show, I always say allegedly according to the calendar, this is what date it is, that thing we call a calendar.
And that is a reference to that, as a matter of fact.
How many people come back and say, what do you mean by that, Charles?
Or Chuck?
I'm sorry about the Charles thing, but Chuck, yeah?
No, very few.
Very, very few.
Yeah.
No one's paying attention.
Well, that's the interesting thing, is that over and over again, we find that people are not paying attention to, well, anything, it seems like.
Anything of substance, I should say.
And it doesn't matter what area of interest it is.
It doesn't matter if it's, you know, food, you did a lot of things with Seth about food and stuff like that, which was really great.
I mean, we did a little bit on that.
We also did a really excellent event on water that, you know, is another thing that people don't pay very much attention to.
Speaking of that, you know, one of the things I'm going to be doing this coming week, allegedly, is that a focus on Flint, Michigan still.
Why?
Because this has dropped out of the mainstream and alternative stream, if you will.
And that is an ongoing issue for people.
You know, what's interesting about that, I had that come across the desk here, let's say, right?
The proverbial, you know, when something comes in front of you, about seven or eight years ago, really six years ago, let's see, what's 2011, what they call, yeah, so it's about right.
Right.
And not for them, but in that area, we did a demo and they sent us some sample water and we sent the water back and they said, this is great.
And when we showed them how it was done, they all went silent because there was nothing to buy.
I mean, you buy something to clean up the water, but you don't have to buy it again.
Once you buy it, it's done, right?
And it uses a media, you know, a media, the water has to pass over certain different types of materials, but those materials don't ever deplete themselves, you know, like, you know, people have to throw away the water filter and get a new one after a period of time.
So it freaked them out and went away.
And I had predicted all of this when I was asked to do some water samples for that area, not Flint, Michigan.
And here's the thing that, you know, or that area of Michigan gets all the play, but there's a lot of other places nearby that have different constituents in the water.
Maybe not as bad, but just as bad generally, right?
You wouldn't want to drink it, meaning, right?
It's not drinkable.
Well, in fact, if people are really paying attention and they were actually checking the contents of the water, there is anywhere from 300 to 3000 communities that are probably in the same shape as Flint, if not worse, depending on how it is you want to put it on the scale.
So truthfully, there's a lot of areas where water needs to be improved.
If people are going to consume it, certainly it would be advisable for a lot of things to be gotten out of it.
I mean, and we're not even discussing the nuclear waste issue or, you know, the chemical contaminants that have been leached into the ground via this, that, the third thing.
I mean, literally speaking, there are water systems all over the place that because of their, what should we call it?
Let's say, lack of management.
Yeah.
Well, I think it's management.
And decomposition, right?
Well, it's like a sick body.
If you keep doing what you're doing, you're going to stay sick.
So the easiest way to heal something is just change your behavior.
No doctor is going to tell you what your behavior is because they only know you for the short visit or whatever history you put down on what looks like a government form.
So, but in essence at this point, and from a remedial point of view, the water can be cleaned up instantly, and they just don't want it.
It just goes across the board.
It's not just the water, it's all around, right?
Informationally, I think the biggest problem is the way the mind or the spirit is guided, right?
You know, you guide that with words and thoughts and sentiments, right?
So, but here's the thing.
If you've got bad water in the physical world, everything else in the physicality of that world falls apart, believe it or not.
Whether you're drinking it or not, your food quality goes down and the actual environment becomes toxic, just like if you go near a swamp, how it stinks.
So yeah, it's not for this society.
But give another example, and this is sort of bragging rights.
Could you imagine going to a petrochemical company, and you know how they skim off all the water on the oil that goes to the top, and they skim it off, and it's still constituents in the water?
Could you imagine assembling a device where they run the oily water, which smells like rotten eggs, the SO2, sulfur hydroxide, and all that stuff?
Could you imagine sending the oil to the bottom, and on top you have crystal clear drinkable water?
Could you imagine what happens to the engineers when they see that?
Oh my.
Because oil always goes to the top, right?
Yeah, well, I mean, again, you know a little bit of my background.
I've actually worked in that industry, and that would be one of those things that they would not believe if they saw it happen.
Yeah, they have, yeah.
And we used to do that, actually.
There's a quote-unquote secret website around, it's in Asia, and they have all the samples and the stuff, because this was going to be used, you know, the largest petrochemical processing companies in the world are in China.
People would say, well, it doesn't sound right, because we never heard about it, right?
So anyway.
Yeah, but then again, I dare anyone to understand that there's a great many things happening in China that they've never heard about, you know, so.
Yeah, well, let's give a quick history, because I used to communicate with this guy who was an Air Force guy, I wouldn't say all the way up, but high colonel, you know, whatever.
And whenever you bring up China, he says, oh, no, that's America's mortal enemy, and I always just have to give them the five-minute history lesson, and anyone could look this up.
What happened during the early FDR administration, they were promoting communism, yes, you heard me say it.
And what they went in there is they promoted, they went through various false flag operations and subversion operations to meddle with the affairs of the Chinese and the Japanese in the 30s, who were basically at war in various capacities, right?
So FDR went there, and he set up the communist government, no, it's not that the communist governments got together and FDR supported it, no, FDR set it up.
And if anyone wants to go and look at old World War II posters or 1930s posters, you'll see a cartoon of FDR and a government poster shaking, you know, someone in a communist, the party, socialist party uniform, that we have to create this to fight Japan, right?
This is in the 1930s now.
Everyone thinks fighting Japan started in 41.
So they ousted the monarchy in China to the island of Formosa, Taiwan, which was given to them from Japan, right?
And China was completely started, as it is today, by FDR. That's why even today they have what's called the one China policy.
There is no official diplomatic relations with Taiwan, right?
When you say, when the Americans diplomatically deal with that part of the world known as China, they include Taiwan, but they don't have any direct diplomatic official recognition.
So when people say they, because the Chinese are communists, this, that, and the other, its entire inception started in what's called Washington DC in the FDR administration.
It sounds kind of bizarre, I know.
But if you start looking at history from the 1930s, you'll find that.
So I just wanted to throw that in there because, you know, the mentality is schizophrenic when you say China, well, they're communists, we're not, so we're enemies, or how can we be working so closely together?
So I just want to throw that in there.
Anyway, is everybody still here?
Yeah, I am.
I just, I had to call them and Skype wouldn't allow me to get out of it there for a second.
So that's fine.
Sorry about that.
But the Middle East is really where it's going to happen, but it's going to happen in a way that you're, you know, it'll have to be normal, right?
Well, I'd like to step back on something you just said a moment ago, because here's, here's where, you know, you and I can converge a bit and maybe roll this one around because it's about awareness as far as I'm concerned.
The Roosevelt family, indeed, have been very curiously linked to a lot of the establishments of various governments, the overthrow of various governments, a hugely significant family that is not often brought up when people start discussing all of their conspiracy theories and things about those who actually run the world.
You know, somebody might say, well, that sounds a little bit out of line, Greek.
That can't be true because, you know, the Roosevelt's fine.
You have these two here that were president at one time and this and that, and maybe, you know, somebody's grandson went and did something, this kind of thing.
But the truth is that if you start to really take a look at the genealogical family tree there, they, for a very long time, played a significant role.
Now, I don't know what that really means, why it is in particular that family line did that.
I haven't gotten that far in my studies.
The Delanos.
Look at the Delano, not the Roosevelt name, more, and you'll see the Delano stretches into various, you know, the tree, you know what I mean?
Right.
Okay, so you knew that, right?
But essentially, yeah, instead of looking for Roosevelt, you'll see who else had Delano family in them.
But the interesting thing is what the hypocrisy within the moderation of moderncy, being modern, contemporary, you know how I say that, you know, the world, everyone says the world's going to end in a week, and when it doesn't, you ask them why, you know, I said that was last week, it doesn't matter.
But they were freaking out at the time.
To put the Roosevelt's, well, the entire hypocrisy of the independent alternative media assess pool is this, in a nutshell.
They're all complaining.
I shouldn't say all, but typically in the political side of the conspiratology, alternative and independent media, that you're always going to hear what being brought up, the Bushes and the Clintons.
And I am telling you, based on the facts, that the Bushes and the Clinton families and dynasties are Cub Scouts, not even Boy Scouts, Cub Scouts compared to what FDR had going on in the 1930s.
No, absolutely true.
That's why I always find it laughable.
Certainly they're worthy of mention because they are relatable figures that people have seen images of and know who they are, but they're not the real big players.
And I've tried to explain this over and over again, and quite honestly, people are way too satisfied with their easily repeatable nonsense.
And again, this is why I refuse the label alternative entirely now.
I've even removed the idea of being the alternatives alternative from my website and things.
Literally now, the slogan is the revelation through conversation.
Well, the alternatives alternative was good while it lasted though.
Well, I thought it was fair enough, but then when I started thinking about it, I don't even want to be the alternative to that nonsense, because as you said, what is the alternative to a cesspool?
Well, it might be a leach field, and it still stinks.
So not digging it.
Yeah, but the bottom line, that's humanity.
That's what they want, you see?
You know, that's the sad thing.
That's the sad lesson, right?
Is that when taking a look at these things, and if I started to really dig into and went into the entire genealogy and went in the direction, which by the way, you know you've just bought me another week's worth of research, right?
By telling me to look at the Delano name instead of Roosevelt.
But the thing is, you try and tell people this, and they dismiss it because it doesn't sound like the crap they're used to.
You know, it's just, people become accustomed to anything, even if it is toxic, even if it is poisonous, and again, back to the water, well, it makes entirely good sense that people want to drink poisoned water, actually, because that would be one of the most essential elements there is in life, most misunderstood, and you don't get to continue on very many days without it.
A lot of other things you can live without outside of that, and it is so essential.
Of course, people are going to ignore exactly how it's delivered, where it comes from.
All they want to know is that they can twist a spigot and something that appears to be right is given to them, and this is one of those things that I've always understood, in a way, but quite honestly, it's through discussions with you that they become so blatantly obvious to me that this is not exactly the planet I wish to be on, considering who seems to be in charge.
Well, the thing is, who's in charge is fitting.
I have no problem with the people in charge.
I have a problem with the gods that the people worship.
Let me say that again.
This sounds convoluted.
This is not plus or minus, this is like quadratics, right?
You got order of operations, you know, you can't just attack the math problem straight on, you have to look at the order of operations, multiplication and division first, right?
So it literally meant that way.
The gods that the people have brought into their lives, literally, what rules their lives
from the calendrical system to their holidays, to their houses of worship, to their laws
is the problem, because now they become hostage to that, and if anyone thinks that a spiritual
being cannot take control of someone else's mind, even in plural, a group of people's
mind is totally ignorant of that realm, right?
So once that happens, it's obvious that the leadership is going to be extracted from that group.
Now, if you had a leader, let's say, that came from another planet, like, you know, the aliens invade from another planet in the sci-fi movies and you have an alien king or whatever, yeah, that, you know, then I would say the leader is the problem, but essentially the function here is the gods that the people have chosen are the problem.
And because of that, there might, you see, so, but that's a tall statement for most people, because you're talking about something they know what?
Nothing about.
And that's on top of other problems.
You have Satan, which is on top of them, gods that they're bringing into their lives.
So you're, you're convoluting the problem.
Well, here's a simple way to do it.
Imagine you saw, you had spiritual eye, right?
You know how people can see auras and, you know, I'm not going to say it, but let's just say there are people that could see things on people like a parasite.
Like imagine, imagine an 18 inch tall anthropomorphic figure on someone's shoulder all the time, but no one else could see it, but you can see it in the room, right?
Kind of freaky.
But anyway, yes, a parasite hanging on, right?
Okay.
But so if that's what, that's what you have on the people, but the planet itself now from a spiritual point of view, from let's say a super fantasy point of view, right?
Release your mind from what you're used to seeing.
Imagine each planet that could be habitable, meaning some form of terraforma has a throne over it.
And just like, what is it?
What is it?
The Knights of, was it King Arthur, whoever, whoever can pull the sword out of the rock has the power, right?
Or whatever.
Well, whoever physically occupies that throne is now king of that planet.
That's how the game works.
You remember our children, you know, you know, you have to make it to home base, whoever touches it first or musical chairs, it's not whether you have the authority or not at this point.
So the earth has a throne.
I know this sounds Greek.
You need some, you know, you know, you have whatever vivid imagination, right?
That's what most people are going to say.
The earth has a throne and guess who sits in that throne is the adversary.
Now what is given to the nations are the sons of gods, lesser gods or different rank.
And their job is to create the borders and the boundaries and the nationalities of the people.
You know, like if you removed all the borders in Europe, you know, obviously Europe is very different than Asia or Africa, but within Europe you have specific borders of all the various countries.
There's a God over that does that.
People look at geographic maps and they think it's just, you know, ink squirt on paper or pixels on a screen now, right?
I'm telling you there is an entity behind that.
So that's something that is not for this audience, only for the well-studied one, not the religious ones, by the way.
So I just wanted to bring that up.
So because when Bruce, you interjected, you know, Satan or the adversary, and when you say Satan, hopefully it doesn't bring any kind of a Hollywood vision or meme in mind, because that's all false.
Yeah.
He's actually, if you were to encounter a being known as the adversary, he would be the most attractive being to you, but you would find him being contrary to almost everything that you said.
You said up, he'd say down.
You say pretty, he says ugly.
You say hot, he says cold, and indirectly.
So and then you have the nation.
So when you have like the United States or Canada or all the various, what is it, 300,
185 countries officially, and it's really like 300 or 200 and something countries, that's
right there as several hundred other minor entities, which we know historically of the
future, there's some place in some ancient writ that talks about the entire world will
come under this goddess religion that has principles and morals and ethics that came
out of Babylon, let's say, right?
And you see that personified in law.
So anyway, that's the visuals of that.
Oh, of course.
You know, with that in mind, I have something that I'd like to bring up here, which is a topic I'm beginning to wrestle with during some of my discussions, and to be quite honest with you, very few people want to engage on it, because they only go so far with the discussion.
They don't get into the esoteric aspects of it so much as I would like them to, because I'd like to hear some ideas about it.
I've been looking at artificial intelligence in general, and this concept that there are individuals who are, through their work, bringing this to fruition or have brought it to fruition or are still bringing it to fruition, depending on how it is you look at it, quite honestly, who have stated quite boldly and publicly that they do not believe in a god, but they are creating it.
On the one hand, I figure this is, you know, hubris, but on the other hand, I also find it to be logical, and here's a hint, by the way, anything which seems to have an order, whether you understand it or not, generally does have some entity tied to it.
So, there's a quick hint, by the way, when looking at a map and you say, well, there's some kind of order here, it doesn't really make sense, it seems to be a bit chaotic, whatever, as far as the borders being drawn.
No, there's an order to it, it's just not in your language, it's in theirs.
So here's the thing, when people talk about this and the ethereal aspects of it, they don't want to go very far.
Some people just want to deal with it as, I'm either scared of it or I'm not, I think it's a great thing.
Okay, let me interject something in here, which might direct, because eventually when you bring up AI, what's the second thing that comes up once the conversation starts to get more on the basis of what AI is based on?
What's the second thing, and I'll say it, it's what's called quantum computing, right?
You've heard of that?
Okay.
Yes.
And there's no one that can explain what that is, just like derivatives.
I can explain it, but I'm not at this point, it's so simple, it's ridiculous.
But if you're going to get into what quantum is overall, you hear that term, quantum physics and all this, right?
Right.
That's quackery.
So what you're experiencing, let me just go back now with the AI, it's just computers.
Now the difference between that is this, there's a mindset behind it, and this is why I keep speaking.
There's plenty of places you can get information if you know how to sort it, but the problem is the mindset, and that's what I like to discuss.
Where is your mind?
Does it get your mind out of the gutter?
That means you're insidious, let's say, you don't have to say it, but there's a mindset.
Okay, the mindset is very, very simple.
Let's put AI on the side, we'll go back to it in 30 seconds.
Other than AI, about a couple of years ago with all these false flags, what was the big discussion?
Second Amendment firearms, right?
Guns, this and that, right?
Sure.
Okay, now let's just stop for a second, and what is a gun?
Isn't it launching a high-speed projectile previously done with tension, like a catapult or an arrow, bow and arrow?
Slingshot, sure.
Yeah, right.
And then that form of mechanical tension got replaced with what?
High-speed chemistry.
You have a chemical compound, then it goes into a reaction, but instead of slow, it happens in so fast that it creates the shockwave to move the projectile.
Early projectiles were what?
You want to get into the ball and powder, and then you got into the cartridge bullet, and then you got into multiple firing machine guns to Gatling guns.
That's what's going on with computers.
What they're doing is sidestepping you with the idea of quantum physics, like for example, you know the double slit experiment they always talk about?
And they say, well, that's quantum.
If you're watching the experiment, the result is one way, but if you're not watching it, it's another way.
It shows your consciousness is affecting it.
It has a complete scam.
Yeah, I went into a box recently, and I had that experiment.
It doesn't happen.
That's a scam.
No one can reproduce that.
It's a lie.
That's why they only show you computer renderings of it.
You can do it yourself, and everyone buys into it, like 19 Arab hijackers with box cutters turn the World Trade Center into dust, and they buy into it.
But if you show them, it's the same thing with the prism that you see on the Pink Floyd album breaking up the...
That's not what happens when you put white light.
The spectrum doesn't break up like that at all.
You get a dark band and a white band, a dark band and a white band, and right where the black band meets the white band, you have a very narrow fringe of the spectrum happening, and I've gotten to what light is before that.
Okay, so quantum.
Whenever you hear, by the way, I'm harsh, and I don't mince words because life is short.
We don't go 400 or 500 years.
The mark of an idiot is when you see quantum coming out of their mouth serious.
Now I'm not saying they're going to die an idiot.
Chances are they will.
But at that moment, up until that point in their life, they were a moron.
I've met some people that used to push the quantum bullshit, and then I showed it to them, and some of them said, oh man.
So they were an idiot up until that point, not because I say so, but objectively, because if you believe in something as a science, and it's utterly a show, a magic show, you're a moron.
You're right?
Okay.
So what they're doing, now you got the quantum part is out, so what are they really doing with these computers?
Well, what are they really doing with a Gatling gun versus a ball and powder?
You see, it's highly efficient.
It's mechanized for force multiplication through mechanization.
That's all it is.
Now what happens, though, but you can't take a bunch of rifles and spin a Gatling gun because it's going to get too hot, and they're going to melt and blow up on you like the early World War I ones.
So you have to now redesign the barrel, and you need better metallurgy, you need better timing devices, right?
Speedwell made the timing devices.
You remember, I worked with a guy that was an engineer at Speedwell.
Do you remember the machine guns used to shoot right through the propeller, the single prop planes, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Right.
Yeah, and it didn't blow the prop off.
You see that, right?
Well, there's a timing device there, and that timing device better not wear out because you'll shear your own propeller off, right?
Okay, that was designed by Speedwell.
So it's not that simple, but what I'm telling you, what's going on with this now, let's just say, why are they pushing the quantum quackery with the computers and all this?
Because they've reached a height where they don't know how to go any further.
So because for so many years, everyone has been looking at, oh, we're getting advancements technology every 18 months or six months doubling, they've reached a stale point, okay?
So now they're like, oh, we have to make stuff up.
And here's an example of where this happened.
Now prior to the automobile, the bus and the airplane, you had the two modes of transportation were steam liner, ocean liners, and on land, it was locomotive or railroad, right?
And if you even, unless you were totally broke and you couldn't afford that, because they even there had third class if you were totally steerage.
Okay, right before they, when they knew with the development of the automobile and the petrochemicals and all this, and they changed the, they knew the convention was going to change, what did they do with the railroad cars right before they went out?
What happened to them?
They became over-opulent.
Go look at, of course they did, yeah, they, they, they made them extremely comfortable.
They added extensive dining cars, sleeping areas.
You can practically live in the things, embellished, yeah, over-embellished, okay.
So what you're seeing with the computing now, and, and because I'm, I'm just getting a little deeper now.
You said you, people don't want to go under that quantum bullshit's always going to be coming up.
Whenever you hear that, it's, we lie and you're going to swear to it, right?
Okay, so what's really- They're just trying to get as much profit out of it as they can.
Keep the hype going.
Well, it's all about, okay, why does a stock, you ever watch, you ever hear about how stock prices work?
If the president says coal is bad, it's public opinion, right, within the media control.
What happens to coal stock?
It goes down.
Yeah.
If the president says coal is good and we have a good way to do it now, what happens to coal stock?
It goes up.
So it's stock.
Everybody's like, I've got stock in him because he speaks well, for example.
So they don't want their stocks coming down.
What they're doing is they're miniaturizing, and I have firsthand experience of this because recently from, well, anyway, I work with certain design work sometimes with audio equipment, let's say.
And I recently, we came up with a, we found out a little problem was too, we didn't know why this part of the board was burning out.
So I looked into it and with the help of someone else, it was an overheating problem.
And he said that this is a diode and a resistor in one, and it is smaller.
I couldn't see it with the naked eye.
Now typically the value, yeah, the value of this diode and the value of this resistor, minimum that I had seen it even two years ago was at least each the size of a grain of rice.
Yeah.
And right now they're a hundred times smaller and you're supposed to remove it from the board with a soldering iron.
I'm like, what's soldering iron?
This is, this is what's called weight.
They use wave solder.
It's called wave soldering machines, right?
It's like a microwave laser type that you can't, it's not serviceable.
So it's the same technology that if you busted open a circuit board 80 years ago, same stuff.
It is, it is 10,000 times smaller because I think you could fit 10,000 of these duplex devices inside of a device, you know, that would normally go to RadioShack and buy a diode and a resistor.
Yeah.
Okay.
So what they're doing is they're able to miniaturize this stuff now and, and you know what's kicking the AI also is the robotics aspect of it with that latest anthropomorphic Susie, Sarah Sue, whatever.
Sophia, Sophia actually, which has an interesting connotation to it alone, but go ahead.
Okay.
But here, how much more evolved is this AI or that robot than let's say the brand new LG or Samsung cell phone?
Not much.
The same.
You can talk to the cell phone.
You could, you see what I mean?
Yeah.
It'll answer back.
Or how much more evolved is that Sophia thing than that Curie?
What's that thing that Amazon, you talk to it and it talks back to you, Alexa, Alexa.
Okay.
Yeah.
Curie's Apple.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Right.
How much more evolved, it's the same stuff.
Now let's go back.
When this AI stuff comes up, I did, I saw in chat and other places, people talking about AI said, okay, these morons are, there's something in the news about AI, I better go look at it.
And lo and behold, there's all these, that's the, that's the story this week, right?
Not the missing airplane and not the corrupt politician, right?
It's the AI.
Okay.
And just to bring people back to earth, right?
I mean, well, actually you want to get away from earth, but to come back to reality, because
what's going on, but what I'm saying is to bring, you know what I did, Chuck, when they
brought the, I dropped in a couple of links on references and how the Greeks had robots
2000 years ago, albeit crude, they use steam, pulleys, weights, water pouring from one
side to the other to displace the center of gravity.
So it appeared to be a fluid motion, no pun intended.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Because weight has water, right?
If you lean, if you have a hollow statue with different geometric cavities, if you move the water from one side to the other, the arm will go up on one side and down on the other.
You know what I mean?
So what they were doing, the reason I brought this up is because the early churches in the
second, third, fourth century in Europe, you know, when the Romans got a hold of them,
they got all the crowds because they would have a throne and like someone that would
be like a robot or a wooden statue of a bishop with a crown would sit on the throne and
stand up and sit down and people would put money to see this.
This is a thousand years, well, 1800 years ago they were doing this, right?
So what's the difference right now?
Well, the difference right now is you're getting it with the nine or 12 year old mentality that you see.
So not much going on over there with the AI stuff.
And you know how I know?
Start looking into the paperwork that the people that make the AI are writing, not what the reporters are saying about it.
You get it?
Right.
Well, you know, the reporters aren't what concerned me.
Here's the correlation that I drew, and it's going to sound rather reminiscent of something that you say all the time.
What are human beings subject to at all times?
What is it that exterior input?
Something like this.
Okay.
Your own mind.
It's your everything's happening on a cloud anyway.
They're mimicking that.
Well, but that's the thing here is that in reality, then, if we are only subject to external delivered information, how real different is an AI automaton that is created this way from the guy standing next to you at the grocery store, really?
It could evolve, meaning unfold, if they keep developing it to that point.
Like the Blade Runner, was it P-Dick or whoever wrote that, where you had the skin jobs, right?
They looked like an invention.
But here's the thing.
If they can do it in a decade and a half, which is possible, they don't have a lot of time to do that.
The whole thing is going to switch.
Let me give you an example.
You know how we mentioned how the over embellishment opulence of the railroad came in at the end of its usefulness?
Sure.
If you asked anyone back then, how much longer is the railroad going to be used in preference like this, they're going to say forever.
They didn't know that it was going to be gone in a few years.
Just like, for example, if you had a discussion in 1989, when is the Soviet Union going to collapse?
They'd say maybe 50 or 100 years.
You'd say, well, how about in like three months?
You know, because it didn't subtract, right?
Right.
There's no way.
That's never going to happen, Greg.
You know, you see?
So I'm telling you, these things are going to have an influence.
The only reason these things exist is to distract the people.
Distract people from the reality of it.
And once you get into the reality of it, what is it?
Okay, let's just say it this way, Chuck.
And this sounds both objective and conformist.
You ready?
Okay.
If someone brings up AI being a problem in a good or a negative way, what's the easiest thing to say?
They're just machines.
Well, certainly.
Now, let's go to the next level.
Let's say you have one that almost looks identical to a human, right?
Like in the Blade Runner.
Let's say, which was synthesized biological, by the way, if you looked at what he wrote about it.
They were not just machines.
Well, and that's the thing, too, is that that technology is being developed.
It's not necessarily available on a mass scale, but it is happening and probably is feasible right now.
As you well know, most technology that, you know, ends up in the public's hands is stuff that is generations behind, where, you know, the people that are actually on the cutting edge are actually at.
So, you know, my assumption, based on past experiences here, is that, of course, they're already at a point where the biological and the synthetic elements that would be required are all fully operational again.
Well, here's another thing to consider.
Their entire system, overtly, is based on death.
So when you go to get prescription medicine or whatever, and they say it's been tested, and if you look at the study on it, they tested it on dead cells, right?
They don't know anything about how living things.
They can give you descriptions, but they can't explain what life is, right?
They tell you, even if you ask anyone what life is, they give you an explanation.
Well, you have muscles and circulation, but they're not explaining anything.
What I've studied, I stopped studying this almost a decade ago, and I know how to look for it, and I look at it now, and not much has changed.
They know how to put together various cultures, you know, like skin and certain basic body parts, and then put them on people.
You've heard of that, like grafting.
They have synthetic blood.
You've heard of that.
It's used in the military now and all that, right?
Sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
They can develop fragments that still require a living host, but they do not know how to form a living host on their own, unlike the sci-fi.
They are not aware of that.
And how do I know they're not aware of it?
It's pretty obvious.
Well, and if they are aware of it, it is so secret that there's not even an inkling of it in the language at all.
Yeah.
Let me just ask you this.
The very people that are going to be working on it, aren't they going to be extracted from the current society and the current training?
Yes.
And they're devoid of what life is.
So, that's okay.
And here's the thing.
Let me just put a bragging right.
So far, I've been 100% correct of everything that I've put out in the past decade or so, in terms of what's coming and all this, right?
So, this is not a fear of whatever.
In essence, it's just a machine.
So, yeah, made by stupid people, all the best.
Oh, I understand that, but it's still pretty sophisticated.
And again, on the other hand, if we are, again, very much, it's just a lesser creation, obviously, but it doesn't mean that it could not be in some way.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me just give a short thing here.
It might help you.
If you can remember this, it'll be very useful when you're speaking to the people that are out there.
You ready?
Okay.
Please.
You hear that word creation all the time, and they try to tie it back to them having a, quote-unquote, spiritual conversation or a higher-level conversation, because when we go back to the convention of religion and what the holy writs are, there's the concept of creation, right?
And you hear co-creation and all this other stuff, and that's our creation.
But what people fail to realize, when you look at the ancient writs, let's just use Genesis, because this is the Western convention, let's say, you see created, created, created, and throughout Genesis, first few chapters, created, created, created, right?
Well, if you go back to the original language, it doesn't say that at all.
It says created, formed, formed, formed, formed, created, formed, formed, formed, formed, formed, formed, and formed.
There's a big difference between creating and forming.
In other words, if I just baked some chocolate chip cookies in common vernacular in a very easy way of conversation, you'd say, look what the Greek created, these delicious cookies.
But in reality, if we were to just spend another few seconds and be a little bit more operating on a slightly different level, it would be very easy to say, look at these cookies that I formed from this egg, flour, butter, milk, chocolate.
You get it?
Yeah.
I didn't create those cookies.
You formed them.
I reformed it.
So you reformed the pre-existing things to form the new thing, right?
So man cannot create a god at all.
Man, as a matter of fact, can create very little, if not anything.
He can reform things.
Right.
I'll give you another story.
Maybe you heard this before.
I like eating vegetarian food or vegan food when it's delicious, not when people are vegetarian because they don't know how to cook.
And when people eat their cooking, it's terrible, and they say, well, it's vegetarian.
That's why it tastes bad.
No, no, no.
So there's a temple around here, and it's called Govindas.
And one day a week, it's all you can eat.
This is delicious, high-quality food.
And it's an annex building next to a temple.
And there was a religious person with us once, quote-unquote.
He thought that he'd come and talk to the Greek and learn more about the Bible.
Ha-ha, right?
But got imploded instead.
But he said, I'm going here.
He says, no, I can't go there.
It's a temple.
I'm like, we're not going in the temple.
We're sitting in the building next to it.
So anyway, he didn't want to go.
So he sat in there anyway.
And the monk is walking around, and they have all these gods formed, like Ganesh and all these other ones.
And he's going to the patrons.
They're eating and explaining what these gods are.
And everybody, all the white people are nodding their heads up and down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is so cool, right?
It's better than Santa Claus, right?
Sure.
So anyway, he gets up to me, and I listen to him.
And I said, well, he says, all right, you tell me about that god.
Let me tell you about my god.
Well, my god made the wood that you made your god out of.
You get it?
So anyway, because how ridiculous.
Have you ever seen children playing with toys?
You see this when you have a young child.
You bring them to first grade, and it's a very well-furnished one, and they've got all the toys there.
And they run for each one.
They run to all the different toys, right?
And it's not time to play yet.
But you know that when it's time to play, right away to play, they just have to reach over and grab it.
I saw it first, right?
I saw it first.
Sure.
Yeah, carry that mentality over to all the conversations that you have in the world regarding AI and all these other subjects that are going to be coming.
They're not creating anything.
Now, if you want to take that to another level, a rational, educated person, I mean educated in a proper sense, understands transmutation takes place.
So you can transmute things.
Actually, you know the story about turning lead into gold?
That's very difficult to do.
That's a high energy.
But there are low energy transmutations.
You turn silver to gold.
You can turn copper to gold.
Low energy.
That's not that hard to do.
I mean it's simple to do, but it can be difficult if you want to get into an elaborate setup, right?
So transmutation is happening in your body right now, right?
Simple transmutation would be put a seed in the ground, give it water in the soil.
It doesn't consume any of the soil and really the water because most of the water is evaporated, and it produces a tree, which is now all this cellulose material, bark, and leaves that didn't exist before.
That's plants are transmutation.
Are you guys familiar?
There's a guy in England who's been publishing stuff now for over 40 years, and no one listens to him.
You can look him up.
He took  he did one of these terrariums in a big bottle, like a liter jug bottle, like let's say a 30-liter bottle or a five, six-gallon bottle.
And he put stuff in it, and he stuck it under a staircase, and he comes out 10 years later.
It's still growing.
He hasn't added any water or anything.
It's been going on for 40 years now, and it's still growing.
And you know what?
Nothing ever has gone in or out of it.
It's completely sealed.
And you know what's happening?
The weight is increasing.
Oh.
So if nothing goes in and out of it, how does the weight keep increasing?
What's happening?
You see?
Well, with that concept in mind
So that's stuff people can't address.
What's that?
Well, see, with that in mind, that's the thing when it comes to this concept of AI and creating these automatons and things like that.
I mean isn't it possible that some transmutation could take place here?
Isn't it possible, indeed, that some entity, in fact, could decide to occupy this
Only then.
In other words, if they grab  see, we know that they're too stupid to understand how nature works.
That's a fact.
Generally.
I mean, you know.
The second level is that there are some people that got more than  years ago, you know, how good of an engineer you were considered, how many sharpened pencils you had in your pocket, right?
The more sharpened pencils, the smarter  people don't even know what a pencil is, right?
Anyway, if you grew up  yeah.
Okay.
Anyway.
So what will happen, if it would, is there's the old Talmudic folklore of the golem, you know, where they take a  a demon goes into a statue and the statue animates, right?
You've heard of the concept, you know, of the occult, right?
I think it's called a golem or a golan.
Right, a golem, yeah.
Golem, yeah.
Okay.
Well, yeah, in that case  but here's the other interesting point.
You're entering into a time period.
This is the last seven-year period of what's called normalcy, but the interesting thing is when you get out of the seven-year period and the shit is just total buckwild, people are still going to think it's normal, right?
So anyway.
Of course.
Whatever is is the normal.
Yeah, I got you.
It's going to change very quickly, but it's going to be okay.
So after this, by the mid-2020s, there is going to be some hyper-fascinating and ultra-fascinating downright miraculous supernatural shit going on everywhere.
Right.
So the thing is to ask yourself what  if you bring that up now, it sounds ridiculous.
So what kind of a mindset is going to have to change, you know, the people's mind to accept that?
That's what I'm looking at.
You see.
But the other aspect  but go ahead.
Well, but you see, that's the thing is that if one looks at this and thinks about it with some context, and we only go back in the past 100 years, considering, say, if we were to take someone from 1918 and drop them here with no explanation in this time period, things would look quite insane to them.
Well, for about an hour.
And then after an hour, they'll try to figure  it depends on how  if they're full of fear, which is weak-spirited and lack of skill, they could go insane.
Right.
If they survive it.
Yeah.
If they survive the initial  After a few days, it would be normal.
But that's the interesting thing, right?
But even still  even still, listen to me.
Even with that in mind, right, and the concept that things have changed in smaller increments because things are accelerating.
We've talked about that before, and certainly the quality of things has gone downhill all the way around because they're not meant to last.
They don't need to.
But this element to me is interesting because it seems as though  look, in a conventional sense, the things that most people are afraid of with it, this is not the thing to fear.
For me, it's the idea that a new vessel is being created that wasn't there before, that wasn't as sophisticated, that couldn't be quite as dangerous.
I mean, listen, if a demon invaded a  a demon of sorts invaded a teddy bear, we're not worried about it.
Well, the key word there is the vessel that might be controlled by what we call ultra-natural or supernatural forces.
There you go.
But mankind can't create it at all.
He's going to form  he's going to create the conditions for this to invite this thing in.
Can that be done?
That's been going on since time immemorial.
Well, right, and that's why I think that in context this is part of that story, and it's going to have some interesting results again because those steam-powered automatons that you were talking about from ancient history and the interesting mechanized things that were designed to do one
We've all seen the robotics, allegedly, of hundreds and hundreds of years ago where they have a sophisticated set of gears and everything and a person sits there, a person-like sculpture sits there and literally creates a drawing.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Well, how about the revival of Pharaoh's serpents?
Yeah, well  Now, this has nothing to do with belief.
The text states that in the initial encounters, Moses was told by the angel whose fire did not burn the bush.
You notice I didn't say burning bush, right?
He was told, drop your staff down, and it turned to a snake at that initial encounter with that angelic being who said, who should I say sent me?
He says, I am who I am, right?
And then he says, pick up the snake.
And Moses is like, okay, and he grabs the snake and it turns back into a staff.
And then he presents this quote-unquote power or magic trick or however you want to view it in your modern language to Pharaoh, and what did Pharaoh say?
Oh, we could do that too.
Now, what's interesting about the scripture, people say, well, you're not supposed to take it literally.
Well, there's mechanisms that tell you if it's literal or not.
So what kind of a technology was known and bestowed as being something unique?
And now it's unknown.
You see my point?
Because the religious people say, well, God, you know how they say God all the time, right?
Wants it to be a snake or staff, he could do that.
Yeah, yeah, but listen, idiot, the Pharaohs could do it too without that God.
You see?
So was it a different God that allowed someone to turn a staff to a snake and back to a staff?
Yes.
Right?
Because it's not the same God.
You see how this conversation sounds like it's going to run amok because people, you know, they don't know enough about their history or even their own culture to use a metaphor, whether they believe in it or not, to see how it would be possible today.
So, for example, in one time in human history, if it was possible to turn a staff into a snake, let's say forget it's biblical, let's just say that, would it be possible to do it again in human history?
Of course.
Would it be possible to have, for mankind to make an anthropomorphic statue and then it become alive like the golem, right, all that?
Yes, of course.
That's possible.
But what I've been addressing in this past little rant that I had about AI is the perspective that people have on it.
The possibility, if you could think it, it's possible.
But you know how the secret societies have a credo that before they victimize you, they have to tell you what they're going to do, whether you recognize it or not, is your problem, right?
Right.
The gods do the same thing.
The gods are telling you that they can animate anything.
So I don't see anything directly coming in the future in the ancient writs that tell us that a statue will be animated or anthropomorphic form or watch out for these robots, you know what I mean?
Or AI.
I don't see that.
Okay.
So what you're saying is, yeah, I understand.
Yeah.
There's three things on the conversation.
One, it's a dummy load.
Two is what's really going on based on what the actual field is producing, not what people are saying, by looking at the people who work on AI, what they put out there.
And they put out more than you can imagine.
And then the other aspect is the realm of the overall possibility, if you have to know what's coming in the future, and is that brought up as a major concern?
And the answer is no.
But is it a concern?
It is.
Because, look, you know what is a concern for a lot of people?
There was a competition.
You know with just basic surveillance, facial recognition, right?
Right.
Well, that's evolved to the point now where you can have a place like Penn Station or Times Square or whatever, where it's just an amalgamation of faces, and they can identify everyone in like 0.8 seconds in the crowd.
Where, let's say 10 years ago, it took maybe a half hour.
Right.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm talking about, facial recognition technology, right?
Okay.
Well, right.
Like I said, it's the acceleration of the, again, force multiplier.
That's what we're talking about here, I think, in general.
And what you're saying is that it's really no more relevant than the thing that they miniaturized already.
It's no better or worse.
It's the same technology still, just looks a little more sophisticated because they've shrunk it down a bit.
I mean is that about right?
Well, in essence, if I were to not say anything about the subject again, and I would put this subject within the categories, it's part of the setup.
You're being set up.
And the outcome is not going to be what you think it is.
But it doesn't mean you should brush it under the rug but don't get caught up.
People tend to view things in a really kind of silly or stupid pointed way of viewing it when you go on the internet.
Oh, yeah.
It doesn't mean it should be discounted or discarded.
Oh, no.
Under no circumstances would I say that it should be ignored.
But I find it really interesting the way that you've just broken it down because it makes a lot more sense than the majority of the nonsense out there.
But then again, that's kind of what happens here, isn't it?
Man.
The difference between you probably is what really is going on and what people think is going on is so different that the two have almost nothing to do with each other.
Right.
It's the idea.
I went into the bookstore and they said, well, listen, all these JFK conspiracy books are 50 percent off.
I said, oh, really?
I bet they're off by a lot more than 50 percent.
Anyway.
That's  yeah.
The last time I think we were together would have been just before I went to Dallas, too, by the way.
So that was an interesting trip, by the way.
I found it rather fascinating.
And also just to  I want to throw something in there that works with that, too.
Like a lot of people tell stories and whether it's any story, but the JFK, you hear this.
If you spend more than a day's research on the JFK, the concept of a lie detector test comes up somewhere.
You're going to come across that often, right, with testimonials and things, right?
Quite often.
Are you aware of bioacoustic technology now that is very different and almost 100 percent accurate?
When I say 100, it's 100 times more accurate or 10 times more accurate than  you cannot be fooled.
Like the standard lie detector tests that have been 50 years old now or 80 years old or however they are.
It's a bioacoustic method, and you just have to speak.
They just have to get a voice pattern.
It doesn't matter what you're saying.
Jack and Jill run up a hill or you could  whatever you're saying.
It could even  you have to speak intentional words.
It doesn't work if you're snoring, right, because you're unconscious.
But it doesn't matter what you're saying.
Well, it works best if you say what you're going to say, and it's almost infallible, by the way.
And the reason why it's infallible is technically explained.
Are you familiar with that?
And the person pioneering it is a woman called Sherry Edwards, and Sherry is with an S-H-A-R-R-Y.
And I don't endorse her work overall, but that aspect of it is spot on.
Have you ever heard of this, by the way?
Well, it would have to be based on some of the previous technology, which was earlier described as voice stress analysis.
Hold on.
It's different.
It works on  not on voice.
It works on which note you're peaking on and which key.
Yeah, yeah.
And the interesting  now here's the interesting thing.
You ready?
In order to get someone in a lie detector test, you actually strap them in or whatever.
People think it's clinical.
This is not clinical.
You can actually just have a recording of the person's voice.
It should be better than what it sounds over a regular telephone.
OK, and then you just play it through a program.
And I'll  I have it.
I used to have the early part of the program on a computer.
I don't anymore.
But if  it's a bioacoustic technology.
It scares the living daylights out of people, and she's catching a lot of flack from it.
But at the same time, they want demonstrations, and when she demonstrates it for government agencies, they outwardly steal it from her.
In other words, like demonstrate it for us, and then it's like, no, we don't want it.
But part of the demonstration is for them to download it.
You get it?
Oh, yeah.
So you get to rip them off.
Well, it's kind of like the weather work.
I'll make rain here.
I'm like, can you give us a demonstration?
And I did.
I'm like, wait a second.
Now you don't need to hire me to make rain anymore because I just demonstrate.
You see?
So anyway.
Well, VSA is similar though because you don't require any of the clinical settings or test questions or comparisons or any of that stuff.
There's just different ways of measurement, and I'm familiar with people trying to work that out.
I wasn't aware that somebody's actually created a facility to use it.
I'm very interested in that.
Well, I gave you the info.
Also, you can use it, for example, someone's voice.
They can tell you what you have a deficiency in, and also they could use sound to heal that, right?
Like someone could be diagnosed with diabetes, for example, and it's not diabetes at all.
They have a particular toxin in their body.
This is really advanced acoustic stuff.
Yeah, there's a lot of applications for what you're talking about.
I wasn't aware that anybody had found a way to utilize that like what I'm talking about.
Like what I was saying before, voice stress analysis has existed for a long time, but it was kind of a tedious process, let's call it.
Well, this analysis, not only can they tell you if you're lying or not, but the depth and the emotional depth in the story and what you're saying, whether you're lying happily or you're being stressed or you're being coerced, and at the same time they could tell you if your liver is dysfunctioning or you're going to have a kidney ailment in 10 years or something like that.
Oh, my God.
It's pretty wild stuff.
I'm not endorsing her stuff because she's a breakfast cereal type, fruit, nut, and flake.
Great.
New agey crap.
Yeah, but it doesn't mean you discount the entire thing.
It's basically edible corn in a pile of poop, so I'm not endorsing it.
Oh, my.
Yeah, so you want to just  you know what I mean by getting edible corn in a pile of poop?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You don't want to eat the poo.
You just want the corn, right?
Just get that corn.
It's been in shit.
It's been in poop, so it's very hard to find clean corn anywhere anymore.
Yeah.
So there's people out there still doing good work, but if you read in the ancient writ it talks about the kingdom is fractured or divided.
Right.
So you have everything you need.
You just have to go find it.
It's in pieces everywhere, and it's not going to come together.
We had a question about can you speak about how cancer can be cured?
Well, there's various types of cancer.
There's one that's too much of something, then there's another type of cancer that's too little of something, and then the other type of cancer is something gone amok, right?
You've heard of malignancies?
Mm-hmm.
So I can't speak on it because 90 percent of the stuff that's diagnosed as cancer is not, but the stuff that is diagnosed as cancer that is definitely cancer are these malignant things where they remove it and it comes back worse or they treat it and it gets worse, you know what I mean?
Yeah, and that's all frequency-based as well.
Look, let me put it this way.
This is a simple thing.
I was having a chat the other day.
You know what food is basically, right, when you take food?
All it is, it's condensed sunlight.
Think about it.
It's sunlight that's condensed down.
What does condensation mean?
Concentrated, right?
So the quality of that sunlight will determine the quality of that food.
So if you have bad quality sunlight, you can have a perfectly looking piece of broccoli.
You eat that broccoli, what happens to your body?
You get cancer.
Oh.
So you have to know how to  that's why I call it, you know, if you're eating too many greasy solar rays, you know.
Anyway.
Didn't you mention something about that thin layer at the top of the atmosphere and how the light is changed?
Yeah, transmutation.
There's no ozone layer.
That's where the nitrogen gets converted to oxygen.
And their spectrography measures it as an O3O4, which is ozone, versus O or O2 in their chemical.
And they say it's an ozone layer.
No.
It's like walking into a kitchen and there's a big pot of beans.
I'll say, well, that's the bean part of the kitchen.
So does that play a part in the food's development then too?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So everything is based on  yeah, and you know what the kicker is?
This is the kicker and the nuts.
You ready?
Or whatever.
Okay, sure.
If you  there is no sun.
I mean, yeah, you do see it through the atmosphere.
But if you go beyond the atmosphere, you don't see anything.
Right.
You only see the sun through the atmosphere, yeah.
And no one knows that yet.
I mean there are some people talking about it now, and astronauts don't talk about it.
And, yeah, you can only see the sun through the atmosphere.
Yeah, I tried to explain to you because of the strangeness of my vision that that makes the most sense about what it is I'm seeing.
Because that's the way it's always appeared to me.
As though there is something which is delivered to this area very much like electricity is delivered to a fluorescent light bulb.
In that sort of equation, I mean that is pretty much like the sun's relationship to the earth.
The earth is effectively the fluorescent light bulb.
So there's no light being sent through space.
Right.
It's just being transmitted.
The energy for that light is being transmitted.
And then the components within this field around this planet are agitated.
Are agitated, yeah.
Are agitated to create the condition of light based on the fact that they've been excited in a particular area.
And that's what I visually interpret.
You know how I teach this to children is very simple.
The way you're being taught the sun is when you've got a stove top and you see the burner lit, you know, gas, and you put the pot on there.
And now you just, you know, the further away the pot is from the actual fire, you know, it's not so hot.
Now that's why that's the earth and the sun.
No.
A better analogy is the microwave.
You put the water in the microwave.
You don't see anything.
And all of a sudden the water starts to heat up, right?
Right.
Yeah.
So what they're teaching everyone is the fire analogy.
There's this big, great ball in space far away.
And if you go out there, you'll see it.
No, no, there's nothing there.
It's like the microwave.
You don't see anything, but the thing heats up.
When you're in space, you don't see the sun or the stars, but you see the earth lit up, right?
Right.
And it's just like the microwave.
If you the denser the material, the hotter it gets.
Just like on a hot day, the air is hot.
But when you sit on the park bench, it's hotter.
You know why?
Because it's denser.
And if you're in the southwest and you have some tools out, it'll burn your hand.
You've heard of cooking an egg on the sidewalk.
It's so hot.
Yeah, I remember that.
Well, you can't cook an egg on a tree.
Why?
Because the sidewalk is denser than the tree.
So the denser the material, the more the absorption.
You see?
That's all.
It's very simple.
Very simple.
But also space has a different quality to it.
But, you know, here's the hypocrisy.
I don't like to discuss a lot about what's happening out there for several reasons.
And the first is I haven't been there.
And if you base everything on a thought experiment, that's not good.
But the other thing is the hypocrisy.
People don't even know what the hell is going on five feet from them.
And how are you going to talk about what's happening all the way out there?
You know, that's the truth.
Yes.
Yeah.
So that's what I have to say with that.
And with that, I'm just out of curiosity, even though it's not a good curiosity.
What do you think of, I'm sure, have you heard of James Sutton or James Files?
He's been interviewed a while back.
Several times he claims to have shot, done the kill shot with a Remington through the fence.
What do you think of that in terms of the testimony on that, by the way?
Well, it's not provable.
No, I know that.
That's testimony.
Yeah, it's testimony, but all I have is dispositive evidence, you know, in a lot of ways of his testimony, let's call it.
Of course, he's been released from prison, by the way.
Oh, it must have happened recently, right?
Yeah, a few months back.
And, you know, it seems to me as though there is not enough evidence for anybody to really work with it.
It's just one of these games that people play with information, quite honestly.
You know, there's other characters out there that do this as well.
But, yeah, no, this person for the uninitiated claims to be the shooter from the grassy knoll.
The problem is that, first of all, there is no physical evidence on the record anywhere that shows that a shot from the grassy knoll actually landed.
And by the way, in case somebody thinks, oh, this is just one of those people who doesn't believe that there was something other than the government's explanation.
You're wrong.
The thing is that, quite honestly, there's evidence for shots other than the alleged Oswald character would have taken, but not for this guy's story.
Right.
They're predominantly from front and behind, almost in line, but not quite 30, 40 degrees off.
Yeah, correct.
Exactly correct.
Which is funny because you haven't even, I don't think you've taken a long time to study these things.
But in short order, you can find out if you know what you're looking at that, yeah, yes, indeed, you're exactly correct.
I've had people try and look at things for 20 years that just cannot wrap their minds around what you just said.
That is what the evidence shows thus far.
But this guy's story, it's just one of those things that's out there, much like Judy Baker.
I was Lee Harvey Oswald's girlfriend, and I was also a CIA asset, and I was also a master scientist who was out there creating a cancer weapon and all this other whatever else it is she wants to make up this week.
Chuck, do you think he was a plant?
A plant.
Well, I could make a joke here and say I don't believe he would be bearing fruit any time.
Or like a conspiracy patsy.
You got the patsy for the public and the patsy for the conspiracy theorists.
There's something just thrown in there.
I think the simplest explanation is this, that he was really a guy who was in prison, who did rub up against a few interesting characters in his lifetime, who just exaggerated stories into, well, he went in this area because this was something that would get him attention, would get him a bit of money to help out the people that weren't in prison at the time.
I really think that's what it comes down to.
And when you take a look at the guy who financed the book about him and the videos about him and all that stuff.
I found that odd, yeah.
Yeah, that part is.
But what about his actual testimony, though?
Right.
Does he make that all add up?
You see, that's the interesting part.
You got to start from somewhere.
Yeah, his testimony is really based on some information that had become available in previous decades, some bad assumptions made by some authors who didn't have the access to a lot of things that we have access to today.
And these assumptions would have sounded great to somebody who, say, wasn't aware that there was five million documents released after that information or whatever, that there was- Yeah, but all that stuff aside, though, in other words, can you tell when someone is lying or not is the basic thing.
Not you, but I mean, is this guy, in other words, if you put this guy's feet to the fire, would his story change?
You know what I mean?
I mean, literally.
In other words, if you tortured him, right, I mean, I'm talking like serious rendition, would he change his story and fess up, or would he take that story to his grave?
You see, that's what real testimony is about.
You know, an interesting one there, Greek, is put him up against that speech analysis thing.
Well, you know, that's the thing I was thinking of, actually.
I put someone on that already, and they said that the audio that they got from him right now must have gone through something like Skype at some point.
Yeah, I have a lot of- I've done enough research that I'm satisfied.
The shortfall of the speech analysis thing is certain things like Skype and certain other- there was one other, I don't remember if it's Obscure or not, but let's just say Skype, will flatten out what you're saying, even though it does sound like- So you're changing the voice.
The compression.
Yeah, the compression.
It could be- it's beyond the compression, though.
They do this funky- yeah, it is- in other words, you're correct, yeah.
In other words, the compression analog that they use, yeah, the- what do you call the formula for something in computers?
The type of compression they use on Skype, yes.
Right, right.
AA3 or, you know, some- with a needle, you know, mechanically moving in a vinyl groove, that will carry it.
Or magnetic tape.
Right, right.
But a telephone will carry it too, but will filter most of it out, not compress it.
Well, look at the difference between the old carbon elements that they use in the telephone and the new little tiny electrics that they use in the cell phone.
I mean, there's- they're- the technology- Yeah, so anyway, Chuck, just to finalize on that, what would the evidence- it's funny, the evidence, right?
Whenever you hear that word, I cringe, but in order to get- we need to get- if you want to run his voice through that, I haven't- nothing has been found on the internet right now that shows the quality that we're looking for.
I say we, I mean, that can be done.
So, like, when you said he's out right now, all you got to do is run up to him and do a 30-second interview.
Just say, you know, it doesn't matter what he says, just say, you know, I shot Kennedy this week.
Say what you- give us your testimony in 30 seconds, that's more than enough.
But not record it on Skype, something else.
Well, what would you recommend for good recording then?
Grammar?
Yeah, no, the best is- no, digital will work.
Like, you know the Olympus handheld audio things that still sell for $100?
Oh, sure, sure.
Those are the industry standard now for handheld recording devices.
Got the little two microphones that pop up.
Right.
Interesting.
Where if you had a- let's say you had a computer or a cell phone on record mode, that's good enough.
But once you run it through Skype, it screws it up.
Okay, so not the compression on the phone?
Because the phone digitizes in compressions, and that's why I asked that question.
No, the phone recordings seem to be fine.
Okay.
A phone has a more dynamic- it's basically got a better dynamic range of sound than- Skype is very- Yeah, it's narrow.
It's very narrow, yeah.
You know, I could get a video recording, and if you put it into a WAV format instead of an MP4- Correct.
That would work.
It will contain a lot more, and I could probably actually get that for you any time.
Right.
In other words, if he had- yeah, the old VHS days, running through a regular TV is more than enough.
More than good enough.
Oh, cool.
Hey, Chuck, if you ever need help with that, I'll help you.
I can turn any audio into any format that you need.
Oh, yeah.
I do some of that work myself.
Okay, good, good.
But I was just saying, I mean, if you wanted to provide this to somebody who could run it through an analyzer, I would love to have not only him, but also that woman I just mentioned, Judy Baker.
I'd love to have her run through there as well.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Okay, you know what?
You know, you've heard of, you know, people are spoken of publicly.
You know, don't be starstruck or whatever.
If you look up Sherry Edwards or Bioacoustics, she comes up.
She has a website.
Right.
She's very easy.
I mean, I have her phone numbers.
You know, I have all her numbers and all that, but what I mean is if you go to the website, there's a phone number there, and she's in Ohio or something.
You call there.
You'll get a receptionist.
She will get back to you.
The best way, because she's busy, is to send her an email, and she will get back to you.
So you can bypass me and go directly, and this way, if there's any questions back and forth, it doesn't have to go through me or someone else that I know.
You can go to her directly.
Just look up Sherry.
That's with an S-H-A, Sherry Edwards, Bioacoustics, and you go to the website.
She has about three or four different websites based on, you know, ones for the public, ones that are more clinical.
I'd say two websites, really, and you can get in touch with her, and I think if you  let's say you had the audio in your hand right now, Chuck, in a WAVE file or somehow.
I think it wouldn't take more than a week from getting in touch with her and having the results.
Oh, I could email those things to her if she's willing to accept the files, and you could have it in a matter of moments.
Why don't you get in touch with her on your  this way, just for the ease of, you know, just look her up.
She's very easy.
That would be an interesting answer to a question.
I certainly would love to do that.
I've just made a note, and I'm going to see what I can find, my friend.
Let me give you a little story, and you'll hear it.
Remember the Jerry Sandusky thing that went on with the football coach?
Sandusky and then his son, yeah.
Okay, well, what they did was the prosecution and some other government came to her with audio files before the trial, and she didn't talk about this until after the trial, but she analyzed just like 10 seconds of his voice when he was in the testimony that he gave, right?
Right.
And she said what  he did what he did, but he didn't think it was the wrong thing to do.
He thought it was just a form of horseplay.
Even though he did molest them sexually, you know, legally gets you in big trouble, in his  he didn't think he was doing the wrong thing, but he's guilty.
He did do those things.
But the reason why he did them was he thought it was just a form of horseplay, and they filed that away.
That's great.
That's a level of sophistication that quite honestly no previous technique has ever shown promise for because they could never give you that.
Like in other words, even with voice stress analysis, right, I could tell you that somebody  and I've been through this a bit, so I understand that.
I could tell you that this person believes what they're saying.
Correct.
Certainly, and yes, that is exactly what  Why they're saying they believe it.
Why they believe it.
Is it actually true is another issue.
Quite honestly, that's a misnomer about that.
Right, and then at the same time she could say, well, by the way, you have a gallstone that's going to make  give you a problem in about two or three years.
Holy smokes.
Right, so then he goes and gets a sonogram, and there's this tiny, tiny, tiny thing in his gallbladder.
It looks like the size of a grain of sand that is growing.
It's like  and it wouldn't show  you would  any radiologist or whatever just wouldn't even notice it, right?
So anyway, it's really  I think the pinnacle of  when you talk about technology, it's all good.
Any technology is only as good or as bad as how it's being used, right?
So she's got  when it comes to the bioacoustic stuff, she's got that down.
The other stuff she talks about is just  you just got to  it's like give me some milk, a bowl of milk and a spoon.
But anyway.
I hear you there.
But it is also another thing to keep in mind that sound in and of itself is one of those things that is highly misunderstood by most people.
There are a lot of things contained within the spoken word that may not be self-evident to the majority of those listening because they're not entirely listening, and your ears are not the best devices, quite honestly, to interpret sound.
This is one of those things you and I have talked about too, and I think that's an interesting thing to keep in mind here that  you know what?
That information is contained within some of these utterances, and there is a great deal more information.
This again is only as far as the technology has taken people, even this woman who is apparently on the cutting edge of it.
But let's be honest.
There's a lot more contained within those sounds than one might be able to gather at first listen.
Well, my interaction  let's just say without  just objectively.
What I've been saying for a very long time is there's  like you just said people cannot discern what's in the sound, right?
That's fine.
They can't discern it.
But another thing they cannot discern at all  you ready for this?
is that their ears are giving off a sound, and your eye is giving off light.
And there's a guy, a psychiatrist named Ross in the 1920s.
He says, man, the light gives off eye.
The eye gives off light, and he set up a dark box, pitch black.
Someone would put their head in, and he had a photoelectric relay on the end, and they would always trigger it when he told them to look forward in the middle of the box.
That's why when you're out in the street or out and sometimes you feel like this feeling on the back of your head and you turn around, it sounds like a tingling, and you see someone staring at you, right?
The eye gives off a beam.
Now, your ear gives off a sound.
Like, for example, I'm not talking about tinnitus now, but you get ringing in the ears and occasional ringing of the ears.
For example, in some Kundalini and even Sufi practices, they say when you reach a level of meditation, you hear this ring, this tone, right?
Well, what's interesting, if you have a reasonably healthy person who doesn't have this constant ringing, in other words, it's not a ringing because a nerve is pinched or something mechanically.
If you hear the ringing, do me a favor.
If any one of you folks ever have a ringing in one ear, especially if it's loud, if there's someone else in the room, tell them to put their ear against your ear that is ringing.
It's usually one or the other, and ask them if they hear a ringing also coming out.
So sometimes that ringing that is in the ear is not just in the brain.
It is actually like a tiny speaker giving off a literal ringing.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Just like a light that triggers off someone's stare.
I'm done.
I've been done for a long time.
Stick a fork in me.
What's your take on reverse speech?
That opens yourself.
That's the same thing.
What's your take on Ouija boards?
What's your take on seances?
What you're doing there is what?
In simple terms, you're inviting something else.
Okay.
Gotcha.
It's not like radiology.
You ever see an x-ray?
You ever been in the hospital?
You go and they got the x-rays.
There's five doctors, their arms in their pockets waiting and waiting.
I said, wait, we're waiting for a radiologist.
What, you guys can't read that?
No.
You see, it's a specialty, right?
We're not talking about that.
Most people think that reverse speech is a specialty.
It's not.
You're actually inviting something else there.
Okay.
But on the other hand, I would say that, yeah, you're correct.
But there's additional bit of information here that needs to be understood.
You know, when something is spoken, there is other intent in it as well.
There's a lot of other information in it as well.
And it's not to say that there can't be information gathered from the interpretation of something in reverse.
The idea that people are actually, you know, speaking in reverse at the same time they're speaking forward is a little bit.
Because you're giving off.
Yeah, it's like the animals can hear stuff that you can't hear.
We also give off those sounds, and those sounds still approach us.
Okay, let me just, without retracting what I just said, but let's just say from an objective point of view, if you have a prerecorded piece of material, which, by the way, most of them are, and then you analyze it reverse speech, that would be more objective.
But if you have someone going around saying, let me record this so I could reverse it and see what they say, now you're inviting something.
Right.
See, a lot of people that do this kind of stuff and discuss this topic usually take something which is prerecorded, and then they interpret it.
They say, okay, listen to this part of the speech, now listen to it reversed.
This is part of, obviously, what is in their consciousness as well.
Well, then it's more objectified, yeah.
Yeah.
So, no, that was the thing I wanted to add there.
Yeah, that would be more formal because lately I've, not lately, well, I've heard of it.
There was actually a specialist in that field that pioneered that field 30 years ago.
Lives here in town, by the way.
It's a woman.
And she used to have a TV show on public access, and I was like, no, no, no, no, this is a little, I could see how it could be viable, but the way they're pushing it is a little too far.
It loses its objectivity now, right?
Well, there's a lot of hands in there too.
In other words, if you have a prerecorded thing and you can objectify it, there's information being given in reverse, that, there's, yeah, I would say that's about objective as you can get, right?
But if you're creating it for the purpose of that, you're inviting something else, right?
No, absolutely true.
But, you know, generally when people reference this, I mean, again, you know that on occasion I go and try and sample the alternative media stuff, and usually it just ends in dismay and I throw up my hands after a little bit.
But when I do that, I do memorialize in my own mind some of the things I encounter.
And quite honestly, what was it?
Jeff Rents used to have a guy on a few years back rather regularly that would take, say, you know, bits of speeches from Barack Obama and play them backwards and say, this is what I think is also on his mind while he's saying this.
You know, and quite honestly, it was usually there to show contradictory ideas when you reversed it.
But then again, when you change the pitch, you change the speed, you can do a lot of things with this.
And, I mean, I've taken live broadcasts of totally unrelated things and played with it enough and created, you know, somebody saying something in a different way just by changing, again, the pitch and the tone just a bit, and it indeed sounds like it.
But then it comes down to are you manipulating something in order to create something, or are you objectively examining it?
Again, these two things are very different, and I'm glad you made that point.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Overall, what I always say is who are you doing it for and why are you doing it?
That's all.
Yeah, which is always something good to consider when you say it.
Good point.
So there you go.
I think you got the lady's name, right?
Bioacoustics, she'll come up, and you're off on your own.
And, you know, there's no specialization here.
She's very easy to get in touch with.
I would say based on experience from many different ways, I'd say that if you got a recording to her now, you'd probably have an answer in a week or two maximum.
Excellent.
In other words, her group and herself are very responsive, and she'll tell you if she can't do it right away.
So there you go.
Again, how many times have we  you remember when the VHS tapes came out, it was like, oh, wow, we're at the pinnacle of technology, right?
Well, this is an ongoing thing.
It's impressive at the moment, and it's not just impressive at the moment.
I'm sure it will evolve even more as time goes on if they keep working on it, but it's enough to do the job, you know, right now.
Oh, right, and that's the thing.
That's why I pointed out that there has been a bit of an evolution.
I mean the polygraph has its place, you know, but, again, it is very clinical.
You have to utilize very specific protocols in order for this thing to even be remotely successful when it comes to the typical lie detector test, right, the one where they strap the different sensors onto you and all that.
It's a spectrum analysis, and you almost need like a radiologist to read it eventually to confirm it.
Right, and, of course, those things have evolved too.
I mean literally testing the skin's temperature, right, the level of perspiration, the amount of tension in certain areas of the body.
I mean all these things literally do communicate something, but, again, you know, you might be able to break up a piece of steak with a hammer, but it is not the preferred tool to get the job done adequately when you're trying to eat.
Right, and it also depends on the person's level of discipline or training.
Like if you put a Taoist master on a lie detector, and if he wanted to, he could do it either way.
You know, if you say the sky is purple, or I mean actually the sky can turn any color, but, you know, say that elephants can fly, it would show that he's telling the truth because he has extreme control over his body, right?
Right.
Do you know like the story of the oracle in Delphi, you know, this woman in a chemical trance,
and she would prophesy and tell people the future and things,
and a guy wanted to prove that it was false and it was a hoax,
and he had a bird in his hand, and he was going to ask the oracle is the bird dead or alive,
and if she said it was alive, he'd kill it, and if she said it was dead, then, you know,
he would just do the opposite, right?
Right.
So if he asked was the bird alive, you know, either way.
So basically when he asked the oracle is the bird dead or alive, she goes it's whichever one you wish.
Right.
So it kind of leaves them hanging.
In other words, you could leave a lie detector test hanging as well.
Well, right, and that's why some people would do things like, you know, insert something into their shoe so that they could cause pain.
Right, so it's calibrated.
Yeah.
So the calibration is incorrect, and therefore the readings are all over the place because you're randomly inserting pain into the equation where, given the controlled circumstances, this should not be the case.
So there you go.
It does have a lot to do with the participant, the discipline, you know, et cetera, et cetera.
But speech, on the other hand, once it's been loosed, I mean, again, this is why I find this fascinating.
There are certain things that are contained within it that most people do not have the ability to control.
Right, because they're not aware also that when you hear things that your ear is actually giving off sound, and that puts a bias on it.
Of course it does.
Have you ever heard of like someone who has a negative outlook or whatever, no matter what they hear, they're always skeptical of it.
They can't be objectified because they've never objected of what they're hearing or seeing because they've never gotten over the subjectivity of what their own body is emitting.
Mm-hmm.
So it's kind of like in the Asian arts, the Taoist healing arts, a master could see, you know how they talk about auras, you know, different colors, and different colors were different diseases and state of health, right?
Like someone could walk into a room, and if they had like a greenish muddy, you know, they could tell them, oh, this person is sick here or whatever, you know, because they have already objectified sight.
That's an interesting thing just to ponder for anyone that's listening.
Can you objectify your own vision and can you objectify your own hearing?
And it sounds kind of clich, but it's the first step to becoming aware of what the senses are really doing.
Oh, right, right, absolutely.
And again, you know, someone's vision and their interpretation, there's a lot of steps in between before you turn around and spit it back out of your mouth to give an observation.
So, you know, there are many different qualities that could be had there, right?
I mean, one quality in an ear does not necessarily make the great interpretation.
You need to have each one of these steps of the utmost quality, which is what the pursuit of these things is about.
So that's something to consider as well, right?
Yeah, it is, but what you have to consider ultimately is who you're going to tell this to, because you're living in a society where no amount of evidence on certain subjects means anything.
Isn't that the really terrifying thing for some people?
You never have a second chance at a first impression.
And the first impression for most people is not just an impression.
Well, it's actually carving it in stone for them, you see.
And you could still erase that even though something's carved in stone.
You could chisel away at it and whatever, but why bother?
Because in this case, you know, they trivialize it.
But essentially you're living in a society where evidence doesn't matter.
And it seems like that has led to all the absurdities that are going on, believe it or not.
Yeah.
And you know what?
And that's because they're subject to the cosmic censorship, which you've talked about before.
All true.
So, you know, I'm not even sure.
Is this titled as something?
Does this end up becoming an MP3?
Yes.
Yes, it does.
Yeah, tell them how it works, Bruce.
It becomes an MP3.
We can call it whatever we like.
We can name it The Greek and Chuck Wachelli and then put the date next to it.
Put the word new next to it so that they know that's the one, you know.
That's about it.
You could write maybe Wachelli and The Greek semi-loaded.
Yeah, okay, we'll do that.
We'll do that.
Wonderful.
Okay, excellent.
You know, and I didn't expect to do this, but this is always, always great exercise for my psychology to have a conversation with you, I've got to tell you, and I appreciate it.
Yes, yes, likewise.
All right, that makes one of us.
Likewise.
That's all right.
That's two.
The whole thing, it's really bad out there.
You know, after a while, you know, when you have young children and you love them more than anything you can imagine, you didn't know what really love was until you have these little small people around you, right?
And the first thing that you think about is, oh, no, eventually, even now, I'm going to have to subject them to all the crap in the world, right?
It's a scary thought.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, well, that's what's going on constantly when I think about things, and I'm like, who am I going to go talk to?
Because if you bring up the subject, because no matter what you want to discuss, it could be placed in a subject matter, right?
And then you look at what's being discussed on that subject matter, and you're like, oh, shit.
You can't say, well, who are you going to tell this to?
Right.
And the reason I bring that up is I've had discussions with captains of industry and Supreme Court judges, and I bring up the truth of certain things, and they look at me, and they're like, yeah, that's true what you're saying, but who are you going to tell that to?
Meaning we got everybody by the balls.
You know, no one's going to believe it.
Well, it's not just those who have everybody by the balls that think that.
I got to be honest with you that a lot of the conversations that I have with a very few people, by the way, in my personal life often end with, yeah, this is all true, but what am I supposed to do with this particular piece of information?
Nobody wants to hear it.
And so occasionally I'll speak about these things and slip those little nuggets, those little pieces of reality into my discussions.
Quite honestly, I'm well aware of the fact that very, very few people will ever actually hear them, regardless of how many people allegedly heard the discussion or allegedly heard the information.
And what's funny is that that is the one thing that you actually taught me, is that that would be the reality ever after, for my ever after anyway, and you were right.
You were quite right about that.
Well, essentially, look, everyone wants to do what they're good at doing, and they want to live well from it and profit from it.
Profit meaning right scales and measures by earning it the right way.
But when you focus and you find  let's say you find out what kind of a shithole this society has been for 6,000 years up until now, and for the reason why it's like that, your main focus is food, clothing and shelter and to get through it, just like doing your time.
And then everything else that you do, you remember that it's not just for now.
Later on, if you're confronted, you can't  no one can tell you, hey, I found out you knew the facts and the truth about this, and you didn't say anything.
But if you say it, and no strings and no expectations, no need for approval, later on, no one can come to you and say, hey, Chuck, you knew this and you said it.
We're the ones that screwed up.
Well, that is for certain.
If there were a grand cosmic court that was convened to judge me about you knowing knowledge and not sharing the reality, the danger, the strangeness that you observed, that is one thing that I could not be accused of.
And I'm happy to do that.
I realize that I'm not quite as dummy load free as what it is you do.
But quite honestly, I do the best I can given the  again, the atmosphere of censorship.
But it did help me adjust my attitude quite a bit about being frustrated over the idea that, look, I've said this 100 times and nobody hears it.
It just  it got me to understand that's the way it's supposed to be right now.
Right now.
That's right.
It's temporal.
That's why I've been speaking publicly for almost a decade or so.
Actually, more than that, even in person, just to live audiences and things.
And very often I'd say it's not time yet.
So there's  again, if you go back to all the ancient writs, there's  what is it?
Patience is a virtue or something.
So, right?
When you look on what's called the alternative media and all that other stuff, all those guys are shooting their load and telling you everything they know, and it's bullshit.
So there's  if you know the time isn't right, say it anyway in most cases or some cases.
But you know that the reaction will be null because it's not time yet.
So now you have to read the times, right?
You have to know the times, and that's where patience comes in.
But ultimately, like you mentioned, the great judgment thing, let's just not air religious or whatever.
There will be a time where there will be an equalization of the spirits, I call it.
You know what I mean?
And there will be an equal footing of the minds, and things will be sorted out.
And that time would actually be more rewarding than now.
Well, yeah, and that's why I tried to leave it in as secular sort of situation as I could, likening it to a courtroom.
Although we know that those things are not anything secular in any way, shape or form.
But best descriptor I had for it.
So there you go.
We know that those things are all religiously based, and again, all you have to do is look at the symbols.
And they tell you exactly which goddess they're talking about, don't they?
Or at least sort of one way or another, right?
Yeah, and it's  the other thing is the waste of time that people spend on thinking things are going to get better.
You just live it through, live your life, figure out what's coming, and live the best you can.
And go on from there.
None of this stuff is going to be fixed.
It's going to be done away with, but it has to reach its peak like a boil first.
So that's pretty much the aspect of it.
Yeah, got to fill up with pus until it bursts.
And that's a pretty good descriptor for the rock I happen to be standing on anymore.
So there you go.
Yeah, and at least the lifespans are 70, 80, 90 or whatever.
They're not 5, 6, 700.
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
If they were in the high level like that, oh, yeah, they would have to be physical  there would have to be a physical change.
In other words, it would have to be beyond what the civil rights movement was, let's say, and women's suffrage and prohibition and all that.
It would have to be very  and if you actually study the times, actually there's very little of ancient days that people did  were more physical in making changes instead of sitting back and saying, hey, it's just the way it is.
So anyway, but now it's just like  it's just a movie show.
Right.
All right, guys.
End credits.
Yeah, I've been through all that before.
Here's the thing.
If I had a basic Greek-speak script and just said that every time, it would come out a little different every time, but I have gotten some feedback.
It's all the same basic stuff, and sometimes I'm like, yeah, it is the basic stuff, but I scratch my head and I say, well, even if I spoke typical Greek-speak stuff for four hours over and over and over, the only place you're going to hear it is at Greek-speak unfortunately.
So the thing is, that's why we do these streams, to relax and do the thoughts of the week or whatever informally.
I've mentioned to people that I put on the page to put out for donations for the very simple reason that that's how people vote.
So, for example, I've been putting out this Greek-speak stuff simply because no one else has.
If there's a topic that's really good and I don't have the information someone else does, it can be objectified.
I just send them there, very simple.
But because I like to speak on things, I hear just deaf.
It's just a silence on that need to be spoken.
I asked for donations, so I figured, well, you never know what kind of world this is, and if it's time, you go to the mailbox and there's $100,000 a month there.
And if that happens, you're like, oh crap, it's time.
Hire people and get this thing moved.
It's time on the planet, right?
That's why I did it.
So the way you know, another way that you know if it's time yet is the way that people, what they're willing to reciprocate with, you see.
Now, most of the people that are successful, quote-unquote, in the media are because they're selling you stuff, you see.
And then on the other, so there's the religious side, you know, the big megachurches grow.
You ever see some of these megachurches?
Man, those are like $20 million buildings, right?
It's like, how did they fund that, you know?
Well, because that preset religious mindset has been around for 1,000 plus years.
The stuff that I'm talking about or maybe the subject matter, never been talked about in public that I could see at all, ever.
So it's not time yet for that.
I don't know.
It's just one of those instances where I would say Greek-speak is an anomaly.
It should have never happened, and it shouldn't be, but it is.
Well, there you go.
And you know what?
You say they only can hear it here.
I would like to take this one and put it on the live stream over at my website, too, just for a little while and expose people to this discussion, if you don't mind.
No, not at all.
You're more than welcome, Chuck.
Yes.
And I don't utilize theI have a portion of my website devoted to Ocelli and the Greek, but this would be just something that I would put out on the live stream, and if they hear it, they hear it.
I think it'sbut definitely a valuable discussion, and certainly I like to give those things away myself as often as I can.
Very good.
So there you go.
Very good, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
They call that in the OcelliI noticed they call that content.
So do whatever you want with it.
Yeah, man, great.
All the better.
If it helps, all the better.
If it hinders, then you know it's hindering.
So either way, and whoever is listening to it, yeah, sure, whatever.
Enjoy it.
Absolutely.
And by the way, you could pick it up at the chat anyway.
Bruce is pretty diligent about posting the two servers, server A and server B, on the Greek Chat Django.
And you just pick it up based on the menu there.
Don't be your heart's content.
Which is a semiit's a semi-public forum, I would say.
Semi-public, you know, it's not linked.
Oh, you know, that leads me to a question I had at the beginning of the program, and it's just a technical question.
You were talking aboutbecause I have a Chat Django room also at my website, which I think is just the Ocelli Effect chat room, if you look it up.
Anyway, if you go to ocelli.com, it's easy.
You go to listen live and chat.
You press a button, you're there.
But the thing is that if you're the owner of the chat room, you have the ability to throw somebody out who's making somebody's life miserable.
You can ban them.
Oh, yeah.
Remove them.
That's a good point, but the earlier chat was set up by others, and those others areI don't know where they are.
I've had no response either.
No response.
You might actually beyou know who it is.
I'm not going to mention her name.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
Very gracious lady.
Yeah, starts with an R.
Right, right, right.
Yeah, and I haven't been ableI reached out, but no response.
I don't know if she's still in this world.
Maybe.
I hope.
She was always quite pleasant.
And she's the one who set it up and various other things.
So when things got a little awry, we could have just let it go, but we have zero tolerance for stupidity.
We don't mind debating or contrary views, but when it's just outright gutter talk, I think it's time to abandon that ship and let the insurance company take care of it.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Oh, I hear you there.
Somebody might have been an administrator over there maybe.
No, that one was no administrator.
But this new one has the administrator.
I have administrative capability, and so does Bruce.
So we can filter it out.
But also we noticed there's a subtle benefit to keeping it semi-private where someone sends an email first right now at this point.
But now if we do have, like, the character that came around before, we could easily sanitize them.
Okay.
Thank you for bringing that up.
Yeah, from a cognizant point of view, this was a learningthis was just the way things happened to be, you know.
Because I've never You showed them a lot of one side of life.
Yeah, I've never set anything up.
You know, people early on when I used to speak, people say, you know, what about this one?
I said, go ahead.
Go do it.
I'll support it.
You do it.
I'm not going to do it.
You want to set this up, set it up.
I'll be there.
And the only thing I did was the website because it was easy to do a website.
It seems to be like a calling card.
These days if you don't have a website, it's like years ago not having a business card, you know.
You look unprepared.
Right.
The website is just for show.
Remember years ago?
I said, what do you do?
I do Carpenter.
You got a card?
No.
Well, you sound unprepared.
If you tell someone you've got some stuff on the internet, what's your website?
Boom, there's the website.
That's all.
It's just prepared.
But there's nothing reallythere's no need to put anything on it.
And I don't think there's a need to write treatises and write articles and all of that because it's way past that point.
If we're talking about how the body works, health, conspiracy conclusions or anything else, all that information, believe it or not, is already there.
Can you objectify it?
Why rewrite it again?
I mean I recently dropped a link in about blood pressure.
You could look up the definition of blood pressure, and there is no definition.
It's just a magic cuff.
They put it on you.
They tell you you've got blood pressure.
It doesn't exist.
It even says there is no successive information on it.
That's all.
Remember, I think, Bruce, remember that definition of blood pressure?
It's all it is.
There's no purpose for it.
It's to get younger.
Yeah.
So, I mean, why do I need to write an article?
There's no blood pressure.
What if you define it?
It's already out there.
They tell you there's no purpose for it.
So, what is it?
It's a show.
It's stupid.
It doesn't exist.
I think it's to make you feel comfortable when you sit down and get ready to be pranked and sit on your thumbtack.
Yeah.
All of these health things I don't write about because they're already out there.
But, you know, there is a point.
For example, I look through notes and things that I've written years ago, and I said, oh, man, this should be put up because why?
Why?
I look it up, and guess what?
I don't see it on the Internet, and I could give references to it.
Years ago, I mentioned things, and a few minutes later on a chat or a forum, someone would say, come on, Greek man, that sounds interesting, but I can't find it on the Internet.
So, no link.
You stink.
And I'm like, you know, it's not on the Internet.
The Internet is subject to human input.
And lack thereof.
So from that perspective, there's a lot of stuff that I've come across through the years that could be inputted.
I think it should be done at some point.
But you have so much to sift through now.
Now, the last thing you want is more.
And people are so used to looking at eating corn out of poop that if you throw down some really clean corn, it's totally foreign, you see.
So there's no reason to write anything right now.
No, absolutely.
Anyway, with that, I think I'm going to depart because we've gone a little while here, and other things are needing my attention at the moment.
All right, well, thanks for coming by.
I do appreciate it.
And, again, you know, it's been a really interesting journey of exploration for me over the past couple of years, and you've certainly been part of it.
I just want to thank you again for all of your advice and the experience of going through this stuff with you, man.
I really appreciate it.
Oh, you're welcome.
And there's more to come, hopefully.
Okay.
All right, Bruce, I think it's a wrap.
And feel free to put it on ocelli.com, folks.
That's where you find Chuck.
Thank you.
All right, guys, thanks.
You have a good night, folks.
And thank you again, Chuck, for coming by.
Absolutely, Bruce.
Thank you.
Bye.
Okay, good night there, and be well, folks.