And how does it sound in Greek?
Sounding good?
Yeah, it just sounds like you're a little bit in a very reflective echoey environment.
I don't think there's there's no duplexing that I could hear.
Okay.
Well, that's good.
That's good.
Yeah, it's just it sounds pretty close to what we sound like right now.
So, okay good.
I think they just posted It's there it's on their end.
I think they were maybe having too many things on at the time, but okay.
Yep.
That's always a possibility.
So yeah, so there's always lots of stuff.
Yeah, yeah, why not?
Wow, very cool.
Yeah, so not much has been going on and a lot has been going on again seasonally It's the end of fall almost and going into winter Watch the Middle East news.
It's sort of sublime But you still have another seven years at least three and a half before things really start Becoming evident that there will be a Middle East Union In place not like any other Union you've ever seen before it's going to be extremely dynamic Looking at what they call the news.
There was a little bit of unrest in Lebanon, Saudi Arabia You know, the the Americans have been playing second fiddle for the past 50 years.
They really don't know that Europe also has got its own problems.
So you're going to see an emergence of
power and
Meaning power it would be just not just focusing on the Middle East, but you're going to see the power base moving there
There's another like minor giving an example how minor it can be but things to watch for
European Airbus jetliner manufacturer
Says that you know
they're the Middle East is going to be doubling and their purchase orders on airplanes and doubling the
amount of planes that are home there or
You know fly in and out of their base in the Middle East.
That was an article.
I think yesterday or today so In the in the American news, what's interesting?
What's what's and you've been getting a lot of these
What they call unfortunate events, you know, like the shooter incidents, right and
Looking around and seeing what how people are describing them and they and it's just not I got a throat
I got to throw in some critical observation objectivity and what's going on with that
Three things well, actually two major things actually just make it the well, the third thing is let's do it backwards
It's false so you got breaking down period right and
Also, you have to let's say make it four things.
There's something if you'll notice Even in local events, they try to brand something terrorism Because there's something called terrorism insurance fund Right.
So if someone shoots someone it's just murder.
Well, how do you tap into the terrorist insurance fund?
Can't so everything now is terrorism because of that insurance fund that's been set up And by the way insurance companies don't have any money to cover anything.
They create it, you know with on the spot using Federal Reserve mechanics All right now the other thing that's going on is the the staging of these things and the actual action Of these things being acted out like on one of them.
There was a what they call an active shooter This is done.
I shouldn't I don't know I was debating whether I should say this in public, but I'm gonna say it Okay, mostly mostly by the FBI.
They have what's called a SOG team SOG
Which is called a special operations group and these are usually
Like imagine in society you have young people that are look like they're going to be really psychopathic and crazy
So that the idea is well instead of leaving these guys at large and then you'll end up reading about them in the paper
Like they killed a bunch of people on their own or became serial killers
The the FBI hires them and they put them on SOG teams
Special
Operations groups and they're completely brutal
They got them all over the world all over the country and when it comes time in their language to do what's called a turkey
shoot
They gather these guys around it doesn't matter who it is and they'll just you know
Have a plan and they'll act through it.
They're just the most cold-blooded people, you know, you can imagine times ten, right?
Unimaginable.
So this is so when you hear about this kind of stuff physically taking action this that's who they're using
The other thing that they're doing
The other thing that they're doing is in case you haven't noticed
the what they call the stupid rectangle and beyond that the Internet is going to be the governance of information and
communication and
Banking and whatever else everything has to be on the Internet, right?
So what what's what they're able to do see years ago when media and stories spread around me They had to refer back to the newspaper companies or you know How many newspapers they sold regarding that cover story or something called like the Gallup poll?
You know how many people watched and what they watched on TV?
Well now they're able to monitor the various apparatus that are put into the system
and social networking a social
What do they call it networking websites, you know PC's book and twit heads and all that other stuff
They're able to monitor all the comments
What they do is they're deliberately setting up scenarios and to see how people comment back to structure
Information flow and things like that.
It's like, you know, how we were talking about doing beta testing These are all beta tests for future communication and apparatus things So so it's basically there these things are made public so they could see what kind of reaction they get from Through the Internet via their systems, right?
They could read and monitor everything that's on there and listen The other thing that's being done.
If anything is live.
It's a saw group special operations group and Also, there's terrorism insurance.
So I mean who's to gain?
I mean, there's so much to gain on many levels That's why it's going on and also you have to keep in mind.
You're seeing a concentration of these events What what season is it?
It's the fall.
It's a breaking down period.
So something is being broken down right now.
All right, so So that's in essence what's going on and listen you would say you'd be seeing a much more increase in this kind of activity then No, well, yes and no If you if you just review the purposes that I state, it's just a more objective critical point of view, right?
Yeah, not an increase.
No, no, I didn't say that at all
I just basically gave an observation that you don't hear anywhere on the stupid rectangle not say anywhere
I don't spend a lot of time dwelling on what these idiots put on the internet, but just doing a cursory 15-minute thing
You know all the major alternative idiots
Independent media on whatever and the mainstream you look at like no one's really speaking of anything real here
Other than they're all looking at each other, you know, and and what they're going to say
I mean, it's it's it's pretty pathetic this human situation, you know when it comes to any any media
There's no one out there and I mean no one with a capital Oh
That is discussing anything objectively
From many points or at least you know, they all have their own little
Specialty myopia, you know, they don't I mean look all I have to say is they don't even know what day it is
You know, I'm just leave it at that, you know
So it's kind of funny to see that and if there's an opportunity to bring it up might as well
And I just did so I gave a few points there that you will not hear anywhere else only for the reason that
Planet full of idiots.
So
from that point of view
What else do you want to continue on we I have the the chat tango open
That popped up in there
when reading about the gods and mythology seems to be
Many seem to share similarities, but have different names in different ages
Different ones are Sumerian biblical Greek Roman
Interesting topic in itself
There was another one
See, oh about the knowledge of the next seven years
The setup so to speak
Yeah, this is the setup.
Well, let's do that one because the mythology
Let's just we could just do the mythology real quick
If you're looking at Western stuff Roman Greco drew it that that comes from cultures that were based on intellectual ism
philosophy seeking of knowledge only
So they they started devising
Taking things and devising them into the gods even though there were spiritual interactions
the majority of the interaction that you hear about it was great power would be more in
The Middle East part of the world in the center the naval part of the world, right?
When you hear about the Israelites and these other ones, but even then it would be minor So the I mean minor in comparison to let's say the gods in the Bible, right?
great, so
There's a lot of intellectual ism that has to be weeded out or gone through with many of the mythology
But you have to realize that when you look at I should say the current society for the past 4,500 years
Came from you know, a group of people that expanded out into the world again, right post-flood
And whatever knowledge they had they gave through oral tradition and written in other ways.
So that's why you have a lot of similarities Because there is a general story that mankind goes through Right from beginning to end and this was taught and it changes, right?
that's why you see pyramids all over the world and that's why there's always a Messiah or Christ figure all over the world and that's why there's a flood story all over the world It's because everyone came from the same that just proves that you had a central point that everything came out from right?
And it's being influenced as it as it expands from that point Just like water is influenced as it expands out of a fountain running down the river or you know expanding When you expand any body it changes as it interacts with the expand the environment that it's expanding into In terms of the next seven years.
This is another period that's going to start in the Let's say springtime summer.
It'll be evident that we're going into another period and It's going to be a transition period that it makes it plausible in everyone's mind that when there are moves and movements and announcements and machinations and dynamics Going towards the Middle East and favoring the Middle East as a power base in many ways.
It'll be accepted So what has to change in people's minds?
Well one thing that you're going to see is a decrease in nationalism You know Here in America.
They had a recent election like make America great again Well first of all America was never great second of all make great at what?
Right, you know, you know, you're not going to have a culture that's based on hot dogs and hamburgers be great.
That's sorry
I mean, that's a prop and that's like the propaganda they give
In Russia, you know, you're in a you know
This is a great society and you see 3,000 people standing in knee-deep snow get waiting for toilet paper
You're not doing here, but you're you know here you're maybe you know, you have your other stupidity
But but you know and also if you look at the history just a short dig on the Americans
You can't trust the Americans not I'm not talking about the people
I mean, they're too dumb, but you know the actual policies and treaties because from the beginning they're telling you
there are a bunch of you they can't be trusted because the country was based on a group of
or a sub leadership or a leadership that rebelled against its
Its king that it had allegiance to
So if they rebelled against their own king as subjects, how can you trust them on anything else?
Right.
Anyway, that's why when you look across through history like in World War one They did a cash-and-carry policy, you know the ally it I mean, it's just it's just a ridiculous Situation so that's why you know from an international level if you're an ally with the Americans You better have more than one or two things up on them because they will screw you right?
That's just how they roll.
So did not to be trusted.
So I mean, you know, so the nationalism everything else based on that
I mean
It's just it's just too bad, but it's not too bad because on another sense
This is also the epitome of the Western culture, you know, you know the concept of a standing wave
It goes out and then it comes back almost the same thing, but it's detrimental
Yeah, so, you know like, you know
There's a lot of fads that started in in what they call America or the States and have moved out to other parts of the world
And it's you know, like that's like the standing wave, you know, yeah
It's just a big marketplace.
It's it's pretty pathetic as a culture.
At least this is now I'm being subjective Other people think it's a great culture.
They don't have a clue.
So we've we've Americanized so many countries.
It's it's it's appalling Yeah to a certain degree you have to realize that you know people Left where they were because justice was destroying them right God is religion whether you want to call it form of Catholicism and its evil daughters Protestantism Lutheranism Quakerism, whatever else and And going forward, you know from there You know, they had to get away and they brought it with them.
So whose fault is that?
You know, so here you are and now if you keep going west you could end up starting at east again
So it just shows you global saturation, you know, you're saturating the entire planet with crap
Yeah, that's why I keep referring to the gods as the mop-up crew because when you get a lot of crap
You need a good mopping
But what you're going to see again just to go back to the seven years
I gave a little dig on the Americans well-deserved
I think and going back is saying that you're going to see a focus on the Middle East like never before
You're still going to have a lot of turmoil there because there still is a level of nationalism
That's retained and maintained by many nations
What what you're also going to see on another perspective
Outside of geopolitics is a desire to learn about things that have people have heard about but know nothing about
One of them is the gods the Society of the gods and the things attached to them and and not necessarily
Again, I've been saying this for over a decade
You you will see more interest in these things, but it won't be accurate, but it'll be more discussed than it has in the past
You know just because there'll be let's say you'll see a couple of more Bible movies coming out or idiots on YouTube
You know talking about stuff or whatever.
It doesn't mean that it's going to be accurate.
I doubt it will be at all What it will be though is a revival of the subject matter in a way that it hasn't been done before especially by younger people hmm, you know so more of a more of a saturation of the information and What no no Just more interest in it not saturation.
Okay saturation will come till so maybe ten or twelve years from now But it'll be in the wrong direction Okay, yeah.
Yeah, this is more acceptable of things old.
Let's say because You you still have a lot of paradigms that are based on this You know last 20th century or 19th century that are going to be readjusted.
You know you You know a very easy way to to judge What's going on in society as you go around a neighborhood and if you see people still enrolling in these schools?
Yeah, you're not gonna much change You know if you still see people watching TV.
You're not gonna.
You've got churches mosques synagogues in your neighborhood
Nah, you're not gonna get much change because the real change happens when the people say okay enough of this garbage
You know and recognize it for the that it is so but they can't at this point
I don't think they ever will I think what will happen is the interest in those things will diminish
so
Yeah, but this is necessarily
You know the wrap-up of a story.
That's 6,000 years old.
This is roughly You know the 6,000 and 20th year since Adam Right was this like new new for newly formed?
Guy one day.
We'll do I saw a small comment perhaps about discussing Genesis.
It's really a wide
Subject and I think the best way to to at least do it is without
Just like I'm doing this right now
Just standing what either pacing through the room making some coffee or whatever not looking at any notes because it'll get pedantic and too deep
I mean I have in some places over 30 pages of note on just the first 28 words
Wow, so there's no reason to really get into something like that and getting into things
But but I can give it the general mindset that can be viewed, but you know here's the intro interesting
Sort of revelatory thought that I've had something that was just brought out to me my into you know
External input is there is no progress in a serious way.
Let's say in a serious way where you really have Mmm.
A lot of tangible effort done unless you have something like a school or an organization or an assembly right?
So I was kind of thinking I was kind of shocked that the thought it just came in it was like Greek you have to Form some sort of a group.
Oh, no.
No, not like a crowd right like Gustavo
but something's structured where there is something every day going on and
backups and all that because you know doing all the sonic events and all the
Instruction on a cursory level or on an introductory level and some things deeper than others has helped many believe it or not
Oh, yes
But to go to the next level where you have
Something more dynamic going on and more clear and even more improvement.
Let's say because yes, it is about improving quality A structure needs to be put together and with that said I just wanted you know when I put on the website getting donations I only still do it by the mail I want to thank anyone and everyone who has sent I've received anything and everything that's been sent through the mail It's about maybe 30 or 40 or so envelopes or so.
I really appreciate that to to everyone but That has done that but I investigated also doing electronic contributions, and they really don't like it when you do Meaning like for example an American Express type deal You know if you do any situation, it's always credit.
It's always credit
You know so they're really coming out and telling you there's no money because it's all credit anyway
And they don't and in order to redeem something lawfully as raffle lawful money
You can't you need to do some kind of
not in
Some kind of conditional endorsement all you have to do is somewhere within each
Transaction each transaction state a demand for lawful money as per title 12 4 1 1 and they really make it difficult
I thought I had it
Down at one point.
I noticed there were some open holes there So I mean it's still it's not about making it lawful money.
There's some people out there I've seen on the internet someone's oh I don't do that the banks don't like I said I know but I went and looked at some of the things that people do And they actually go to the bank demanding lawful money.
That's really stupid because you're not gonna get it
This is you're too far gone for that
You know that's like going to someone who's in critical condition and asking them to run the you know an Olympic track
It's really it's it's not their fault that they're not doing it's your fault for asking that it's capable so
So again, I don't see how this is going to really go to any other level
That's why I haven't really been putting much of an effort in creating structure behind the scenes with the streams and the pod being in
All that because there's just too much that can be done
Otherwise just showing up and satisfying some
Esoteric interest because here's this guy called the Greek who says things no one else does and it sounds interesting and it works
But whatever you know there's another level that can be
Examined on this and I'm still just you know hanging out waiting to see if anything will come around in that more dynamic point
but again your idea of the
Modules was a very good idea I believe
Yeah, yeah, they are like doing module.
You know lessons and things like that right right?
Yeah You know so it'll somehow come together.
We'll see I'll just state this right now that if there's any way that I can help you just let me know Sure well you know the easiest way I always tell you if you read Even the ancient writs the purpose of money is it's portable.
It's portable land.
You know that's why for example You know now that you know people don't have rights you see your wealth is based on your land So if you want to know if a country is wealthy It's how much access do the people that live there or born there have to what the land can give right in America?
It's virtually nothing because they you know there's no value is the value in America is given to by fiat You know you have to work and get Paper signatured stuff you know you know it's frowned upon to do gardening.
It's frowned upon to you know dig wells
It's frowned upon to get minerals and all that other stuff so so either way so
Again I don't see myself doing conventional banking as most people would imagine
So the only the only really just to say truthfully as truthful as I could be the only way that I could see anything like this
Developing is by having some one individual or group multinational corporation
Or a monarchy step forward and say yeah, let's fund something like this
You know in the tune of you know seven or seven figures plus
It's not going to happen by people mailing in donations
Even though it's much appreciated that the donations that I get are very helpful.
I have a cigarette and coffee habit I really like really good coffee good cigarettes, and it gets expensive Right the one day.
I just penciled it in I spend about three or four hundred bucks a month on cigarettes and coffee So the donations don't cover that but it's it's it's okay.
It's not a while.
That's what it costs
For fun we're being gouged, but nonetheless so so you know maybe 10% or 20% of the coffee habit
Or all that is being taken care of so I pre I'm you know appreciate it, but
Yeah, there's not you know here's the other thing
I'm
Checking out of this reality is totally a cool thing to do by the way
But you you want to do it gracefully meaning like you know having the spaceship
You know where a company car come pick you up and get you away from what's going on here, but on the other hand
You know people have all these aspirations.
Oh, we've got to get this done in my lifetime.
We're either forget it You know the thing is everything is so close right now Meaning a decade and a half to you know Well, there's more discussion.
I've never really gotten into what will happen actually at that point But but there's so much going on that you know yeah before this time comes a lot of things will be exposed I don't think I'm going to be the one to do it By the looks of it, but on the other hand it's really kind of a conundrum to think like man.
You know There's so much to share, and how do you do it right?
Right so so that's just where it's at right now, so
Okay, any any other questions that you want to think we gave it up about the next seven years any anything else
I believe so that see is America perhaps to Babylon referred to know in revelations
Now when you read here's the problem with most people have with scripture, and they don't know it any writ
Any ancient writ, it's always about the area that it came out of or it's referring to
Always and it's always about the authors
No, there's bloodline play effectiveness.
It's only bloodline.
Yeah, Babylon There's a spiritual Babylon which refers to the spiritual America or a spiritual England Spiritual Israel or whatever each nation has a spirit behind it hmm and also angelic presences, right?
Malevolent mostly on this planet mm-hmm Towards man right right But the problem That's why I think you know the problem that most people have is this thing called the Judeo-christian ethic and religion, right?
That's why earlier.
I mentioned.
You know the Catholicism and its evil daughters You know which is the rest of Christianity, and it all came out of Simon Magus with a magician, right?
So imagine if what Christianity basically is is imagine Bill Gates and David Copperfield and Houdini got together and had a baby Ouch All three of them yeah, it sounds like a freak show yeah, so yeah, it's ridiculous That's why you know for example.
I'm going to harp on the Christians a little bit In a proper way you know they you know you know how I used to say you know or much I still do if someone asked you do you believe in God?
That's a ridiculous question walk away because you won't find evidence of anything like that in any writ other than the King Jimmy and The nouveau international versions and all that other crap right now.
It's God's plural, right?
I always like to call it new vogue Yeah, so it's it's God someone asked you to believe in God you walk away, right?
So there's no such thing right was Lewis Was Zeus a real living God is he different from the Creator God of other cultures?
Is he still alive?
No, of course.
He's different.
He never he never claimed to be if you study a little bit on the Those questions will be answered with a cursory study on the subject, okay, okay?
Let's see who is he was on it in terms of he was an Olympian right and before the Titans and all that that was a
Into intellectualism from the Greeks they there are entities there that would like to be called Zeus
so
Yeah, but essentially there's there's a lot of strong historical work done that Zeus was actually a Minoan King
You don't hear much about the Minoan
Civilization they were around the early dynasty of Egypt.
They were probably the most powerful civilizations on the planet
This is like the during the time let's say 2,500 BC or so
They were there if they're like the palace of Knossos
Knossos and the island of Crete very few people
Hey, yeah, okay interesting
Yes, so we get a translation of the scriptures
It seems like you will but it'll probably be more an attitude than an actual translation
Because you hear either why I mean by that the attitude will change
Because it doesn't matter if you have a real translation or not
What can you understand it how many times have you ever heard?
Me speak publicly or privately and tell people they have to study the scriptures never why no no Because you're not gonna understand anything in it anyway, so why would I recommend it great?
So even if you had people have still asked me.
What's the best interlinear?
I'm like none of them and all of them you have to be familiar with everything
But you have to know where to spend time and what should take precedence
Over another like something like you see Lord and God
I mean that's like you know a doorstop
But you still have to know it because you're gonna be communicating with morons who that's all a they have they're actually
People in America they have their own form of Christianity
They think the King James Bible is this holy relic you could put your hand on it's got a man powers
I mean, I I mean how I mean this is about as bad as it gets the talisman, you know
Yeah, but here's the other thing I wanted to get on earlier
But someone asks you do believe in God walk away because there's no such thing.
It's a plurality right, but the other thing that I Don't really say It's very simple, why do you need to believe let's say it was just God So, let's say someone says do you believe in the gods?
Well, even then so what you know why because they know who they are.
They don't need for you to believe in them The thing is the proper more proper definition of that question would be do you believe them?
in other words, if you acknowledge their writ, do you believe what they are saying and The answer to that is no most people don't believe the gods because they don't even know what the gods are trying to Communicate.
Let me give a small little dig against is we're gonna dig on Christianity a little bit That they taught they have all this crap born again.
This that you know blooded Jesus.
I don't even like saying that name And I don't think anyone should but You know many levels like that now if you read the New Testament I can give 30 examples in five minutes off the top of my head, but I won't you know scripture if you read the New Testament objectively without the Christianity what you will walk away with if you're halfway sane Not fully sane is in someone asked you.
What is that about?
Right, right
It has nothing it will you won't say anything that even resembles what Christians say say this thing called the New Testament is
unequivocally positively absolutely and entirely about a new form of government that's coming to the earth the
government of the gods and
It was ushered in
Not ushered in it was announced by this Christ type figure Messiah who also did as this blood sacrifice
It has nothing to do about religion.
It has nothing to do about Anything being done away with or anything coming in nothing to do with a circus or a church absolutely nothing You could if you look at let's say the first book of Matthew in the Beatitudes all of that is about a coming You know blessed be the peacemakers for they shall write blessed be the meek they will inherit the blessed You know the right the poor and spirit.
They will it right all this stuff.
It's about a coming time period Okay, it's all about a coming I am announcing to you the kingdom of God right if you read in the King Jimmy, right You know, it's not like you're going anywhere It's coming here because it doesn't say, you know, when you look at the better blessed be, you know, you'll you'll inherit You're not going to you're not going to inherit the kingdom in heaven.
You're going to be kingdom of heaven meaning It's it's of that right?
It's coming here.
In other words.
These people think that you die you go somewhere It's just you're talking about a sick group of people we're talking about a billion, you know, very ill mentally ill people So is this part of that perfect society?
Thing that you were alluding to no, no, it will it will attempt to be no
The perfect society thing is what it mankind will be sold in the by the mid 2020s
That'll be ushered in
Which I can give I give more details in private, but there's a group of ten people that are like a worldwide leadership group
And one of them is a very charismatic young man of a Syrian a Syrian descent
And one thing I'll just put out look when you read about this instead of Christ or anti Christ figure
That's going to be coming on the scene.
He'll be on the scene in roughly nine or ten years, right?
You know how you hear a lot of people saying oh this guy's the end of crisis guys the end of Christ, right?
This is stupid stuff.
I Would wager to say that the majority of the possibility of this man's identity being complete secret is very high why?
Because he's a model of the Christ that was in the biblical text and he is his identity was a secret
That's another thing when you read the New Testament, you will find out objectively now
You'll find out that the main character there is this Christ figure and it seems to be his identity is a secret
But yet you have a billion people professing 400 denominations of the religion
With iconography everything from a guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper to everything else you can see
Like they know like they have some idea
We're talking about the ridiculous
you know
Conjecturism here in presumption
So if you read what's called the New Testament by the way
You don't even have anything close to the New Testament in English or in your Greek interlinear
That's why I rarely get into it also
So as the Greek I think
Is a copy of a Latin which is a copy of another Greek which is a copy of the original Aramaic?
And what was around by the way for the first?
until about
The 50 AD was just the book of Matthew and I'll give a little secret here
That's why when you read even the writings of Shaul or Paul
He's he will say things like as it is written, and he's quoting the book of Matthew
So the only thing they had was the book of Matthew
And it was about announcing this kingdom of the gods on earth ruling mankind it has nothing to do about starting a religion
nothing to do about
the circus or the church or or anything and
No one knows who the Christ is because no one really reads the text objectively
Right the the the Quran is wrong about it, and that gives that's one of the giveaways on who really wrote the Quran
But if you just want to see the you know how the they categorize the yashu guy
You know so it's really an interesting
Situation I think more information will be given in that direction that it will be distracted.
I believe that there is a Possible in secret translations being put out, but it's really hard to do as a book as a large collection Right right because the people are going to be bringing the very reason why you're not going to get a good translation Or an excellent one is because the very P.
Where are you going to find the people to do that?
Right where right who has not been corrupted by the satanic religious?
Moral ethical thing that's been put on mankind based on the Judeo-christian who who's going to do it.
Yeah to find anyone very rare and Yeah, so and also the amount of Funding wherewithal and resources to do behind it.
Yeah, it just does not an easy undertaking But what will happen just like anything it doesn't matter if you had the good translation or not because you won't understand it anyway Why because you meaning you were raised in in this particular society thinking that you know?
you're going to Take what you've been told about it with some slight corrections and figure out what's being said now I'm telling you that's not going to happen unless you approach it with the most Objective mind you're not going to really understand it or you're just going to run into stuff.
So yeah, I understand It's just like I was told but maybe a little more detail no no sorry Yep, so it's quite interesting and of a predicament We got another question about what can be discussed about Paul being a trap?
Even if you well you can read it's in the book of Shimon Kepha or Peter wrote about that
He says Paul is difficult to understand right now
Continue reading about that continue reading what the Isaiah said many will come to it, and it'll be a stumbling block
Here's a little bit about Paul Paul is definitely if you look at one of the most vile institutions in humanity
It's any modern religion right and then of course it's the legal society in every society because if you want to know
for example
who
What God a society has allegiance to just look at where and how they get their law?
Right so the Western culture majority of the culture in the world right now gets it from the female goddess justice, right?
Okay, so let me just tie that in then you and then you look at Then you go look at where they get their academic or their knowledge base from and it's not necessarily Academia doesn't necessarily have a god or a goddess over it directly It sort of does a little bit here and there smattens right, but it's in full agreement With this goddess religion known as justice, right?
Okay, so when you go back to the times of Paul.
Let's say or show He was appealing to two groups of people one was the Greeks and one was the the Hebrews or the Judeans, right?
Because you got to realize Israel had broken off a hundred years or more before that even within the the occupation that took place and by the Romans so Well, they were actually broken off many years before that But it was a big division is the northern part was pretty much gone They were mixed up with the Samaritans of your like term good Samaritan.
They were nothing but good
That's why they tell you they're good
so many
aspects of that
But I would suggest that when you're reading Paul
you're going to be confused because he's trying to appeal to people that knew the law and
also and knew that the law was more a spiritual law and spiritual knowledge was higher than man-made knowledge and
Also appeal which were the Hebrews let's say and then the Judeans and then he was also trying to appeal to the intellectual little
Based culture, which were the Greeks which thought that knowledge was, you know superseded any spiritual law, right?
So he's trying to appeal to both.
So he's saying one basically You know one group knew the law what the right way to do things the other one didn't know the right way But try to figure it out.
So he's trying to reckon to both of them
because
What you have to realize he's driving right down the middle of the road
right and also this was a time the first century especially after 33 or 35 AD was a time of turmoil and
There were a lot of supernatural things going on
I say a lot meaning there were some supernatural quote-unquote powerful dynamic events going on and people needed explanations, right?
It's kind of like, you know When they nuked the towers down the residual that was still a news story a year later, right And and and you have all these idiots online trying to figure out what happened.
They're all making stuff up This is exactly what you see going on at the time That's why when you read a lot of the commentary about Paul is to be careful because you know We're trying to do something good.
But already we got people they're gonna flip this thing around and Turn it into a lie, you know, even right now, right?
Hey, so so the trap with Paul is
I've given on many levels is
Imagine a scripture being from kindergarten what they call the 8th is the Old Testament from kindergarten to high school
K through 12 the New Testament would be like a unit college bachelor's degree to master's degree and Paul would be a doctorate
So yeah, we have people now who don't even just barely going into an interlinear figuring out
You know, there's you know that are not even kindergarten just figuring out what spiritual laws are, you know how to live on this earth
Let's say right food or loathing all this stuff time
You're basically in the third grade and you're trying to ponder something in PhD
Level ain't not gonna happen.
It could happen I'm not gonna say not gonna happen because occasionally there is you know, you read occasionally there's a 13 year old, you know A 12 year old that's a professor could you know, whatever is capable of doing that?
Yes, yeah, but it's not going to happen until you master the rest of it and I'm and I'm I don't think anyone really is
Going to master it including myself
But at least you have a masterful grip on what is being said there outside of what you've been told
Now, I don't mean to be contrary
I mean sometimes I'd go on roundtables and people say Greek you we say this you say that you know
You see the opposite as well.
I'm not trying to be adversarial It just so happens to be that everything is so adversarial.
It is that way?
That's why I always say take anything turn it upside down.
And once you turn it upside down, guess what now?
It's really right side up
right, so Paul is a trap in the sense that it's a mind trap and
And also you it can't be that good
Initially if one of the most vile institutions ever known to man is using is basing
All of its doctrine on writings of Paul if you look at Christianity, it's basing all of its
doctrine on
Misinterpretations and isolated verses out of context out of Paul, so it can't be good.
I Mean if it's just a very simple, you know You know broad stroke pretty accurate analogy, right?
so so there's many levels to it and then within what Paul is writing you could see the traps within it too and the distortion but that's again on a high level you and Unfortunately and any time you have a gradient this is not too great, but when you have a gradient progression in whether it's a knowledge of something or physical Exercise, you know, we're actually physically developing.
There's a gradient
You know
There's a time where as you spend more time doing it properly
You develop and then things can be done more as you're more developed versus in the beginning great
so
Let's see
We have another question is the right direction to study society in those days
To get a better context of where the authors come from their view is not ours regarding scripture
Yes, you could say that but you also have to realize
That's a lot of history
Well, yes, you can but you also have to realize that it was these were messages that
Okay, let me just put it this way
If it was truly a
Inspired more than inspired but a dictation from the gods it bypasses history, right?
Because it's not it's not an author like Melville or Emerson or someone writing a creative writing.
This is not creative writing This is an actual transmission, right?
Right, right
But on but on the other hand you the history helps you put things in order and understand little
Details a little bit more because you can expand them on on what you know about history
given another example
Like if you look at all of the prophets and other things like that in the book of in the Old Testament
Up until maybe a thousand years ago or even the first century or actually a thousand years ago
It would be more accurate, which is a thousand nine hundred years after the first century
Most people were not aware of book of Isaiah Jeremiah
Micah any of these prophets like you can't access today
They didn't have access to that or even know about it
Because they were already the people that this was given to were already in captivity
They were in really piss-poor shape when these prophets were writing
Taking dictation to write what we call the book of Isaiah book of Jeremiah
That was not though as you see the script compiled now was not really done up until a thousand years ago
So really everything that you see in Scripture the people then didn't really have access to
In other words when Isaiah was writing Isaiah that people there didn't even know it was going on till a thousand years later.
Oh Think about it.
Yeah, so yeah, so these are discussions on you know, when you look at your history You have to keep in mind.
Why are you studying history also?
I was gonna ask how does Marlito or what does Marlito of Sardis play into to this?
Don't know who that is.
I might have come across basically.
Yeah, there's tons of people.
Yeah, he was one of the people who
again wrote a
Actually the separation between Old Testament New Testament kind of fell in his lap
Back in that time, you know, and I guess I was kind of curious on your take on that
But I'm not fully briefed on it myself at this point still digging
Yeah, there was a lot of what happened was there was okay, whatever there's funding you develop an institution or institutions
okay, developing around this because people that had a lot of access and wherewithal like to fund these things and
Most of the things that they are talking the Vatican here
Sure, and when these things were funded at the time
They were all spread apart across the world and they wanted clear concise ways to communicate
So they start putting verses and chapters on things right so they could make a catalog of
reference points
Right.
Yeah and discuss it but but they see at this point.
Yeah It's money talks BS walks Yeah, how would you describe if you understand the the timeline of mankind, you know the first?
Thousand years very dynamic two thousand years also very dynamic most everyone's wiped out brought back You have a very dynamic time period at the center of the earth You know the part of the Levant and the Christ comes and you have nothing for 2,000 years But how can you you know and within that nothing you have all the stuff that you've seen for the past 2,000 years, right?
Wow amazing So it's kind of hard to swallow that when you just live 70 or 80 years to say well Nothing has really happened in a thousand years No, not really.
No not along these lines, but a lot has happened along the low-level stuff Level crap.
Yep.
Yeah, you get to see a pretty interesting picture of all that kind of
Just manifest itself out of nothing
Yeah, because this is the time period for it's a curing time period, you know, no one could say
Well, we didn't have enough time to to test out these theories and these other things, you know, we've had two thousand years flusted
Yeah, exactly
It's not it's not a it's not a here
I would suggest that later on when everyone's brought back and all that, you know
If you mentioned to some because people will be born again
I mean born then also if you tell them you lived in the earth on this period they're gonna be like wow
Man, that was like a horrible time, you know
I
Read about there heard about that
That's like, you know
You're running someone especially when I was growing up in the 60s and 70s that grew up during World War two in Europe and they're
Oh, man, you're like, oh, you know
You heard so many stories that after a while you're like when you found out someone was growing up during that time period in Europe
During World War two you're like, oh what a horrible life.
It must have been in most cases and it was right
So the strife and the war and all that so
So this is but picture that on a 6,000 year, you know scope or 4,500 year scope because we haven't yet had much
Information to commune or communicate with anyone or information from pre-flood
Which was an incredible time period where people lived to a thousand technology abound
Incredible spiritual contact with angelic beings and gods and things like that.
So we have very little information.
Thankfully so To a degree because it would be so much of a distraction.
You wouldn't be looking at the smartphone or the stupid rectangle, right?
Be trying to achieve that again.
So the gods are pretty smart on that end, you know about censoring
Certain well actually censoring the majority of the people on this planet to the point where they are just
Focusing on what's been given to them, you know at the moment along the time period
And the whole thing essentially this is basically very short way to describe everything that you read in
Scripture forget about everything that you've been told.
This is good advice, by the way, not just advice but good advice
it's a story about forming mankind as part of the creators family and
Anything you see about the future or anything forming in there it's about the gods ruling on earth again
It's not about starting a religion or you know, a lot of people say love they don't even know what love is
Forget, you know, I mean they could say it all they want
It doesn't mean anything because they don't even know what it is.
It's not this esoteric emotion dry emotional drive That they have you know, and you know, it's a it's complete selflessness like someone someone once said motherly love All right.
Well motherly love fine.
Well, first of all, I don't know how much she really loves her child Objectively by all the pranking that she's doing number one number two.
She's this is the you know, they're confusing the carnal physical part
Number three the other part would be is sort of selfish again because she will love her child more than her neighbor's child
right
So motherly love again, you know, I'm not saying to poke fun at it or break break it apart
But it does it doesn't hold up very well either but there is a very good condition with motherly love because there are
Actually a physical etherical aspects to it, you know
That because you're connected through the umbilical cord even when it's cut there's still a presence there, right, right?
So but other than that it stops has nothing to do With the gods at all what what the gods are saying about love in that respect, right?
so So there's very little understanding if anyone were to take any subject that that is very much needed It's all through history and expand on it on many ways properly would be the subject of love All right, and that that's one of the things I touched on on one of the previous sonic events with Ocelli And I kind of froze up.
I was like, you know, I'm kind of like just mentioning these things They need to be expanded so people can see really what's going on and how little love there really is in the world Yeah, you know and I misinterpreted a lot of it now it does, you know, so There's a whole other level too.
I think that one statement you made one time of more people die Prematurely of just being alone Yeah, that's that's a little bit different, but there's also what how about how about dying prematurely if you're alone But might be even worse is dying prematurely when you're around other people The worst thing is to be around other people and feel alone.
Yeah, because you can't definitely You can't justify it, right?
If you're locked up in solitude well, you can justify that because you're physically but When you start gaining certain knowledge about the reality of being on this earth It doesn't matter if you're in a crowd of people or whatever or you're alone Yeah, yeah, but the irony of that is you're never really alone because you always don't want so Go ahead and give me about 15 seconds.
I need to go out make some adjustments.
I'm gonna I'll be right I was just I was just gonna say well if we want we can hold over and just mute out and come back maybe in 10-15 minutes or so that way we can both give ourself a little breather You got it.
Okay.
Okay, sir.
See you soon Oh So we're gonna just kick a little music back at you.
We're gonna mute out and we'll be back in about 15 And there we are.
We are back Okay So, where were we Let's going anywhere at all.
We were just kind of roaming around I believe on many different levels and topics All of them quite good mind you Okay So anything else in the chat, I'll make it my way back into the office here.
I'll see what you've got Otherwise there just maybe A question from sticks.
Do you?
Do you do anything in particular to mitigate the negative effects risk of cigarettes?
No, I Don't have any negative effects now other than Engaging in the smoke of it or a tar or nicotine or whatever, correct?
Right?
No, I generally a pretty healthful healthful into you know a body so It's just one of those things that I enjoy people call it a habit or whatever, you know, it's fine, you know Yeah, I understand totally.
I'm one of them Mm-hmm, although I've been thinking of rolling my own which probably wouldn't be a bad thing Yeah, we're growing and you know, here's the thing try growing it and then consuming it It's really harsh and you'll appreciate what they do package for you Yeah, the amount of choice that has to go through to figure out what actually smokes.
Well, yeah, so
Most tobacco I would say more than 90% of it is for commercial industrial purposes other than you know
You smoked as a tobacco product
So pretty it's it's I wouldn't say like honey
but there are certain things that have been quote-unquote domesticated to a point where they're
Think of it as the opposite of what's going on with food what's going on with food right now is a
Most of the products or types of foods that were grown and
We're very healthful now or not and they went more towards the animal strain variety versus human grade
because like with wheat, you know you hear about
Gluten and all this and peanut allergies and all that.
It's not because all of a sudden you've got allergies It's because they examine the various Species of seeds for wheat and peanut and whatever and they said well look at this one here requires less water And it's more resistant to bugs.
Why don't we plant that one instead?
Right, and it was not necessarily as good of a strain or a good of a breed of seed.
Let's say So they're downgrade are deliberately same with soy deliberately planting inferior Species, you know or types of that species and they make better cost less to grow Exactly all of all profit.
Well, there is no profit because there's no money.
It's all right Even well that makes it that just reminds you where you're at, you know, what?
What a shit what a shit society it is
They can't even see what's in front of them, you know, you know one
No one that's active in society can can deny him and be with with excuse later that I didn't know was a credit-based economy
You know, you can you know, well, you know if you want to just take it a little bit
Well, I think by the 1950s and 90% of the country's the nationalities
Let's just say the sovereign governments were in bankruptcy to the central banks
now, I'm not an anti Federal Reserve guy or an
anti-credit guy or
Whatever.
It's just it's it's not lawful Great, so, you know am I anti lawful?
Yeah, you could say that indirectly I like things to be lawful, but you know, they're none of your religions are lawful.
Not a one None of your money is lawful.
None of your Legal people are lawful.
None of your doctors are lawful
You know, none of your professors are lawful
If they try to be they won't be in those positions for very long
That's why I say none there might be
Might be some that are figuring it out
I've met quite a few and not a few more than well
On one hand doctors lawyers those types of people said I found out what it was about and I quit
How to do something else like wow, okay
So it's like one out of you know
It's usually like one out of maybe five hundred thousand or a hundred thousand that have any moral fiber in their body.
Mm-hmm Go look at the man on the street Yeah Everybody cover your ears, but the average person you run into is a complete and utter scumbag Right now you could uncover your ears now What I mean, you know, so, what do you know?
What do you expect?
how can you have a lawful medical legal religious and government when the
Ninety nine point nine nine nine nine percent of population are scumbags and psychopaths
Yeah, not a lot of good odds there
No, it's that's what I mean
The only there is you know, you're not gonna be able to separate yourself so very successfully from these idiots
And there is as well, so I mean this is the reality of it, you know
It's very that's a very accurate and safe statement, by the way
Mm-hmm
Well, I don't see any other things in Chad
Is there anything that you had on your mind that you wanted to just get across?
other than Not really.
I have a lot on the mind all the time, right?
But for public consumption and archive now other than just getting yeah
Yeah, there's I mean there's a lot to do there's a you know, like I said earlier starting off
I started kind of got hit the past few days like oh, no, I wouldn't say that what I'm doing is wrong
But I wouldn't say it's really right
Because this I've spent almost 15 years looking at this stuff and just doing sonic events is not the way to go, right?
It needs to be done a little bit more form formally and it has to have a backing and So far that hasn't happened, so that's why I'm kind of like very lax about doing anything formal I have everything in place.
We have a stream.
We have a pod bean and you have a website Me no big deal to do like before a sonic event Every week or two times a week or what have you?
You know people do it almost every day and just keep plugging away at it I mean then it's just you know, I think like you said earlier a module a little I think that's a great idea You know, maybe like an eight hours on Genesis, right for for two-hour things on just Genesis And not even getting into the patriarchs just covering to the flood.
Really really a good mindset to have and then of course covering You can't and it's not just Genesis.
You'll be going into what's called Job New Testament believe it or not also you going into but a proper New Testament and you'll be going into the Psalms and a lot of the prophets also, so Yeah, and also giving a little bit of the history on it.
Believe it or not because there is a history in Genesis that's given even before the patriarchs that can be matched to a lot of geodesic geological records and finds and archaeology Remember a really good liar has to sound like he's telling you the truth.
So the academics who are lying Have some truth in there and they sat and the reason see you can't be completely contrary to the truth and sound like the truth Because then that just doesn't buy it just doesn't the frequency then is completely completely off, right?
What they do is they have a carrier frequency like a submarine the extra-long Wavelength that what they do is have a carrier frequency and then they ride the other frequency on top of that one, right?
like sideband Like side bending, right?
Okay, so or maybe not really but similar to yes
And I would say that what they do is they put out an air of truth that grabs the confidence
Just like the bait on a hook and then now you're hooked and now you can't get it out of your jaw
So I'll show you how much of what's called scientific data, but real scientific data the stuff
that's not plugged in university textbooks anymore, but anyone could still access it correlates with many of the
Archaeological and anthropological finds because it's not what you think.
I always say it's not what you think Yeah, and other thing is the problem is it's two Two sides there one thing.
It's not well, the other thing is what you think Let me just address the second part if you're thinking you're gonna get in trouble So it's not to do so much of it But when it comes time to think you should be able to do it.
You see what I mean, right, right?
Yeah, I don't suggest anyone go off and become a thinker
you will find yourself eating out of a garbage can unless you have people that love you around you and you have a
Very narrow, but very, you know
You can get what you need in life
Because if you start becoming a thinker, you're not able to function properly in this world
But when you the will come times in everyone's life where you do have to do some serious thinking
So if you don't have that skill, how are you going to see?
so So it is important to Be able to think Well, as I said before if there's any way that I can help you all with the mods Any kind of support that I can help?
Sure But as it is right now in terms of putting out a lot more stuff It's it's not I don't see it other than getting into detail.
I mean, I think the cursory approach I know that for myself included doing on other Platforms or the once-a-week thing the sonic events, you know the past couple of years was actually refreshing for myself and I knew in the background that Someone might have heard something that kind of like, you know Gave them the wake-up call just for a minute, right?
Or some other people more than that for a few days or other people actually implemented it in their lives But I believe that there is a point that I've crossed just in the past few days that this thing needs Tremendous back backing.
Yeah, and until that happens, it's not I can't see myself really delving into even Many subjects and in depth like how I would enjoy to know because also be taking time away from what I need to do So But but you know on the other hand, you know, this is and we're not a one-armed person, right?
We've got two hands.
The thing is doing these regular little sonic things is fine.
I mean, okay, I think it because I've realized that the the spiritual landscape meaning mental Landscape in the world and including people who listen is an utter wasteland So I might take for granted.
Yeah, I've learned this and I've been doing this Let's say for 30 years or 20 years or 15 years There are other people out there that don't even have a clue of what I'm Let's say contemplating that even just the slightest Bit of impart impartation or imparting is going to help them tremendously, right?
Right, so you don't know what you're gonna say and when you're gonna say in what depth or not
That is really going to affect other people and I have seen privately through emails and messages and you know
Even this real minor chat or whatever
there are
there it has made a
positive
qualitative difference
So, you know that I think should keep going on but
There's there's many levels to it and also the time period
This is a an interesting time period, you know
I should say that if you asked me five years ago, would I be speaking now?
Right now, you know five years in the future about these things.
I would say no I would have probably either waited till much later, you know, or just done a bunch of stuff and then stop So it's a very interesting way to predict one's own behavior is to think where I'm set was five years ago I mean very often there are things I have in private conversations Oh, I'm never gonna say this publicly and then six months later.
I do or a year later I do and I noticed that if you say it It's like as if you didn't say it or as soon as you get this a lot not push back in a bad way But a lot of response like wow, man, you know, that's really cool.
You see so it's it's kind of Let's just let's just say it this way Back to why people are here why we're here.
It's for character building
It's for the development of the spirit through that you see what the gods do is they give you everything in life
They also influence basically your your mind is is is like a cloud on the computer or server remote server
Right, but when you put all of these things together in the material sense
You are going to have within the exercise of where you want to be on the cruise ship
You know free will versus the whole ship where it's going
How we do these little minute things and you go about based on what you've been given as part of your development you see
So tying it back to doing sonic events and all that
I believe that as I put out things and see what kind of feedback there is or interest or whatever again develops
The information itself than if it wouldn't have been
spoken
But but essentially I've been mulling over like there's been requests about discussing Genesis for example, let's go back to that and
I looked at it
I said there's no way I'm gonna be able to refer to notes and do a sonic event on this because like I said
It's just four hours on the first verse
Great, right easy easy.
That's just not it's just gonna kind of really well, is it gonna help people?
Yeah, but we're talking about most people don't even you know, right after the word the they get lost great, right?
Mindset isn't there So the mindset needs to be put together and one way to do it is to just discuss it openly as if we're at the bar You know or in the parking lot some of the best discussions I've ever had Business or otherwise was after a meeting at the parking lot.
No one-hour meeting
We all decide to leave and I'm at the parking lot still speaking three hours later and after three hours like, you know
We should just go sit down at a bar somewhere
Then do another three hours there, so I mean that was some of the best
developmental efforts I've seen
so I was thinking, you know, there's many levels to it, but
You know one is of course doing the modules in a semi pedantic way
And the other way is just doing so throwing several sonic events at Genesis to get the mindset
But again, you know, I'm not considering the audience at all
Very often you see any successful persistent venture.
That's why people say what does it take to be wealthy?
What does it take to be successful?
You just have to be persistent I mean just look at the the let's just use the internet as an example.
It's just rubbish throughout 99.99% of its garbage You know other than having a watch or a clock on it You know the wind-up toy the calendar and a telephone book and reference.
Let's say a telephone book is like your hardware What am I looking for?
So instead of just finding the store now you can see if they have a website what they have on their shelves It's just more in-depth.
It's just otherwise other than that.
It's garbage, right?
so when you look at What makes it so successful its persistence?
It's always there, you know, they put it on the phone deliberately so it could be persistently around you Yeah, look at something like McDonald's what made them is they're persistent you know the It's persistent.
So I don't see I'm not looking to see in order to be persistent.
Also, you have to be able to focus on the audience I I really don't look at the audience that I'm addressing other than I keep reminding myself.
This is planet Earth They're all morons.
I'm meaning all statistically.
There's a few that are not very few, right?
But it doesn't mean it doesn't mean you shouldn't impart because of that you just impart and disqualify it say look When you give a piece of information, you also have to show the contrast This is very contrasting to what's going on.
And here's the other thing.
I've said many times before in the past
Back to the internet or movies or fiction or whatever
Most people it's best that they don't know some things
The reason I say this is because you can take the most outrageous
Conspiracy theory the most horrific scenario you've seen in film or the deepest darkest
Craziest shit you've seen on the internet and reality is ten times worse than that worse than that not better worse
The last thing you want to do is just figure out how bad it really is you see
What what it really what is really going on is like you're you're asleep on a bunk bed on a tightrope and you don't know
it
All right
So but fortunately the people's lives are so short that they can't grasp it even
And of course, there's also a remoteness aspect to it
Like fortunately, it's not directly happening to you directly you are being affected indirectly, but directly, you know, you've heard me
Give the metaphor you'd be thankful that no one came through the window last night ate your liver out of your body while you're sleeping
Yeah
That's very direct, but that is going on but not to you.
Obviously you wouldn't be here most likely so it is that bad
But you don't want to focus on that because most people are so weak-minded
They're gonna say oh, I don't want to be around the negativity and you shouldn't but there's a level of objectivity that once you attain
In any field you will see it is really that bad
But again tie it back to how short your lifespan is the you don't see that as affecting you in within the short lifespan
So there's many aspects to it.
That's why like when I bring up religions on how vile and disgusting they are It's not because I find them to be that way It's because anyone can find them to be that way when they look at them objectively There's a difference there, right?
Unless you're totally into coprophagia You know and which most people I would say not most but quite a few enough for the population is That the worse off the worse.
It is the more that they like it So that part I don't want to go down that line of understanding.
So yeah, there's a you see the balancing of information mean so You know, there's there's many levels to it and the level I think that could be discussed is objectifying it showing the contrast and And then just walking away but you know, there is a You know, there's several like we discussed the modules earlier, right?
Right, which sets for more on a personal note even to develop the Genesis module to do it, right?
It's going to be at least four two-hour sonic events.
That's going to take me at least two weeks full time to do Wow, so I'm You know, where's the inspiration on that?
Right?
No, I follow you.
There is nothing Yeah, you know and at this point if it came if it went with me to the grave, I'd be totally fine Screw everybody, right?
But then but then that's one side.
The other thing is well, you know, you've got to make an effort to do it anyway right, so You see how it works.
Oh, yes Yeah a little while back you dropped something about the first five Books of general of the Bible and the words be beside them and What it means?
Yeah, every book should be done that way Everything every name a year for years.
I've been saying when you read scripture Let's say the book of Zechariah, which means Yahweh remembers when every time you see Zechariah in the script itself Look at the paraphrase the phrase and insert that into the verse Yeah, and then read the verse and then you're like, oh what a change Yeah, same with Danielle the same with the names of the books, right?
So yeah, if you look at better sheath, right you you look at Genesis Exodus Leviticus numbers Deuteronomy Right, it would be better sheath, which is beginnings Exodus the names Leviticus pronouncing numbers Bambi Bambi did our desert and Deuteronomy means the words So in the beginning the names are pronouncing in the desert the words is what's the first?
Yeah, it's right and then you go on and then there's another level to it within the names
You know like the names of the first seven
Patriarchs actually tell you story the the the the first letters of the first word in
Genesis tells you the whole story
better sheath
the bat rush
Aleph shin tough those letters
They give you the whole story of the scripture the 28 letters in the first verse of Genesis
They're their numeric position and the meaning of the letters give you the entire story of the entire book.
Oh my god, right?
yeah, so I mean, you know and then you have a Directional aspect to it where the book of Leviticus?
Well, you see the book of Exodus and the book of Numbers every seventh letter in Exodus and book of Numbers Spells out the father's name YHWH every seventh letter in Exodus.
It doesn't have to write In numbers, it does it right left, but it's not in Leviticus.
So it's as if there are two arrows Pointing at Leviticus if you want to know who why?
Hwh is you better read Leviticus That's why his name is used more in that book than any other directly than any other see when you read his name in the book Of Leviticus, it's consolidated.
It's not spread out
So it's as if you have two brackets or parentheses as the book of Exodus and the book of Numbers around the book of Leviticus
Yeah, right
You'd see, you know
If you could just do it if you look at the interlinear you see every seventh letter starts to begin to spell his name
So there's many levels to that but that's not what I want to get into Genesis in Genesis
You can include make that knowledge inclusive, but just discuss, you know when it discusses mankind
How many types of mankind are there?
That's right in front of you.
Yeah, and when was it done?
No, and when and it's there's no discussion on this I mean there is a little bit there's some rabbinical circles that have discussed it a while back and maybe even now There's a lot of people fighting this it really turns a lot of people But but the thing is then do we take is it metaphor?
Is it literal?
But you what if we take both?
Yeah, you see what if we take both if we look at it as metaphor and we look at it as literal and they match Well, guess what?
We've got it If we take it as metaphor and then we look at it as being literal and they contradict Well, then you have to make a choice like a four in the road Both or you can in a counter spatial way and I always refer to counter space Counter space going on in Genesis because if each day of creation is a thousand years Why does it matter if it's evening and then morning one day great?
That matter where is where does the 24-hour day or the rotation of the earth come into play and it does Even in a thousand year period and discuss that see so and also you when you look at Genesis Is it the first day or a first day a second day or the second day?
Are you aware of that concept?
Yeah, there's a big you know ordinal versus cardinal let's say or numeric, you know, or in order of time and in just a Given number or select of many Right to say that I have three cars outside.
Here's here's a first car.
Here's a second car.
Here's a third car Well, the third car might have been the first car I bought right?
I Didn't tell you which car I got first.
I just said here's you see So this is an interesting concept that needs to be looked at and we we can do that But you know, so and here's the thing I've given believe it or not I've given enough hints so far through the years on Scripture that you can do I've gave all the hints So if there's someone who's fastidious Diligent and really has the interest you could have done this already, right?
Yeah on the other hand I Suggested earlier the only way to really do this properly is with a group or that some kind of an administrative body That has like a collective to it, you know, right?
So and it's all sonic events isn't really going to do it
But it can like I said, maybe we'll do a module of four two-hour deals
Maybe it could be done in just two two-hour deals, you know with Genesis and see how that goes
You know, so like the bullets week or two full-time putting it together
But there's another you know, there's another level also, which I always bring up which is is a time yet if it's not time yet
It's not going to happen.
You'll be met with natural resistance natural meaning the natural world around you'll prevent you from doing it so Let's just let's just see on that.
I think Pursuit of food clothing and shelter is the most important still because if you don't have a body you don't have a consciousness You go unconscious So, you know pursuit of good food good clothing, you know comfortable clothing That's because clothing can affect the health and also the shelter the health in your mindset.
So Those things are going to just go very well There was a couple questions in the chat, would you say mystery Babylon would be Jerusalem in the end Of one of yeah, that's a good question.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
It'll be placed there.
Uh-huh at one point Especially after this new edit a new old edifice is revived there That's one thing I brought up in one of the sonic events You should look out for what's called actually not would say rebuilding but the building of a temple building In in Jerusalem, and it's not going to be on that ridiculous Mount Moriah Platform So it's going to be The temple Mount, right?
Yeah, that's not the temple Mount.
That's a that's a that's like going That's like going to a soccer stadium and saying that's the Vatican.
Oh Okay.
Okay You know, it's not it's a military base what they're These religious quote-unquote Jews are banging their heads against the wall over there Yeah, it's a prank.
Yeah, but the rabbis you have to realize I have discussions with people that were born and raised in Israel and
Most of people that are in that part of the world are either atheists or secular
They're non-religious the majority and the reason why I mean they they are aware of the days that they do on the Babylonia
Because remember the modern-day Jews are on the Babylonian
Dark moon and their festivals are in line with the Babylonian stuff Egyptian Babylonian not scriptural
You know, there's no such thing as a Saturday Sabbath actually or the day starts at sundown only, you know
They never started at sundown
But Babylonians did it for several reasons.
I've gone into before and the dark moon came out of Egypt in Egypt in Babylon
we're sister cities, but
going back to why most quote-unquote people in Israel are secular is because the rabbis are like little
despots like little
Gestapo's once once you
It's a have a pun there right once you decide to be religious the rabbi comes into your life and runs your life
Based on his opinion, of course, you don't want that.
Nobody wants that right?
You don't want like a scout master Whatever a little Nazi kind of attitude.
That's what they don't have there Wow, you know so these guys got to go those rabbis got to go their attitudes got to change and they're not that smart They sound smart, you know, they're into the tradition, you know Kind of thing.
So that's that's there that watch that.
I haven't really got into when I do have discussions with people from Hot it's it is odd.
It's Israel, which is the land of Israel
There a lot of very often
They're quite pleased to discuss these things with me because there's a we discuss things that they can't discuss with anyone else
But on the other hand those people are going to be going through a drastic change and to go back to mystery
Babylons, which is secret Babylon
There is no word is sick secret Babylon, which are the secret Babylonian rituals that were developed after the flood
Will be revived there, which is one of the secret Babylon things.
Are you familiar with Zaro isms arrow is?
thruster ism It's sort of parallel to Mithra ism It's the religion of the Persians that you have a super like your society will be saved by a special individual That's endowed with superhuman powers that will come out of your society.
That's where you get all of That's where you get all of the comic book heroes for you know, they put on a cape and they save the day You know, oh, yeah, one dog mighty dog Batman all Superman.
That's a Zara Zara thruster ism zero ism out of Persia.
That's one of the things Mithra is is Another which is the you're here of the holidays in the winter.
That's Mithra ism.
Oh, okay Holidays in the winter.
Yeah so These things are minor but there are going to be revived Abominations so to speak and that's an accurate term for that.
That will be coming in the mid 2020s a Revival of things you see a precursor to it now just like I've given too many examples You know, it's like some people say Greek why so relaxed?
There's no privacy.
You're being bat-bugged and it's a police state Because this is a precursor of what the future is going to be like but not in a Malevolent way like it is now in the future, you know, you will know you have no privacy But it will be okay because it'll be good.
You'll have nothing to hide, right?
You'll be lawful right now.
You're unlawful That's why you need passwords and all this other stupid stuff and whatever And terrorism insurance, right?
Right
The police state is it's obviously it's run by the Attorney General's, you know, there's of course, it's unlawful
right, but in the future you're going to have police state that makes this one look like but
Not even Boy Scouts Cub Scouts, but it's going to be lawful
You see
So so you're being sure
Yeah, it'll be lawful
People don't know what lawful is it's really and anyone I think I'm the only one around really that's discussing it on an ongoing basis
regarding all things, you know, you have a lawful and unlawful side and
Anyone that hears this kind of discussion?
I assure you it takes you a minimum of three months to a year For that concept to just settle in forget about realizing what lawful and unlawful is just the concept Because that's how far removed this society is So, so when you tell someone you won't have any privacy, but you don't have any privacy now to those that matter anyway Who matters?
God's the gods matter.
You think you're gonna hide you can't so that you see so there's many aspects to that The only thing that'll be more overt is when you have Enforcement of a lawful society, right?
You say we well, I can't do what I want Well, you will be doing what you want, but you'll want lawfulness.
So it'll be fine You see right, even though these these demon attorneys they say well you shouldn't even the people say they got people trained Well, you shouldn't worry about it.
If you're not doing anything wrong
They forget to leave out the part that they're predatory
Right and parasitical the legal society is and the police and all that everything comes around the clerks the courts the judges the police
The grandma's the people that say, you know all this stuff, you know
Well, it's not completely unlawful crap
But this is the time period for it so you should be at peace with it, you're not going to change it and
Fortunately, you don't hear that anymore as time goes on you notice people saying we have to do the world better
You don't hear that at all anymore almost
Still was a little it's still a little bit was around five years ago.
Thankfully that stupid shits gone away They people are getting an idea like you're giving an example, you know how I discussed the The amount of time left you could look at architecturally a thousand years ago structures were built to last a thousand years a hundred years ago Both to last a hundred now Especially starting in the past decade or so.
All these big structures are designed to last just ten years I mean, I'm sorry 20 25 40 tops, right?
Now the other thing that's interesting is about two weeks ago the Bureau of Standards which revises and upgrades Every I think five years or every decade or even every year is an international convention that last month or so They announced that they will no longer ever be meeting to upgrade the standards anymore Why they've been downgrading them for the past hundred years.
They had national international convention now all of a sudden They don't need to do it anymore.
Oh
Maybe they think they're starting if their heart is letting them know that there's no reason to
You see so you be aware of the short
temporal nature of things that are proclaimed
right, I mean
this is the the aspect of and I like for example in America, you know, like the best thing the administration to do is devise a
Distraction about something about North Korea
Shooting missiles and going to war with them
How is the US how is the US going to go to war with North Korea when they can't even find it on the map?
Yeah Can you can you answer that first and if you can if they have made it there or nearby there It's totally by accident.
I'm sure I mean, that's a that's a state.
Yeah, that's a matter Yeah, it's a statement an analogy on the intelligence level, right?
Yeah, so I mean there is no discussion about anything I mean how many people are saying this country has been bankrupt and insolvent and in receivership under a credit-based Economy for the past 80 years and we should maybe start addressing revising that How many people are discussing?
Yeah.
Yeah, I haven't heard a peep Finished that's why I keep saying they're Unrehabilitable unrehabilitable means you can't fix it like Humpty Dumpty.
They teach you that as a young child
Yeah, you can't fix it
It has to just run its course just like when you take a shower and you you know
You turn off the water and you look down at the drain and they're just a limited amount of water
You're not gonna you're not going to capture that
It's going to go down the drain there all the soap scum and all the hair and all that's going down the drain
There's nothing you could do to stop it
And if you stop try to stop it someone else is going to come and pull the plug because it needs to be drained away
Yeah, this is human society at this point and it's been this way for a very long time
the interesting part is that you're you're going to be
coalesced spiritually mentally in a in into a state of
Let's say the final state where you will be given a false idea that
You'll you're going to be fine, right?
It's kind of like have you ever heard of anyone getting a dislocated soul if you know anyone who used to let's say race bicycles Gets into a bike crash most common thing.
It's a broken collarbone or clavicle or dislocated shoulder, right?
Yeah What they do is they you know, you're in pain and they they have you sit outside and an orderly comes up to you and he says we're gonna go see the doctor now and there's two big guys one guy grabs You one guy holds the arm says but I'm gonna move your arm on three You're ready and they go to one two, and they pull it on two not on three, right?
Because if you know because you're gonna flinch you're gonna tighten up on three.
This isn't what humanity is going into Right in the mid-2020 you're gonna be told that this is gonna be a perfect society for the next thousand years and Then you have a little few years of that and then the kill shots start coming Yeah, and you're not gonna and everyone's gonna be good What kind of a mindset does society have to have what kind of a fervor?
Where you read on the news or whatever that a billion people were killed last night and it's okay.
We're gonna clean up Right.
Could you imagine that kind of a that mindset does not exist now?
Does not exist as we stand right now So what kind of a mindset change are you going to have in the next seven years plus to accept that Well, you're also you're also gonna have other events is gonna be two three billion overnight And you're gonna be like, okay, what so we'll just get back on track.
It's alright I mean, yeah, it's sad or whatever, but we'll fix it.
Could you imagine that what kind of a mindset?
You're gonna be set up for in the next seven years So when someone asks, what is this next seven year like think about the how radical of a change of mindset.
I Mean right now as it is what you people are accepting across the board whether it's food Social scientific education religious across the board that if he was presented 52 people from 50 or 70 years ago There would be an ultimate shock Very them would be the ultimate shock to them.
They'd say we have to stop everything we're doing so this doesn't happen But right now what I'm telling you is as a screwed up as it is today Or as it was yesterday.
Well, I think about what kind of a mindset change how drastic it's going to be that a billion or more Over dead overnight.
It's going to be acceptable in the next seven years.
So watch out for that Watch what you what how people's morality?
Well, what's what what warped morality they have is going to be stretched to its elastic limit Watch for that.
Oh Okay think about yeah, oh, yeah, it's a lot All right.
Yeah, you guys are getting a lot you get more than a nickel's worth that's for sure.
Oh god.
Yes, so Anything else or we should maybe start wrapping it up.
Let's see here.
We got anybody else Are the scholarly article stating Yahweh was just a low-level storm God at one point true No, no, not at all Here here's the the aspect to scholar scholars, they'd never really go direct It's very rare that scholars go direct to source documents.
They always like to read what someone else wrote
They'll spend their entire career on what someone else wrote
Hmm, I'll use names like these morons like Jordan Maxwell
I mean, I don't like to put out names
But I will pray and who's the before him was the he based his work on whatever these guys are total moronic
And I know it's funny how
It's like the magician
idea
You like or the the Gnostics which was based on magic and you know, even Tyson's still support them
what makes them nervous is for example, if you're a magician on stage and
You're performing what makes you nervous is another magician comes and sits down in the audience
Because you don't know if he's gonna open his mouth and tell the people in the audience how you're pulling this illusion over them
and the illusion that most of the people that have been on this stupid rectangle like I mentioned Maxwell and I mean
There's thousands of others, but he just jumped out.
Someone sent me a link.
There's always stuff is great What do you mean?
Oh boy, you know forget it.
You don't get it
If you see, you know, he is counting on your ignorance
University is counting on your ignorance scholarly documents are counting on your ignorance
The people on the rectangle are counting on your ignorance
And if you they're very very superficial and they're basically liars and frauds basically at the root of it
Now I'm not saying this has to do you should go and be naive and
Go around and say well, this is a source document.
It's good.
No, that's being naive Crazy, so there's another level to you have to do what's called proofing so and You know, fortunately, I don't get it as much lately as I have in the past people just throwing stuff at me for approval You know, okay, right But you know on one hand it's like oh no No, this is it does several things when people ask for approval one.
It shows well the person is looking for approval They're not sure.
The other thing is showing that how bombarded and how Would have a sad shape, you know the information stratum of society is right?
There's so much stuff out there That how is any how can anyone humanly possibly go through all of it and figure out what's correct, right?
Yes, and the other the other level as well There's a level of discernment is it is the person who's asking the question really listening to what I'm saying?
Because I'll tell you the majority of the time already answered it Yeah, black already answered it.
So, you know, there's many combinations to it all to be Again, you know, this is a gorilla.
I'm a gorilla informist I come out.
I just do a hit and I run right, you know, there's not that's why you go to the website There's not much up there You know and whatever there's no reason to at this point.
Mm-hmm You know if there's three people on the planet that got what I'm saying That's three times more than I thought I would have get gotten, you know, correct.
So So we're all good.
Yeah, very nice.
Well, sorry And he get rid of that word, all right, so why don't we call it an event I think we got an hour and a half or I think we did.
Yes.
Yes, we did Well, as always, thank you, and it's a great pleasure And we'll keep in touch, okay.
Thanks everyone.
Bye you have a good night now