Okay, how are we doing?
Yep, we're here.
Alright.
Taking out the box, and we're on.
Yeah, so about light, I think we went over it a little bit.
It's very simple.
It's one of the least understood things because we're so sensitive to it, especially people that can see, of course, just like we don't think about most things.
But I don't know, I mean, it's a perception.
You know, you could not be perceiving light and still be alive and perceiving other things.
Is that interesting?
You know, the blind, for example, right?
And I think someone put internal or external light.
You know, in the future, people will discover that darkness is also a form of light.
They're both, I would say, work with each other.
That's how you get color, okay?
Color is not in white light, like the rock and roll album that shows a prism.
If anyone has a prism and puts white light through it, you're not going to get what they're showing.
And even MIT morons in training, textbooks and things like that, you're going to see dark bands and light bands and certain colors emerging on upper bands and lower bands, meaning where the light and dark interact, you know, through the refraction and diffraction of the prism.
So what's interesting in the ancient writ, scripture, it states that the darkness was bara, or created, and the light was formed, or yitzar or asar, formed.
There's a big difference between creating and forming.
There's a big difference between creating wheat or making bread and cookies and crackers and pancakes.
So the bread and the crackers and the pancakes and the cupcakes and all that is forming the wheat into something, where actually creating the wheat, let's say, is something else entirely.
There's a big difference in the practice.
Yeah.
And also light doesn't travel, and the notion of a photon is ridiculous, because any light bulb is in a vacuum condition, right?
Remember years ago, even with the old incandescence, when they started getting really bright, that means the vacuum was lost and it was literally combusting and then it went out, right?
Right.
Yeah.
So if it's in a sealed vacuum, how does the photon go through the glass?
Right.
There's no mass.
Nothing.
Yeah, there's nothing there, really.
It's a wave.
Again, it goes back to magnetism.
If you comprehend magnetism, one thing we used to do is take two same poles.
If you take two magnets, the opposite poles attract and the like poles repel.
But if you rotate them a certain way, you can get the like poles to stick to each other.
It's very sensitive.
If you just breathe on it, they'll pop apart, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, because the magnets are not made perfectly.
There's a weaker spot and you just put the two.
So if you put two norths together, they're going to repel.
But within that magnet, there's a weaker north and a stronger north.
So you just keep rotating the like poles and you'll feel they repel more in one aspect of the rotation than the other.
So if you could sort of like wind them in together and get that vortex to start locking and screwing into it, just like a nut and a bolt, you'll get them to lean together and they won't repel.
And this might sound like an oxymoron, but the stronger the magnet, the better it works, right?
So you're like, that doesn't sound right because the stronger magnets seem to repel more.
Yeah, that's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about screwing them together, literally screwing them together.
You ever try to put a nut right on a bolt?
You can't.
You could force it.
It seems like the bolt is repelling the nut, but once you start threading it, they wind in, right?
So you wind them up.
Okay, well, once you do this and you lean them against a table or a book or something, walk away about 50 feet or more and take another magnet in your hand and start aiming either side of the magnet towards those two magnets, and all of a sudden they fly apart at 50 feet or 100 feet.
So what does that tell you?
You can influence from that far away.
But if you did that, let's say you had shavings like they show you on a piece of paper, that's not the magnetic field.
No.
When you put shavings on a paper plate and put the magnet on it, you see that figure eight or whatever, you're just turning those other shavings into little magnets.
That's not what the field really looks like.
I mean, yes, it is when you affect it that way, but you can't say that is the magnetic field.
Right, because there's other forces at play.
Right, so imagine at such a distance, light being able to reproduce that field through various materials.
That's why in the fog, light doesn't reproduce that well.
But through a vacuum, light reproduces very well, but there's nothing there.
It's a vacuum, yeah.
And also, light reproduces well through most gases and translucent, transparent objects.
But what light doesn't seem to want to reproduce when it hits a brick wall, does it?
Right.
Yeah, so what do you get on the opposite side?
A shadow.
Is that absence of light?
But I thought the shadow was dark, but I thought the darkness was created and the light was formed.
Right.
So what you go back to is where the light comes from.
And there's got to be other forces that are moving along with that particular light.
Well, yeah, the light itself is the waste product of the ether.
The heat that you feel is a waste product.
I shouldn't say waste product, but it's way down the line meant to interact with the physical world.
Light, heat, electricity is way down the line of this ether.
So it's a bottom of the scale.
In the material world, yeah.
It's descending, yeah, that's why, you know, descending into materialism and ascending into non-materialism, right, where the things are.
It's always better to control...
When it's formed, one is created.
Sure, well, right.
The stuff that's created is the raw material, and the stuff that's formed is the working of that raw material.
So one can say that light is the working of raw material of darkness.
Now, there is a spiritual side to this.
When you're bound to the material world, as we are, meaning we can only be animated through material.
In other words, if you remove the material, you go into disanimation, no consciousness at this point.
The darkness tends to be a bad thing.
That's why the forces of evil tend to be associated with darkness, because it will put you into basically a death state.
Right.
And death is to be avoided, right?
Yeah.
Until you can manifest the light on your own later, and understand how these things really work, and then you're no longer subject to that death state.
So what happens when you're no longer subject to death, you also won't be subject to darkness, unless you want it.
So these are interesting.
Now, that starts to get into more, sounds like more philosophical stuff.
Right.
But I call them counter-spatial issues.
Like the most basic counter-spatial issue that can be explained in tradition is, you know, the thousand angels dancing on the head of a pin, but yet each angel is 30 feet tall.
How can you do that, right?
You know, so because it's a counter-spatial relationship.
Understanding dielectrics is a counter-spatial relationship, too.
Right.
Electricity.
That's always been a weird one.
Well, you know, Tesla, I'll give you an example of simple bounce around with light.
Light is not much to talk about, other than it reproduces through whatever medium, and if you aim light at something, and you can't see light, by the way, if you aim light at something and don't see any other side, it's because it can't reproduce through that material.
It's very simple.
It's a wave.
You can never see light.
You know, if you point a flashlight in pitch black, you're not going to see it.
You're only going to see where it lands on or, you know, where it stops to, you know, be reproduced.
Right.
I'm not talking about the dust particles and all that, because that's still a gas.
But to give a little bit of the counter-space and make it more tangible would be considering what Tesla's comments were regarding nuclear devices.
He says those nuclear devices they're making are but an infant's consumptive breath compared to a capacitive discharge.
And what he meant by that is, you know, the concept of work, you know, watt.
When you say watts, right, or whatever, you have, you know, slew rates and you have power factors and things like that.
But essentially, it's when you say a watt of power or energy or joules, it's versus time.
Correct.
So if I say we're going to use one watt of energy per second, well, that might be like your headphones or so, you know.
Or a very, very tiny speaker or a very dim light.
Right.
Released into the environment at one watt, at a rate of one watt per second, right?
But what Tesla was discussing, that a capacitive discharge makes a nuclear device look like an infant's consumptive breath, is that a properly constructed capacitor, when it's fully discharged in a very short period of time, if you can get that time to go to infinity, zero, right, nanoseconds, is how you get that energy release.
For example, you know, we mentioned the one watt per second, right?
Right.
Well, if you can release one watt in a billionth of a second, it does the same work as a billion watts.
If you can release one watt in a trillionth of a second, you see, because what will happen is when it's released so fast, it creates a shock in the ambient environment.
And then you have a thermal stress or whatever, photoelectric stress.
And that's the basis.
Or is it moving into one of those situations of create and form?
Say that again?
Or is this a technique in using creation or form?
No, that is the counter-spatial side of things.
Okay, right.
The counter-space, because if you say someone, I have one watt of energy, that doesn't seem like a lot, but most people would say that's not a lot of energy.
But from Tesla's point of view, if you could release that one watt in a trillion trillionth of a second, that would be like releasing an H-bomb, you see?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so that's what he mentioned.
That's a lot of energy.
Well, it's not.
It's still that same watt.
Right.
It's just how it's being released into the environment.
How it's being released, right.
Into the environment, yeah.
Huh.
Yeah, that's why, you know, when I hear about all the crap, you know, about guns, bullets, weapons, I'm like, ah, that stuff is so primitive, you know.
Right.
And fortunately, the primitives or the savages on the planet rely on that, and they don't rely on more advanced thinking and application of things.
Like, I remember they were saying they were going to take all the guns away a few years ago.
Well, it's kind of stupid, because you want to just take the ammunition away.
Right.
Then they become peashooters.
But even if they took the guns and the ammunition away, what are they?
They're just high-speed chemistry projectiles, aren't they?
Right.
Powder is a chemical reaction you're relying on.
Mm-hmm.
And a high-speed chemical reaction to send a projectile.
Well, prior to that, they were launching projectiles many different ways, you know, from slings to arrows to crossbows to catapults.
Right.
And chemically, there's something called Greek fire that they still don't know what it is.
The Greeks would launch firebombs on their opponents, you know.
And it was chemical-based, but they say it's been lost.
And to a degree, it has.
But, like, for example, in the American context, they're so proud of having their arms, and they call them firearms, which they're not firearms, by the way.
Right.
You know, the legal definition of a firearm is a shotgun sawed off to an overall length less than 18 inches, a machine gun, chemical weapons, or a grenade.
So do you know how many people are sitting in jail for illegal possession of a firearm and it was just a pistol or a handgun, which doesn't qualify?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
It's ridiculous what's going on.
Just like I mentioned, you know, Title 21 in the U.S. Code is narcotics and all that.
You know how many people are in jail over possession and all that stuff?
Millions, right?
But what they fail to tell you, under public law 9843 or something, Title 21 has no criminal effect.
It's been repealed.
But they don't bring that up when they charge.
See, most people watch too much TV.
Right.
So in order for you to go to jail with possession of any amount of drugs or whatever, legal or illegal, is it has to be only civil.
In order for it to be civil, you have to have a pretty strong sworn affidavit that you hurt someone doing that.
Right.
How does the local police put someone in jail for a joint or even a kilo of powder of some sort?
Because of their ignorance.
Now, the police don't know, obviously.
They don't know either.
The Attorney General knows and the big judges know, but they're just, you know, they're so apathetic.
Well, and that begs the question that at the point of contact, they always claim you're all, at that point, in their jurisdiction.
Yeah, jurisdiction is fine.
You can give a frog jurisdiction if you're in a pond.
The point is they're not doing the process.
First of all, it's not a judicial issue.
None of it is.
No one is in prison legally or lawfully.
Not even close.
None of this stuff is really judicial.
The judicial process would be, it's very easy to look up.
You know, people get a traffic ticket and they have to go to court.
That's completely illegal.
In order to go to court, the cop has to have a probable cause and an affidavit filed into the court before he gives you a ticket.
Yeah, yeah.
And nobody discusses this.
And if you do, they kind of let go, mom.
These things are just based on ignorance.
Just like, you know, the guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper in church.
Right, right.
That's got nothing to do with Santa Claus and all that.
I mean, it's got nothing.
They say a guy nailed to a diaper?
A guy, whatever.
You get the point.
So all this stuff is just ridiculous.
That's why I never, ever, ever, ever, ever get involved in current events.
Never discuss those things.
It's just the people are so far away.
They're going to have to take 50 steps just to go to zero.
Well, you know, and you and I kind of come from the same time period.
And you remember watching the destruction of the families.
You know, mom going to work and all that stuff.
And then you got the stupid rectangle presented on the people.
Before that, it was radio.
You used to sit around and listen to the radio.
Sure.
But I want to address one thing about the destruction of the family.
Okay.
From a traditional cultural point of view, it's viewed as a negative.
But from more of a higher point of view, it is not a negative.
Because what kept those families together were traditions like Christmas, Easter, and their basic religions.
And the gods are not having that anymore.
So you want to keep your families together, abandon all that pagan crap or the demonic crap.
But people would rather not.
So their families are being destroyed by the gods, by the way.
And the women's lib.
See, before women's lib, they didn't have to work.
And a man could work at the post office and make more than enough for everyone.
Well, certainly.
So it took it away.
So that's why I bring up the thing with the same-sex marriage and the LGBTQ whatever.
This is going to be their downfall, them coming out like this.
Now, people don't see it now.
But it's like heavy artillery, right?
Yeah.
So all of these things I don't view.
I try to view.
I don't view them personally.
I don't view them.
I try to view what I've experienced from how it can be seen, not how I saw it.
Right.
Like when I spoke to Ocelli at one point, I said there's a big difference.
Recently, there's a big difference discussing what you would like to know versus discussing what can be known.
Right.
Because once you start getting into the habit of discussing what you would like to know, you go Gustave Le Bon all the way, and then you have people like yourself around you, and then it becomes incestuous, right?
I mean, you know, mentally or spiritually incestuous.
It's like all interbreeding thoughts that are low to begin with.
But how about discussing what can be known and start prioritizing?
Food, clothing, shelter.
Yeah, you don't have to talk directly about food, clothing, and shelter, but if you look at what's discussed regarding the authorities imposing things on the people in any country, people don't take any mind to it unless it does affect food, clothing, shelter.
Like shelter would be banking rates for mortgages of houses and furniture and things.
Clothing perhaps would be, you know, look at how come there are more uniforms with deadly weapons, and food would be obvious, you know, the price of food to the chemicals in the food or whatever.
But speaking of clothing, there's a less obvious point.
You know, if you want lawful clothing, which is non-mixed fiber, for women it's almost impossible to get undergarments these days, right?
And socks are another thing that are very difficult to get that are not mixed fiber.
And there's people that work with, here a little bit of an echo, people that have agreed to work in a position that wear uniform or corporate garb, they tend to be of mixed fiber as well.
So, you know, these things don't have to be, and mixed fiber doesn't mean that synthetic fiber is bad.
If it's synthetic fiber, it should be just synthetic fiber, right?
Right.
There's got to be a whole scientific premise behind all those lawful…
There is.
Yeah.
Well, the foods are pretty clear.
Very clear.
Across the board.
And vegetation is something I've never got into, but it should be with vegetables, it should be green at some point and bear fruit with seed or seed.
Right.
And seed won't come until it has a fruit around it.
You know, some even the thinnest membrane.
Right.
So, for example, mushrooms are not green.
They don't have seeds.
They don't have fruit, you know, so those are out, right?
Like spirulina is green.
They call it a superfood algae, but that doesn't bear a seed.
It goes through mitosis, so I don't eat that, right?
So the thing, just like the four-legged animal is clove and hoof, chew the cud.
Right.
It just chews the cud and it doesn't have a clove and hoof, it's out.
If it just has a clove and hoof, right, it has to do both, right, to a degree.
And it's about discernment.
That's what you won't find in any other ancient rites.
Like if you look at other things like the Koran, they don't give you discernment.
They don't, other things, you know, other ancient rites don't give you discernment.
But regarding the…
It's almost like it keeps you trained to keeping your eyes open and, like you say, always with discernment.
And there's a whole working practice of mindset in the principles.
Now, fibers tend to have an ethereal value.
Certain fibers are hollow, like cotton, and certain other natural fibers, and other fibers like silk are not hollow, right?
You have, for example, garments in certain priestly functions had to be of a certain full coverage, right?
And they give very…
These things affect the very subtle fields and energies.
But essentially, if you just want to break it down into layman's terms, and you can go around the universe seeing the positives and negatives of being lawful, but the bottom line is when you do these things, you do them to show allegiance.
Because your father told you to do that.
Right.
Like let's say you're a child and you are…
In other words, you get your law from your God.
You're invulnerable or not.
Right.
If your father says, let's say you're eight years old, if I was to be home at quarter to five and everyone else is at five, and all the children say, well, why can't you stay until five?
My dad said, I have to be in at a quarter to five.
And you're like, why?
He says, well, I don't know.
It's good enough for me.
All he has to do is say it.
Exactly.
So one way to…
Once you go around the blocks, in the beginning when you get turned on to certain information, you're like, oh, there's got to be a good scientific or plausible reason beyond just it being stated in a writ from 3,000 years ago.
And you can still explore all that, but the bottom line is it shows allegiance, right?
Right.
Yes, it's divided.
There's a lot of division, and that will not change, but you always want to be on the winning side.
Like if I said to you, you're going to play a game and there are two teams, and Team A is going to win and Team B is going to lose.
Which team do you want to join?
You'd have to be a terrible tactician to join Team B, right?
Correct.
Or other things.
And there are people that say, yes, I'll join Team B.
So it's up to you again.
One thing you'll notice in the ancient writ known as the scriptures, it's all based on free will.
If you look at what's called the lawful sections, it must be a free will offering.
You must bring it on your free will.
There's no conversion.
There's no convincing.
There's no selling of an idea.
That's one thing you'll notice in the ancient writ.
There's no racism or prejudicing.
It's if whoever comes in, let's say a foreigner, a sojourner, a stranger, a different color or race or whatever, it doesn't matter what they look like or what they did in the past.
If they are aware of what you do that is lawful and they pledge to do that, you accept them as one of your own.
You won't find that.
Like in a lot of the Western cultures that had strong Christian ethic, they had segregation and all that.
Oh, usually, yeah.
But it was only for that reason because of the color of your skin or whatever or your race, let's say.
You were bad just because of that.
In those other cultures, the visitor or whoever was always welcome.
Well, they were welcome once they agreed to understand what was lawful in your culture and they would do it.
Right.
So it doesn't matter if you went into ancient Israel as a China man or a black man or an American Indian or whatever different shade of Eastern Indian or a different shade of Asian.
There's like seven or eight different types of Asian people you could say easily.
Wherever you look like or came from, if you were aware of what was lawful in this society and you agreed to do it, you were integrated.
You were welcomed amongst them.
But when it came time to, let's say, intermarrying, they would suggest that you find one of your own so your child ends up being like you.
That was really something where they kept that bloodline.
Yes, to keep your bloodline.
And the reason why they did it more back then, believe it or not, is because intuitively they knew it was a long way to go still.
Right now it doesn't matter because you don't have a long way to go.
I mean it always matters.
But as the way things are in society, only 5% of you are going to be around in less than 14 and a half years or let's say 10% on the outside, right?
Right.
So it's quite a hit on the population.
And really when 90% of the population is wiped out, it's going to look like everyone's gone in some places, right?
Right.
So in a big city especially, right?
It'll look like you ever go to New York City on a Sunday afternoon and it's raining.
It looks empty.
Or Chicago, right?
It's like where did everybody go?
That's what it'll be like.
So these things are interesting to ponder and think about but I always like to bring it back home to something simple.
And the simplest way for anything or any subject, even quote unquote scientific or objectivity, is how can you use that information now?
The bottom line is if you do a three-hour discussion or let's say write a long paper on something, why do you have to – there should be something along the way, each chapter, each whatever.
So whoever puts the book down or stops listening at that point already has something they could use practically, right?
Right.
That's the point of I think communicating at this point.
I should say otherwise I would just go away and not say anything and part of it – I actually have done that since the last thing on AFR.
I was thinking, oh, man, I put out so much stuff, not just information but points of view and all that.
There's going to be plenty of people who are going to pick this up and run with it, right?
And it just hasn't happened.
I touched on a lot of different subjects for possible future times and a lot of them sound pretty good.
Oh, yeah.
Just scratching the surface.
Yeah, but the whole thing is, again, the two whole things is this.
Like I mentioned earlier,
I don't talk about what's going on right now in current events
or anything like that unless it actually leads to what I've discussed in the past
sort of in a subjective way, meaning how the society is going to change
because it's just such a dummy load, right, everything that's out there
and pretty much everyone that's speaking out there
is pretty much just dummy loading the public.
There might be occasionally some information that's sort of valid, but then it's like trying to eat corn out of somebody's poop.
And then there's the aspect of why aren't the most obvious things being discussed?
And then the other aspect of that is why is what people use as a reference is not within that reference itself?
Just like I say, there's no religion that knows anything in the text that they allege to subscribe to.
You see?
There's no proper use of references, I should say.
So that needs to be sort of discerned.
It's like their whole vocabulary was dumbed down right along with everything else.
Well, yeah, there's the way words are being used and then there was what they really mean, but the people are so casual and indifferent that at this point one of the major ways to get any change of mindset is to capture proper and have command over the definition of words, not just the words themselves, you know, speaking them, but the definitions.
I'll give you an example.
I recently got someone reached out with an email and he said, I looked up the etymology of the word version and it shows how it's used in different languages, but actually the meaning of it as you get to the bottom of the etymological definition means to destroy something.
So the King James Version actually destroys the scriptures.
So I found that to be a very interesting definition.
So if anyone wants to go to the etymology, Etymonline, look up the word version, V-E-R-S-I-O-N, read through the uses in various English and French cultures, and then as you get to the bottom it says means to destroy or destruction of.
And that was a really good, I'm glad that was brought forward.
So there's more to go.
And I've been saying that indirectly to some capacity, but I would say that if you, let's say a comprehender, can command the definition of the word version as being a form of destruction, you can emphasize it.
And it is.
So many times you hear when someone doesn't like what someone else is saying, you say, well that's your version.
It's a whole different spin on it.
What's your version of the truth, right?
Right.
That would be the most twisted.
That would be perfect for all the alternative or independent media.
That would be great.
That's exactly what they, no reason to harp on the morons out there in the world, but because they don't like it when you call them moronic or their listeners moronic or any researcher is a moronic, but that's why they go into the oxymoronic stage.
There's another interesting thing.
It's really difficult to also glean objectivity from, quote, unquote, researchers.
You've got researchers doing all kinds of stuff out there on mainstream and alternative, and when you read their stuff, it's quite far from being objective, you know, in most cases.
So that's another pitiful thing to look at.
But it's actually all quite simple once you start.
In other words, you don't have to do a lot of work in a particular field or direction to discover what can be objectified just by having command of the definition of words.
We had a question when we were talking about the Title 20, what was it, Title 21?
Yeah, not near the notes.
Do you want me to look through some notes and pull that up?
Yeah, yeah, please.
Okay.
Yeah, that's a goodie, because how many people are wrongfully imprisoned?
Well, ultimately, if you make a point of this, the prosecutor, attorney general, judge says, well, they agreed to it.
Right, and there's entrapment, yes.
Yeah, and they all do that, yeah.
Well, you know, they're part of the justice religion, and also they represent the adversary boots on the ground.
Right, right.
Just like, for example, the Pope represents ball boots on the ground, right, and various other.
All of the majority of the religious figures represent some form of ball, you know, lord.
And they tell you, they tell you, we represent or worship the lord.
They tell you.
Here we go.
It's 18 U.S.C. 4201 is repealed, public law, it's public law 98-473, Title 2.
So it's public law 98-473, Title 2, subsection 218A5, which is October 12, 1984, 98stat.2027. And if it sounds like they're hiding it, yes.
And it's actually, you will find this on the U.S. Government Publishing Office, and it says in their motto, Keeping America Informed.
And they passed this in 1984 to take effect in three years, so anyone that's gone to prison for criminal violation on anything narcotics, which is Title 21, is illegal and unlawful, and it's against public law.
I'll drop this into the...
The notes that we're going to create for your...
Yeah, maybe later.
Because if you scroll down, it says everything that's been affected is Title 21, and I just clicked Title 21, and when you go down...
Now, this is not as clear as it might seem.
You're going to have to do some researching, because remember, what...
Could you imagine figuring out how this works?
Right.
Could you imagine the kind of reparations they're going to have to pay to all the millions of people that are in jail for, you know, 100 tons of cocaine or a joint and everything in between?
Yeah.
Yeah, they're not going to take that too well.
No, they'd rather blow themselves...
They'd rather blow the country up before doing this, you know.
Yeah.
It's funny, it says on the top, U.S. Government Publishing, or Keeping America Informed, and yes, they are.
Oh, yes, they are.
And if you scroll down to Chapter...
If you go down to Title 21, it's got all the sections, Chapter 1 all the way to Chapter 24.
It's got all of that.
All the way down to International Narcotics and Trafficking has been repealed.
Biomaterial...
Actually, I enabled...
I clicked on 21 before I put in the link.
You scroll down, and all of Title 21 has been repealed as being criminal, because 18 U.S.C. is sentencing, basically.
Right.
Yeah, which is, you know, what...
So anyway, go ahead and wrap your head around...
There's a guy named Rod Class who made a point.
He hasn't really made much of a point.
He's another good guy to look up.
I said another good...
But Rod Class, he's a...
You know, I wouldn't say take it with a grain of salt, but you have to sift through a lot of his stuff to get the good stuff also.
But lately, a couple of years ago, he did put out some good things.
But no one else is really discussing it.
There's a few other people.
A guy up in Washington discussed this for a while.
There's a story I could tell you where...
This is before all the medical marijuana and all that.
This was more than 15 years ago.
Someone was growing 100 plants, and they came and busted the house and took all the plants and all that.
He was like, you can't do that according to law, you know, using this statute and other things, right?
They ignored him.
But finally, he pushed back, and they said, yeah, you can.
And he's growing them for medicinal purposes.
But he gets a traffic ticket or something later on, and he goes back into court, same judge, and he starts rolling a joint in the courtroom.
And the judge is like, what are you doing?
And he says, I'm going to take my medicine.
This was in Washington State about a decade and a half ago.
And the judge says, you can't do that here.
Go smoke that in the bathroom.
So he does it.
He goes to the bathroom, and he's smoking the joint in the bathroom.
And in walks just the bailiff.
He can use the bathroom.
And he says, what are you doing?
And before he answers, he throws the guy in handcuffs, brings him into the courtroom.
And he says, this guy is smoking a joint in the bathroom in a courthouse.
And the judge says, yeah, because I told him to.
So, I mean, this is like a skit out of – this is true, by the way.
Yeah, or Cheech and Chong or something.
But I'm telling you, if you understand how these things work, and you push it a little bit.
But nowadays, the people are so savage, you know, from the people little grandma.
I could prove to you any little grandma generally is savage.
All the way to the attorneys, to the doctors, to the judges, to all the lawyers, your parents, whatever, they're operating on a savage level.
In other words, they have ingrained in their minds that it is illegal and awful.
You'll go to jail.
And when they beat you up for trying to push the issue that it's not, the people that you know will not sympathize, back you up, because they already have decided that it's illegal in their own minds, right?
And I get into that with the old people.
Why do they throw them in nursing homes with diapers, bad food, and they die in a pool of shit, basically, with drugs?
It's because if you look at the American family and the Western family, it's grandma that wants to get everybody together for Christmas, right?
And if you don't travel across the country, you're bad.
She guilt trips you, right?
Because guess who's the pillar of this stuff?
So, this is really harsh.
This goes against what people think is – that's why when you look at Scripture, it says what you think is good is really evil.
So, that's why they're being thrown into nursing homes and treated the way they are.
It's not because of bad on the children being neglectful.
No, it's because of the sign of the times.
The gods are not having it anymore.
Destroy that family.
Yeah, and they're doing it because the family, if they don't – there's enough information for the family to realize that what they're doing is downright satanic or ball worship.
I mean, that's not a secret.
It never really was.
All they have to do is ask, like, three questions in five minutes, and then now they're on the path to figure it out.
But because they're not doing it, now these events have to slow down and stop.
Well, what you do is destroy the family because if you destroy the family, these events start to become less frequent.
But they haven't yet because they still do Black Friday and all that and all the people line up at Walmart and all that.
But that will still prevail to a certain degree.
But go after the family first is what the gods are doing.
We're talking about the benevolent gods now.
That's why if you look at Scripture, especially I don't like to recommend the Book of Revelation, but all that destruction on man's society, not the earth, on man's society, because remember the earth is going to be helping it out, is done by the good guys, not the bad guys.
The bad guys don't do that kind of stuff because they want you to keep doing what you're doing.
You see?
So anyway, yeah, it's an interesting thing.
A whole different look on it.
Well, it is.
I don't know any other way to do it.
There is none.
There really is none.
Yeah.
Oh, actually there are, but they're just not objective.
Right, right.
I believe last night's conversation on if you were put in charge.
We'll leave that alone.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it's very easy to fix any country.
I think you could fix any country and bring it almost to a perfect society within a month.
Yeah.
If it's a rural society, it might take six months because you can't really get to everyone as quickly.
Yeah, but we'll get into that in a few.
It's a little harsh for people.
It is.
But to put it this way, a lot of Disclaimer and warning on that.
Yeah, 10% to 30% of the population will not survive it.
But at least it'll be overt.
It won't be covert like it is now because right now you're losing 10% to 20% of the population every 10 years anyway through that negligence system, right?
Yeah, yeah.
A million from the doctors and another quarter of a million or so from the other.
Yeah, so just in America alone.
So what they call the states.
Yeah, it's pretty harsh.
But right now you're at a time where you're in the credits.
The gods are going to do it.
Yep.
Which is going to be something to behold.
Worse than what you would have done.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, much worse.
Actually, no, I think they're going to be better at it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Technically.
Yeah, what I've suggested, by the way, to clean up society is not for this society.
It wouldn't go over very well.
No.
But it will be the norm for the next society, by the way, of mankind.
So, yeah.
You won't have doctors and lawyers and things like that in the next society.
And you won't have these entitled classes.
And you will have certain entitlements, certain people of authority, but they're going to be working for the benevolent side of mankind.
So they'll be representing the benevolent, not the malevolent.
Right now all of you are entitled.
You're professors, you're priests, you're rabbis, you're doctors, you're lawyers.
You're psychiatrists.
All these people that are viewed as high.
They all are representing the adversary at this point.
They don't know it, which sometimes might make it worse, right?
Because that means there's no way they can control it or have a feeling or a sense of what they're doing to change it.
They think it's okay.
Now, of course, the ones that do know it might be a little worse.
Actually, they're going to be held to a much higher standard.
Yeah.
But at least the ones that do know it can be confronted on it and there could be a rational exchange dialogue.
But if you go to a priest and say, well, you're really working for the devil, let's say, and using those simple terms.
Or an attorney, you know you're working for Satan, right?
And he's like, no, I don't see it.
But if you go to a high-up attorney, like an old guy, he knows that.
Like a high-up, if you go to the Vatican, you know that they have allegiance to certain ancient deities.
That's why when you hear a lot of the child molestation, what they're doing is they're emulating the bishops.
The bishops have allegiance to an ancient deity, which the way you evoke this entity is by inflicting pain on a child through sexual means.
Wow.
Yeah.
And this has gotten around.
It's not because they're horny because they can't marry to whatever celibacy.
It's because they're being inspired and influenced by this.
This is the norm in what they call the Catholic religion.
And, of course, they have a lot of followers and all that.
And it's also the norm in many other older sort of sequestered places, like in Afghanistan.
It's very normal to have little boys raped in rural places of Afghanistan.
People don't know this.
And if you ask, why is this being done, it's because of a particular religious right.
But it's gotten to the point where they don't know.
They can't give you specifics.
And Saudi Arabia.
Yeah.
Saudis are an interesting mix.
And the camel thing, you know.
Well, that's what you mean, like bestiality?
Or eating?
No, the jockeys.
Usually they're a very exploited group.
Okay.
Give us a little more.
You want to present that?
I've just said they are first picked, let's say, for sexual exploitation.
The jockey or the camel?
The jockey.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I haven't heard anything about the camel.
I'll keep you apprised, though.
Yeah, that's one entity.
Another lord is insisting allegiance and evocation by people cutting on themselves.
And you'll notice that in the Book of Kings.
That's weird.
Yeah, that's why if you see some people from the continent of Africa, they immigrate here.
In some places in the Caribbean, you'll see very fine cuts on their cheeks in geometric patterns, like a keloid scar in a geometric pattern.
And the genital mutilation and all that other stuff.
Sure, that's all inspired.
A lot of what they call homosexuality is also part of the religion.
And the way that it inspires people is through the way you're inspired, through a dream.
So people can be inspired.
Inspired means to be affected by the gods while they're awake.
These social, cultural things that you see coming around are not, by happenstance or random or Gustave Le Bon crowd mentality.
And even if you get into the book with Gustave Le Bon, he discusses it.
And Gustave Le Bon was censored also, but he did a bang-up job on most of that book.
And I'm not recommending the book.
I'm just saying it's a place to go see something more objectively or clearly on the matter.
But he even suggests…
Yeah, but he'll bring up the point also several times, or at least one time I remember, that there is a supernatural element that brings crowds together that can't be explained.
He was not aware because he has that Christian-Judeo ethic.
That kind of hampered him in his writings.
Someone put in chat, scripture, numerology, and how to approach as a novice.
There's numerics.
There's many levels of numerology and numerics and what they might call gematria.
But that is more like looking at fingerprints to prove that there's a complex system.
There's another level of it where you look at numbers and numerology like that to understand a communication because numbers are the most rational way to communicate something.
So like seven has always been viewed as something fortunate or they say lucky.
It's also the number of the divine.
I think I've gone through the number four and one and seven and how to break up seven.
Six is the number of man.
Five comes before man, man system, or what man has been into.
So that's pretty much a simple thing.
There are numbers that keep adding up and presenting rational communication.
But as a novice, the only suggestion I would make there is understand when you see the number seven, the number four is the first position.
It's considered four as the head of it.
Imagine the number four in the center, three on the left, three on the right, and that's the number seven.
And the first one is last and the last is first.
So the seventh one and the first one are interchangeable.
And this is from a cardinal point of view, not an ordinal point of view.
Where ordinal would be I have seven items, here's one item, here's a second item, here's a third item.
That doesn't mean that's ordinal, meaning ordinary or whatever way of counting.
But cardinal is we say this is the first one, this is the second one that I've got, this is the third one, this is the fourth.
That's more cardinal where they come in sequence.
So you can view the number seven in both ways where the fourth position is first, whether it's ordinal or cardinal, whether it was the fourth one in sequence or whether it's the fourth one that was given to you which could have been, let's say, the first one.
And what happens very often when you look at ordinal sequences of seven, the fourth item that was presented is the one that gets prominence.
And later on you'll find that got that prominence because it really was the first one in position in time or it just later on adds up to be that way.
So there's no real novice way to look at it.
The novice thing is just be conscious of seven and three because three comes right before four, right?
And then be conscious of five, six, and seven.
All right?
But really, yeah, there's ordinal.
A lot of things in scripture you have to think of as being ordinal or cardinal.
A simple way to do that is ordinal will be I've got six eggs in a basket.
Actually, eggs are not eggs.
Let's say things we get through time.
Let's say cars.
I've got three cars outside.
An ordinal way to describe the cars would be, hey, here's a car, here's a second car, and here's a third car.
A cardinal way would be this is the first car I got, all right, and this is the second car I acquired, and this is the third car I acquired.
So that's cardinal.
You have the first car, second car, third car versus a car.
Here's a second car and here's a third car.
The first car in the ordinal could have been the third one that I've got.
You see there's no sequence here being shown.
You'll have to sort that out.
In the King James, you don't get that, by the way.
In your English versions, you don't get a difference between cardinal and sequential ordinal.
I don't know.
Did I preface that okay?
I think you did.
I think you did well.
Even the last time when we were talking about it, it took a bit.
You did well.
All right.
Keeping that attitude going through things.
The whole thing on numerology to begin with, that's a whole different world, but it has the potential for opening things.
It does.
But numerology itself and the gematria and all that transcends the ordinal and cardinal usually.
Yeah, and there's got to be a lot more at play still to be discovered.
Sure, sure, sure.
But I'd like to maybe bring things up to speed as time goes on.
Stuff that has been bouncing around in the head for the past decade that I haven't brought up at all would be interesting to see what else people can do with it.
But it's not a TV sitcom.
Believe it or not, most of the stuff I've been doing over the years to address the TV sitcom mentality is where you have it all neatly wrapped up in 30 minutes or an hour and the world is saved in the end, right?
You don't want to do that.
You can't.
Most things are not like that.
There is going to be a level of introduction to the introduction to the introduction, and then you get to the meat of the matter, and then you have to show how it all ties together.
So essentially, I would say to anyone, I get a lot of commentary and communications privately in e-mails and even comments about newcomers to scripture.
And for the people that are new to it and they have zeal, meaning they want to put extra time and make more of an effort than normal to learn it or see what's in there, keep in mind there are biblical scholars going back even 1,000 years or 2,000 years that have devoted their entire lives, entire lives.
I've met some of them recently, some 70- or 80-year-old heads that started studying scripture at 12, and they went to all the universities and taught at university, Bible colleges, theology, and all that, and they couldn't grasp the communication.
They memorized it and could tell you where things were, but they couldn't string it all together.
It was just like having a box of beads and not a necklace, you know?
They didn't know how to string this thing, this whole communication together.
So whether you're new or old at it, and that's why when I see people that are new at it, I'm like, how do you just tell them, just try to get what's being communicated out of it communicated to you.
Are you getting the communication, right?
And the answer to that is no when you look at most historical aspects of it.
You can go on the stupid rectangle, and there's websites I haven't done any
searches on, but I'm sure it hasn't changed in over a decade,
on any subject scriptural, and there might be a little nugget in there,
or something that's true, and then they spin off into some crazy
churchianity or crazy Christianity or Judaism and stuff that's not in
scripture, and they try to, you know, read into it, right?
But again, remember when you were talking last night, and you mentioned that about one of the guys, one of the priests, or people who studied scripture all their life, and they gave you a little nugget, and it was like, you know, you guys have been going at this for 25 years or 30 years, and this guy just gave it away for free.
Oh, yeah, exactly.
Like I'd bring up, I'd run into, I figured, you know, if I want to learn about scripture, go to people that say they're learned in it.
And I realized from the little that I had studied, what they were saying was not in there.
It was religious stuff.
And when I would bring up how things were not, what they were believing or saying was, you know, part of the doctrine, it was not in scripture, they got rubbed the wrong way.
But occasionally they would bring up, when I would bear them enough, and I figured I'd have to disconnect from that.
I would ask a question, and they'd say, hey, listen, this is not really known, but check it out.
They'd ask me the question.
I said, no, I don't know the answer to that, but look right here.
And they'd point to it, and I said, wow, I read that, and I didn't see that.
And they're like, wow, thanks for pointing that out and how that connects to the other side.
But they just had one little nugget like that.
Yeah.
If you brought up timekeeping or there is no crucifixion or, you know, what's going on, they said, no, no, no, we don't want to get into that.
We've heard of something like that, but we don't want to get into that because that divides people and all that.
And I'm like, what?
Okay, I'm out of here, you know.
But at least I thanked them.
In the beginning I said, oh, he's a dirty-ass pagan, you know, and walk away.
But after a while I was like, you know, this guy spent his whole life studying this to discover this nugget, and he just gave it to me, right?
And I'm like, I've got to thank him for it and walk away.
Exactly.
Just because he thinks church is a good thing or whatever, and Christmas, you know, I'm not going to mock him for it, I mean, even though he deserves it.
And that shouldn't be done either.
No, it shouldn't.
As you mature in this, you'll see that what that is is getting – that's why I came up with the analogy of eating undigested corn out of somebody's poop.
That's tasteless.
But, you know, if you find a gold nugget in someone's poop, you could actually wash it off and make it clean.
So these were actual real nuggets I was getting from certain people here and there.
And then I walked away, and I realized this is not really that good because these people have dedicated their lives to this, and I haven't gotten much.
So guess what?
If I want to get more, I have to do it on my own.
And my point was always don't get wrapped around the axle, as they say, on what everyone else and everything else that you've heard about it.
When you go into subject matter, try to view it with clear eyes, as if you're seeing it for the first time objectively, and then comprehend that it also can connect to another part of the Scripture, right?
Metaphorically, to show you that there's a repeat of an event or an influence.
And always bear that in mind.
It's called harmonization.
And just to go back to those that study Scripture, I've read Usher and Newton's work and these great minds, whatever, and they were censored.
They didn't know.
And so why am I so encouraged to speak on this now?
Because the time that these men are considered greats in this field, even the 70- or 80-year-old heads that I met, it was not time yet.
One of the promises of being in this time is that everything will be opened up.
So you can see it.
It's right in front of you.
Do you remember a film called It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World?
Yeah.
With the treasure.
And they had to find the big W, and they couldn't find the W, and one guy's leaning against the location of the treasure was the W, and they're all looking on the ground, buildings.
Finally, a bunch of people are leaning against a car, and they're tired, and they see some palm trees in the distance and W, remember that?
Yeah.
And they're like, there's the W.
And they're like, wow, was that easy, huh?
It was just sticking out of the ground in front of everyone all the time.
Right?
Something like that.
I think I caught it right there.
That's a spoiler.
The communication of Scripture is very simple.
I always used to pride myself I can explain Scripture in 30 seconds or 100 words or less or 50 words or less, all of it, even though people are just trying to say it can't be comprehended.
You've got to be mocking the gods.
You mean if the gods are all-knowing, and especially the Most High, and they give you a communication that everyone thinks cannot be communicated or comprehended, wouldn't you say that's an act of futility?
Right.
Right?
They don't act in futility.
So once you understand their timing and all that, but generally even in 10 seconds to describe Scripture, you have an unseen intangible society that has a leader, and that leader is making a personal family of new beings.
And right now we are not in that society.
We're in a little tank known as materialism.
And we're getting the harshest treatment in order to go to the next level.
It's very simple.
And the rest, that's all it is.
It's like a video game.
You're on stage one for people to use that.
Or if you're reading a novel or something, it's the beginning of the adventure.
Right?
Right.
And it was interesting that because we are in matter manifested, that was one of the big battles and divided a whole bunch.
Yeah.
Essentially what you'll get out of it is it's a race to make the most out of us being so limited and showing that us being limited through material, that we'll never pursue and grasp the higher things that are immaterial, but at the same time we're supposed to grasp the best of what we have in material.
Being able to create spirits on that side is one thing, but making a spirit that is only animated through material was very objectionable.
That's how we are.
Almost like the prosecutor, you know?
Showing his defense and here's the example.
Perhaps.
Yeah.
Kind of an interesting flow in a lot of the reading.
Okay, I'm back.
I just had to plug something in.
How are we doing on time?
Let's see.
We are currently at 2 hours, 8 minutes, 58 seconds.
Why don't we just call it a whatever for now?
This is just a beta test.
Maybe we'll do one more and we'll start scheduling.
Nicely done, by the way.
Okay, good.
Nicely done.
Yeah, nothing planned, just throwing stuff out, seeing the audio and all that.
Let's see how it comes out on archive.
You could also edit it.
Correct.
I'm going to probably break this down into two separate hours, fade in and out with the Bach music when we come back to chat and all that.
Okay.
It's just a beta.
We'll nice it out and this will be the test 2 of the beta.
Okay, yeah, the test 2, I mean test 2.
Yeah, test 2 or the part 2 with the archive.
Yeah, we'll see how it works.
Yeah.
Okay, thanks, sir.
We'll get those links in your folder and get that set up tonight and look forward to many new treats as always.
Same here, and I'll redo the Uncommon Radio site to reflect that there's some events coming.
Yeah, maybe there's a simulcasting we can do.
There's all sorts of tricks of the trade, I guess, as they say.
Yep, and I think I'm going to be also experimenting with electronic credit transfers.
I think we discussed it and I might do a discussion on that.
That's right.
I might actually do, believe it or not, a PayPal, only because I discovered that a way to do it lawfully, even though they don't provide a way to do it lawfully.
So I think it's going to be quite an interesting thing, because one of the things about you're never going to get lawful money, but Title 12, Section 411 just shows that you have to have evidence that you're demanding it.
Right.
Right?
I think I've come around and figured a way to do it, and it might be a way for anyone who wants to contribute to the cause and show some gratitude that can be done that way.
I have pretty much everything that I need.
In other words, if I needed shelter, a cardboard box would do fine, right?
You just said you need shelter.
But the thing is, if anyone wants to contribute or do exchange or whatever or show appreciation, it can be done.
If I was on the other end, one thing I'd like to say is, not regretfully, but not at all really, because I see it as a sense of accomplishment, but when I started a decade and a half ago, almost full-time researching things all the way from worldview down to whatever, I had no one laying stuff out to me objectively at all.
It was very, very difficult to find.
There's a lot of self-help gurus and reference manuals and history to look up, and you get lost in the sauce, and I found the whole thing was mindset.
You've just got to keep asking yourself the same questions.
What is it based on?
Is this a bunch or is this a version?
What is the reference to this?
Are they saying what they mean and mean what they say?
What do words mean?
How to keep time?
All these things I had pretty much on my own, so if I had discovered someone like myself 15 years ago, I would want to give them back something for gratitude to say, hey, thanks for laying this stuff out.
So there's an interesting aspect to it.
Yeah.
And you feel good doing it, you know?
Bottom line, the person who gives should be out of the heart and with no questions asked, period.
Okay, yeah.
Because you do.
I do, but I should just be doing this, communicating,
because really humanity is in bad shape,
but not communicate it because it will make humanity better,
but because there's some heads out there,
that's an old ghetto term for people,
I think they use it in the navies also,
that are ready for it and really would like something that's simple
and almost oversimplified and yet enriching, and to continue it.
Because really I'm not going to be, I think for the rest of the life that I have left over a century now, it wouldn't make sense for me to start going down other roads of an industry and things that I've done in the past.
I think it's best to retire from making things and doing things and consulting captains of industry, because it gets you, it wears you out after a while, because remember I've wholeheartedly…
It's a burnout, I think, you know?
Well, I've also wholeheartedly told you, I've been around high-level leadership in the world and captains of industry, and they are just as moronic as anyone would be classified as a moron, and I'm realizing…
Surprisingly.
Yeah, more and more so, that you are not in control, people.
The gods are full on in control.
But in essence, at this point, to be able to maybe just speak to people and get information out is probably what the Greek's purpose is left.
Because, you know, why go consult a billionaire for a petrochemical company that is totally blind to anything, that he just knows that if he does what you say, it'll work out better than he thought?
He's drank too great.
Why do that when you can just do something like this that just gets put out, and you don't know who's going to hear it, and it really might affect someone's life, so their lives are better, or more…
They don't have to wonder why things are the way they are.
And they've done it on their own.
And they do it on their own, and not on a social level, because that ain't going to happen, but it is going to happen when the setup gets in.
You are going to have a perfect society, and I discussed that.
Right?
So, but at least, you know, we'll see how this…
Yeah, and maybe mulling over stuff, getting deeper into subjects, and communicating.
And there'll be, again, I'll try to figure out an electronic conveyance, because I think people do like to show appreciation, and I like to receive it.
Yes, they do.
And who knows?
And here's the thing.
If it does grow, let's say, through a credit-worthy financial way, then that could be invested in and have more infrastructure put together.
Who knows?
But never to make the society or world a better place, but to perhaps multiply, a multiplying factor.
Because, you know, I would say, we joke around, you know, but I would say .00001% of the population might be ready for this kind of information, and that leaves several million, that's several million people.
That's a lot of people.
Yeah.
And instead of going to bed and figuratively saying, you know, there are still people being plagued by dreams.
I mean, that is totally unnecessary, or hauntings.
Now, hauntings can get a little more devastating, but, you know, they don't understand the spiritual influence on humanity, and all you have to do is acknowledge it, and these things are remedied.
Yeah.
Very interesting.
We'll get into quite a few things, and we'll see how it pans out.
Yes, yes.
Well, as always, Greg, a pleasure of talking to you, and a pleasure with all mine.
Okay, that's right.
Thank you.
Yeah, it was a pleasure on this end also.
And I wasn't even touching myself, and that was for the most obvious comment I like to throw in every time.
All right, folks, we'll see you again.
Yeah, have a good night, Greg.
Thanks, you too.
Bye-bye.