Greetings folks, we're live with the Greek.
How are you doing tonight, Greek?
Greetings, okay, fair to Midland, almost the same as I was last week.
Yeah, cool.
There doesn't look like there's much going on other than an email that I got about seaweed.
And that's a tricky one because when seaweed is harvested, you know, as food, lots of crustaceans, barnacles, seahorses, things like that stick to it, so those are unclean animals.
So the quality of the preparation, and then of course, is it a fungus?
No, it's not a fungus.
Is it a plant?
Yes it is, an aquatic plant.
And does it bear seed?
Typically the kelp varieties do.
So you're going to have to do your own research on, you know, particular seaweeds in that respect.
But there are some that obviously don't have seeds and some that are not so obvious that they do.
If you've ever swung kelp around, you'll notice there are little seeds that pop out that look like cherry pits, you know, or smaller.
So that's the answer on that.
It's basically harvest, you know, are you eating, you know, certain hamburger places say 100% beef?
Well, you know, in Spain, if you order a hamburger, it's 100% horse meat, unless you specifically order a beef one.
If anyone in Spain wants to validate that, please do.
So, you know, they would mix it with other animals, just like the original hot dogs were pork, or no, were beef and lamb.
The original hot dogs, yeah, there were beef and lamb and then they went to beef.
So, you know, is it 100% seaweed, you know?
I guess the question brings up unclean things.
You know, it was interesting, I was doing a little bit of research on clean and unclean.
You could go look up the words in Greek are very different.
They interchange several things.
But essentially, the essence is, you know, the intent of translating it to unclean is fairly accurate, which is not unclean, as your normal idiot uses it, it's just spiritually unclean, right?
And it's spiritually unclean depending on which deity you profess to have allegiance to and laws to follow.
Right.
Right, because there are certain deities that demand children to be eaten, so you see what I mean?
But anyway, the interesting part is there are verses that you'll find, like, in what they call the New Testament, I believe there is, you know, and there'll be no unclean thing on the earth and unclean spirits and, you know, if you examine what that really means, meaning it's things that fall out of the lawful ways, basically.
Permissible or not permissible, in Arabic it would be haram and halal.
You know, halal is permissible and haram is impermissible.
Right.
Not necessarily to you, but to the way the order created by the most high deity.
So, you know, these things need to be explained in terms of what they are when there's interest.
And like I said, I think, last week, the only thing left to do, and I've been watching now for about a decade,
actually I've been speaking publicly since what they call 2003, 2004, on the pagan work schedule, so it's more than a decade,
and I've noticed that initially people get interest because it's different, and then you become a moron magnet,
you know, you attract people that are morons, which is not difficult to, it's difficult to work as planet earth,
I mean, generally most humans are morons, and then it just becomes like, oh yeah, this is way too out there, you know.
So, in essence, the only thing left to do because of that established condition with anything is to warn people,
but not the boy who cried wolf, and not the dyke is going to burst, but just basically people are not interested in learning,
the general group, and they're not even interested in hearing or seeing,
but the warnings should come in a way that they can also handle it, otherwise if they can't handle it,
then it's not really, you know, the communication hasn't been established, that's why you have international symbols, right?
Right.
It transcends language and things like that.
So that's, I think, the communication technology from, you know, it's been for a while and for the future, is how do you give these idiots the warning?
Now remember, the warning is two-fold.
One is that that's all that you can basically communicate to these idiots because they can't comprehend anything else beyond that because they're so stuck and censored, but on the other hand, it also makes it easier for the spiritual side because now their guilt is on them, you see?
Right.
So you have to comprehend the guilt, right?
You ever see someone being executed, hung, or they read the charges again, and they understand, you know, in a court, they ask you, do you understand?
And you say, yes.
Well, okay, well, that's it, you know?
That's that, yeah.
So the technology, the communication technology, is how do you give the warning message to these morons?
You know, the 7 billion plus, whatever.
By the way, in terms of human population, just to bounce around a little bit.
Sure.
If you add up, you know how they say there's 7.5 billion people on the planet?
I was having a discussion with someone about a year ago.
They're a number, they're a bean counter.
I mean, you could, they have a mathematical mind.
You could say, like, what's 462 divided by 56?
They'll give you the answer to two decimal places almost instantly.
By the time you even reach a calculator, they've got it, right?
Right.
And there's simple techniques on how to do that, right?
Mm-hmm.
But anyway, what they did was they did some research, every country in the world, and they added up the given population.
It was way short, even than 7 billion.
So it seems to be almost three-quarter of a billion or a billion people missing from that 7.5 billion statistic.
In other words, the aggregate doesn't make up the whole.
Right.
You see?
So anyway, when I say 7 billion or 7, that's suspect.
I'm seeing the population on the surface right now.
We don't know much about those below the surface.
Mm-hmm.
So, yeah, that's pretty much the message that I have to give.
And also, by the way, it's what they call the pagan new year, I believe.
Yes.
And I believe that if you've got more than two brain cells together or one in the mirror, so it looks you think you have two, you've noticed all the idiots in the past couple of weeks, what they get caught up in, and not only of the Judeo-Christian ethic, but other religions as well.
Mm-hmm.
So let that be your warning on how to structure the way you communicate with these morons.
Because remember, a small percentage, given maybe single or I'd say double-digit percentage, are dangerous as well.
So beware.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I don't see – I haven't really been in chat much.
I haven't been looking at the chat.
Not that I ever expected anything.
I think the chat is more of a courtesy.
I think there's more people than meets the eye on the chat.
Because I remember when we moved over to this chat, I got over 70 or 80 emails.
But there seems to be always the same three or four people.
So I think people just come to see what else is new.
They prefer to be silent, which is good.
And Jeremiah says, in times of evil, the wise will be silent.
But I don't think the chat serves anything.
So I don't really spend time – You're just typing in and saying hi or looking to see if anything's new.
But other than that, yeah.
Yeah, but in terms of the chat, it's better to get hi than to say hi.
But anyway, I would say, yeah, there's not much just going on with Greek-speak.
I think I've done my job, I should say.
Or job, in this case.
So I know that Sam, who was on last week, has the – If you haven't figured it out, he's got a little Greek-speak project, right?
Right, yes.
And he might be doing a podcast or something.
So I might be doing that.
But otherwise, I don't really see continuing in any public way, even though this is a very small venue.
I don't think there's – I mean, believe it or not, this is probably the first time in several thousand years that everything and everything under the sun could have been discussed and brought to mind.
No one else – pat my own back – no one else in history has ever done that from a secular or spiritual perspective outside of scripture or anything extraordinary.
I'm not saying I'm extraordinary.
I'm saying what's been brought up is truly extraordinary.
So I think just going back to not necessarily visiting sonics like we do on a – it doesn't take much to do it, you know, to come around and do it.
But I don't think there's any need for it.
I don't need to hear myself.
And I don't think people need to hear anymore.
There's not much going on.
No one's coming forward to move it in a productive way other than Sam and yourself.
And even then, it's just minuscule.
I mean, some people in the past have heard me say, oh, this is going to be really great.
It will go worldwide.
No, it's not.
Not in this world.
In another world, maybe.
So I'm pretty happy with, you know, accomplished – I could say myself as a vessel of put forward more than anyone else has in the history – known history in terms of every subject known to man brought up, not in depth because it can be.
Researching it together is good.
We've covered everything above the earth, below the earth, on the earth, the human body, the mind, everything.
And I don't think it's either the right time to move forward with anything substantial or it's probably not going to be done public just like anything else.
But I think I can retire from these sonic events, and you could free up what you call your Tuesdays and all that as well.
And I think this might be just a farewell message to the chat and the sonics and all that.
The e-mail will still be up.
I don't have any plans on doing anything on the website, so there's no reason to go to it unless you don't know how to – you know, you forgot the e-mail.
So pretty much I just – yeah.
So, yeah, I think we'll just go on, take each heartbeat, each breath on this wretched planet right now.
It is wretched, by the way.
It's beautiful, but what's been, you know, habitating is horrid and make the best of it, right?
Correct, yeah.
So I don't see any purpose to continue on sonics or development.
And like I said, you know, Sam might be doing some podcasts or whatever.
I said I'd jump on that.
Sure.
And it'll probably be more structured than anything done before.
He'll – you know, Sam will sit back and ponder subjects and all that, and we'll go over it, and there'll be an hour or 55 minutes.
But I don't think there's much – this is the wrong planet for this.
They're in the wrong time, so let's not be foolish.
Which is a shame, yes.
Hmm.
What's been shameful from the beginning?
Look at Adam and Eve.
Yeah, yeah.
They screwed up big time.
Now, the people before, I think they were caught in a dynamic that they really had very little control over.
But we measure time from Adam and Eve in that group.
Right.
So it's still a pathetic situation.
But in essence, I would say there's not much to – I mean, there's tremendous things to discuss.
Like lately I've been doing a lot of experiments, both thought and practical experiments with sound, electrodynamics, magnetism, food stuff, biological stuff.
And there's no – I mean, I just look at what the response – not that I – you know, what was me or anything.
It's just that there is – first of all, the response is not there, and I don't think it will be even if it was – more in-depth information was put out.
And secondly, if you put out too much information with proof, so you'll have a knock at the door in the middle of the night and they'll drag you out, literally.
At this point, the stuff that I'm working on is to that point where you don't want to be public.
You know, about health stuff or energy stuff or anything.
I mean, it'll be dangerous if you – in other words, I could bring stuff in passing about health and things, but actually to sit down and do a three- or four-hour on how to build things and make things and apply them, that'll get you in trouble.
Yeah, we don't need that.
We don't need that.
Yeah, so I think, you know, it's too bad the conditions are the way they are, but, you know, again, like recently I had a discussion with someone about all the misery and how people still ask, well, you know, God is an asshole because look at all the misery and suffering.
They don't even know what they're talking about, you know, which there's never a singular God, right?
Correct.
But the thing is, what we're promised is what comes after is so great and so rich and so abundant that all this stuff that people question and are involved in, including myself, you know, just looking at how idiotic everything is, will be compensated for, you know.
It's like tripping on a sidewalk and breaking a toenail and you're given $100 billion for compensation.
Correct.
And it's not that you need the $100 billion, but that much extra, you see.
So that's what's coming.
And in the meantime, I don't see, because I've been coming around for about a year now on the, you know,
we've been doing the Tuesday and I thank you for the effort, but I look at it and I'm like,
there's no inspiration, there's no need, there's no, I mean,
and I look at the people that I've interacted with in the past decade and it's like,
this is a pretty fucked up situation, so just, you know, keep it to yourself unless it's necessary.
Right.
Yeah.
And I don't see any need anywhere.
I think just everybody needs to live out their life day by day or however you think you want to plan it, week by week, year by year, however, and whatever delusion you enjoy, and that's it, pretty much.
And the only thing that really deserves seriousness and apologetics, meaning to defend, is the warning on humanity.
And it can be as subtle as a young parent telling them there's no need to save for college for their child in ten years, it's stupid, because there are going to be no colleges, you know, but all the way to letting people know the existence of the spiritual world.
Now the problem with that is, not to harp on anyone directly, but indirectly I could say generally, I haven't met anyone who can at this point even articulate the basics.
So again, there's no need to continue.
It's just a really bad situation.
I don't see any questions.
Let me see if I have the email open.
But it's kind of good for me as well.
I could just consciously put the idea of speaking and doing streaming and all that stuff out of my mind and be more focused on other things, even though, like I said, it doesn't take away much of the focus, but it's just an odd thing that you want to come and share and there's no venue to share.
There's no interest.
Is a room a room if there's nobody in it?
That's right.
Well, I myself have got to say I'm deeply grateful.
Oh good, so am I.
It's been quite the eye-opener and it's forced me to take some very hard looks at things and career and all that and I'll be always eternally grateful for that.
Okay, great.
I appreciate it.
But remember, it's evil.
Remember, you tell children, go to college so you can make fake money, so it's going to be a fake education at a fake job with fake science and fake medicine and fake food and fake love.
It's all fake.
It's evil.
So if you could go through a universal mindset, you scan the universe and see what's happening on earth, you would never speak a word to anyone.
You'd be like, what the fuck?
Get me out of here.
So the aspect of existing and all this other stuff is simply that, food, clothing and shelter.
You've been given a fleshy body for a reason that you'll find out later because it's the best vehicle at the moment and the condition of everything being fake and delusional and deception is so the time period passes.
Because if you overtly show people the evil behind it, they'll all check out.
They'll flip out.
You won't be able to have anything function.
So it's basically the waiting room.
You can't have people waiting in a hallway in a dentist's office or a doctor's office or whatever.
They get too fidgety.
You have to make it comfortable enough, but not so much that they forget that they're in the waiting room.
But now people are in the waiting room and they forgot that they're in the waiting room.
So it's too fucked up to address.
Okay, cool.
So just do your things, everybody.
The Uncommon site, Uncommon Radio, which is a kickass site in terms of URL.
I have no plans on putting anything up there or doing anything with it.
The only thing is just a courtesy for the email.
And that's pretty much it.
And I've been, I created a stream, web streaming, rebroadcasting old events.
Okay.
And that's been going well.
That's been going well.
Yeah, good.
Again, this is out of time, out of place stuff.
And if you feel like you're out of time and out of place, I don't just leave people hanging.
If you understand even 5% or 10% of Greek-speak, you'll see how things are just too fucked up to do anything.
So the only thing to do is food, clothing, shelter, live a basic life.
Check your desires at the door.
Heck yeah.
And be very, what do you call it, even.
Key on set apart.
What I mean even is don't get, be efficient.
Don't get caught up in all the bullshit.
Because it's been, not just now, like people think, it's always been bullshit.
And it will manifest.
Oh yeah.
So with that said, I don't think any...
Well, thank you.
Like I say, I've been very grateful for everything you've given.
Yeah, right.
And I very much appreciate it.
Well, here's the thing, not to be sarcastic or anything, but it's nothing you couldn't have figured out on your own.
You just needed a little hint.
That's all.
If you tell someone, you know, a dog took a poop in the room, well, it's not that they couldn't have figured it out on their own.
You just give them a heads up, right?
Right.
You'll smell it in a second, right?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, okay, thanks.
But after a while, then it's like, it doesn't matter who told you, it's just that now you know, right?
Right.
Yeah.
And remember, the gods are about knowledge.
They couldn't give a rat's ass about belief.
So, you know, that's the first thing you're going to find out at the resurrection, by the way.
So belief has nothing to do with it.
The only time belief comes into play is if you're given information and the way you view it as being speculative, reliable, or unreliable.
And when the gods give information, especially the most high, it's reliable.
And that's the only factor for belief.
So the rest of it is a waste of time.
Not a waste of time, just taking up the time.
I mean, can anybody be in a waiting room and say you're wasting your time?
Well, isn't the waiting room set up for that?
Right.
It's not going to be wasting your time in a waiting room.
What is a waste of time is the manifestation of the evil or the unclean or the deception for so long to us.
Yeah.
Let's see, one last question.
Will it be reunited with family and friends at resurrection?
Who the fuck would want to?
I think you're going to run the other way at that point.
There's so much money.
No, you won't.
You'll be given a choice on that, and you'll be surprised.
And that's actually, Christ is very clear about that, by the way.
He's very clear.
And no, the answer to that is no, you won't be reunited.
It's inconsequential.
There's no irrelevant.
Irrelevant.
It's like if you have puppies, are they ever going to be reunited with the bitch that bore them?
That's a proper term, by the way.
People use it as if they think it's...
Or is the egg you had for breakfast going to be reunited with the hen that laid it?
Or siblings?
No, the answer is no to that.
It doesn't mean you'll be barred or banned from it.
No, but it's irrelevant at that point.
I think if anyone who has looked at even cursory examination of what they call the New Testament, or even prior, you'll see that there's actually a dissemblance or dissimilarness of what a spiritual family is and an earthly family is.
And I'll give the example when Christ runs out of the house saying, you are my brother, you are my mother, you are my sister, to the apostles.
So...
You see?
And my first thing is, when you really find out what your friends and family are, why the hell would you want to be reunited with them?
I mean earthly ones, you know, the ones that are earthly.
And that kind of question is always posed in a secular manner.
Right?
And I'm taking it as a secular point of view.
Yeah.
70% or 80% of all homicides or murders are friends or family, and 90% of the time they take place in the kitchen or the bedroom.
You take that and figure out what I'm trying to say.
Right?
Yeah.
You talk about relationships with people.
How negative does a relationship have to be before you actually are driven to kill someone?
And why is it that more than three quarters of the time it's a friend or family close, and it's always in the kitchen or the bedroom?
90% of the time.
You think the old Ford motor light would have came on and said, time to leave.
Right.
So why the hell would you want to reconnect back to them later to do it all over again?
Anyway, yeah.
Okay.
Study people, and it's not what you think.
That's what I always tell you.
But how can you understand it's not what you think when you don't even know what it is, or you don't even see it?
Yeah.
Right.
You can't even see it.
All right.
And if there's ever a need for a sonic event, but don't rehash stuff and loose general stuff.
If there's anything specific or a project anyone wants to do, I'm up for it.
And, by the way, I've been asked to do, I've turned down, more like indirectly, like, oh, I'm doing interviews and stuff.
I think the Ocelli and the Greek was good.
I think 90% of the people on the chat are from Freeman, which Freeman doesn't fly, and Ocelli has no effect, by the way.
So doing that kind of, consider that filler and just getting out there.
Yeah.
And that's why I did it, by the way.
I mean, neither Ocelli nor Freeman, after I said the, I lost them.
Maybe Ocelli got a little bit because he still uses a little bit of the time.
He got the time part a little bit.
But he doesn't understand how significant it is.
But, yeah, I mean, I look at people that want to do an interview or a show, and I'm like, I'm going to lose them and their audience after I say the word the.
And that's like, do I really want to keep, you know, like, for what?
You know, I'm not a public-type person.
There's a room in the room and nobody's in it.
Yeah, so it's like, oh, shit.
So, yeah, it's just like a light bulb.
Yeah.
Okay.
All very well understood.
Very well.
Hoorah.
Okay, so that's pretty much it.
And I don't want to be a moron magnet.
And, you know, as you get older, as you get older, you have fewer and fewer people.
You know, when you're young, you want to, you know, you start bringing out more and more, you know, relationships and acquaintanceships, I should say.
And as you get older, you start finding yourself with fewer and fewer people.
You know, not always, but, you know, if you become more discerning.
I can attest to that.
Yeah, so this is a type of world where if you are trying to do the right thing, you will die alone, by the way.
I won't guarantee you, but I assure you, but you're never really alone.
No.
So that's just the essence of it.
Yeah, I think more can be discussed, more can be said or not said.
So I think the not saying it wins out.
But, again, if anyone is looking for advice, which I do give, is learn how to warn these idiots.
Not only for their sake, they have no sake.
It's to make it easier for the angelic realm, right, because it's going to be known.
Like, for example, if you read in scripture, there is no way Israel would have been deported or ousted from the land unless the prophets had told them they would be.
So, yeah, the best way to get back to these idiots is not to get back to them in a bad way, but just to relay back is, you know, how do you warn them?
Right.
Not inform them.
They have no interest in your dumb animals.
I think as you've proved here, that's going to be quite the uphill challenge.
Well, you can work on it.
Of course.
Yeah, and see if the moment comes up.
But you've still got quite a ways, not quite a ways, years before it's more evident.
You know, the Middle East Union is your sign, by the way.
Right, exactly.
But the whole world being homogeneously infected is, in essence, you will see parallel things happening in your household, neighborhood, country, when those parallel things are, you know, the implementation of the goddess religion.
I think I've discussed that at length, but not at great length.
And also the, you know, the deception, the evil.
But within that, you're going to be exposed to what is lawful and what is, you know, who the true, who the high, I say true God.
No, even the lesser gods are true gods, but not the gods of truth, meaning the boss.
Right.
So there's no knowledge of that yet.
So there you go.
Yeah, I don't think there's anything else.
Let's see.
Ocelli in the Greek is set out very well, like an index in the book.
Yeah, it is.
I'd say it was a good project and thankful to that.
But, you know, if you look at like Ocelli or Fremont, that's a good example.
You just go on about, you know, the goats, not in a bad way, but, you know, you eat at the moment.
Wherever you're with is what's the best.
You know, there's no discernment.
Right.
Unless they personally piss you off, then that's the only time you discern when it's a personal matter.
And then you, that's common.
That's the nature.
And then always alone or never alone.
Yeah.
Being alone by oneself is not easy for everybody.
Having three young children, I miss them when they're not around.
Depends on how young.
Yeah.
If they can speak and watch television, they're fucked.
So, I don't know.
The new modern nanny.
Yeah, they're just demon food.
But, yeah.
Okay, 15-year-old.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Well, a 15-year-old is pretty much on their way.
They know they're an adult more than they're a child at that point.
Yeah.
But if they're interested, yeah, that's fine.
It's not a Greek speak.
It's just, you know, are they interested in doing the right thing.
Right.
So, yeah, I think it's meant to be.
It is meant to be, because it's the waiting room.
And it's an interesting.
There's so much more to talk about.
Maybe in the future.
Who knows?
Yeah.
But right now, I don't think it's conducive or popular or necessary to come around the chat.
Not that I'm going to be avoiding it.
But if there's anything anyone needs, like an e-mail, if you want to do a sonic on anything, we can do it.
I think Bruce will contact TXB29B.
What is it?
TXB29B.
Yeah.
On the chat.
And you guys know how to get in touch with me.
It's easy on Skype.
It's the same as the e-mail.
But, you know, coming around, it's just like, yeah.
Like today, I was like, I would do a sonic today.
Like, why?
You know, last week, I was like, why?
And the week before, why?
Why bother?
You know, it's like nothing going on.
I mean, there's so much to do.
There is so much to do.
You know, like the remediation of toxicity and things like that in the body.
I mean, there's just so much to do.
You know, it's like, never mind.
Well, as I always have said, I extend my services anytime.
Oh, you've done great on that.
You know, I don't think I've ever maybe a little bit tried to come on and access what you've done.
But I think most people can.
And I really don't know what you've done with it.
I haven't been around it to look or monitor it or critique it or, you know, pat you on the back.
But I'll just give you a veritable pat on the back.
Thanks for doing that for other people.
You're welcome.
All right.
Well, with that said, I don't see much going on.
Like I said, Sam is going to – I think it's the Greekspeak.com thing.
And we might be doing podcasts and all that.
But, you know, why bother?
So in the meantime, enjoy.
I think you've got several hundred hours or a couple of hundred hours at least.
It's in the high 200s, I know that.
Yeah.
Good.
That's more than enough.
So that's always rebroadcasting 24 hours a day.
Mm-hmm.
And there's people taking advantage of it, which is good.
And then, of course, we've got the archives up there.
That'll stay.
Cool.
Just leave it alone.
No effort to running it.
It does it by itself, actually.
I have no need for it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, the server or the program sorts it, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So it's pretty easy that way.
Occasionally I come across a few things here and there and I pop them up there.
Yeah, good.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's all about mindset.
It is.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Well, with that.
Well, thanks, everyone.
Thank you very much, Greek.
And you be well in all your endeavors.
You as well.
And thanks for all the archives and stuff.
All right, guys.
Thanks.
Thanks, Bruce.
Yeah.
Bye-bye.
Bye.