Greetings, folks, and we're here with the Greek.
And how are you doing tonight, Greek?
Greetings.
OK, good.
I just want to wish everyone a happy
seventh month.
I don't know how many of the species
that are listening, the various species, I should
say, understand what the seventh month really even
means, because most people don't know how to
study.
They have to get their information from someone
else.
Someone else has to tell them what the
scripture says.
Someone else has to tell them what this
is.
Someone else.
Right.
So giving them hints and having them go
off and looking at source material, heaven forbid,
that's not going to happen.
Not out there tonight.
It's getting worse and worse.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
It's going to get.
Yeah.
The speed.
Well, you know, the species is set up
for destruction right now, which actually I was
listening to something, well, more than just listening,
researching and trying to find how many people
understand external input and very little, even those
that have researched, quote unquote, demonology.
And what I mean by demonology, a demon,
a demonion in ancient Greek just meant a
spiritual being.
But in Western civilization, that means something negative.
Well, usually it is.
And I could get into it a little
bit.
You know, it's the seventh month, which is
one of the highest months.
What's interesting about that, just for a moment,
and I'll get into what the demonology and
all that stuff really is.
You know, the first month is a high
month because of what happens with man.
And the seventh month is a high month
where that happens with the divine.
If you notice all of the appointed things
for the most high appointed days in the
seventh month are geared towards him, where when
you look at the first month, it's geared
towards man.
Right.
You know, and then you have.
So this is a very different mindset.
Most people don't understand, again, why they do
things.
They'll mouth off, well, because of this, but
they really don't get it because they think
that it's black and white, cut and dried,
right and wrong.
There's because of the culture that they're in.
You know, it depends on what culture you're
in.
Right.
So let's go back to the what they
call demons.
And when you look at it from that
perspective, it means it's a it's a Latinized
Greek word, which means spirit, basically.
But what's interesting is when you put that
together with, you know, the Septuagint, which is
a Greek witness of the ancient Masoretic texts,
well, they weren't really like you call Masoretic,
not really, but the Hebrew cognate, because remember,
the Hebrew cognate was Akkadian Armenian, Aramaic, Canaanite
languages also.
So it was a cognate, just like Latin
cognate romance languages back then.
So so the only other witness to that
that we have is maybe some Egyptian, maybe
and but mostly the Greek Septuagint.
When you how many times you ever heard
me say, that's not what it says.
And you go actually look at it.
And even sometimes in an interlinear, they they'll
mess it up, too.
But if you study the word, it's not
what it says.
You know, like Moses, for example, comes down
off the mountain.
He has horns on his head, but they
put that his head was shining.
Right.
So what's interesting is, I think if you
listen to Greek speak till now, most people
understand that what I've said, can be followed
through with source material and references.
And what I mean by that, well, what
did I say that can be followed through
with references and source materials, that there's a
society of gods, it's not just one God,
and all this, right.
And he rolls around with an entourage, he
has agents and all that.
Well, one thing that is has been brought
up in the past is like, from apocalyptic
writings, the four horsemen, the four workmen in
Zechariah, the book of Zechariah.
One thing that isn't really discussed are that
there are four types of beings that do
follow him around because that he rolls with
that are not necessarily part of his character,
but do attend where he is in many
cases, just like a shark with pilot fish,
you know how they're stuck on him, right?
Okay.
Now, if you look up, for example, these
things keep showing up and they're very vague,
but they're clear once you know what to
look for.
There are four entities that accompany the Most
High when he's dealing with people.
And remember, if you understand good and evil,
both good and evil come from the Most
High.
See, Satan is not good or evil, he's
just a deceiver, a liar, a murderer.
He's basically everything, it's his world, everything you
see in the world.
But, you know, good is, you know, pleasure
and prosperity and pleasant trees, pleasant things, you
know, food, clothing, shelter.
And evil is basically destruction, pestilence, and all
these other things, right?
Terrors.
And those words are key words because one
of the entities, you'll find this in the
Psalms, you'll find it in Habakkuk, and you'll
find it in other places if you find
the words.
I think it's like Psalm 90 or Psalm
91.
There is an entity, he's known as the
night terror entity, the terror of the night,
right?
I think it's Damuk Laila, right?
There's another entity that accompanies the Most High
when he's dealing with civilizations, and he's the
day, the spirit of the midday, and he'll,
they translate that into arrow quite often.
There's a prayer where it says that I
miss the arrows and the midday arrows, okay?
Now, if you look up the words for
the terror, the midday arrows, those are Canaanite
gods.
Literally, one is a demon or a spirit
that brings terror by night.
You know, like very often people understand that
bad things come at night while they're sleeping
or while they're doing other things, whatever the
culture is.
Even the ones that try to appease or
summon, you know, they do rituals at night,
right?
Then you have the other one, which is
midday, which is literally the midnoon day one,
and he brings arrows.
Then there's another one.
The Hebrew and Canaanite names vary, but they
basically mean the same thing.
These are four different things.
The other one is the pestilence.
He's the spirit of pestilence.
When you look at the word that's used
for pestilence and find it in the Hebrew,
then you'll see that it's a Canaanite god
also.
Then you find the other one for destruction.
There's a spirit that brings destruction.
When you find that word in an interlinear,
you'll see that is also a name of
a Canaanite god that brings destruction.
Here we have four gods that follow the
Most High.
They're like in his toolbox.
To bring terror by night, terror by day,
or basically peril by day, then you have
one for pestilence and then one for destruction.
They're in his toolbox, and they're evil.
Obviously they're not there to do good.
He unloads them on people based on societies
and individuals, depending on what he sees fit.
That's a little advanced for most people, but
I think if you understand Greek-speak, this
is not a black-and-white, cut-and
-dried thing.
It's a very elaborate society, very elaborate, meaning
there's a lot of variety and many levels
of hierarchy and power.
You can keep going and finding what these
words mean, and you'll find them very often.
I think Sam tried to touch on some
of this notion with Canaanite gods.
There's a lot of people trying to say,
Yahweh is a Canaanite god, and this and
that.
No, just because he shows up in Canaanite
writings, it doesn't mean that he's a Canaanite
god.
Just because these other guys, the pestilence, the
night terror, the day danger, let's say, and
the other one is the destroyer, shows up
in Canaanite writings, Phoenician writings, let's say, doesn't
mean that they're their gods.
These gods are cross-national, by the way,
so they can be adopted by people, they
follow people.
So anyway, I just wanted to bring that
up because Seventh Month is a good month
to get into the spiritual side studies, by
the way.
It's also the breaking down period, harvesting this
whole month, so watch for things breaking down
in the media and the news.
If you know a place that's important, let's
say, I'm going to go wireless, I'm going
to unplug these wires, hopefully I won't lose
sound.
Let me know if I do.
I will.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's say, how to watch the news, let's
say you see your ends in the news,
right?
All the time about this, that, and the
other.
Give an example, Persia.
And then all of a sudden it's not
in the news.
Well, that means they have nothing petty to
say.
That means there's some serious shit going on.
Because it's the opposite.
Remember, these are liars, right?
Everything that's ever been memorialized to the populace
is a lie.
Even food, when you go to the food
aisle, look at the grocery store, it's all
a lie.
I was talking to someone recently, I said,
well, if it was a society of engineers,
they wouldn't have the label of the food
or the name of the food out, they
would have the ingredients enlarged, and the ingredients
would be the label.
So the engineer is walking down the aisle,
and he says, oh, water, soy, maltodextrose, red
color, okay, I'll take that.
But, you know, they call that American cheese,
right?
Right.
You see, so for the idiots, you call
it Cheerios, or McDonald's, or American cheese, but
for the engineer, he's not interested in what
you call it, it's what's in it.
You should have in big letters all the
ingredients, and just very pronounced, bold on the
front of the package, right?
Right.
So anyway, you see, so this is the
elements of Greek speak, is try to bring
out what's in it and make it bold,
versus what people talk about.
You know, they still, yeah.
People lack the mindset within their realm, meaning
the realm that they understand.
Like Dimitri says, there's something called, he uses
the term a lot, I forgot what he
was using, Kalazov, ideology.
Okay, yeah.
There is someone like, for example, on a
local Craigslist, answering back to the people complaining
about the Air Force jets' noise, and he
says, oh, you're a bunch of pussies, you
know, these guys are defending your freedom, you
should appreciate it.
I mean, oh boy, because they're not.
You know, the military has nothing to do
with defending your freedom, they work for the
oligarchs, and they, yeah, they're weaponized morons.
So someone like that doesn't understand what freedom
is, obviously.
So what I mean by that is, people
that say they're spiritual and religious don't know
anything about that, you see?
Like people who say they're defending, the military
is defending your freedom, don't know what freedom
is, they don't know what the military is.
Even if they do it, even if it's
their job to say that.
Obviously they lack the ideology of what freedom
is.
The minute you see constitutional, republic, or justice,
prepare to be enslaved, hopelessly.
Right?
Amen.
So, yeah, so that people that say that
they know scripture, or know spirituality, know about
that, be prepared that that is just a
farce.
Right?
Because if, the reason why it has to
be a farce, is because if it wasn't,
no one would listen to them.
Right.
In other words, what's popular is not true,
and what's true is not popular.
So anyway, I'm going to make some coffee
here.
Hopefully, I'm going to mute out if I
have to grind.
I want to thank the fellow in the
Northwest who sent still a great variety of
coffee, a couple of kilos almost.
Light roasts, very delicious, so I've been enjoying
them.
And a really long letter.
And I also want to thank the fellow
on the East Coast that sent a contribution
a few weeks ago.
Again, I just want to thank them again,
those two.
So much appreciated.
So okay, anything in chat?
Anything?
I'm just going to go back into the
office here shortly, and I will see if
there's anything else.
Otherwise, we'll make it a real short one.
Okay.
Let's see, there was one from someone here.
I saw on chat just a couple of
people realize that it's the seventh month.
Yeah.
Well, at least compared to...
If there's anasonic event...
And there was a question about weight loss.
Yeah, weight loss.
Let's see, since we don't understand the container,
we can't possibly understand weight loss and proper
how-tos.
Also, is there a better exercise regime than
others?
Thank you in advance.
Not really.
Fasting, weight loss, the best way to lose
weight is to get stressed out.
That'll do it.
Depends on the emotional state, the feeding emotional
state.
Some people get stressed out, and they hide.
Typically, fat people will have a stash of
candy bars, and they'll gorge themselves with it.
Or something, potato chips, fast food, they'll hide.
They won't keep it, especially if they live
with other people, they won't keep it where
the food stuff is.
They'll hide it in a shoe drawer, or
a closet, or a garage.
Get outside and work hard.
For your average of the species for losing
weight...
I don't know, that's a very conditional statement,
conditional question to ask.
I don't think weight is a problem if
the individual is balanced with their weight.
Like, for example, I think women should be
thick, not bony.
You know what I mean?
Let me just...
everybody close their ears.
Thick women, I didn't say fat.
You know, if they're from the Midwest.
Yeah, like in Midwest America, you know, corn
-fed mama, you know.
Corn-fed.
Yeah, healthy.
Healthy, yes.
Healthy.
You know, healthy.
In the ghetto, it's not healthy, it's healthy.
Healthy.
Healthy, yeah.
She's healthy.
Yeah, so you don't want to lose weight
if you're healthy.
You know?
So anyway, skinny chicks came about with the
modeling when the sodomites, the gays, got into
it, the homosexuals.
It's scary sometimes to look at.
You know, you look like...
Because they hate women.
You just want to give them a sandwich,
you know.
They're that thin, and I'm like, holy...
Yeah, and it came from the Shakespearean days
where the women were not enacting.
They would use paramours, young 13-year-old
boys.
So it's a pretty sick society.
Don't bother with anything on the internet about
pedophilia or human trafficking and human sacrifice.
That's not going to go away until kingdom
come, because the idiots in this human society
do birthdays and Christmas, and their holidays are
based on human sacrifice and pedophilia and eating
of babies and destroying children.
That's a whole massive culture.
It's just like the Pope, the gay Pope
in Ireland, and the Irish are protesting.
That's like a bunch of pigs getting up
on their hind legs, you know.
It's like, what are you talking about?
You do birthdays and Christmas, and you're protesting
the Pope raping boys?
Yeah.
I mean, come on.
If you're gay, if you're a homosexual like
that, and you're strung up on coke like
that for two days in a row, they're
going to want a young boy based on
their religion, because that is their religion.
And you've got the population protesting that?
Well, they themselves do Christmas.
What is it, Irish?
Who's the greatest Irishman?
You've got to make fun of them a
little bit.
Bobby Sands, who did the hunger strike.
And Jesus Christ himself, greatest Irishman that ever
lived.
Good Irish accent you got there, Lottie.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I mean, talk about a bunch of
idiots.
That species has just got to, oh.
So, you see, before you get into weight
loss, you've got to look at it like
that.
Is this like weight loss because it's for
fashion reasons, or is it for health reasons?
By the way, if you go all veg
and dairy, you're going to lose weight if
it's meant to lose weight.
If you're skinny, and you're unhealthy, and you
go all veg and dairy, you might gain
weight, because that's where you should be.
Right, right.
If you have a tapeworm bigger than the
state of Cincinnati, and you lose it, you're
going to gain weight.
So, weight loss, other than chopping off heads.
Yeah, heads are eight pounds.
Arms are three or four pounds.
Legs are six pounds.
I don't know.
What do you mean weight loss?
But, anyway, yeah.
I don't understand what that means.
Most Americans are overweight because they're in starvation
mode.
It's horrible.
Well, what happens is the body, you'll see
this with Native Americans, when they get into
the American food, they get fat, because the
food has no nutrition.
So, the body says, we're working this digestive
system, which takes up most of your energy
when it's working, and there's no nutrition in
it.
So, we go into starvation mode, which is
storing fat.
So, it means Americans are the way they
are because their food has no nutrition.
It's denatured.
That's a very common thing, is if you're
eating a lot, to look bloated.
And the body produces fat.
The body produces cholesterol, by the way, and
all that.
So, the Americans are lost.
They're lost.
This is Satan's world, and America is Satan's
armpit, if you know what I mean.
I was going to go for the crotch,
but okay.
Yeah, the crotch, too.
So, either way.
So, I don't know.
It's kind of hard.
Depending if this is, I can address an
audience outside of America, let's say, or the
States.
You know, go back to your traditional foods
and traditionally prepared and traditionally stored and grown,
and you'll be fine.
Yeah, the French drink more wine and smoke
cigarettes more than anyone, and they have no
cancer until recently.
Speaking of that, going back to the guy
who cries freedom and Americans, the Psychiatry Society
says 26% of Americans are mentally ill.
Now, you know how they fudge the numbers.
It's got to be double that, right?
Easily.
I'm surprised they didn't jack it up so
they could get some extra pharmaceuticals out, you
know.
Yeah, in the water, at least.
Yeah, right.
Well, it's already in there.
You got enough chemicals in there to start
your own little pharmacy.
Weight loss could start, well, gaining weight could
be liver problems, right?
Because the cholesterol is produced in the, you
know how many people don't know that cholesterol
is actually produced in the body?
You can't eat cholesterol.
There's no such thing.
Right.
It's like saying brains, you know.
You don't eat brains.
Well, some people do, you know.
But, yeah, it's not something that you eat.
It's something that's in the body already.
Yeah.
And the way the cholesterol drugs, all they
do, it's a dumb drug.
It's a hormone and some kind of other
antihistamine mixed with something else.
I may not be accurate, but it's a
very dumb drug.
It's not highly developed.
And all it does is retard liver function,
which then affects pancreas, kidneys, and all.
So, basically, they're poisoning your liver so you
go, that's all right.
The people that own the countries that you
live in are tired of your asses.
So, too many slaves, too many animals on
the ranch, time to thin it out.
Not because it's naturally not whatever.
They're just tired of it.
And they don't see, they see the owners,
the oligarchs, they see that the people are
very well entrenched into their system.
So, meaning they have children and they send
them to those schools.
So, the oligarchs know 99.99% of
the idiots having babies are still sending them
to our schools.
So, we know we're just going to have
another generation of scumbags and so on and
so forth.
So, I think it's time to start calling
these idiots out.
And they're behind schedule.
I'm just saying this because it's true, not
because I, you know.
But the thing is, see, they're shooting fish
in a barrel.
See, at least the oligarchs could have some
fun if you had a civil war or
revolution here or there.
They say, oh, 2% are resisting, let's
just go kill them.
At least we have some fun.
We could do some death pool betting on
them, you know, while we do it.
But they're not even doing that.
I'm not saying you should, you know, because
you're not, they're too irresponsible.
They don't even know.
You know, they want freedom, freedom.
The Americans will say it was the greatest
Americans, Ronald Reagan, John Wayne, and Jesus Christ
himself.
These are talking about people that are beyond
stupidity.
I mean, there's no help.
So, at this point, the food is the
biggest thing.
I don't know if you've heard warnings through
many channels through years.
Do not eat pre-prepared foods, you know,
like the frozen foods, pre-prepared meals.
You know, the big name brands, those are,
they have specific things in there to keep
you, you know, so.
Also, when you say weight loss, most people
think, well, the easiest way to lose weight
is to cut off large body parts, right,
obviously.
The second easiest way is to stop eating.
You go into fasting mode, semi-starvation mode.
But starvation, when the body indicates a starvation
mode, it's a complex process, and you can,
your body can go either way.
You can actually get damaged, or you don't
recuperate from, like, you know, places that don't
have spring water or good food.
The people have, let's say, a lower IQ,
right?
That's why Americans have such a low IQ,
for example.
Like, they never had real milk, real bread,
real good water.
There was a test done in South Korea.
The IQ went down, and the children got
bigger within 10 years by introducing different types
of dairy, synthesized dairy, you know, like powdered
milks and changing the diet.
So, the IQs went down, and the bodies
got bigger.
So, the third way of losing weight is
to go veg, and high quality, and seasonal.
So, that's all pretty much.
And when you go veg, you also have
to consider when you have what they call
carbs, grains, rice, cereals, they need to be
as whole as possible, not stripped or processed.
Like, white rice, avoid.
Not prohibit, but avoid.
If you have no choice, have the white
rice.
But if you have a choice, get the
unprocessed rice.
And a cereal.
You know, wild rice is not a rice,
it's a cereal, right?
Oh, we lose you.
I think we lost a Greek.
Oh, you're almost there.
Oh, we lost him.
We'll see if we pick him back up.
There we are.
Call dropped.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Yeah.
You've got a lot of Skype, huh?
That's fine.
It's free and it's deplorable.
Yeah, exactly.
All right.
Not much on weight loss.
Are we on again?
Yes, we're on.
Okay, so not much on weight loss other
than cut your head off, cut your arms
and legs off, or go into fasting mode.
That's the fastest way.
And we said weight loss, so just pure
weight loss.
And then there's obviously changing the way you
eat.
And purpose, examine the reason that you're doing
this.
Some people going to a better diet gain
weight, depending on, you know.
Like, for example, if someone has irritable bowel
syndrome and they're a meat eater, and they
switch to vegetarianism, they gain weight.
I've known a couple of people like that,
and they kind of freak out.
They're like, oh, I'm eating too many starches.
I'm like, no, you're not eating too many
starches.
That's how you really should be.
You're getting back to where you should be,
yeah.
Yeah, you're getting back to where you should
be.
So either way, why bother?
I mean, and if you have so much
weight loss, need weight loss that you can't
fit through the door, that's, I think you're
listening to the wrong, need to go to
the regular Western route, get parts cut off,
you know, put a vacuum cleaner with an
eighth-inch or quarter-inch needle under your
body, and they suck it out.
What's that called?
Liposuction.
Liposuction, yeah.
Yeah.
Or Jenny Craig, you know, she makes money
too.
Which is food, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Which is the prepackaged food that'll kill you,
will cause cancer.
Right, right.
Which you're going to, you know, they want
to get rid of most people, so why
not have them go by cancer?
They'll suck.
If you're going to do it right, get
them in the hospital.
They could monetize cancer more than anything else.
Heck yeah.
That's very high monetization for these morons.
So there's a spirit behind all of that.
So nothing else?
Yeah, that looks to be it there, Greek.
Nothing really much else than that.
Yeah, nothing much on the emails, just some
sort of personal stuff.
Other than catching up on the seventh moon,
that was about the highlight there.
Yeah, it's a quick year.
It's a breaking down period now, so it
should be quiet because things are getting more
serious.
The building up is interesting too.
Oh, we lose you again?
Uh-oh.
I think we might have lost you, Greek.
Logan?
We keep dropping.
I'll let somebody go plug in.
I think there might be some maintenance work.
Ah.
Yeah, we just dropped you again.
This might want to be one of those
events.
Usually things are kind of...
There we go, we got your back again.
Oop.
And he's gone.
Thank goodness for editing.
Log in.
Okay, it keeps dropping.
We'll try again next week.
We'll see you.
Thanks, Bruce.
Okay, you take care, Greek.
Take care.
Good night now.
Bye-bye.