And greetings folks, we're live with the Greek
and how are you doing today, Greek?
Oh, doing.
I see we're okay.
I'm just going on to the chat.
I'm going to drop a couple food photos,
maybe one of a four minute pizza, literally
just a very simple pizza, yeasted dough.
And you build it, if you have a
gas stove, you just build a tent right
above the broiler area, remove the broiler baffle
tray and your thermostat no longer works.
And if you have a pyrometer, it'll reach
six or 700 degrees within three minutes, which
is really good for doing a pizza.
Yeah, you'll burn down, you don't want to
run it for more than 10 or 15
minutes because you could damage the steel and
the fixtures on the door handles and all
that, depending on whatever.
So I think we're going to have someone
join us as well.
I'll bring him in right now.
Let's see if he picks up.
He says whenever he's ready.
People have heard.
It's Sam.
So what are you doing?
I think he's on.
Sam, welcome.
We're off with Bruce.
Greetings, Sam.
Greetings.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
A little bit of microphone rumble of some
kind, but otherwise it's okay.
Yeah, I was just moving it.
I don't think it's rumbling anymore.
Okay.
Yeah, so I just opened up doing some
work today and stuff and how to modify
an oven to make a four minute pizza.
Came out pretty good.
That's pretty clever.
I just dropped it in a Greek chitango.
Oh, there you go.
You see it?
Yeah.
And that's a pesto.
I have basil out in the garden, chopped
it up with some garlic.
That makes me look hungry.
That's a pretty professional looking pizza.
And it's actually, the crust is really thick,
but the actual pie itself is extremely thin,
cracker thin.
Right.
And I used a Fleischmann's yeast, honey, olive
oil, salt, two hours for rise, knocked it
down, spread it out using a wine bottle,
and there you go.
It's about 14, 15 inch pizza.
So I had most of it yesterday, some
of it for breakfast.
Very well done.
The cheeses are like cheddar, brie, and a
little bit of fresh mozzarella and parmesan.
So there you go.
I just wanted to, I don't think I've
ever posted pizzas that I make that you
don't have to, I mean it looks pretty,
you could put it on a cooking magazine,
right?
Oh, yes, yes.
You don't have to use yeast.
It'll work well, just as well with a
flatbread.
If you do use an egg with the
dough, you'll get a little bit of rise
because egg offers leavening.
Right.
So there you go.
There's a pizza.
Looks nice.
Yeah, it's four minutes to cook.
Yeah.
Two minutes and then I rotate it.
What I should really do to offer more
of a semblance of how to do it
at home is to open the oven and
photograph what it looks like in there.
Yeah.
How I rearranged everything.
Now if you look at the pizza to
the top right, you see the rectangle, look,
gray metal.
It looks a rectangle bar kind of thing,
like an ingot.
That's a four pound or two and a
half kilo or two kilo diver's weight, and
you can see the slots in it.
That's where you run the belt through, so
you put those around your waist when you
go diving to hold you down.
I have four of those that I use
in cooking, you know, and right behind it
you'll see there's a white porcelain thing with
a groove cut in the bottom.
That's a coffee mug, and I use the
diamond blade to cut that groove, so when
you have a strap handle lid, it straddles
the lid.
So that's my ghetto pressure cooker.
What I should do is take a photo
of the kitchen area there, show you how
it's been modified, what I've used, just so
you can...
You are a man of many talents.
But basically, the easiest way to modify any
oven or range is you allot whatever area
of volume your food tray or whatever, let's
say it's a pizza, you don't need a
lot of height, right, because the pizza, you
know, give yourself two inches is plenty.
If you're going to tent at three, it's
more than enough, because the pizza is not
going to be that high.
So basically, on the bottom tray, you just
measure up about three inches or so the
first rung, and just coat that with aluminum
foil, completely closed off.
So when the fire comes up from underneath,
it will form a tent area.
Now, your thermometer, I mean, your thermostat no
longer works, obviously.
You know, if I set the thermostat to
300, it's still running.
But if I put a pyrometer underneath my
tented area, it's at 700.
You get it?
So this is just something to do a
fast high...
Yeah, I figured I'd post it because it
came out...
And all the pizzas I do look like
that.
I don't mean to brag.
They all look like that whenever I've done
pizzas, even the ones that have no leavening,
but you don't have the crust, you know.
The ones that don't have leavening are done
under two minutes.
And by the way, that's still bubbling, the
photo there.
You could see the cheese is still bubbling.
So, okay, well, I just wanted to throw
that in there.
I like to be practical other than doing
lower ball joints on minivans and stuff like
today.
So anyway...
Yeah, thank you for the pizza insight.
It also works on what's called a mini
electric oven.
It works the same way.
You just tent off the area, you know.
So an electric stove or oven, they have
elements, I think, above and below, right?
And you need both in an electric.
So you're going to have to figure out
which one you're going to use, because if
you have an electric, I'd say use the
top element or the bottom element, depending on
which tray you're using.
See, this is a double layer metal sheet,
not the thin...
You know, a lot of cookie sheets are
real thin single, but the better, more professional
ones, let's say, have a double layer so
the thin metal doesn't burn.
You're familiar with those, right?
So with an electric, what you want to
do is...
Two things you could do.
It's difficult to tent, because you need both
elements.
You...
Instead of doing it on a tray, you
do it in a large pan.
So you put the pizza in the pan
and put it on the stovetop and start
heating it on the stovetop and get under
it with a fork until it gets golden
brown.
And then you just stick it in the
toaster oven or the electric range as high
as possible, top element, just to brown it
on the top.
So it's a two-stage cooking.
Wow.
Hmm.
Right?
So here's one thing about...
The cookie sheet acts more as a diffuser,
then, too.
Yes, it's a diffuser.
You've ever cooked with metal, thin metal, it
always burns?
Yes, yes.
So the more utilitarian cookie sheets are double
layered.
If you...
Most of the...
You don't want to...
When you buy cookie sheets, they're real inexpensive
and flimsy, but if you go to a
restaurant supply or a good baking supply, you'll
notice they're not as flimsy, even though they
are thin, because if you look at it
closely, it's two layers.
And they usually have a mineral fiber in
between.
Right.
So you don't get that burn.
So each thin layer tends to overheat and
it diffuses exactly.
Yeah.
So instead of spending $1.50 on a
pizza pan, I think the double layer one
costs about $10, because it's...
More worth it, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, because it's a restaurant or
whatever.
Now, you could use a stone also, which
is superior, but you're not going to get
a four-minute cook with a stone, because
the stone has to be hot.
You don't want to put the pizza on
a cold stone.
Right.
So you're going to have to give it
an hour to heat.
So anyway, I just wanted to throw this
in, because I think I've discussed uneven heat
application in food is what renders those complex
flavors that you get when you have a
good meal.
You know what I mean?
Well, you got me curious again, and I
think that'll be on the list soon.
Yeah.
Try it.
And tent off a variable volume stove.
Okay, yeah.
And it saves on energy.
Imagine your standard oven, to get it up
to a 350, preheat, takes 15 minutes at
least.
Even tell you on the white people food
packages, 15 minutes, right?
Right.
Preheat.
Well, when you partition the volume and decrease
it, it goes to 350 in about 40
seconds.
So what that shows on the utility bill,
right?
The difference.
Also makes sense if you're off the grid,
obviously, right?
Oh, definitely.
Some people have to have propane tanks full,
you know, when you go out of the
city, if you have gas or whatever.
Anyway, okay.
So what's going on?
Sam, since you're here, you want to bring
anything forward or I haven't looked in the
chat for questions, but knowing why the chat's
been for the past year or two, I
don't think there's anything profound in there.
There was some questions last week about Genesis
and such.
All right.
There's always questions about Genesis in there.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I don't know if you had
any outline for what you're going to talk
about tonight.
I mean, on the biblical end, mainly I'm
looking into a lot of the Israel captivity
stuff to see, you know, where different tribes
disperse to and what can be in there.
Of course, there's a whole community built up
around that.
So you have to be careful because a
lot of zealots post inaccurate stuff.
But that's mainly what I've been going through.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm just joking.
Yeah, of course.
Well, here's the interesting aspect about it.
You know, I speak on how screwed up
things are and everything's moronic.
And, you know, and then you parallel that
with the spiritual side, which is also in
turmoil in some capacity.
You know, when I say some capacity, because
we only know what we've been told in
scripture and in other levels, right?
What's interesting is when the Israelites go into
captivity or they're in a diaspora situation, you
have to ask yourself, what I've always asked
myself is once I determined that Yahweh was
their patron deity, is was he still their
patron deity when they were dispersed and taken
to captivity?
Or does he abandon them?
In other words, retract his protection and retract
his power over them as a nation?
And the answer to that I found every
time is the latter, he does.
Because there's no other way that they can
be affected spiritually if he's protecting them.
So that's like an obvious example of how
the Most High pulls his protection, even though
he's diminished himself to be like the sons
of gods, you know, over one nation over
instead of over the world, which it's not
time yet, right?
So he does pull his protection, you know.
But if he did pull his protection completely,
then they would have been annihilated, which we
know that they aren't because they will be
reassembled.
So not completely, though.
Right, he keeps them around as seeds, just
that he gives them just enough protection.
So the seed is not damaged, you know,
in other words, some seed is maintained.
In other words, there's no more field of
crops, just a store, small storehouse or a
box of seeds around.
Yeah, it's pretty rough.
Yeah.
I mean, looking at it that way, when
you then get into these alternative historians that
have their own expositions on what happens with
the 12 tribes, and they want to claim
that certain Western nations are various tribes, if
we then assume that Yahweh has in fact
abandoned them, then they aren't really the tribes,
though, if they've been abandoned.
Well, as in, abandoned on a national level,
like where the Creator comes and he takes
a position as one of the sons of
gods over the nations, instead of the Creator.
And he just happens to be the Creator,
you see.
Yeah, there we go.
Because when he comes down and he gives
them protection, meaning, you know, what they call
the Shekhinah, you know, his presence, and the
temple is built and their offerings and all
that directly through, you know, the proxies that
he sets up, you know, the angels, he's
still not in his complete form.
He's in a form as one of the
other, as the other gods are supposed to
do over their nations, you see.
And what's interesting is about, you know, people
say kingdom come and all that, that's when
the Creator is on earth to rule over
the old, the entire earth overtly.
So, there's going to be a big difference
then as well.
That's what, the reason I'm bringing that up
is because there's a mix-up you hear.
People aren't able to put this in its
proper perspective.
And the perspective is simply that the involvement
of, let's say, what we see in scripture
and Yahweh with Israel as their patron deity
is not, it's on the level of as
the other gods of the other nations are
to them.
And the difference that people, most people don't
realize, some do, very few actually haven't run
into many that have, I'm just saying it
to give some leeway, is that when the,
in quotes and air quotes, the return of
the Christ and the kingdom come, is the
Creator will rule over the earth and everyone
will have to fall in line, meaning the
other gods as well, the ones that are
not killed and whatever.
And there's going to be an overt presence,
you know, and then there's a whole handful
of things, the resurrection and all this, so
that is the main difference, that if you
put that in perspective, just like many other
things, like for example, when you bring up
anything biblical, people automatically say, well, I don't
know the Bible, I'm not religious.
And when I say, what do you mean
about religion?
They say, Christianity, and they think of this
guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper,
or Christmas, or Easter, or church, and that
couldn't be, you know, that's some kind of
demonic fantasia, you know.
So when you do have things in a
perspective, when you say the Christ, you know
he was born on the fall on a
tabernacle, and you know he was stoned to
death with two others on an almond tree,
and you know that he ascended, you know,
a month and a half later, roughly, and
you know this, and you know that, biblically
and historically, let's say, when you bring up
another subject, you can discuss it once you
have that mindset in line.
But when, again, just to go outside of
what we're discussing in this particular sonic, if
you were to bring up this argument or
debate on what's right or what's wrong about
scripture or any subject, usually the person you're
conveying these thoughts with have not established what
I just mentioned.
They're in this false reality, you know, they
think of crucifixion, they think of Easter, they
think of Christmas, they don't know.
So the double difficulty here comes in where
it's nearly impossible to seek information and research
and have discussions on this, because the mindset
is not there, the proper mindset.
So, you know, when you carry that forward,
again, to have the proper mindset, it seems
like it's taking a really long time, but
we know what happens.
Just to maybe interfere a little bit with
the progression of what you, the subject, I
mean interfere, because there's not much of a
discussion when you understand what's called, you know,
the second advent of the Christ and all
this, that Israel would be given preference, preferential
treatment to the majority of them, if not
all of them to a certain degree, regarding
the resurrection and imbued with powers of rulership
in the new society for mankind.
That's where it ends up, right?
That goes without speculation, that's stated as fact,
right?
So now we're at that time prior to
that.
So the question is, with any subject matter
discussion regarding Israel and eschatology and all this,
is, well, we know how it ends up,
and we know where we are now, and
is the discussion to bridge the gap?
Or is the discussion to correct misinformation?
Or, you see what I mean?
Because ultimately we know they're going to be
given preferential treatment, and they're going to have
partaken some, you know, pretty significant aspects of
the rulership, you know, meaning of other humans,
ultimately, is how they end up.
And here's the mistake that people, you know,
very few people put in perspective.
It doesn't happen immediately.
Apparently they're taken down to the wilderness, as
they were after Egypt.
So, again, that's why on previous Sonics I've
gotten into a little more detail when this
society ends, on the surface and below the
surface, you know, the powers that be underneath
there also, because there's a whole other world
there.
There's going to be about 40 years of,
you know, what the fuck happened here, you
know?
I'd say more than that, but before the
dust settles.
So, yeah, most of what you say, I'm
sounding very echoey.
Yeah, a little bit.
Not too much.
It's audible.
It's legible.
Well, other things that I've looked at recently,
I don't know, based on the biblical information
about pre-Adamite man and the archaeological finds
in places like the Balkans in Eastern Europe,
where you have carbon dated items that go
to 6000 BC-ish.
What can be said about the Danube Valley
civilization of Eastern Europe?
Obviously, that's connected to a lot of goddess
religion things as far as, I forget the
lady's name, but I think it's like Maria
Gimbuta, with her books about the goddess religion.
She uncovered a lot of stuff, at least
archaeologically, in that place in the 60s and
70s, and in recent times you have certain
museums and universities in New York that are
putting a lot of things on display within
the past few years about that civilization going
back to pre-Adamite man, if you line
up the dates.
Right, well, with carbon dating, you know, it's
good for 80,000 years.
It's pretty accurate.
You know, after 40,000, you could say
the accuracy goes down.
It's good to about 80,000.
Anything past 100,000, by the way, doesn't
work.
So if anyone says this is X amount
beyond 100,000 years or 80,000 years
and it's carbon dated, you know you're being
lied to, just like DNA testing and all
this other stuff, right?
Like with DNA testing, if you don't have
110 samples or 111 really crossover samples, it's
a very speculative study, right?
You can take a banana and bring it
to a DNA lab, and in three days
they can tell you, well, it's probably 40
% human, right?
So, I mean, the information with dating, you
almost have to look at how they dated
it, and that's almost never offered other than
the label, carbon dating, you know?
So whenever I, there's very little online.
You can sometimes get it if it's in
print, but not online.
If someone says something's been carbon dated, well,
I want to see the report.
On the carbon dating, you know, how it
was done, who did it.
Now you sound like a total ass when
you do, right?
It's like, what's wrong with you, right?
But I'm serious.
That has to be taken because you can
take a banana peel, scrape off a micro
amount and give it and say, this is
someone's DNA.
Can you tell me?
In a week or three days, all they
can do is tell you it's about 40
% human so far.
Do you see my point here?
So when they throw all this stuff, you
notice how they never give you validation.
They just tell you it was carbon dated,
and it's the scientism, the God, it's a
religion, the God behind that, and everyone bows
down towards it.
And I'm calling foul and bullshit on everything
they present publicly, like I said before, nothing
that the public knows is true, and the
truth is not known by the public, and
whatever the public thinks they know is not
true.
But that is different than saying that the
information is not publicly available.
It is publicly available.
It is, but no one cares.
Because this is a society of idiots, as
a group, you know.
So I would say that regarding the goddess
religion, it's not only in one area, but
it's everywhere.
Another aspect of it would be, you would
want to ask about how did pre-Adamite
man expand on an even radius around that
part of the world, or did they take
certain paths?
You know, was maybe the north, you know,
the Caucasus, you know, or that area that
you mentioned, let's say, populated first, or did
they divide down to the African continent, right?
Or did they become seafaring and go across
first?
We don't know.
We don't have that much information other than
dispersion and the lineages given in Genesis, right?
Yeah.
I am referring to the archaeological finds, though,
which they don't go back that far.
It's just 6,000 BC.
So this is within a safe carbon dating
radius.
6,000 BC is on the money in
Genesis, six-day man.
Right.
And when they, by the way, when man
was made and put on this earth, or
made on the earth, let's say, though the
six-day man was made on the earth,
they were fully enabled.
You know, they didn't, they weren't running around
wondering what, you know, what, how to do
things.
They were enabled by spiritual beings, you know.
You know, they didn't invent the wheel.
They didn't invent swords.
They didn't invent the shovel.
They didn't invent farming.
It was given to them, right?
I know it sounds kind of far-fetched,
you know, but, and I don't need to
refer to works like Enoch and Jasher and
other things like that, Book of the Upright,
but you could refer to any old societal
mythology or legend.
Nowhere in any ancient culture did man invent
anything.
It was given to them, right?
Right.
Yeah, I mean, as far as what's been
found archaeologically, you have quite a few items
with writing on them that, you know, some
scholars will say it's not writing because it
predates the Sumerian script, so they're not really
sure what it says.
But you also have graves with a lot
of gold in them that sort of go
beyond, you know, the reasonable amount of gold
and valuables that have been found in other
places like Egypt and such.
So I'm not quite sure how to string
together all of that to form a conclusion,
because the writing is not decipherable, as they've
expressed anyway.
It'll come as time goes on.
Let's say you won't be asking this in
five or six years.
I think there'll be more information in public,
or maybe not, because you have to understand
this is a society of secrets, right?
So when you read stuff in scripture, for
example, about the coming world condition, you know,
it might just come and nobody will realize
it, but it's happening.
You know, because it's about secrets.
So I would say that the promise that
things will be revealed in the end is
still there.
I think that all this is known.
You know, the Fictionasia Scientifica is very quick
to dispatch anything that is not in line
with their teachings.
Right.
You know, like the Smithsonian Institution was the
first CIA.
If you ever found an anomaly, like a
giant skeleton, or something that resembled, you know,
an ancient spacecraft, or something, a hundred years
ago, the Smithsonian Institution was quickly sent to
you to cover it up, even though it
made the news.
You know, so and so was plowing the
field and found such and such, and the
Smithsonian's on their way, and then you never
hear of it again.
So the reason I brought that up is
because it may not make the news, right?
Right.
Because now you have the Smithsonian still, and
you also have the CIA, and the FBI,
and the FDA, and the University of buttfuck,
whatever, you know, excuse the medical term there.
So yeah, it's really bad.
And here, when I say it's really bad,
it's not going to get better as we
go closer towards the time appointed, let's say.
So you could piece that together.
I think understanding the historicity of Genesis is
the biggest advantage you have, other than, depends,
you know, if you want to be the
archaeological type, you know, an archaeologist is someone
who spends their life in ruins, right?
Anyway, bad joke, but, or do you want
to be the one that is just satisfied
with good, solid information?
I've been through both routes, and I found
out that it's the good, solid information takes
precedent over the experience.
Yeah, I mean, some people are trying to
be economical with their time and their energy
towards certain ends, and other people do need
the experience in order to internalize things, depending
on the stage that they're at.
But, you know, the tree falling in the
forest, and does anyone hear it?
Does it make a sound if no one's
there?
If you find it, the first implication, you
know, let's say the Freudian ego and all
that is to share it with others and
see, you know, self-importance, you know, but
you remember, I'm not saying this is you,
but I'm saying many people like to bring
forward discoveries and attach their persona to for
glory or profit or gain of some kind.
But you have to remember, when you go
beyond a retarded or moronic level or second
grade level or third grade level, people don't
care, you have to keep it stupid.
So now, bringing forward viable or valid information
about anything that goes against what's already been
put out, or the mindset, is not a
good thing, believe it or not.
It's actually a bad thing, because you're going
to be ignored by the population and targeted
by the powers that be.
Yeah, sure, that is understood.
My suggestion is take it as it comes
and watch what happens as this new world
system is put in place, what they allow.
As long as you know what you know,
you'll be fine, because this new world system
that's going to be put in place is
going to show itself as being good and
provide good attributes, social attributes, but it's going
to be downright the worst thing that's ever
happened.
And here's the other thing, even if everything
were to end tomorrow, and there was an
advent of overt spirituality, meaning we get to
see the spiritual world, and most of the
idiots on this planet are dealt with or
dispatched, and the evil is mostly tampered down,
you still have 40 years of smoke and
dust before it settles, roughly.
So, it's a long process, either way.
Have you read or heard of the idea
that, well I'm sure it's been expressed, but
if it's valid is what I'm wondering, this
idea that a lot of wars that took
place in the 19th and 20th century, and
perhaps even some current ones like this ongoing
Syrian one, or perhaps the Vietnam War to
an extent, have a covert purpose of bombing
or removing certain relics or remnants of older
civilizations from those areas.
Like, currently you can read articles about how
the Russians are bombing a city like Palmyra
in Syria, and then you look at pictures
of those cities in the news reports, and
you see this Greco-Roman ruin or something
near the city, which shows signs of prior
bombing, like you're bombing this almost obscure area
where there's nothing happening in the name of
getting ISIS people in caves, and it doesn't
really make any sense when you could have
gone in on foot to get them, like
it's just a few guys in a cave.
Wasn't there a lot of that in the
Iraq War?
I seem to remember hearing about that a
lot.
There's several ways to look at that.
One is, if they were so great, why
didn't they maintain it?
Those temples are pretty useless, because the gods
that they supported or were temples to in
the cities that were built on those gods'
names, by the way, you know, and usually
when you build a city, you dedicate it
to a god.
I know most people think that's crazy, but
if you do some research, you'll figure it
out.
For example, if the local post office was
blown up right now where you are, I
assure you, I'm not going to say guarantee,
but I assure you within a month or
two, it'll be rebuilt with no signs of
it ever being blown up, right?
It'll never be in ruins.
Even if the local Walmart was blown up,
or Target, or store, or church, or whatever,
they'd rebuild it within a very short period
of time.
But these things lay in ruins for a
long time for a reason, spiritual reason, right?
So, do they have any use?
And if they did, does it serve you
well?
And the answer is no all around.
What I say, I take the Stalinistic perspective,
these things, have you ever run into a
real communist, like a hardcore brainwashed communist?
I did in the 80s.
He was actually a leftover.
He was pretty old at the time in
the 80s.
He was around 80.
He was working for an engineering architecture firm.
I was at a place called Snug Harbor
in Staten Island, and they were restoring all
these old buildings.
And it was like an architectural fart where
each building represented a certain style of architecture
from Greco-Roman, Palladian, and Victorian.
They were restoring them, and I said to
the engineer, basically, in short, what do you
think of this?
He said, I think all these buildings should
be leveled down, and they should grow potatoes
to feed the people.
Right?
So, now, I wouldn't say I'm bitter.
I think I'm objective.
It just comes off as being bitter, because
when you're objective about a turd, it doesn't
sound good, right?
I think that these antiquities and stuff don't
mean anything.
No, I don't think they mean anything, but
the governments are busy doing their thing, and
there are certain high-net individuals that make
it a point to go into countries in
the Middle East and raid them for their
antiquities.
They think it means something.
And then there's also this aspect of covering
up past civilizations, like, you know, the Tartars
and things like that, where it seems that
these things shouldn't be talked about.
Or I would invite you to consider that
they think it means nothing, and we can
profit from it right now, like a mobster
does.
They know.
They know it means nothing, also.
Now, I know it sounds very, I don't
know, pick the term, but all this stuff
about these ancient antiquities is nothing more than
romanticism.
They have no use, if it's, you know
what I mean?
You know, if all the museums, all the
masterpieces were burned, and all the antiquities were
destroyed and leveled, and they built up ticky
-tacky houses, I wouldn't spend not even 0
.3 seconds saying, oh, all that stuff is
gone.
No, I get that.
It doesn't profit me anything.
It doesn't matter to me at all.
As a matter of fact, I encourage it.
Why?
That stuff doesn't serve anybody.
It's just somebody else's livelihood.
You know, I mean, what, they're still trading,
who was it, the guy who splashed paint
on paintings.
That was 120 million bucks for his, who
was the guy who just splashed paint on
a canvas.
I had an acquaintance, Dori Ashton, actually I
was a tenant of hers a while back.
She was one of the biggest art critics
in the world, and she had a bunch
of his paintings around, and they're going for
120 million right now.
I mean, I've been in the house where
Andy Warhol and other contemporaries were around, you
know, it was no big deal.
There's a bunch of people, they're degenerates if
you ask me.
I had Marcel Duchamp, some of his studio
equipment, and who the hell is Marcel Duchamp,
right?
Anyway, people don't, you know, so it's like,
screw it.
It's somebody else's, here, you want to go
into what the mindset behind this crap is,
the antiquities and the art?
Hello Kitty.
That Hello Kitty meme that they have in
Asia, it's worth like hundreds of billions, right,
in Asia, or whatever billions are.
It's garbage.
The Mona Lisa and all that stuff is
also, you know, if you ask me, that's,
you know, but it is commerce.
It's a form of, it's a complex attribute,
one of the complex attributes of society, because
when a society rises to, well, achieves a
certain point of, let's say, industry and technology,
they have a surplus of people called artists,
and they produce these works of arts and
these other things, right?
Now, you have to separate that from the
dedications, you know, because when they classify that
under post-immortality, yeah, like an apotheosis type
thing, maybe.
But whenever you have the, you know, you
could look in the anthropological aspect and standard
bullshit, they'll tell you, you know, when a
society reaches a certain level, then they go
into art level, art form, right?
When, you know, a small group of people
can sustain a large group, then that large
group doesn't have to work on sustainability, like
food and clothing.
They can take up other things like being
philosophers, writers, poets, artists, painters, sculptors, jerk-offs,
whatever.
I'm not saying that that's not a good
thing or a bad thing, I'm just stating,
you know, one of the things that we've
seen.
It's an emergent class or an emergent aspect
of society, as you see it.
I mean, even if you read in scripture,
there were classes of musicians, right?
And artisans, so I'm not saying it's a
bad thing, I'm just saying at this point,
it's pretty useless in terms of the value
aspect.
For what I see intrinsically, the only reason
these things have any value is because you've
been raised believing that they do.
Well, there's a sense in which value is
always a matter of perspective, like if people
say that gold suddenly isn't valuable, then it
isn't.
Unless you can show something empirical that says
that gold is valuable.
That's what I'm interested in.
Well, it is because the gods say it
is.
Sure, it becomes that way because when you
reach a terminus, whenever you're dealing with the
gods, you reach a termination point, and it
may seem open or more open sometimes and
more closed than others, depending on what they
want you to know.
If the gods don't want you to know
something, you might as well consider it a
termination, because you're not going to know.
But if they want you to know, and
they want to expand on that with you,
then obviously you get to see more of
why things are.
I think I've given many talks about what
money is.
It's just portable land.
So when you go from one place to
another, you bring what represents the value of
your land.
And the reason why you don't have substance
-backed money anymore, and I've been saying this
for a long time, and I ask people
and they still can't answer, not because I
say so, but because it's subjective.
When you lose substance-based money, what do
you lose?
Also, you lose law.
Now you go under what's called legal system.
Death, that's why I used to tell everyone,
the death to the legal system is species
-backed money.
It could be anything.
It doesn't have to be gold and silver.
It could be labor.
The reason why I used to argue with
these patriot idiots a decade ago that this
country and the world will never have species
-backed money is because then the legal system
goes under, and you have to go back
to law.
And you can't have a law unless the
people are educated in it.
So if you see the legal society falling
apart from the inside out and outside in,
meaning like hanging a million attorneys tomorrow from
lampposts, which is not going to happen, because
people think they're good, is you're not going
to get species-backed money.
Because once species-backed money comes in, you
lose your legal system.
You have to go under law, and you
don't need what's going on.
There'll be no charges and things like that.
I brought this up at a constitutional forum.
These people used to meet every week discussing
the Constitution.
And at one of the meetings, I said,
well, Constitution, U.S. Constitution, you can wipe
your ass with it.
And they all got really upset when I
said that.
And I said, no, not really, see?
Then they relaxed.
And I said, well, you have to crumble
it up really well to soften it, then
wipe your ass with it.
Right?
Sacred document, my ass, it's toilet paper.
And the people know that.
And by the way, anyone wants to, I
have a thing printed in 1952 by the
Freemasons and another one by the Scottish Rite.
Every Freemason needs to know the Constitution and
Declaration of Independence.
And if you idiots think the U.S.
Constitution is valid in any sense for what
you've been told it is, why don't you
look up the Freemasonic Constitution of 1721, which
is about 76, 77 years before it.
If you print out the Freemasonic Constitution and
the U.S. Constitution, hold it up in
the light, it's almost word for word.
There's nothing original about it.
Garbage.
It's not a sacred document.
That's what you've been told.
Yeah, look it up.
It's a Freemasonic, that's why I like Dimitri.
He doesn't know about the core of many
aspects like the people that listen to Greek
speak do, but he understands that it's a
Freemasonic scenario.
I think he blames it too much on
the Freemasons.
I think the Freemasons are idiots, but not
because I read something online and criticized them
because I've run into enough of them.
Well, concerning what we were talking about before
though, I was less on about the antiques
aspect and more about the fact that certain
aspects of civilizations and histories are purposely kept
in the dark.
So when you look at a list of
wars that have taken place in certain time
periods and you try and go and do
research on those wars, it almost feels like
that particular association is fake.
Like there was no real war, but they
went in there to do something else.
Yeah, it is.
Well, you know, the Vietnam War, I listened
to someone that was pre-adolescent in the
60s and his father was a colonel in
the army and told him that, you know,
I want to talk to you about drugs,
son, you know, and what's going to be
happening.
And the child thought it was directed to
him and the colonel was basically saying, we're
going to go fight this war in Asia
about controlling the drug trade.
This was a few years before it went
hot in the news, right, before the Gulf
of Tompkins and all that.
So maybe that's the perspective.
In other words, why are they going into
the Middle East then, right?
That's pretty simple.
Like, you know, they say the U.S.
is after Assad.
What a crock of shit.
I wouldn't have said this in the past,
but I'll say it now.
Most people don't know that the DEA and
the CIA work together and most people don't
know that the DEA sends a lot of
its people to a prison in Damascus, Syria,
even today.
Not today like today, but up to about
a year ago.
In other words, the American agencies are running
a prison where they send people, you know,
for whatever rendition or whatever in Damascus, Syria
currently.
So where's this whole overt bullshit about the
U.S. wants to get rid of Assad
when they're using his own, you know what
I mean?
It's all bullshit, right?
Now, recently, I got an email about, you
know, I pat myself on the back about
Trump and Syria.
Nah.
When does the U.S. government not lie?
When does the French government not lie?
When does the Russian government not lie?
When does the Colombian government not lie?
When does the Chilean government not lie?
When does the Arabian government not lie?
They all lie.
They're not pulling out of anything.
They're just changing the way they're presenting it
to you.
I think I did a sonic a few
months ago about revisiting a map or make
a list, go into scripture of all the
territories that David had conquered or subjugated and
make a map.
And you'll see that Israel went way up
into Syria, east of Damascus, west of Damascus.
They didn't take Damascus, but they were just
all around it, right?
It went all the way to the Nile
and all the way to the Euphrates, pretty
much.
Definitely on the other side of Jordan, right?
The river Jordan.
You had Manasseh and a couple of other
tribes settle in on the other side of
Jordan, right?
Where now is proper.
All this stuff that you see about ISIS
and all that is just to soften up
the area for Israel to come in and
take over.
I know you don't like, people don't like
to hear that, but I'm not making it
up and I'm not taking sides.
You know, it's interesting as the scripture says,
those that bless Israel will be blessed.
Doesn't say you have to take sides though,
does it?
You don't bless without taking sides.
You can't bless somebody.
And then when somebody comes and asks you,
why'd you bless them?
You say, well, I'm not on their side.
I just blessed them.
Sure.
Why not?
No, it doesn't.
Enemies are going to come after you.
Well, blessing is not arist.
It doesn't, it's not constant.
It's just an act like sneezing.
I'm not sure I get that.
It's not a constant thing that you do.
A blessing is a blessing.
Oh, like a one-time thing.
Yeah.
Remember he says, bless me so I can
be, remember when in Genesis, right?
He dressed up like his brother.
It wasn't a constant thing.
It was just, just do this one blessing
for me, right?
Yeah, they have my blessing, but they're all
savages over there.
They're all savages.
Oh, wherever you go, humans are savages.
So the thing is, if you, you know,
anything to get the, the, the ball rolling,
which no one can stop anyway, but you
don't want to be rolled over by it.
You see, I always bring up the thing.
There's a fixed game.
Team A is going to destroy Team B.
Which one do you want to join?
Well, obviously, you know, it's rigged.
Team A, I'm not going to join the
losing side.
And it has nothing to do with morals
and ethics.
But if you bring in morals and ethics,
the, the one that sets morals and ethics
for the universe is the one that's going
to be winning and destroying the other side.
So there's another rule that you can follow.
It's morally and ethically correct to be on
the winning team for that reason.
And it's also for a plain rational reason,
you want to be on the winning team
because you don't want to suffer the loss,
the consequences of what comes along with losing.
And we know, I think I'm the only
one that's expressed the verses in Isaiah that
quote unquote, Israel will never be viewed as
being righteous in any capacity until they run
out of judges.
It's in the first chapter of Isaiah, which
is prime ministers.
I mean, the whole scripture is pretty detailed.
I mean, you can convey information by not
saying something or by saying something, right?
Directly, you know, sometimes by, by omission.
You can focus on a point as well.
I will return to your former judges and
then you will be known as a righteous
city.
You meaning like after or righteous people.
So but I would suggest that back to
it's wintertime.
So you're going to see a lot of
movement, right?
That's what happens in the winter, international movement
or traveling and you don't do things that
you're agriculturally demanding, like sowing and growing and
harvest.
So there's a lot of change in winter,
you do things that normally don't happen in
winter.
So you're going to see Israel starting to
get extremely aggressive.
Of course, it's none of it's going to
be shown in a good light.
Also, you're going to start to see the,
you know, the powers that be, especially the
United Satanic America is taking a second fiddle
to other powers.
And the current leadership is going to be
was worse than the previous and the next
leadership is going to be over, you know,
the the dog and pony show or the
dog, what is it called the donkey and
elephant show.
It's already said, you know, there is something
I put up on Chatterwild back the New
Order of Barbarians 50 years ago, the deindustrialization
and dumbing up of this country was already
set and the homosexual agenda, the sodomites and
lesbians and the food poisoning and all that
was already set 50 years ago.
The political stuff that everyone sees is just
a show.
Those are not the leaders.
Those are the administrators for the leaders.
We don't know who they are.
Someone was asking me, Greek, unless you told
me who the powers are, I don't believe
that.
And I was like, there's an Ocelli type
character.
And I said, well, OK, there's 400 Navy
SEALs.
Give me all the names and where they
are right now.
Can you do that?
Right.
No.
Why not?
I don't believe the Navy SEALs exist unless
you tell me all their names and where
they are right now.
But we know they're Navy SEALs.
We see them on TV.
Yeah.
But you see how stupid, you know, there's
3500 FBI, you know, G20 FBI agents.
Give me all their names and where they
are right now.
Can you do it?
Well, this group that I'm talking about that
are the leaders of the world are extremely
secret.
So.
You see, it's very simple.
I mean, they were able to blow up
450 kilotons or 350 kiloton underground nukes in
broad daylight for the whole world to see
in lower Manhattan.
And it's still, you know, well, we don't
know what happened.
We need to find out what happened.
And obviously, you know, it's not fair to
say it because this is not.
But the information is there.
It's right in front of everyone if they
want to delve in.
You know, I had a retired military person
once said to me, I spent over a
thousand hours researching 9-11 never did know
that it's not nuclear.
I'm like, you could spend 10,000 hours,
10,000 hours researching on the Internet.
You're not going to find unless your mindset
is correct.
Remember, you're living in a society where evidence
doesn't matter.
At all.
I think I told you about the college
professor who said that we went to the
moon and I don't know who he is.
But even if the astronauts went on TV
and said it never happened, I still believe
they went to the moon.
So we're talking about deep psychosis here, too.
I think getting a firm grip on prophecy
is a very good way to answer a
lot of questions regarding history, where things are
going, how things are, and looking at it
from the God's perspective.
You know, Scripture was written to you.
It's not for you or about you.
It's about the gods.
It's usually a discussion amongst the gods.
But it was done in a way, Scripture,
so that it would be given to man
for man to have for as their own.
So, you know, in other words, it's written
about you and it's written to you, but
it's not for you.
Because here's the interesting aspect.
I tell a lot of people, and I
find this to be true still with most
people, I say, don't even bother reading Scripture,
because when you start reading it, you're going
to notice that the actual text has an
aversion for stupid people.
Most people say, I don't understand it.
And they say, well, that's your interpretation.
It can't be known.
Well, that means if it can't be known,
the gods work in futility.
No, it's just that gods don't like stupid
people.
That's the first thing you notice when you
read Scripture, try to comprehend it.
And if you read Scripture and don't get
it, guess what?
You're stupid.
It's not my thing.
Maybe you were born that way.
Maybe you were raised that way.
But just move on.
Pick up something else.
It's not for you.
That's the harsh reality, you know.
And stupid, I'm using in a very loose
sense.
You know, you're a moron or whatever, if
you don't get Scripture.
And I don't mean picking it up once
and reading the King James or whatever.
But you don't get that there's something different
there.
And the text itself has an aversion for
morons.
It's like self-filtering, you know what I
mean?
No, I get it.
I know.
Yeah, if you want to hear shit, it's
off the cuff.
You listen to Greek speak, right?
I think most of us are used to
it by now.
Yeah, but no one else is saying that
if you don't get Scripture, you're stupid.
And the reason why...
Yeah, it's mean.
Yeah, because it was set up that way.
It has an aversion for stupid people and
ignorant people.
And I don't mean smart in the way
that people decide what is smart and what
is stupid.
Look, even
the people that put the King James and
the religions, you know, Judaism and modern Judaism
and Christianity are pretty freaking stupid.
How many Christians do you have running around
and saying, well, we have to create some
order and some accuracy.
Why do we have a J-E-S
-U-S when it's when the Joshua, if
we're going to use the letter J, right,
we use it for Joshua.
And that's exactly the same name as the
Christ.
So why isn't the Christ called Joshua?
If we have to use the letter J,
right?
Isn't that more accurate?
What's the difference in name between Yahshua HaMashiach,
the Christ, and Yahshua, what I call the
prophet or a judge or, right, or a
cohort of Moses.
What's the difference between the book of Joshua
and the character that's mentioned in the New
Testament?
What's the difference?
There's none.
Do you see how easy it is if
you have to use the letter J?
It's Joshua.
Let's start there.
I mean, is that so?
Because they're not talking about anything biblical.
It's Christian, right?
The same with the Jews or the Muslims
or the Hindus or the whatever.
Just large corporations.
It's Gustav Le Bon mindset.
What you do is you make something so
simple so the masses can adhere to it
and you've simplified it so much that it's
now distorted and no longer resembles its original
form.
Definitely being steered.
Yeah, I mean, they condemn themselves.
I mean, Scripture talks about Yeah, you put
the curses on themselves.
Look, you can talk to anyone.
Is it so unreasonable to call him Joshua
instead of J-E-S-U-S?
Right.
I mean, it's obviously like just pissing on
you.
They're just shitting all over you and you
love it.
I mean, you meaning, you know, the people
of the planet.
I mean, that's like the first thing that
you can introduce as a not even a
salient point, but just as a point that
should be considered to start putting it in
order, at least if you have to use
certain terms.
But it's not going to happen.
You see, many times I've said this system,
this society, this culture, these traditions cannot be
fixed.
They have to be flushed away, destroyed, cleared.
What do you call it?
Deleted.
There's nothing to fix.
The people cannot be fixed.
They have to be deleted.
And I mean physically as well.
So, not because I say so, Scripture tells
you that as well.
It's not, it's not a, you know, here's
the interesting part though, when you consider the
natural world, you know, you want to use
it in parentheses or whatever you mean by
the natural world.
You want to pick highland forests, low valleys,
deserts, tropical, you know, desert, any, what's called
natural environment, and go look up a doco,
a documentary or whatever.
It's one animal eating the other, isn't it?
Right?
Or even plants eating animals, and animals eating
plants, you know?
So, get your mind wrapped around that this
idea of carnage, carnage, you know, or meat
being handled and torn apart or discarded or
killed or whatever, is the way of the
earth.
It's the way things are here.
And it's going to carry through on to
the end, right?
Until it no longer is.
Yeah, the older wars were more correct.
Well, if you don't like those people because
they could bring evil, let's go kill them
all.
Alright?
That's more honest than the bullshit everyone here
is now.
Where you're still being killed off, you're just
being poisoned slowly or whatever because it's just
not time yet.
Just the way that it is.
The earth is a violent place.
I have an unrelated question.
I think you've talked about IQ before, as
far as it being something suspect.
It is and it isn't.
It's just like university, you know, if you
don't have it, right?
PhD, you're not going to be considered at
the top of your field.
By the way, have you taken an IQ
test or anything?
Years ago.
It was probably just...
What did you get?
Do you remember?
As a 16 year old or whatever, I
think I had 115.
But I don't know if that's reliable.
I think I got a 156 or something.
You're so smart.
Yeah, right?
No, I'm not.
But anyway, I shouldn't even be sad.
It's embarrassing to say that.
But go ahead, regarding IQ.
No, I don't understand it very well.
It's something that's...
I mean, there's various levels of understanding of
any topic where you have the sort of
scholarly or the learned perspective for people who
actually develop these propositions or work in the
field.
And then you have the sort of pop
culture understanding.
And IQ is obviously something that's well-existent
within the pop culture sphere.
Like, this is just something that you have
to be smart.
If you have a lot of points, you're
smart.
So I don't know what it is per
se.
But my understanding is that within the social
sciences, they would define intelligence as being sort
of like how a computer works, like the
aggregate of cognitive processing power that your brain
has and then memory capacity.
Right, because it's based on timing also.
Right?
You're timed.
But that's okay.
I don't think that...
let's go back to the cognitive...
about the headhunters, right?
It depends on the culture.
You know, you might be familiar with countries
in the African continent.
The majority of the people that work the
land and sustain themselves from the land are
far more intelligent than a PhD in technocracy
or technical whatever in a Western country, in
a general sense.
But one would flunk in...
you know, if you interchange them or exchange
them, they would flunk in their corresponding...
in their new environments, right?
They would be viewed as total failures.
The Bushmen would be a failure in the
IQ test.
And the guy who has the 156 IQ
would be a total failure in the Bush,
you know, PhD or whatever.
But is there something to be said for
the fact that perhaps in the long run
you could teach the PhD guy to be
successful in the Bush, whereas the Bushmen might
never, you know, wrap his finger around the
type of abstract thought that the PhD guy
uses for his profession?
Right.
Because another way to use the abstract thought
is, if it's not lawful or grounded in
anything, which it's not, it's fallacial.
It's fallacy.
It's bullshit.
If you ask the...
even just a simple colloquial Bushman, what came
first, the chicken or the egg?
I mean, that's not...
never pondered as something like a Westerner would
be, you know?
Oh yeah, that's a...
right?
You'd be like, what kind of stupid shit
is that?
Addressing it is stupid.
So, you know the old one, a rooster
lays on the ridge of a roof and
lays an egg.
Which side of the roof does it roll
off of?
Yeah, roosters don't lay eggs, yeah.
Well, hold on.
One thing that they do know, the leaders,
is that you have too much time on
your hands.
Have you ever heard that expression?
So they have to fill it up and
they have to keep you running.
Which is okay, I mean, because they've...
the moral, ethical and lawful abandonment of modern
society, it doesn't matter what country you're in,
but especially if you're in a country where
you have too much time on your hands,
you're going to have to fill it up.
Especially the ones that have grid systems, you
know, and educational institutions and medical institutions and
legal institutions.
They've abandoned all the things that are important
that they still have access to.
Like, take the western society.
Any human in a western society, even machine,
has access to biblical stuff, and how to
put it right.
Has access to law, has access to proper
science.
But none of them want to use it,
or refer to it, or use it as
a basis.
You know, to give an example, that's why
when you go online and you look at
NASA, the National Aeronautics Agency, everything they've been
putting out for the past decade is CG.
You get no more photographs from telescopes, no
more photographs of anything.
It's all computer generated, all of it.
And people are still like, wow, look at
that, Mars, oh, wow, look at that, this.
It's fake.
All of it.
So, you might say, well, they don't have
access to it because they're given all fake
stuff.
Yeah, but who's raising their hand in class
saying, why are we seeing fake images?
You know, very simple.
It's twisted and distorted.
And the spiritual beings that have allowed this
and inspired the leaders to be so twisted
and distorted, they have an IQ of two
million.
The only thing to do is wait until
they're gone.
Displaced.
Sure.
Well, actually, there's only one measurement of intelligence
being IQ, and then it's expressed through different
talents and temperaments.
Well, depending on the social order and the
culture, again, like Jack Fresco's, you know, if
you live in a society of headhunters, to
have a high IQ there, you have to
be proficient in shrunken heads, right?
So, which culture are you speaking on?
In certain cultures, you're not considered to be
intelligent unless you know a lot about the
spiritual world, which in this culture would be
considered paranormal and not true.
It's bunk.
You know, but getting away from the cultural
aspect, there is an objectivity that we can
bring to bear on analyzing what is intelligent
and what is not.
Like, if you pose a problem, can you
solve it?
If you can solve it, then by that
particular metric, you're intelligent.
Like, if you play the piano really well,
it doesn't matter what country you go to,
you're still an intelligent piano player.
If you play it too well, they'll lock
you up in an insane asylum.
So, you have to play it much better
than what's considered to be good, but not
too well, because then you'll be considered a
nutcase.
Unless you fit some purpose or usefulness at
the time.
Sure.
Remember, it's very, very twisted.
So, yes.
In other words, you could have
let's give another example.
You've got 10 people, equally talented, you know,
of course, with a variation of a small
bit, but equally talented, and one will be
extremely successful financially, culturally, or whatever, the other
one will be homeless.
So, the meritocracy falls apart there, right?
Then it becomes, you know, is it fate,
you know, or kismet, like they say in
Islam, or is it, right, who you know,
who you blow, your family, right place, the
right time, there's too many variables to be
considered.
I've visited insane asylums in the past, as
a guest, to get more detail, I was
not an inmate, and I mean, because I
am anyone on this planet is an inmate,
but it is an insane asylum, but the
ones that are in general quarters or general
area all seem very normal within the first
few minutes, right, you know.
And then essentially you engage them and you
see that there's something really wrong with them
on a general level, but specifically many of
the people that are considered to be institutionalized
or whatever are quite intelligent and can be
beneficial, you know, used in some trade or
some science or whatever.
So, again, how do they end up there?
Why do they end up there?
I mean, you understand the story, whether it's
folklore or not, it's written in the story,
Victor Schauberger was making all these advances with
energy, water, and materials, and the powers that
be, the Schusswaffel, the SS, didn't like his
advances because he was shaming the academics with
the classical training, so they decided to take
him to a meeting, they said, and the
meeting was actually putting him into an insane
asylum, you know, they just locked him up,
right, for a year or something.
It's in his bio.
It's a very, very unsure subject.
IQ, intelligence, success, I'm bringing the element of,
you know, success, you know, why are there,
you know, you can have equally intelligent people,
I mean, here's another thing, have you ever
met any captains of industry, like I haven't
met like Bezos of Amazon or Bill Gates,
but I've met people on their level, and
they're idiots, right?
You know, you're an idiot, not in a
sense, actually an idiot, actually in the definition
of the word, right?
You know, you keep saying that a lot,
but anybody who works in psychology would claim
that those definitions are archaic at this point.
Okay, but psychologists are the witch doctors, you
know, there's no science behind that, they're a
wicked group of people, and they have a
propensity of destroying their children and the people
around them as well, you know.
Using that art.
Like, was it Golden, Samuel Golden, or Golden
Meier, or the film, anyone who wants to
see a psychiatrist should have their head examined,
right?
They're pretty sick, just like the people in
the medical industry and the legal industry.
Religious industry are pretty sick.
Right?
Sure.
A lot of sickness going around.
But no, the intelligence thing is hard to
figure out, because other than IQ, you just
have to observe how people's minds work and
infer things from their choices and the way
that they act to see how smart you
would, you know, rate them.
But it's hard to find an objective metric,
especially when you have different types of aptitude
that manifest in different areas, but don't necessarily
triangulate into one thing that you can say,
well, this person is smart overall.
They're just good at different things.
And not so good at other things.
Yeah, you could take, well, if you want
to, it's really difficult to keep anything sanitized
and secular.
You know, the moment you omit the spiritual
realm, you fall flat on your face and
the science or the understanding of the subject
becomes paper thin.
Right?
Okay.
There's a spiritual influence behind all this stuff.
Yeah, but I mean, a lot of the
ancient Greeks discarded their mythology completely and still
came up with intriguing things.
I mean, they don't last in the long
run, but it's good conversation and it's, you
know, you can take something from it.
Well, you know, you've heard like of Enochian
magic, which has nothing to do with Enoch
or whatever.
You know, they just branded themselves with that.
But that was along the thought form that
if you study, especially Pythagoras, right, who was
trained in Babylon and was involved in a
lot of mystic occult stuff, right?
The moment you go back and look at
philosophical sciences and science and philosophy, however you
want to interchange it, there is no separation
in the inner group between them and occulted
knowledge dealing with spiritual stuff.
Like, give you an example, like Aleister Crowley,
on one aspect, you know, he gets the
reputation that he has, but on the other
aspect, he was pursuing scientific endeavors, right?
He was too mixed up in the spy
world and the political world and other things
like that.
But when he was doing evocations of Athena
and Apollo and that creature, the lamb, you
know, and all these demons and all that,
that was a science, right?
In other words, that was dealing with that
world as being as anything real, you know,
as real as anything else, right?
If you look at the history of the
jet propulsion, Jack Whiteside Parsons and Scientology and
all that other stuff, all of it is
occult, right?
You could look at the Native Americans and
the Skinwalkers, right?
There's ritual, it's real, you know, the werewolf
or the werewolf, you know, people transforming into,
you know, shapeshifting into animals or other things
like that is real, right?
But there's no place for that in science.
So, would a Skinwalker, someone who's done the
occult rites of passage, which are pretty horrible,
which was known all over the world, even
since Babylonian times, to transform into another creature
with those attributes, and it really happens, can
modern day science or even then explain it?
No.
You just knew that if you did this,
you did that.
It was a ritual, just like today, science
is a ritual, just like back then.
When you get to a certain level, you
don't understand it anymore, you just know if
you do this, this happens.
So, that's the ultimate intelligence at this point,
when you realize the limitations, is how well
can you do this to get that, right?
Well, as far as being practical, yes, because
you want a result.
So, I guess in the sort of power
game, yeah, the person who does this to
get that the best way ends up on
top and wins.
But he's not necessarily...
Not necessarily.
Strategically, he's smarter, but he can still be
an idiot.
But you win what?
See, ultimately, when you have a physical body,
it's about territory, right?
Like, give me an example, like technology is
nothing more than more elaborate tools, right?
That's all it is, right?
What's a cell phone, you know?
What's the difference between a cell phone and
a pay phone once you're using it?
Nothing, really.
Then you have a smartphone, which is a
combination of a computer and a phone.
So, it gets more and more, you know,
it's a tool, right?
It's basically a tool.
The spiritual world is also a tool.
But when you get to the spiritual world
and you're given certain instructions, if you do
this, you get that.
Well, how many questions do you want to
ask in between, right?
If someone wants to learn how to be
a shapeshifter, you have to kill someone that's
near and dear to you and give up
something that's very precious to you, right?
Then you have to do cannibalistic acts, and
then you have to make things out of
the body, and then you have to choose
what animal you want to be at certain
times, and then eventually you end up having
that power, right?
So, if you start asking questions in between
all those processes that I just brought up,
what kind of an answer are you going
to get?
None.
They're going to say, well, if you really
want to be a shapeshifter, you have to
bring us your child or your parent or
your wife or your husband and kill them,
and then engage in cannibalism, necrophilia, right?
And then you have to make all these
things out of what's left of the body.
And if you ask why, well, they're going
to just basically tell you there is no
why.
You either do it or you don't, right?
You see, when you get to that crazy
and the reason I'm bringing that up
as an example is because you're going to
see a resurgence of this stuff happening.
I mean, if you go into the Native
American and African continent, I mean, they see
more of it happening than it ever has
before, because especially now the white industrialists are
like, oh, yeah, you could really do that?
All right, here's a plane ticket and a
place, so why don't you come and show
us, right?
Now, look, you're going to have a bunch
of crazy white boys doing it, right?
So if you start asking in between, why
do I have to kill someone?
Why do I have to eat their spleen?
Why do I have to wear this animal
skin?
There's no answer for that.
That's just how it's done, right?
Like, for example, when you look in scripture,
you know, my people will do these things.
Well, why?
Well, you ever heard of the game Simon
Says, right?
You just do it, you know.
What's his name?
Solomon asked questions, like he wanted to know
stuff, and they said, okay, we'll let you
know how to know stuff.
Like, we might not tell you everything directly,
but we'll give you the means to access
what you need to know.
Right.
But you have to be specific.
Go back and study that.
Like, for example, I've heard people say, well,
when you go to court, don't say anything
or put words in my mouth, put words
in your mouth, right?
Well, I've heard people going to court say,
I'm not going to say anything.
They yell it up in jail, and they
don't say anything, right?
Because if the scripture is misunderstood, when they
go back and read it, it says, if
you are brought to court on my sake
regarding me, I'll put the words in.
But if you have a traffic ticket and
don't say anything or whatever issue, you better
speak up, you see?
So there's a little bit of this and
a little bit of that, right?
Solomon wanted to know, if you look very
closely, he wanted wisdom because he wanted to
know how to approach the deity directly, right?
Because he knows it's about knowledge and not
about faith, right?
It's not about faith going to the gods.
It's about the faith, and the faith is,
you know, how to do the right thing.
Again, it goes back to knowledge.
That's the faith, by the way.
The only thing that I find sort of
incongruent with that, even though it makes sense,
is that nowhere in Kings or Chronicles or
anywhere, maybe I haven't read songs of Solomon
or Lamentations well enough, but I don't really
find that Solomon ever uses his wisdom to
access the main deity in any kind of
way.
Like, he's shown being wise.
Yeah, in the Chronicles it doesn't, but in
scripture it's written, I want to know how
to go in and out.
Yeah, but I mean, apart from that, he
says that one thing.
Why he wants wisdom.
Yeah, but then show me the examples.
Well, the examples are very simple.
He was sequestered to live a material life
like everyone else.
He wasn't translated into another realm.
He wanted to do the best he can
to access that realm from this realm.
Right, and we don't see displays of that.
Like, we see displays of his wisdom in
a kingly, administrative sense.
Like when he judged between the two women
and the child, or when he explained complicated
things to the Queen of Sheba, even though
details are not given.
It's just said, look at these things that
he did.
He's a smart guy.
How do you access the main god?
I don't see him doing that.
Well, no, yeah, what he did also was
he negotiated a position that gave him the
upper hand with all the countries and nations
around him to maintain tribute.
But it had nothing to do with the
main god.
No, because he was sequestered to living a
mortal, material life.
Yeah, but you can still...
I thought it was to access him, to
go in and out.
So show me the going in and out.
I don't see establishing a world empire as
going in and out.
Essentially, that's an interesting thing.
You could say it's slighted in a way
because who is really given the right to
do that?
It's the high priest, right?
And Solomon is not a high priest.
So it's a moot point.
Again, futility.
Like, if the temple were there and they
asked you what to do, what you would
like, and you'd like I'd like wisdom so
I could know how to go in and
out, meaning of the highest point in the
temple, that's kind of a moot point, isn't
it?
Because you're not a high priest, so why
would you ask that, right?
But it's not denying himself.
No, it's not.
I wouldn't say that it was directly, but
indirectly, he's not a high priest.
The high priest was the only one that
had the authority to do that on the
time of the Day of Atonement.
But then he can't be talking about that
because it's given to him.
Why not?
Wouldn't you, if you had a strong desire
and love for the Father, and His temple
and His set-apart place was here, and
you knew that it was, if it was
knowledge-based, wouldn't you want the knowledge on
how to enter that place?
To be closest?
Without dying?
That would be the ultimate thing, right?
Right, yeah, but let's be real, as far
as just going into the temple and performing.
I think he was pretty real.
He was pretty real about it.
I think the dedication that his father had
towards Yahweh was also somehow realized by him.
Maybe that's why he said it.
But we can't be talking about the physical
going into the temple, because that was already
laid out in Leviticus, how it worked.
That was not a secret, what the priest
did.
We know what the priest did.
Obviously Solomon knows what the priest did.
He built the temple.
He already knows what's there.
Sure, but his father was able to grab
priestly garments that you can communicate directly with,
that he allegedly was not of the class,
but he did it anyway.
Does it say you can't touch the garments?
I don't remember.
No, he accessed garments, the vestments and things.
Yeah, but you can touch the garments.
No, no, he actually placed them, he wore
them.
Okay, you can't wear them?
I wouldn't say you should, no.
Oh, come on, you can wear them, though.
You just can't go into the space.
Of course you can wear them.
Well, he did.
And he asked, should I go against the
Philistines?
And he's like, no, don't go against the
Philistines.
And the other place is, yes, go against
the Philistines.
Yeah, I don't know if that's exclusive to
the priest.
The priest was to wear the vestment, the
breastplate, the shoulder.
You can put on a police uniform, it's
not illegal, but you can't go out and
pretend to be a police officer.
That's a different thing.
Actually, what's interesting is the actual police are
pretending to be police, but anyway, that's a
whole other discussion.
Right.
But for me, it's the Solomon thing that's
interesting because there's something about him in his
situation that's being obscured, or at least it's
not self-evident.
Because he asks for wisdom for a particular
thing, but he's never shown displaying wisdom in
the going-ins and the coming-outs of
anything.
He's only shown wise as a king.
What's chronicled in Scripture, no, we don't see
him doing any kind of a liturgy or
any kind of a let's say, presence in
the presence.
We actually don't have a lot of, I'm
sure it exists, but Scripture doesn't give us
a lot about Solomon.
I mean, as much as you think, here
we have the wisest man that ever lived,
and there's what, maybe a dozen verses?
If that?
Yeah.
Two chapters maybe, a chapter and a half?
Here and there?
And there's a couple other mentions, and that's
it?
And then you have the writings, if you
want to attribute Koelath to Solomon, which is
arguable, you know, Ecclesiastes or Proverbs, you can
attribute that to him.
There's speculation on that as well, the authorship,
let's say.
But directly on his works as a chronicle,
memorialized in Scripture, there's very little that we
know about him.
You know, his actual doings, for what his
request was based on.
Right.
Yeah, so, I think prophecy is the way
to go, timekeeping is the way to go.
What?
No, everything is the way to go.
What do you mean?
Well, yes, the archaeology is a tough nut,
you know, the history, the actual, what do
you call it when you have physical history?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, those are probably in some rich guy's
collection somewhere.
Oh yeah, it's just not for you to
know.
Like, here's an example.
Whether you, you know, every field you study,
you'll notice that what the institution holds as
being true is contrary to what's in their,
memorialized in their field of study.
Right?
So, you don't have to, what I'm trying
to say here is you don't have to
go very far, even now, even though most
of it has not been overtly brought out,
to find the truth on any matter.
Right?
Like, if you want to talk about health,
guess what?
You know what it's about?
Hygiene.
And proper food and good water, right?
Hygiene, again, clean.
Right?
Think about it.
You know, you want to talk about law?
Well, it's law, not legal.
There's not an attorney in the world that
knows or practices law properly as it's written.
Because once they begin to do that, they
lose their privilege to do that, and they're
fired.
Every time.
They're all a bunch of liars.
There's not a priest, a pastor, or a
minister, or whatever, that knows scripture.
Because the moment they do find out, there's
no way they can do that, unless they're
completely evil.
Which, I would say a good percentage are.
It doesn't mean they know scripture anyway.
So, I mean, you go on and on
and on and on.
If you listen to Eric Dollard's recent ravings,
the grid, especially in the US, is being
dismantled.
Well, not being dismantled, but it's being altered
so it's subject to an EMP attack, right?
So they're going to a Y connection wiring
on the transformer ground versus a delta.
Yeah.
Which means that if you, you know, the
ground goes to the transformer, so if you
lean on something metallic, and there's a big
short somewhere, like a power line down, you're
going to receive that voltage.
Right?
It'll still filter through.
Most of it will filter through your local
transformer, but you could die.
There are cows, farmers that have cows that
are reporting the cows are falling down near
transformer lines right now.
So, as far as I notice, the skies
are still being sprayed.
These are all global agendas.
So, my point here is, don't focus on
the national agendas, focus on the global agendas.
Because the instead of, or antichrist is a
global thing, not a national thing, right?
But it has to emerge from the nation
of Israel.
They are to provide the antichrist, right?
That's why beware of those that say that
are Judean, but are not.
Not, you know, the King James says Jews,
but are not, right?
Isn't that talking about the Samaritans though?
I would suggest that the antichrist is of
Assyrian descent, but he's going to claim to
be of Judean extraction.
So, it gets complicated, right?
I don't think that, you know, I was
pondering this, I think last week when we
were going to do a Sonic, it didn't
happen, was putting together the pieces and just
starting to discuss how when you read End
Times scenarios, that most of them are not
going to be known to the public, or
by going on the internet, or whatever.
You know, the specifics.
It'll be a secret, it'll be very confusing.
Like, the people will not know who the
antichrist is, even till the end.
They're going to fall for it, right?
The Assyrian would have a mindset, wouldn't he?
Well, he's of that extraction, he's going to
have a Judean mindset.
Because he goes to the Judean God.
Like, if you met a person from Pakistan,
very distinct, when you meet him, you know,
the language, the mannerisms and stuff, wouldn't this
fellow also display similar He might.
But he could be raised in Judea.
He could be raised in Israel.
There are Assyrians living in Judea, just like
if you were raised in a society of
headhunters, you would act like one.
But again, knowing prophecy, what's interesting, it's winter,
the middle of winter right now, just past
it, or the other side of the world
is in summer, but it doesn't, these teachings
don't go by the other side of the
world.
So, this side of the world, it's middle
of winter, I would suggest that by the
time we get towards springtime, you're going to
see a little bit more of what I've
been talking about, meaning the western world playing
second fiddle, you know, and more of an
emergence of a sense of drastic change leading
to cooperation in the Middle East, which it's
not time yet, it won't be until around
2025 that you'll have that in place, the
full cooperation.
But those changes will still be there.
I mean, the changes will be more evident
as we get into this spring, you know.
Watch Jordan.
You know, people watch Syria, you know, don't
forget about Syria.
Syria is done.
Yeah.
Watch Turkey, watch Greece.
You know, what's been popping up a lot
on what they call the news is the
settlement, beyond negotiation and complete settlement of a
pipeline between Greece, Cyprus and Israel.
Right?
A pipeline is not just a pipe or
a tube underground or under the sea.
It requires a lot of maintenance and financial
backing, scientific backing, right?
It's like a subculture, right, that's going to
be developed, which always existed.
I mean, if you've ever, if you know
people that live in Israel, they do appreciate
Greek culture.
Right?
If you're like the Elvis of Greek music,
you go and you do a lot of
concerts in Israel, even though you're singing in
Greek.
It's just an interesting Hellenistic bond that's remained
for a long time.
There's a pretty large quote-unquote Judean or
quote-unquote Jewish community that still lives in
Greece.
It's over 2,000 years old.
You know, kind of protected, you know.
But anyway, you could say that about any
place.
But my point here is that forget about
Syria, watch Lebanon, watch Turkey, Greece, Cyprus, watch
Jordan, watch Iraq, but don't forget about Syria
completely because remember, the newest Syria is going
to take land from Syria and Turkey.
So, there'll still be an autonomous region in
Syria, of course, what's known as Damascus.
But watch Jordan.
That little short guy there, the king in
Jordan, that little guy, who the Americans got
a leash around because they showed him, you
know, they trained him as a helicopter pilot,
you know.
And he likes his Harley Davidson or whatever.
He's got to go.
Not because I say so, it's because scripture
says so.
So.
And Jordan's going to be broken up.
Maybe not next month, maybe not next year,
but watch for it.
I would suggest it's going to be an
extremely fast maneuver.
He'll either perish or he'll be in exile.
But he won't, that kingdom will no longer
be as it is in the near future.
So.
Lebanon and its history as it is right
now, it's going to be part of Israel.
Territorially.
Not as you know, it won't be Israel
proper, but territorially run by them.
As parts of Syria will be.
More of the western side of Damascus.
That's why when I saw the pullout of
American said they're going to pull their troops
out.
That's total rubbish.
Wherever there's underhanded business, the Americans are there.
You know, if there's rape pillaging and thievery
drugs and whatever, the Americans are not going
to leave.
But it's interesting how they put that in
the mindset, you know, publicly.
Yes.
You have what they call 2019 on the
hopes work schedule.
Isn't that the year that Blade Runner was
supposed to be?
Yes.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So where are the flying cars and all
this stuff, right?
I'm not going to get anything like that.
So they're probably going to make, you know,
remember how cell phones were getting real small?
You know, and then the smartphone came out
and it got really big again.
I think they're going to have to make
those smartphones really small so you can put
them up your butt.
Yeah.
That's your technology.
So yeah.
I think Back to the Future was last
year or something.
The year before.
Yeah.
And when he goes way into the future,
meaning when he goes forward into the future,
yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
The World's Fair in the 1930s they said
by the 1990s you'll be, you know, on
the moon and all this flying highways in
the skies and what, 2001?
A space odyssey, right?
Remember the Hilton?
Out in outer space?
So.
2015.
Anywho, just one last thing on this social
science IQ stuff.
In general, I guess the purpose of science
is to uncover and rationalize how the natural
world works.
But as you've mentioned before with a few
things, psychology and medicine don't really do that.
And the closer that I look at them,
the more it seems as if these are
more like engineering fields than anything else because
the aim of psychology and medicine seems to
be more to build something or to construct
something that is, you know, a human being
that works a certain way.
And even if you sit through a psychologist
session, they'll tell you that their job is
to help you get better.
And get better has really nothing to do
with science.
So they're kind of already saying that they
have a constructionist viewpoint and not a dispassionate
one.
Well, the ultimate society from the goddess religion
is to have male with male union, female
with female union, and they procreate hermaphroditic or
asexual creatures.
But this is a joke.
Right?
It's not possible.
What I just said is the agenda.
What they do is just a matter of
the agenda has to happen over a certain
amount of time and they just take up
your time.
They're just idiots.
I mean, Freud visited the US for the
first time, I think it was the late
20s, early 30s or 30s.
And he was quoted by the press and
his colleagues more than once that he said,
we're bringing the plague to America now.
Meaning the plague, meaning psychiatry.
What's the plague?
It's disease, right?
It's death.
Again, what they say they do to the
people and what they say they do memorialized
in their own stuff is very different.
Look at the legal society.
Right?
In America, for example, they say the Supreme
Court is the highest court.
Well, yeah, it's written in some places.
But the workings of the Supreme Court is
not a court of record.
It's an appellate court.
Right?
So the highest court of record is the
oldest court of record which would probably be
in Pennsylvania or New York somewhere.
But that's completely demonic at this point because
what's demonic about it is most people don't
understand that slavery is a voluntary concept.
If you went throughout history and asked a
slave how he got there, he would tell
you exactly how he got there, and it
was usually by consent of some sort.
Even though it was not favorable.
It was because they were too poor or
there was a form of indenture they had
to do, but they knew why they were
there.
Right now, most people don't know that their
property, through the birth certificate and through their
other contracts that they do.
And by description, they don't know that they're
slaves.
That's why it's demonic.
Right?
Yeah, but you had people that were taken
into slavery through war.
Right, but they again, they were given the
choice.
You either die or you become a slave.
And it may not be vocalized, but if
you're taken as a slave and you try
to escape, you die.
Right?
Yeah, but come on, it's not voluntary.
Sure it is.
You don't choose between dying or slavery.
Sure you do.
You're just psychologically not taught that anymore.
When somebody stands over you with a sword
about to chop your head off, that's not
a bad thing.
That's not a bad way to die.
If your head is chopped off, you've got
about 20 seconds of consciousness after that.
That's a lot.
Yeah, it can seem like an hour.
You won't feel anything, or too much.
Yeah.
It'll just feel like a burn.
Yeah, sure.
It's better than 20 years in whatever.
Look, biological and suicidal are the most successful
way to wage war is biological.
Poisoning the wells, spreading disease on the enemy,
and then suicidal army, or whatever.
The ones that don't are willing to give
up their lives.
But it has to be tactical and strategic.
It can't be just go get slaughtered like
the Americans do.
They love having a body count.
They don't care who it is.
Or the English do that also.
They don't care if it's their side or
for their god.
I'm not talking about the god they talk
about, but behind the scenes.
Right.
The Japanese used human driven torpedoes.
A lot of the American ships during World
War II that were sunk, and the captains
were taken for court-martial because of incapable
or incompetence.
There was nothing they could do because the
torpedoes that were sent towards those American aircraft
carriers, or battleships, or frigates, or whatever, were
human powered.
There was a little guy, a little Jap
in there, sitting in a pronated position, laying
on his stomach.
A little nip.
Nip is another term for them.
He was laying on his stomach.
They picked the smallest guy.
And he guided the torpedo.
So when the ocean currents he would adjust
and speed up and slam it into it.
There was nothing he could do.
When you have a human guided...
Right now they don't need human guided.
They have drones with cameras on them.
I had a conversation once with the first
missile with a video camera on it.
It was used in Vietnam.
I had a conversation with the guy who
actually piloted the missile.
He was in an airplane.
It had a camera.
It was very grainy.
It was to blow up a bridge in
Vietnam during the Vietnam War.
He had a joystick and the whole thing.
It wasn't very accurate.
When the camera showed that the missile was
slightly off target and he tried to correct
for it, it was very easy to over
correct and put it off course.
But it did hit the bridge and he
steered it in with a video camera.
It was very grainy.
So right now you don't need suicide armies.
Because they have drones and robots to do
it.
Isn't the army recruiting young people that are
good at video games for that?
It's been known for a while.
They could steer the missiles in right now.
What's the difference?
In other words, there is a sentient intelligence
behind the weapon that is the only way
to be effective in war.
Not dumb bombs where they carpet bomb everything.
They have everyone still believing the atomic bombs
had an effect in World War II.
Douglas Dietrich talks a lot about it.
He's pretty psychotic.
Anything he says outside of World War II
stuff is gibberish.
But when he gives the points on World
War II, he's on point.
More people, more ordnance in terms of explosive
ordnance and more people were killed during the
firebombing of Tokyo which was upwards of a
quarter of a million than both atomic bombs
put together.
But no one talks about that.
They have to talk about the atomic bombs
because they want you to worship atomic energy.
But then they figured out that atomic energy
was safer than they even thought so they
had to reverse it and make it more
dangerous.
Do you know that when they tell you
about radioactive waste and all that it's not
so much the actual material that's radioactive but
all the surrounding materials that you need to
purify it.
The distillation process is very nasty.
I don't want to get in trouble by
talking about how it's done publicly because they
do guard a lot of that.
But I would suggest that they do still
worship it.
Look at 9-11.
Even the Pentagon was a nuclear event.
It just didn't go off.
It was a nuclear missile that was fired
at the Pentagon.
But it just the idiots that launched it
didn't have the arming codes for it.
How do I know?
They didn't have the arming codes for it?
Well, Washington D.C. is still there, right?
So it was a nuclear event and it's
still being used more than ever.
They've even convinced people it should be medicinal.
They do radiation treatment which is stupid.
But nonetheless we were talking about war and
they brought in the idea of the guided
missile the human guided missile aspect and now
it's been replaced by cameras.
And young, snotty 19-year-olds or 18
-year-olds or whatever.
Yeah, but another aspect of the guided missiles
was that they were kamikaze pilots and that
they were sacrifices to the gods.
Right, right.
Sure, and the more they sacrificed, the more
power they got.
Which is, you know.
They did win the war, by the way.
The Japanese.
But it wasn't so evident because you know,
Hirohito had no less than 20 insurgencies inside
of his own palace even.
You know, people amongst him, admirals, generals that
wanted to get rid of him.
And there was even attacks on the palace
by his own people, more than one.
Where he was spared by hiding in secret
rooms.
Where is that memorialized?
Is that Dietrich?
Yeah, I've seen it in Dietrich and I've
also seen it in other...
You could do a research where I looked
at this a little closer more than a
decade ago.
You could look up assassination attempts on Emperor
Hirohito.
Just Google that and you'll see there's writings
about it.
On the Showa.
He was known as the Showa or you
could put in Hirohito assassination attempts.
43, 44, 45.
Those three years were very difficult.
Assassination attempts also on the Fuhrer of the
Third Reich.
Oh yeah, that we know about.
Were prevalent, yeah.
Both from his own people and international attempts.
You know, people coming in as spies.
Another thing that's not known is Roosevelt was
assassinated, but it was secret.
I spoke to someone once a long time
ago that was alive then and he was
part of the OSI or whatever, the secret
group.
He says, Roosevelt died of lead poisoning.
Now you could say that publicly and most
people say, yeah, I know you could die
from lead poisoning, right?
No, no.
I mean like instant lead poisoning.
Like as in a slug of lead.
Yeah.
You know, for people that won World War
II, the Japanese don't act like it.
No, because the winners write history.
The people don't know.
The people are morons just like the Americans
and just like the Iraqis and just like
any other Russian or whatever.
The people never know.
They're just kept in the dark.
It's none of their business.
It's most, the larger the event, the more
of it is a need-to-know basis.
Yeah, but the leaders don't even act like
they won.
At the time they did, but now time
has faded.
The thing is they had suffered a lot
of damage.
Right?
The Americans suffered a lot of damage too.
It's not known because morally it affects morale.
There were thousands of people killed in the
US and a tremendous amount of industry proportionately
was destroyed by sabotage, both of Japanese and
German.
You could look up factory sabotage during World
War II.
Munitions factories and I don't mean where the
actual shells are being packed, but the places
that develop the chemicals for the munitions.
Right?
You need a little potassium nitrate and carbon
and borrow whatever chemicals to make explosives.
Those factories were sabotaged.
You don't have to sabotage where they're packing
the shells with gunpowder.
You just sabotage the suppliers.
It's more effective because they're less secure.
Ports were sabotaged.
Ships were sabotaged.
Factories were sabotaged.
The American dirigible program was sabotaged.
Flying blimps, hot air balloons, things like that.
You don't hear about it because it was
considered detrimental to morale.
I see.
It was not an attack like the Americans
flying over Tokyo.
They were people that would lie about their
nationality or people that were hired to go
work in a factory.
You work in the factory for a few
weeks acting normal and then you just unscrew
some valve of a critical part of the
machinery.
It's like cutting the brake lines in someone's
car.
You don't completely cut the whole brake line
because the moment they put it in drive,
they notice there's no brakes.
You cut it so it leaks.
It's a very little volume.
When they brake two or three times then
all the liquid is out.
There's a lot of stuff that people don't
know about because it hasn't been presented to
them publicly.
I guess I was more referring to being
able to infer people's motivations by looking at
the actions.
If you look at the actions of the
Japanese government and the people, they don't act
like war winners even covertly.
For several levels you want to see how
they don't act like war winners.
One is you have to consider the main
aspect, again culture, is they're very feudal.
Feudal society.
Ancestral worship.
So right there they're pretty good craftsmen.
They're very disciplined but they're pretty moronic from
a spiritual point of view.
The second aspect is that they did suffer
attacks.
So you had displaced people.
So basically the whole point about the media
having them as losing the war actually doesn't
really say they lose the war or surrender
was never really used.
It was acceptance of the foreign powers to
come in and rebuild and clean up.
You see, you've got to realize that Hirohito
had tribute from everyone in Swiss Army.
Swiss banks in American dollars.
Internationally when a country admits defeat their current
is reset to zero.
So if you were the emperor Sam, and
I said you have an equivalent of 100
billion in dollars and we're going to reset
the dollar to zero.
Should we do it?
Yes or no?
What would you say?
You're going to do whatever you can to
prevent that from happening, right?
But there's no like, if he had had
the leverage he could have just made the
Japanese currency the reserve currency.
So clearly he was still taking orders from
some bank or somewhere to not be able
to.
Well, here's the other thing.
It depends on a basic financial level, yes.
But on high finance, no.
It's like bridge.
There's no winner or loser.
It's who controls what and what do you
wager.
You know, people say it's chess.
It's not.
It's bridge.
You have partners and you wager.
There's no winner or loser.
It's just a matter of how well your
wager is.
And also Japan is a small country that
doesn't have a lot of resources.
It has resources but not a lot of
resources.
So why would you want to maintain an
imperial, why would you want to be a
target as an imperial nation?
Do you want to seem like you succumb
to world trends and always have the upper
hand?
It depends on how the posture of your
society is.
You know, there are people that tend to
be modest, believe it or not.
I mean, now everybody's out of control, I'd
say.
Have you ever watched Japanese television?
I mean, like a Japanese television show with
the commercials in Japanese and all that?
I know their game shows are crazy.
Oh, I mean, I've had, I had a
videotape, long story but I need to get
into it.
I got a videotape because I might as
well say it, I was on Japanese TV
a while back and the producers sent me
the whole videotape, you know, and it had
the commercials and everything.
It was aired and it was really bizarre.
I mean, like totally bizarre, right?
So.
Now, that's normal to them.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah, there's some very strange aspects to their
culture.
Say again, Sam?
I've got to take a break for 30
seconds.
I'll be right back.
I've just got to go outside for a
moment.
I don't think this is going to work.
I'll be right back.
You guys speak amongst yourselves, okay?
Sure.
Speak amongst yourselves.
What's that?
No, nothing.
We're just killing the family, I guess.
No, but I'm going to end up taking
it off soon as well because it's getting
late here.
Yeah, and I get the pleasure of working
early tomorrow, so it all fits in pretty
good.
Fascinating discussion, so.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Yeah.
So, there was no broadcast last week, after
all?
No, there was a mix-up.
No worries.
Alright.
Okay, so what's the consensus?
We've been on long enough, right?
Yeah, I would say so.
Yeah.
Just watch Prophecy.
Learn about timekeeping.
We're in the 11th month already.
Right?
It's the first week of the 11th month.
No, the 5th.
Yeah.
I get something like that.
And I would say that it's going to
be a rollercoaster ride, especially after the next
year and a half.
Two years, I should say.
Because we're one year into this period in
springtime.
So at the three and a half mark,
it's, you know, another two and a half
years, it'll be pretty evident to those that
know what's going on.
Right.
Just keep your plans within, you know, less
than a 10-year limit.
Anybody comes to you with a 20-year
plan, say, forget it.
Even a 15-year plan, forget it.
You can keep it short-term.
Short and dynamic.
And keep your head down.
The reason I say keep your head down
is because whatever you do, you're going to
be dealing with these morons, you know, humans.
So you don't want to get too deeply
involved with their affairs.
Wise words.
Oh, yeah.
And when it comes, it starts happening, you
know, what you hear about culturally called as
apocalyptic scenarios and all that, it's going to
be very, very quick.
You won't be able to react when they
start coming, right?
It's whatever mental preparation you have prior.
And you don't want to get caught up
in their bullshit.
Actually, it's kind of hard to say that
because it's all been bullshit for the past
two millennia.
So how can you not get caught up
in it?
But you know what I mean.
The stuff that's coming.
Indeed.
All right.
Well, thanks for coming on, Sam and Bruce.
Thank you, Sam.
Of course.
And I'm going to sign out unless there's
anything else.
I just looked at the chat.
There's nothing on there.
I see.
Well, thank you both again.
Okay.
Fascinating subjects.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, look up a lot of the stuff
that I brought up.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay, guys.
I'll see you next week.
Take care now.
Good night, Sam.
Good night, Bruce.