There we go.
All right, we'll bring ourselves back in.
And greetings, folks, when we're back.
And a nice little pause there.
Okay.
Yeah, organic coffee is on sale.
So some coffee.
Yeah.
That's a joke, right?
But it does taste better.
It does.
It's just crazy.
So it just shows you how even when everything gets starts to get pushed to the side and thrown into the trough, you know, for all the pigs, there's still something that's left on top that might work out.
So but it's really bad.
So any questions in chat?
Let's see.
We were just talking with Vandy a little bit about the ISA.
And uh, oh, yes, there was a question in here.
What was that?
Did you confirm with what the heck?
Oh, was I presumptive?
I think you were.
I think Vandy acknowledged that you were in the right direction there, I believe.
Okay.
There was a question.
Yeah.
So what was the fig tree?
I got Gabby there for a second.
So I wasn't painted.
Question about the fig tree.
Yes, yes.
Well, there's fig trees.
Yeah, was the fig.
Let's see Eddie.
Was the fig tree refers to Israel?
Why did the Christ curse the fig tree?
Well, you know, I have gone over that.
But maybe I'll go over it again.
Mm hmm.
And it's not a pat answer thing, because the pat answer is because he did.
Right.
And you know, when you talk to most people, you could do anything you want, right?
Because they, you know, they're trying to defend something they know nothing about.
Because for most people, faith is something that they know is not true.
Right?
Or they know can't be defined.
But the definition on that is quite simple.
When you know how I adverse I am to people asking me for verses to show one specific thing.
Unless I get into a specific thing.
So this one is a specific thing.
So you can easily say on the surface, yeah, because he did.
But there's a long explanation.
And the story starts off with Abraham.
There was a scene where Abraham is goes into a covenant with the Elohim.
And what's interesting about that covenant is it's mostly one sided, although almost all of the performance, if not all of the performances on the Elohim, on that agreement, isn't it?
With Abraham, right?
He doesn't have to do anything.
At that point, speaking when the cup is made, he's all the performances on the gods.
So at that point, and the most high right when I say Elohim, because you know, he does it by proxy, right?
And then and then you move down.
Well, before we get out of Abraham, there's a scene where he has a vision where things are horrible.
He sees these really horrible things happening.
I don't know if you remember that.
It's a dream.
It's a it's a multiple part dream.
Well, we only are told to get the reaction.
Yeah.
All right, fast forward.
The reason I bring up Abraham, because that aspect starts with him, right?
Right.
This particular aspect directly, because before that he the gods are working with everyone, right?
Okay, now fast forward to Daniel, which is another thing that people don't understand, no matter how hard they try, because it's not time yet.
But you'll get a lot out of it, if you just read out of it.
Now, Daniel takes place at the 70 year Jeremiah in the book of Jeremiah.
You know, you find out in other places, they're told they're going to have 70 years of captivity, or 70 years of indignation, or 70 years of not in the land, right?
Right.
Not good, because of their actions.
Prior actions of 370 some odd years.
Yeah.
So, okay.
So, or, you know, maybe two centuries, you could say for sure, 200 years.
Now, when you look at the way Daniel is interacting, by the way, I've never said this publicly before, I'll say it now.
Daniel is a good role model, if you want to know how to interact with the gods, by the way.
I'm going to say that again.
When you read scripture, read it like a screenplay.
You know, when you read a screenplay, it's not just a book.
You know that it's going to be acted out, right?
That's why it's a screenplay, or a movie, or a theater, a play.
If you'll notice how he, wouldn't say, let me, in a not so respectful way, over embellish it.
I'm going to say this non-respectfully.
I shouldn't really, but let's just say, you know how he overdoes it when he's praying, right?
Yes.
You know, but is it overdone?
Not really.
I mean, it's just, you know, he'll start there praising the Allah, right?
Which is where the Arabs get Allah, for short.
Right.
Which means the God, because his name is not used there.
So, right?
If you look at that, I just want to throw that in there.
You know, you start, you know, Christ said keep it short, but that's not something you should shorten, I should suggest.
No.
I would suggest.
Just keep the praise, because what that does is, it's not only for the gods themselves.
They don't really need that.
They know, they're very confident, really.
They don't need your praise directly to know their position.
But it shows your character too.
It shows your character, and also it's a signal beacon to the angelic presence, because they're the ones scouring the human landscape, looking for who's, you know, wants to send a message, right?
Because they're the ones that bring it.
Right.
Just like, just like, you know, years ago, what you, you put the one on the rural, especially at the post box, and when you had mail to go out, you lifted the flags, and the postman knew that you had to, you know, there was mail outgoing there, so he had to make adjustments, he can make adjustments to his bag, or get the outgoing bag before he got there.
You know, very, just the economy of movement for the angelic that delivered the messengers, right?
Right.
I never really got into that before, but anyway.
Yeah.
Okay, so we start off with Abraham.
You see some things that are really horrible, and we'll fast forward to the book of Daniel.
We know about they're in there for 70 years, really one other year, but one of the things that Daniel presents is what's going on with the nation, or the people, and he is told that there's going to be another 490.
There's a 490 year thing that's brought up.
Why?
Because if you don't correct it in the first 70, then they make it seven times more.
Right.
Get it?
Yes.
Now, and they didn't correct it, and they didn't, and now if you don't correct it during the time, you get another seven times to correct it, you know, of indignation, let's say.
And if you still haven't corrected it, and then you get what's called condemnation, and that's why the Christ cursed the fig tree, because it was the end of the road for them, from that spiritual end, not what they did to him, specifically as a man on earth.
That came later as well.
That had to be done no matter what, which is still a secret, believe it or not.
Yeah.
No, well, no, it was known that they wouldn't...
Okay, that was a poor choice, Jess.
Well, when the gods condemned, yeah, I don't see a lot of tests, but...
No, I meant as far as the Christ, for him coming back, it was a proof of after death.
Oh, no, yeah.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
I wasn't saying that about the other...
Oh, no, that's fine.
The Christ said one purpose only, strictly, was to show those who knew, and ask the question, what happens after death, and prove it.
He was there to prove it for them, not to start another religion, and all the people who didn't know scripture.
He specifically said that, I came for the lost of Israel, right?
Now, if you look at that word lost, it's not lost like your lost dog, or, you know, you're lost and found.
The word is perished, I mean the dead.
He came for those that have died of Israel already, not the living, but he is living, and he's here for the living to see, because the living are the ones that know about him being here.
So, there's a dual-sidedness like, you know, to it, right?
Because if no one had died yet, he wouldn't have to come to prove it, right?
Right.
So, but there's another...
That's why the entire, I keep saying confidently, the whole notion and concept of the Christ is still a secret, because how do I know?
You still see Christians around, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Like, what are you talking about?
Get out of here, you know?
I hope this is a pretty good signal right there.
Or you still see what academics are writing about stuff.
It's like, what are you talking about?
Get out of here.
It has nothing to do with that.
You know, they try to put him in...
So, in other words, what people think the Christ is is completely false.
That's why they categorize him with Buddha and Muhammad and all these others.
I'm just surprised it hasn't been made into some kind of superhero, as doggy as this society is.
They have.
Really?
They have one, the Christian one, that with the bobbing head that you put on the bar.
Oh, no.
Oh, okay.
Yes, yes.
When they made a song about the plastic Jesus.
Yeah, they've got a shroud.
Yeah, they've got a shroud in some basilica in the Vatican, thinking it's a shroud, you know?
They should take that and make a cape out of it.
Make that the cape.
We'll do a Jesus superhero cartoon, and his cape is actually the Shroud of Turin, also an image on there.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, God.
These people are ridiculous.
But anyway, but here's the other point to cursing the fig tree and condemning Israel to that, is that the highest Elohim chose one group of people to keep order, and these people couldn't do it, so he basically condemned all of humanity at that point.
What did he condemn them to?
Remember, he went 70 years of captivity, and then it went to 490, now it went to 2,000 years.
Yeah, yeah.
Two days, and how do we know?
There's three days and three nights in the grave, right?
Right.
So you know how the numbers work when you're in your second year, when you're two years old, you're in your third year now.
You're in your third year.
See how it works?
Yeah.
So three days would be 2,000 years.
You're in your third day now, right?
You're in the third, you know, so.
That's some serious, serious whoop-ass.
Yeah, and you're born in it, and everyone that you've ever known, everyone that they've ever known, over 15, 20 times, you know, is born in it.
That's a lot of generations.
Yeah, and what that means is you're disconnected.
Right, right.
You know, as you were before.
You're not completely disconnected, because we were speaking about the chi, the prana, and the ether before.
Right, right.
You know, they could just think it and shut off everyone's ability to breathe immediately.
Oh yeah, in a heartbeat.
You're not completely cut off.
They're just hands off completely.
Almost like we're pushed into the corner, you know.
Right, right, but also they're hands off openly, like unlike they were before, where you know, an army was told to stand down, and because the angels are going to go in front and fight for them.
You see, and it wasn't just, oh, coincidence, you actually saw that happen.
See, all that's been cut off.
So, from that realm, you know, from that higher realm, the lower entities, oh, they've been busy as hell, you know.
Yeah, they have.
And how do we know there's their presences everywhere?
And the only way they get away with it is by presenting themselves as good, just like doctors, attorneys, and accountants, and preachers, and ministers, and pastors.
Hope, Ryan, and Zucker.
Yep, yeah.
So, that's, don't take, I tell people, don't take, there's nothing you can do about it, and don't take it personally.
So, just think of it as a, you're in a really, you know, what do they call those country club prisons?
You know, like the club fed, is that what they call it?
Club fed, yeah.
You're in club fed right now, everyone.
You're in prison, really.
But it's a spiritual prison, you know.
So, if you want to know, we're basically talking about the outside world, the free world right now, which is the realm of the gods.
I'll pour a little more coffee.
Any other questions there?
I don't see, just that somebody had made the point that, Hope, you're recording this, we don't want to have another one of those.
Another one of these, or those, but.
Yeah, the program that didn't exist.
Oh, that's fine, that's all right.
I know, well, I've got it all between the ears, I think, or somewhere.
Oh, no, no, that was when we first started this, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And yes.
Yeah, it's all right.
It's out there somewhere in the ether, right?
Yes, it is.
But for safety's sake, yes, it is being recorded, and it will be there later on.
Check out for what I'm saying.
Yes, yes.
An interesting time you'll have when you do.
I hope so, yeah, because you don't want it to be boring, which is a fun thing.
No, no, and I always go off to some other tangent that takes me here, takes me there, and I'm like, oh my god.
Yeah, I assure you, if you asked anyone out there at this point, I'm being saying this with humility, of course, ha ha ha, but you know, as much as possible, why was the fig tree cursed?
You're not going to get a simple, you know, it's going to be so oversimplified that you're going to walk away still wanting to figure it out.
Well, I'm trying to show you that all of these things are not about one thing only.
You have to go to where the entire, where did Israel start?
Where did Israel, right?
And not only did Israel start, where, why was Israel, Israel because of who?
You see, the patriarch, right?
And then you got to go there, and that's why there's so much confusion, is because it's all fractional.
Yeah, yeah, like a broken mirror.
Yeah, you don't see the whole body, just a little piece.
So, I would suggest that answering these things simply, and showing how, you know, from the beginning to the end, where it goes, is one way that someone can say, well, you know, I heard it, do I understand it?
Well, I might have to just trust the Greek, because I haven't read that or studied that.
See, that's where you go to the next level now, and you say, well, he said all these things, let me see if I could find them.
Yeah, yeah, best way to do it.
You said, you said if you go on the way, then you've just done a year's worth of study in a few minutes or an hour, right?
Because you've gotten the shortcut.
I believe in shortcuts, shortcuts are always the way to go.
But it doesn't make it, if it compromises quality, then the shortcut is not good.
Right, right, and it's a heck of a journey when you do, when you do go and check it.
Anyone wants to look up in front, by the way, where does that cutting corners thing started from?
Remember that?
Was it a document thing, or was it something else?
You know, when you're cutting corners, it means your quality goes down?
Oh, yeah.
So what?
Yeah, that was another thing you were always going to do, was a little episode on cliches.
Yeah, cutting corners.
I'm trying to think of a word that, I'm drawing a blank, Greek, I'm drawing a blank.
It might be a reference on it if someone wants, but you see, shortcuts are good.
I think everyone has gotten used to, especially with the rectangle, finding out that doing a shortcut is more ergonomic.
So if you start taking, let's say you take 10 biblical questions, and you show how the situation started, all the way to how it affects where you are today, and you draw this pathway through the scripture, with each one 10 times, you've covered the book, vast swaths of the book very quickly, that way, in understanding.
Which I want to bring up, by the way, because the religious cultures, all of them, regardless of what they are, it's either the clergy or congregation, or the followers or the leaders, they have an unwritten rule that it's forbidden or taboo to give proper interpretation, or any interpretation.
Then when someone tries to say something, they say, well, that's your interpretation.
It just shows you how they're all just massively ignorant, right, and evil, you know.
The hive mentality.
It's forbidden, you know, just like if you deal with an attorney, it's forbidden to show the of the law.
Earlier I mentioned with the attorneys or so, about the, I just want to say this real quick, you don't have to learn the law, you just have to learn, you do have to learn the law, but the way you learn the law, the man's law, is by learning definitions.
So when you're charged with something, they'll cite what code it is, so you just, the code could be hundreds of pages long, but the definitions are only less than a page long, and if you see that that code doesn't apply to you by definition, it doesn't matter what they're charging you with, you stick on that, you see.
Yeah.
You get it?
So, okay, someone is handing me another smaller rectangle here.
Cutting Corners.
According to an analytic dictionary of English etymology by Anatoli Lieberman, the phrase cutting corners may have derived from the cater corner in the 16th century.
The verb cater was first recorded and defined replacing something across diagonally.
Okay, so when you cut the corners, I guess, and you measure diagonally, the thing is shorter, right?
Thank you.
So, yeah, you know how televisions were measured diagonally and to make them sound bigger?
Remember that?
I think they still are, aren't they?
Did I lose you, Bruce?
Are we still streaming?
I don't know if we're still on, so I'll mute until I hear from Bruce.
Sorry, Greg, I had myself muted and I was in the channel, couldn't get back to the window back quick enough.
Oh, that's fine.
Yeah, we're still on, right?
Yes, oh yes, we're still going.
Yeah, so it has to do with measuring diagonally, and if the corners are missing, then it's shorter, right?
Right.
Cutting Corners.
Got you.
Okay, anything else?
Not at the moment.
That's what got me into trouble there a little bit.
I couldn't get out of that window.
Exiled to spiritual Siberia.
Is there a god assigned to each person?
That was something you brought up one time.
Yes, well, it's done by, again, let me go back to Abraham.
He was told to leave an area because of the gods that were there, and the ones that, not because of the gods that were there, but because of the conditions of the people around him and the gods that they worshipped, right?
He couldn't do, so there's a physical change, yeah?
Yeah.
But I wouldn't say there's a god assigned each person.
The way you do that is by jurisdiction, family and country.
But we see now, part of this time period, there's nowhere to go.
The entire world is under the goddess religion and under the adversary, you know.
So where are you going to go?
Well, you know, I heard someone recently, well, I'm going to move, and I don't know where I'm going to go.
And I'm like, well, just remember this.
Wherever you go, there you are.
And that's really where you're at right now.
Wherever you go, it's about being set apart.
You're not going to run into anything, any lawful society or anything good that represents the good.
Now, you're going to run into a lot of things that represent themselves as being good falsely, right?
No one's going to say, hey, we're a satanic, well, you know, we worship the old lord of darkness, and we'd like to enslave you and whatever, abuse you, come to our country.
No one's going to say that.
Right, right.
Or how dare you, you know, whatever.
So yeah, they always, it's a counterfeit.
Vandy had one here about, what about the saying, to feel it in your waters?
Where did that come from, I wonder?
Well, you know what, here's the interesting thing about that.
Let's look it up.
No, I don't know what that means.
All those cliches, I think at this point, the most immediate way to look it up is on the rectangle, isn't it?
Yeah.
But if you have conflicting, or some either seems inappropriate, or not pertinent, or not direct, then you're going to have to go into print.
By the way, the rectangle is far better off than things that are solely in print, if they're accurately on the rectangle.
Right, right.
Because you can access it now, you know, if you have a book, let's say, you know, I have a book here, I never retrash and say it, it's here, right, and it got passed around and ended up with me, and it's an old book, a very old book, and nothing on it is on the internet, right?
But if it was, right, I could travel without it, and go on the internet and access it.
Right.
But right now, if I travel without it, I don't have it.
Yeah.
You get it, you see what I mean?
It's like, you know, the Outlook emails, how they're not web-based, you have to be on the computer that it's set up, versus Gmail, you can access, right?
So the rectangle does that, and it allows you to tap into that, you know, universally located access.
Right.
Where the stuff in print doesn't.
Now, here's an interesting thing, there's commentary,
if anyone can find it, when the printing presses were being produced, and plans were being given,
and training on how to print material in Europe, there was a lot of commentary about, oh no,
this thing, the printing press, is going to ruin society, because all these gossips and tales,
and people orally speak on, you know, they dissipate, you know, over time, but once they're
going to print, once they put this crap in print, it'll be around much longer.
Yeah.
Now, from that respect, I could see like, for example, 9-11, JFK, and all these other conspiracy stuff, they rely on the internet to keep their crap going.
Conspiracy theory, right?
Where if they had to actually go out and print a book, you wouldn't see as many notions and stupid stuff on those things, for example.
You know, like those two things I'll just bring up.
Like, JFK is a closed case, as we already have confessions on that.
Who did it?
I'm not going to say.
If you want to find out, you can research it yourself.
If you can't find it, go ahead and email me, and I'll tell you who did it.
9-11, you can look at it all you want, you're not going to figure out how those buildings were turned into dust on your own.
You have to have a certain knowledge of high energy dielectrics, let's just put it that way.
And that technology is about 80 years old now, 90 years old.
It's not from space, and it's not nanothermite.
And if you don't know how it was done specifically, you could, don't, well, I shouldn't say email me, and I'll tell you I don't want to start going in those directions.
But yeah, email me, and I'll tell you.
I'll put it in chat one day.
I think you have, I think you have to some degree.
There was a video that you posted about a ship in the water.
Yeah, a 10,000 ton ship turning into dust.
And it's on my server, folks, in uploads.
Have a peek.
Very nice, very, very interesting piece of work.
I wish they would have left the camera roll just a little bit longer.
Oh yeah, I think at that point the wave, I think the water wave caught it by that point.
Yeah.
There used to be some really good ones on Project Plowshare.
They took them down like 15 years ago, or like say 2003, 2004.
I bookmarked them, and now they're gone on an old computer.
But it actually showed you a series of buildings as a radio tower, and they did, you know, the device went out, the zero box, and zero time goes off at ground zero.
And you saw everything turn to dust.
Oh, let's see, I got some four critters here.
And so you saw everything turn to dust, just like at the World Trade Center, you know.
And I'm like, oh, this is a piece of cake, you know.
And then having conversations with Dimitri takes it to a whole other level.
Yes, yes.
And JFK, there's a confession on that, and if you want to, if someone confesses, and you can't tell if someone is telling the truth or not, that's not the person who's making the confessions problem.
Right, right.
That's your inability to understand if someone is telling the truth or not, and that's a serious human problem from that respect.
So anyway, because you're living in a society where evidence doesn't matter.
How do I know?
Well, look around you.
Yeah.
That's why they put labels, put it this way.
If you lived in a society that was just 5% reasonable, or really 1% reasonable, 1%, all of the, especially in America, the supermarkets and grocery stores would close because no one would buy anything in there.
How do I know?
Because simply of what's on the labels of the food that you buy, right?
You would read and see, I say, oh, this shouldn't be eaten, and no one would buy the food.
But because it's you buying that food, I know you have no, evidence means nothing.
Now, what I mean by that is, I'm going to put some toxic or semi-toxic material in a container and put a label on it that you know is there, and everyone knows is there, that states that, and you still buy it.
And a nice, bright color.
Yep.
It doesn't matter, though.
Yeah, because you know what the color is.
It's the information.
I think you shared one time.
That's what the children's, yeah.
Yeah.
And then some of the constituents, some of the, what was there, plaster.
And some of them, if spilled out in a city or something like that, you'd have to get a hazmat team to come in and clean it up.
Yeah, it's okay if it's in the cereal box.
It's okay if it's in the cereal box.
If you pour it on the sidewalk, though, it's a thousand dollar fine.
Easily.
Yeah, easily.
For toxic waste, yeah.
And cleanup time.
That was an interesting thing.
At one point, Phoenix Water had gotten up to a thousand parts per million, and the EPA said anything more than 700 parts per million on the sidewalk is a thousand dollar fine, but the tap water is, yeah, see.
Evidence doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter at all.
No.
You know, it says it right on the money, Federal Reserve note, and then who owes the note?
The United States of America.
Yeah.
You know, people in commerce, like you take a $10 bill, but no one asks who's going to pay that bill, right?
Who's going to pay that bill?
Yeah, who's going to pay that bill?
These are bills.
Yeah, who's going to pay them?
That's why when they're in Congress, they pass bills, because they're putting out all this spurious, presumptive debt.
And, you know, the financial people are like, you're putting a law and a bill.
Who's going to pay that bill?
The people.
They're so stupid.
We'll charge them with stealing rocks from the moon.
And they have, the reason they pass bills is because you have all the credit.
Yeah.
It's kind of like, you know, let's say you go to a restaurant, and you have nothing, you're Congress, and you're in a restaurant with all these rich people, and they give you a bill for a tuna fish sandwich.
You're like, I don't have any money.
And you're like, well, you know, there's all these wealthy people in here.
Maybe I'll convince one of these guys to buy me this $5 sandwich.
And chances are they will.
No one will.
You see?
It's like watching a bad TV show.
Yeah.
Well, TV is bad because of this.
Oh, true.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, yes.
It's just, but, you know, again, it's, they're accommodating the people.
If you haven't been out in public lately, or if you don't have any family or friends, I suggest you go temporary, we'll do a temporary rent-a-family-and-friends thing to find out if you don't want to go out to the shops and talk to people.
Live on air.
If you have any other humans or surface-oriented habits around you, you'll see that you are surrounded by morons.
It's very simple.
It's scary.
It's a cosmic problem.
See, I'm one of the few people in the world that say this consistently nonchalant.
It's not a pejorative thing to say it.
In other words, I'm saying it because it is accurate in the sense that, like the Forrest Gump, stupid is as stupid does.
In other words, do not expect anything beyond what you see, because it is completely out of their control at this point.
Not because it is out of their control, because at this point it's out of their control, and it's been out of their control, because they're incapable, incompetent.
How would you say it?
You know, they're just not capable of it.
They're just not.
Because of the very simple things that we, you know, always discuss.
Eddie's asking, why did Moses have horns in some pictures?
Because he did.
Yeah.
It's in scripture.
Charon.
You know, there's other words for shine.
Why did they pick the word charon?
Because that's where you get chariton from.
A horn is a symbol of power.
Now, there's many ethereal explanations for it, but essentially in scripture you have an altar with horns.
You have horns being broken, and then you have someone being given horns.
Well, if you want to know exactly why, exactly and specifically why, you'll get a chance to ask him yourself in the future.
But all I can say about horns is that they're a prominent feature that is shown in places of power.
And Moses was chosen to be in a position of power.
And there's an entire story about Moses which can be discussed, which you can get out of the few verses about him personally out of scripture, combined with how antithetical most of the things that they were told to do were from where they came from and where they were going.
Antithetical meaning opposite of the societies, the traditions of Egypt, and the traditions of the Canaanites, meaning where they were leaving and where they were going.
There's a specific reason for that.
You'll never see that anywhere else in history because everywhere else in history when people had traditions and laws and things they blended in from where they came from.
But what's interesting about the Torah or the teachings and the laws that were given to Moses as, let's say, a constitution of a nation or a family or a group of people were contrary to the others.
And there's some pretty deep stuff in there which I probably won't go public with for still a couple of years.
I'm going to wait and see how the understanding changes because it gets pretty deep.
I mean to the point where it's not politically correct at all.
I'm not one for being politically correct.
I'm just saying that it'll be simpler if some of the censorship as it starts to move along and better texts get put out and more people read.
And then we could go back and say, see what this says right here?
Do you want to talk about that?
They're like, wow, I've never saw that before.
I'm like, yeah, isn't that interesting, right?
Yeah, I try to keep everything for the past 14 years, 15 years basic publicly as much as possible.
Same stuff.
Everyone says it's the same stuff over and over.
I'm like, great.
If you got it down pat, you have license to go out and use it.
I'll never say you got that stuff from the Greek.
Go ahead.
Go.
Go start speaking.
Huh?
Needs to be said.
No one else is.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it will be.
Well, here's the thing for people to remember, regardless of what interests you have, because whatever interests you have, most likely are ones that are earthly.
The main point to speaking, if I were to just be
given 30 seconds, it would be that this whole thing now, especially, is that people acknowledge
the gods truly who they are, lawfully who they are, not something that you believe in or don't
believe in or whatever, and that they made us and that they're coming back to get us to set the
earth up for humanity 2.0, let's say, or the next level of this situation.
That's the whole point.
So no matter what you're interested in, whether you're a bus driver, a plumber, a clerk, a writer, whatever, a singer, a cyclist, a chef, a welder, it doesn't matter.
The thing to keep in the back of your mind is that the entire society in the next 14 years or less, actually probably less than 10 now, by the early mid to 2020s, is going to acknowledge mid to slightly after that, acknowledge that the gods are real.
It's not something you believe in or whatever.
It's just a real thing.
So once you acknowledge that they exist lawfully, not the fairy tales that you hear through religion, then it's time, then lawfully they could act upon what they have to do.
Because if the gods start doing things and no one understands who they are, then later on the humans will be like, well, we didn't know who you were, so why'd you do that?
You didn't give us enough time to catch up.
You didn't give us enough time.
They don't want to hear that.
You see what I'm saying?
Yeah, it's lawful.
So everyone is, yeah, people are going to go into the next level knowingly or conscious of it.
Another example would be like, I don't think anyone will ever be at the resurrection not knowing they're at the resurrection.
Right.
You see, so there's a level of cognizance that's going to be increased here.
So, and those that don't know about the resurrection, which is the majority of the people that have died, there's going to be some kind of instrument or application or something that's going to make them aware of it.
But what's interesting, that's on that end.
See, they're done already.
But for those that are here right now, which makes this time unique, is such an application or instruction will be done on earth prior.
Not about necessarily resurrection, but just that the gods exist.
Yeah.
And if you read, there's like two billion Christians, a billion, two billion Muslims, and those people don't know anything lawful about the gods.
I mean, forget it.
Or the Hindus or the Indy culture or the Buddhists, they don't know anything about the obvious.
You just go along the rectangle, look at books that have been written.
You know, you could press the most ardent believer in any of these faiths about where they get what they're saying, and then they fall apart.
It's a straw man argument across.
So this is going to go, this is going to change.
And once it changes, that's when things are going to get really good, you know, down here.
And that's just, you know, a setup again.
Yeah.
I hear more and more people say that I'm not into organized religion, which seems to be more predominant now than it was.
Well, whether they like it or not, they're going to, they're going to be into organized destruction when the gods.
And that's a tough subject to try to broach.
I tried lightly here and there, and it didn't, didn't take quite as well as I was hoping, but that's, that's fine.
That's fine.
Well, that's a difficult one because it's not just addressing that particular part of the speech.
It's the character of the individual.
Yeah.
You have to draw, you have to draw a line.
There's several lines and several, let's just discuss this maybe for a moment, several forms, levels of this.
You have to discern who they are.
Like one of them is like, okay, judge them quickly and say, well, is this someone I want to engage?
Exactly.
Right.
Do they have, are they a space here?
Are these one of the ones that are going to go to the grave completely clueless?
Or is this one that's falling for the Antichrist?
Actually, the answer to that one is yes, because everyone is pretty much going to fall for the Antichrist.
Right.
And the other thing is you can discern them and say, can we talk about this later?
You know, or the thing is addressing the organized religion aspect is, is a catchphrase as part of the hive mentality also, you see.
Yes.
So you got to see they're locked into a hive also.
So you could tell them that you prefer the disorganized one, the one that's so disorganized no one even knows about, no one will ever really know about in this lifetime, you know, and that might, you know, just the opposite.
But that's the interesting thing right now is that there's going to be a sorting that's going to be done, you know.
And when I mean sorting, I mean literally a sorting, you know, when you sort things out to separate them.
Right.
So, see, it's been done before also.
You could see that some people, you know, were the complete, you know, antithesis of what would be a model, let's say you set apart a person and they were made to be, right?
You know, everything that, you know, the gods have a way of doing that.
If it's meant for someone to do something, and when they're not doing it on the cruise ship, they'll lean the entire ship so they do.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So, or they'll send agents down to move it around.
It's very interesting.
See, if you know how these things work, it's really interesting.
But if you don't know how they work and you just always chalk it up into the, you know, because you're censored or whatever, oh, you know, whatever, then life is just, you know, you have to find, I'm sure you still, your interests lie somewhere else, you see.
And there's most people always find their interests in something, usually stupid stuff.
You know, anyone could say, well, you know, who says it's stupid?
I'll tell you it's stupid and I'll give you a hundred reasons why.
But that's all they can do.
You know, if you try to tell a fish they could climb a tree, they go insane, right?
You tell a monkey to climb a tree, right?
Or a cat.
Right.
Yeah, they, they're not, you know.
Bloodline.
And see, you had kind of a hard one to dissect here.
Subjects on the bloodline.
Not sure how to interpret that.
And Greek, did you ever DJ in Studio 54?
No.
No?
I've been there, but not DJing.
E-flow, especially blockage at the spinal column.
Huh.
You guys are not supposed to know that I, that I worked with music, but anyway.
Yeah, there was no hint of that.
Let's see.
You know, the thing about music, if it sounds good, it is good, right?
It is good, yes.
And friends don't let friends listen to bad music.
They're not, no, there's questions about the, what was that, about the chi blocking the spinal column.
Is that a question on the chat?
Let's see in here.
Yeah, yeah.
Blockage at the spinal column.
That's because the, the spinal column blockage is an interesting one.
In, if you look up spinal column in German, it's not called the spinal column.
It's called a spiral column.
Get it?
Yeah.
As in a spiral.
That's interesting because if you look at it from various principles, what is it composed of?
Let's just start mechanically.
It's very dense and then not so dense, you know, the cartilage in between and, and then dense and then not, it's alternating dense and not dense.
Okay.
What does that tell you?
Right.
And then you have, it's hollow and you have a nerve that goes through it, right?
So the denser the material, the more reflective it is, the softer, the more absorptive it is.
So when you look at the spinal column, you have absorption, reflection, absorption, reflection, right?
Because the, the, the heart bone reflects and the soft tissue in between absorbs.
So you see the alternate teeth, like teeth on a zipper.
You have air and then metal, air and then metal, the metal reflects the air absorbs.
So that is the key to understanding a blockage in the spinal column.
So, okay.
No question.
Just reporting.
I tried the cashew tempeh mix.
It was banging.
Thank you.
Oh yeah.
You know, I'm going to, I've got a lot of veg recipes, by the way, I went away from the blockage, but I gave the key to it.
So let's see if it unlocks anything.
The, the food issue is important because you're at a point right now where still we all are eating to stay alive.
And the higher the quality of the food, the higher the quality of your life that goes without saying, right?
And highest possible quality food.
And also that allows one to be in the highest quality state is a non-animal based diet.
Now, the interesting thing about that is a murdered animal or a killed animal is different than an animal product.
There's some people that have intolerance to animal products like eggs and milk right now is an egg, an egg is an egg, a whole, you know, when you're eating an egg, you're eating an entire chicken, feathers, the beak, right?
You see the energy there, right?
It's not just the chicken, right?
So an egg, I would say yes, is an animal, but the milk is not.
What's interesting about that because the milk is a by-product that's a living excretion for the young cow or boat or sheep.
Semi-dilutaneous puss-hacks of bovine.
Right, but actually most people, I could say it's the most Americans have never had real bread.
Most Americans have never had real milk.
Most Americans have never had real vegetables or real cheese or, you know, those kinds of things.
Yeah, well, you look at what they've stripped out of it.
Yeah, so okay, but it would be good with cashews also.
Cashews really soften up when you eat them, but chestnut and cashew mix, oh yeah, it's banging, yeah.
That's what I call umami.
Umami is like another flavor which is just simply delicious, you know, like if you've ever been around Japanese and they really enjoy food, they go, oh my, you know, that's like delicious, yum, that's their yum, right?
Yeah, so I would say that non-animal is the way to go.
You know, there's more nutrition pound for pound, believe it or not, but the thing that people need to again learn is technique in that as well.
You know, you've heard, I've mentioned before, the technique of you should chew your liquids and drink your solids.
Yes, yes.
I mean, don't guzzle, you know, move it around in the mouth for liquid, so you're chewing it.
Everything begins in the mouth.
Just drink the solids, you chew them until they're liquefied and you'll eat less that way.
I mean, scripture, I've been saying this ever since I found it out a long time ago, or not a long time ago, you know, let's see, 16 years ago.
It indirectly promotes a vegetarian diet.
Now, why do I say indirectly?
Because it states that if you touch the flesh of a dead animal, you're unclean, simply.
Yes.
Right?
So, if you're eating a chicken sandwich, are you touching the flesh of a dead animal?
I had once, someone says, it doesn't say eating it.
I'm like, so how are you eating it?
Oh, you know, there's an old, there's an old ghetto joke.
That was so good.
I didn't even touch my teeth.
Right?
Yeah.
Fascinated.
Right.
So, so yeah, so it indirectly promotes that.
So I would suggest it is noble to be quote unquote, vegetarian, you know, intake.
It is the most noble.
That's clear.
You know, from that perspective, from scriptural perspective, right?
Because it's not noble to be unclean.
It's more noble to be clean.
And if you touch dead animal, you're unclean.
Well, then it's noble to not touch that animal.
And if you're not touching that animal, you're not eating it.
Right?
I mean, you can say there are more different ways to say it than what it says.
That's why I keep saying it's indirect, but it's, it's rational, you know?
So I'd like to get more into all the recipes.
I mean, we will speak on food again.
Yeah, you had a pretty good role going on that, on chat that one day, and it was some very interesting preparations.
And some of them I'm definitely going to try.
Good.
Yeah.
Now, the, unfortunately, the most variety you're going to get is in the Asian and Middle Eastern cultures, when it comes to non meat eating variety.
If you tell, you know, an average American, no meat, they think it's canned string, string beans, and pasta or rice or something, you know, right, you know, red rice, you know, they have no idea of, you know, they think they have to, it's a, you know, a freakish thing to get into whole foods.
All their food decisions are made by the stupid rectangle and media of some sort.
Oh, that sounds good.
And they're still promoting mythical calories.
Yeah.
You know, the definition of a calorie is, you know, one degree, one, right, gram, one degree Celsius of water, you know.
So, I mean, it has to be carbonized.
All caloric determinations are made by completely carbonizing the object where the caloric determination is being made.
So, if you are pooping, that poop can be burned.
Yeah.
And calories don't apply.
Now, if you're pooping charcoal, if you eat food and you poop pure carbon, then the calories do apply to you.
And we want to hear from you.
And they think that the energy that you're moving around and staying awake with is heat energy.
I mean, you talk about a useless trade like haberdashers.
Remember growing up?
Nutritionists, they're completely useless.
Yeah.
But that's okay.
You know, accommodate the morons.
You got to keep these morons busy because the last thing you don't want them switching from morons to barbarians.
Yeah.
You know, when barbarians, I mean, in the loose form, not the just, you know, people of barber and, you know, the ones that were called barbarians in a pejorative sense, but I mean, savage, barbaric, and just, you know, murderous, because it doesn't take much for it to do that.
No, the ones that are just here and there in the news are quite enough.
We don't need a whole group of the damn things.
The greatest curiosity is see how the gods are going to turn it around.
So people, all these morons, I mean, I'm, I'm watching.
See, the thing about prophecy is, you know, what's happening, going to happen, but you don't know how it's going to happen.
It's kind of like getting tomorrow's newspaper read to you in bits and saying, well, you know, a silver Corvette is going to, you know, crash into a burger joint.
And you're like, oh, which burger joint?
And where?
Right.
And I got to look around and where all the silver Corvettes are registered to.
And where all the burger joints are and see if you can go and look at all those spots.
And it'll happen.
You just don't have the exact.
I don't know when.
Yeah.
Where the Moons and the Greeks Israelites was a question posed in question or in the chat today.
It's a mixed bag.
Today is a mixed bag.
I would say the Greeks were, I mean, the Romans were Greek.
That's there is a small group, I would say, of people that would be identified as the true Romans.
But the population and the true Romans, let's say, that were considered, you know, to be as a culture were all Greek anyway.
If you go to the island, if you go to Sicily, the oldest temples are all Greek inscription.
Not because they were conquered by the Greek, but because that was the language which developed into Roman later.
Right.
And there's many aspects of it.
I mean, here, you know, in Italian or Greek, so we're not out.
So meaning, you know, you have one face, one race.
Right.
Literally is what it means.
But you could say that, you know, how Brazil was or is a penal colony of Portugal and Australia was a penal colony of England.
Right.
You could say that part of Italy was a penal colony of Greece, essentially, you know, as a culture.
But there were people, you know, that lived there and, you know, there's myths about it and there's some very sparse information about it, who the original Romans were.
But were they Israelites?
No.
Were they heavily, heavily, heavily ordained to be interacted with?
Yes.
You know what I mean by, ordained to be interacted with prophetically.
Right.
Predestined.
Yeah.
And also to have the, to show, you know, to show the way for this lousy 2000 plus years, you know, 3000.
It's all been crappy, but don't take it personally.
You know, how do you just navigate it?
Right.
And watch to see which Corvette hits the Burger King.
All right.
I'm very curious about milk.
Well, I guess you should be.
As Vianney writes, I was very curious about milk.
Well, there's stuff in milk that is, well, milk is intended for baby cows.
And the, the aspect of using milk as it comes out of the udder is for a baby cow.
The most, I would say processing it into cheese or yogurt, you know, even though it sounds like a type of milk product or whatever is the smart way to take it because you're not a baby cow.
When you process it, you change it.
You know, when you go to a sandwich shop and you get a pickle, you know if I tell most people, especially in America, that's a cucumber, they look at you all funny because they've had a cucumber, you know, and that's what it is, the pickled cucumber.
Right.
But it's totally unrelated.
I mean, it doesn't resemble a, you know, a cucumber, fresh cucumber has a melon flavor to it, right?
Like a melon, right?
It's just, it's really, it's what it is, it's a melon.
What you pickle it and cure it, it changes it completely.
An alchemy.
It is a form of alchemy.
So cheese and yogurt and other milk products are more digestible than, than milk.
And if you were to do raw milk, that would be the best you can have.
But it would be a sustenance thing.
Yes.
You know, it would be because there was nothing else to have.
You would adapt and there's a reason.
Sure.
Like if I, like if I were told to eat pork, I'd rather eat what the pig eats.
Right, right, right.
Then eat the pig itself.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
What is the cow eating, you know?
Why don't you eat what the cow is eating?
I'd agree.
Instead, you know, well, you know, yeah, I mean, they'll, you know, they, they, the cows are, you know, very interesting that way.
They'll eat all the choice stuff first and they'll go after all the other stuff down to the point where, you know, sometimes it looks like they're just eating dirt.
But yeah, you know, I used to interact with people that managed like, you know, big money portfolios.
And when the whole stock thing went down in 2008, which I told them it would happen in 2006, 2007, because they were, you know, but I was a little late.
But anyway, I was on several conference calls and, you know, they managed, you know, billion-dollar private portfolios.
And this guy's personal portfolio went from 12 million to 3 million.
He's like, oh, I don't know how I'm going to survive.
And I said, survive?
I don't think we're talking about the same thing.
If I see a blade of grass growing in the median of the road, I know I could survive.
What are you talking about?
Survival.
Yeah.
What does that mean?
You know, so when you get down to it, if there's vegetation, you will live.
Now, there will be a point in the future, well, you won't have much time anyway.
The vegetation will all be gone, right?
It'll be all of it burned up.
Yeah.
But then after that, you won't be worried about vegetation being gone.
So anyway, yeah, you wouldn't be worried at all.
You know, it's another interesting thing.
It's not in scripture, but I would suggest that those that are left here, if there's no vegetation and the animals are fixing on biting your leg off, what are people going to eat?
You know, well, we've been given examples before in scripture when there was nothing to eat, they were given something to eat.
Remember the manna?
It's quite interesting.
The scripture everyone's going to eat.
Survivors are going to get manna.
But I'm just thinking, you know, you have to provide, just like when you throw someone on death row or prison or whatever, they still give you food.
I mean, typically.
Typically.
You know, I'm just thinking, yeah, they call it a rite or whatever, but yeah, so.
Yeah, last week, yeah.
So, I would suggest, again, I wouldn't suggest directly, but indirectly as much as possible, a vegetarian type thing.
Now, vegan, a vegetarian diet, but vegan is something that comes up often.
Mixed review, vegan is excellent if you know how to do it, but what I have found, I'll give you, I'll share some personal experience.
In short, what you see in most western cultures as being vegan is white people that don't know how to cook, and when they make their food and it tastes bad and you complain, they say, well, it's vegan, that's why.
Right?
Where it's quite the contrary.
Properly prepared vegan food is some of the most delicious food you'll ever eat.
I'll give an experience.
About 35 years ago, I was at Thompson, Tompkins Square Park on the east side of lower Manhattan, and someone says, hey man, the Krishnas are coming, you know, they're gonna pull up with their Krishnamobile and they're gonna feed everyone.
Let's go eat.
I'm like, nah.
But anyway, I went there and I had the most delicious food and it's all, you know, vegan, right?
No animal products whatsoever, right?
Right.
So after that, we went to this one restaurant, maybe 10 years later, and I was like, oh, this food is dry, there's no flavor, and the waitress says it's vegan.
And I'm like, oh.
And then I went to this lady, she was baking vegan cookies.
You know, these are white people in a restaurant, you know.
And I said, these are terrible.
She goes, oh, it's vegan.
And I went to someone's house, says I'm vegan.
I said, this food is horrible.
She goes, it's vegan.
That's why I'm like, wait a second, it doesn't add up.
So when all the people that ethnically know how to do it, it's delicious.
And when these Westerners get into it, it's not very good.
Oh, I see what's happening here.
Yeah.
Leave it alone.
Just say you need to watch more late-night cooking channel show, whatever.
You just don't have it going.
So leave it alone.
So that's essentially what I found out.
And it could be some of the most delicious food you'll ever eat because there's a lot of various schools of thought.
Like one of the things I've learned, like you spice the food a certain way.
So if you were, let's say at the beach and you threw the food on the sand, the seagulls and the crabs wouldn't eat it because of the spice combinations, you see.
So it's supposed to only for humans.
And you know, you see what I mean?
So that's like one philosophy.
There are many schools of thought, but the Vedics, by the way, in the Mahabharata, were always the culprits.
They would be like the Sadducees and the Pharisees of the New Testament.
They were not viewed very well.
They were extreme.
They were dogmatic and deviant.
But you know, so everything is kind of backwards.
But this is a whole other conversation if you want to get into those writings and read them positively.
But I would suggest that, again, maybe doing future discussions on quote-unquote vegetarian applications.
It excites me.
One of the simplest things to do for people is, I suggest before you get into this or as you get into vegetarian type cooking, get as familiar as possible with Middle Eastern and Asian ingredients.
And then once you get familiar with those ingredients and you get the immediate satisfaction because the quick recipes and the quick combinations will yield good results, then you start to learn more local, and I mean cross-latitude substitutes, right?
Right.
So if you don't have tahini, which is sesame butter or paste, you know, liquid, you can substitute other nut butters, right?
If you don't have one type of grain, you could substitute it with another.
And so it's basically grains, legumes, which are beans, right?
And vegetables.
And you have to understand the use of root and leaf and spice and all that.
And you can create some really delicious meals that way.
And quote-unquote meat hearty meals, you know, meat substitutes, if you're living around the carnivorous types.
I think here it posted, let me just read it again, it was the tempeh-chestnut mix.
Tempeh is a fermented dry soybean cake, right?
It's an easy way to say it.
With chestnuts, which are underused.
If you've ever had roasted chestnuts, that's a common thing, especially people growing up in rural environments or where they're available, you know, they split open and they have a wonderful inside the chestnut.
It's a sweet, pecan kind of, you know, it's a wonderful nut, or I don't know, it's a fruit really, what's a nut really, isn't it?
Yeah.
Now most dried nuts like walnuts, almonds, cashews, and things like that, when they're heated with moisture, they get soft, right?
Right.
If you've ever, yeah.
So, you know, when they're heated with moisture, they'll absorb the moisture and take on more of a softer fleshy kind of texture and flavor changes as well.
So we can get into sort of describing quick meals and the best thing to do when you, let's say you, well just like anything, you know, like taking notes when you hear something new, right?
And you refer back to that.
If you're going to learn to eat vegetarian, let's say it's good to develop a menu so you don't have to wing it, you know, and go get some burgers, you know?
You see what I mean?
And also you have to be careful, there's a tremendous market towards the vegetarian people, like veg burgers and so some of that stuff is just crap.
I wouldn't say most of it, I haven't tried most of it.
I steer away from pre-packaged stuff.
But, you know, there's a big market, you'll see veggie burgers and veggie this and veggie that and soy this and soy that and especially to the American market, I would say the quality is spurious and questionable and I wouldn't, I don't, yeah, I wouldn't say that it's something that you should pursue.
Right.
The pre-packaged stuff, now unless you know that it's a reputable, you know, and then you'll end up paying more pound for pound than a steak because you can get a lot of beef and chicken and stuff at just a couple of bucks a pound.
You look at a thing of high quality veggie burgers, you know, it's like not even a pound and it's 10 bucks.
You're like, uh, that's now I'm getting to the price of prime rib, right?
So it's just vegetables.
So they're telling you, hey, look, if you're lazy, we're willing to separate you from your credit.
Yeah.
So, all right.
Anything else, any other questions, any other considerations?
We had Vandy Man asking about, uh, let's see, only missing the milk with cooking plant-based substitutes give different results.
How about a shortcut pointer, please, for making sauces and such.
For making sauces and such, some shortcut pointers.
Oh, uh, let me see.
Only missing the milk with cooking.
Well, milk is a thickener by the way.
When I've made soups and sauces for people, especially if they're not tomato based, when I add milk, they're always wondering, oh, this is delicious.
How did you thicken it?
I said, with milk.
And they're like, what?
They don't think of milk as a thickener, as a flavor agent.
It has a lot of, you know, flavors.
Well, if you cook it, see, if you, if you warm it, it has a lot of flavor.
If you heat it, it doesn't.
But if you boil it, it does again.
Milk is one of these things, almost like onions.
If they were hard to grow, they'd be a delicacy.
You know how onions are sulfury and pungent when you cook them, they get really sweet.
Right.
If you had the transformation that takes place with an onion, if they were difficult to grow, they would be like truffles.
It would be very expensive, right?
Which truffles are not, by the way, lawful for me.
They're like mushrooms.
But, uh, I would suggest that, um, milk can do that.
But anyway, I just spun off on that.
Okay.
Given different results.
How about a shortcut pointer, please, for making sauces and such?
There is no shortcut for that because sauces, there's an entire school of cooking devoted just to making sauces and stocks.
And the simplest way I could say with a sauce and let's say such would be a broth in a stock and any other wet consistency, uh, would suggest that if you bring it up to a high heat and you see a foam or a scum or anything rise to the top, that is not one particular ingredient.
Skim it off.
That's all the undigestible stuff, you know?
Uh, the other thing I would suggest is, uh, you have to understand that, uh, if you know the ingredient, um, you, then, you know, each individual ingredient, what, you know, started, what combination is complimentary to the next.
Like, you know, for example, when you're making a stock or a broth with veg, if you cook it too much, you kill all the flavor, right?
Have you ever, have you ever like, uh, cooked a carrot, uh, let's say for 15 minutes and it's got all the wonderful carrot flavor, but if you cook it for 45 or a half an hour, it has no flavor.
It's just like eating a vegetable fiber.
Yeah.
So yeah.
So, but you can cook a carrot.
I could show you a cook carrot for six hours and it'll have more flavor than ever.
Yeah.
How do you do that?
Well, it depends on how the heat is applied.
It's all about heat management.
Now, if you're going to get into gazpachos and things that are cold combinations or raw foods, the combination is more critical because you're not looking as a factor for heat to change anything.
You know, if you put raw onion in a raw, uh, sauce, it's going to be raw.
It's going to taste just like that unless you can combine it with something that will maybe direct the, uh, the palate somewhere else, but it, that it will not go away.
You know, that raw onion sulfur will not go away.
Right.
So, so it gets, if you get into raw foods, then it gets a little more complicated, but it, but then it's, it's still complicated when you're adding heat.
Uh, I would suggest always what, what I do just, and this is also very conscientious of the evolution, I should say the unfolding or the way humanity has been.
I can give, this is, if I'm going to give just a short hint of an anything is inconsistent heat, unless you're baking a cake or something with a batter.
Inconsistent heat is the key to delicious sauces and delicious stocks and broths.
Why?
What I mean by inconsistent heat, you know how people have a, either a gas or electric stove top and they set a timer or they set, they bring something to a simmer and then turn it down low and it's consistent, right?
Food preparation was never that way.
I mean, the thing is it could be with a hearth that is hot enough, but you always had varying temperatures.
You know, let's say, imagine you have a hearth and it's not stone and you're cooking on it.
The coals will burn down and then you add more coals.
So as they're, you know, the food goes on, it's very hot and then the temperature drops a little bit or a lot.
Then it goes back up again when you added the fresh coals, right?
After 20 minutes, cause you're cooking, let's say a roast.
So you have this heat that goes up and down and up and down.
Now you don't want that for batter baking, you know, like a cake or something that could ruin the cake, right?
Uh, that's why the best bakeries have very heavy ovens.
But for sauces, what I do, I'll give you an example.
If I'm making, let's say a sauce of any type, uh, I would, uh, bring it to a simmer, bring it down low and then turn it off, walk away five minutes, 10 minutes, an hour, come back, bring it up again to a simmer and then turn it down low, 15, 20 minutes or so, turn it off, walk away five minutes, 10 minutes, an hour.
You see, and then you, you, what happens is this expansion and contraction inside the, the, the ingredients, right?
So when you're applying heat, let's say to a carrot, that's in a Bugs Bunny cartoon, you know, he's in the zoo, what do you, you know, thanks for the bath and he's slicing the carrots in there, you know?
But what happens when you, when you, when you put the, I'm using the carrot all the time here as a reference, and as the temperature goes up, the pressure around the carrot increases and the flavors or the carrot material moves away from the outside.
When you, but the heat, the heat changes it though, makes it more flowable because it, you know, the cell's being broken down, let's say softened up.
But when you turn down the heat, the, the liquid around the carrot now contracts and it pulls the, the flavor out of the carrot, doesn't it?
Versus compressing it in, right?
Right.
And you just do that several times and you've drawn the flavor out of the carrot by inconsistent heat.
That's why like the worst thing to me is crock pot cooking.
All these white people think crock pot cooking is so good.
I'm like, oh, there's no flavor.
What is that?
What?
Yeah, I see there's like, you got this side and the other, but that doesn't, that's just, why?
Because it's consistent heat.
Yeah.
Consistently, you know, for hours or whatever, eight hours, whatever the thing goes on.
That's not how things are cooked.
I mean, this is not how things, well, you can cook it that way, but that, it doesn't work well.
Not recommended.
For, for, at least for the, it depends on what kind of a palate you have.
You know, if you're dealing with people, if you're dealing with people and you ask them, how is, how does that taste?
And they say it's good.
Well, obviously, you know, you have two, there's, there's a fork in the road there.
One is you have to start explaining to them how to communicate what food tastes like, or they never, they're just not, they just not into, they're not attached to their palate.
It's either good or bad.
And they can't tell you what it is or whatever.
Right.
So there's several different ways.
Like a simple example would be salt, you know, a very good salt when you just taste it, let's say plain, you know, just a grain, it should initially be salty.
And then it gives you the essence of the mineral is a little metallic, a little earthy, or whatever.
And then it should have a sweet finish.
That's how high quality salts are.
Right?
So when you first touch it on your tongue, you know, it's salt, you get the salt node going, right?
And then it's what you look quality of the salt may taste a little earthy or metallic or sharp.
And then it should finish off being sweet.
If you get like the iodized salt that most people have a restaurant serve, you put it on your tongue, it's salt, and then it's salt, and then it's salt, and it's saltier.
And it just has like this electric galvanic buzz.
Yeah, that's not good.
That is a chemical, I mean, byproduct that is a, you see, so like a high quality salt will always have a sweet finish.
No, it doesn't make any sense.
I try it, I don't taste it.
I'm like, well, fine, it's not for you.
Then food is either good or bad.
You know, I mean, that's a whole other category there.
Most people don't taste their food, and they don't want to know about tasting their food.
And the only reason I'm saying it this way, well, you know, most people might say, well, that's not me Greek.
I know.
But I'm just saying, this is the if this was not the predominant mindset, you know, why is it you can't find good places to eat?
You see, so I believe you summed it up once before standard American diet, sad, sad.
Yeah.
So again, giving the example with assault is is a simple way to, you know, understand the palate.
Good analogy.
You guys are not supposed to know that I used to do private chefing and all that other kind of stuff, too.
So I'm not supposed to know that.
Not supposed to.
So anyway, you've never gotten that from the conversations.
No, no, I don't think so.
But it gets interesting.
I think the food stuff is important because it's really the fuel, you know, in a different world.
Yeah, yeah.
It fuels the the the passions of the individuals, too.
I mean, I think I've mentioned before, when I was out in the Midwest of America, various classes of people, meaning people living literally out of their cars, people living in trailers, people living in small homes, and people living in, you know, McMansions.
Right.
And they all whenever I stayed with any one of those, I felt sick because of what they ate.
I'm like, are you joking?
This is how you people eat.
I feel sick, you know, in the Midwest.
And the irony of it is that's where all the food is produced.
Yeah, yeah.
So I'll never forget.
I can definitely tell just from listening to you, you have a passion, a great understanding.
And it must have showed very well in your work and probably still does.
I hope so.
I try to keep to myself more than I ever have in my life before.
But I just want to give a little food story.
I was in an upper middle class place in the Midwest.
And the lady says, preparing lunch.
I'm fine.
I walk in and there's a smell of like warm cardboard.
And she has this big plate and I see these things.
I said, are those egg rolls, empanadas?
What are they?
She goes, oh, those are hot pockets.
And I'm like, what?
I've heard of something on television.
Let me just try it because it didn't smell like food.
It just smelled like warm cardboard.
Fat, smell the fat in the air.
Yeah.
And it just had no, it was just salt and some kind of texture.
And I was like, no, thanks.
So, you know, this is, I mean, this is the culture here, you know, and again, I'm addressing the American audience.
Shame on you guys for, you know, having the breadbasket of the world, you know, which really is Russia.
But the problem is you can't get, they don't have the infrastructure developed as known.
They are now.
Yeah.
But America was typically with all the coastal waters.
They don't have as many rivers and coasts to move things.
They have to move by land, you know, and even though they have rivers, it's not, they're not as connected as well as here.
So it's interesting how you have the most availability of food in what's called the states.
But I noticed that you won't engage in the best quality food in the states unless you're on the coast, east coast, north or west coast, more towards the south.
You know, that's where you have the European and Asian influence and demand.
Yeah.
So, you know, because they do demand it, you know, it's not this challenge.
The biggest challenge, if I know I'm speaking to American audiences, anyone in the Midwest, and I start doing a cooking talk, it's like, where are you going to get the ingredients in the Midwest?
Yeah.
You're going to drive 40 miles to get a miso.
And even if they know what you're talking about, you know, so, you know, I'm not, it doesn't have to be, I mean, there's many, you can make everything from scratch, but I'm just saying, I think one way to give immediate direction is for immediate gratification to, so you feel victorious.
You know, you don't want to start out your journey and defeat.
Yeah, right.
You want to feel victorious every step of the way, and not to build a false confidence, but to to encourage confidence on a new path, let's say.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
So, it's going to be interesting with the food, but so far I've always kept it very basic, you know, very basic stuff with high success.
Anything else?
Anything else going on?
I understand the talk of the palate.
I was instructed how to eat and taste only in my late 30s.
Anglo-Saxon diet is garbage.
Yes, we, so we have a little confirmation there.
We do have some confirmation.
And so, one out of ten people agree so far.
I think there was a struggle that was ensued.
There was a spiritual problem behind that also.
You know, spiritual meaning the people that, you know, that set the culture.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
You know, and I've gotten into the, the...
It was orchestrated.
Well, the Anglo-Saxons were the Babylonians that did all this really nasty shit right after the flood.
They were on the run, and they were so much on the run that even they couldn't even stay at the Mediterranean Rim, you know, the Mediterranean Rim where they could be gotten.
They had to go all the way, way, way, way, you know.
Wow.
Yeah.
And, you know, not everybody, not everybody in the Middle East looks like when people, you know, say, oh, I'm not, I'm red-haired and really light-skinned.
I'm like, yeah, so what do you think?
If you came out of Babylon, you're supposed to have like dark skin and a hook nose with black curly hair.
What are you talking about?
You know, everybody, you know, that you had the entire, you had blonde hair, blue eyes in there, as a matter of fact, still today.
So, and, you know, the Danites, well, we'll get into what people looked like back then.
And the best thing, though, is to actually bring up some supportive material.
Yeah, and the bloodlines, how that transfers, that'd be an interesting subject unto itself.
Yeah, if you do, see, if you start doing research without doing research on what someone researched that someone else researched, you can get more objective, but you still, the shortcut is important, you know.
You can see what people look like if you research on your own, but, you know, look at everything, you know.
Like if you talk about a certain, let's say, bloodline or whatever, you know, in a conversation or even within your own research, you'll find a lot written about it.
But that was written because someone else wrote something else about it that got it from someone else that wrote something else about it.
So, you go through all that really quickly and see what the sources are and go there and start looking at source material as much as possible.
I think they call it mirroring now on the internet, right, when you mirror something.
That's been done by academia for its time immemorial.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, that's why, you know, they tout Greek philosophy and you look at an ancient Greek and you're like, that's not what it says.
Because they were mirroring bad translations, you know, from a thousand years ago now, you know, still in print.
Oh yeah.
Well, the Bible is an excellent example of it.
Example, yes.
We all know how that one got ended.
All right, what do you think?
How long have we been going?
Let's see, let's just take a little peek here.
We're at an hour and a half on this segment.
Yeah.
Okay, anything else from anyone?
I'm not seeing anything.
Let's see, you can take one more final peek here.
Because we're not coming in with, you know, a subject here to fill in.
So, this is kind of open.
Yeah, and we didn't get any calls.
That was kind of a shame.
Oh, can Greek go into picking apart more lies regarding nutrition and about blood sugar?
Is there such a thing as low blood sugar?
Is anything true in respect regarding insulin and how the body handles sugar consumption?
There was some study done on that about fruit and the sugars and, of course, eating of the fruit.
You were also eating the stuff that helped break down the sugars out of the fruit.
Okay, let's just go back.
I don't want to get into the specifics because looking at the myopathy of the whole thing of nutrition is very simple.
When you eat anything or drink water, if you go study, very often when I would do this in interviews, I would drop to the host what the intestines look like.
And then I would show it next to what a steel-belted radial tire looks like.
And there's almost no difference.
Nothing ever gets through inside.
When you eat anything, regardless of what it is, or even water, it doesn't pass into the body at all.
It passes from the mouth to the anus and it goes through various induction centers, you know, the mouth, the throat.
You know, you have taste buds in the throat as well.
And it goes down to the stomach, duodenum, small intestine, large intestine, colon, and out.
And by the way, most people eat, they probably have taste buds on their anus.
But anyway, so if you look, if you study all of those, the mechanical or the anatomical aspects, and even though, you know, when you see across sections of the entire digestive system, those are from dead people, by the way.
Yeah.
Because they're not putting it under a microscope when someone is alive, especially in a cross-section.
I mean, there have been experiments, you know, with digestion years ago, about 200 years ago, a guy came in with a shotgun wound in the stomach, and they kept it alive, and they kept putting food in there with a string.
Do you remember that, doctor?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, wasn't somebody with a glass stomach?
Yeah, or something.
Yeah, something in that order, yeah.
Now, remember what happens when something dies, it starts disassociating, right?
Like, a cadaver flesh is not as firm and as ductile as a living flesh or skin.
So, remember, even though you're looking at all these anatomical diagrams, that is from dead things, and they still look robustly sealed, and closed, and hermetically sealed.
Could you imagine how much tighter it is on a living being?
Much tighter, right?
So, when you see the distance between the cell walls and what's called an intestine, that's on a dead tissue slide that's been preserved.
In the living creature, they're much tighter than that, even.
Much, much tighter.
See?
So, now, let's fast forward.
I need to leave, like, five years for what I just said to sink in, before I talk about anything else.
But, what I mean by that is, if there's too much or too little sugar in the blood, or minerals, or whatever, how did it get there, if nothing goes in?
Yeah, because if it went through the intestines or anywhere else, you'd be dying in sepsis.
Yeah.
That's right, you will die.
And, stop thinking that there's so many millions of doctors, and students, and universities that teach you get absorbed.
Yeah, there's a planet full of morons, why should they be?
Where did they come from?
Where did your scientists, and doctors, and animaticians, and all these people come from?
Alpha Centauri, Mars, Pluto, where did they come from?
No, they're from Earth.
Oh, oh, okay.
No, thanks.
Now, they've done a lot of grunt work, because, how do I know?
They've taken slides from dead creatures, and cataloged them, and illustrated them, haven't they?
That's a lot of grunt work.
But, they can't see anything other than that, right?
They can't.
So, how did it get in there?
How did any sugar, or any water get in the blood, and how did anything?
That is the real question.
What is the mechanism behind that?
You see?
And, there you will have your answer, yeah.
Yeah.
And, that goes on into specific things.
So, how do, the best way to deal, you know, do the opposite for more effect.
Sometimes, you know, something becomes too much of one thing, it flips, and becomes its opposite.
So, in this case, if someone is diagnosed with a low blood sugar, that, unless you were, you came out of the womb like that, and developed into your formative years like that, if it is a later condition, that condition is done by two things.
One, it's a, what they call hereditary, or genetic timing, right?
And, the other thing, the other thing would be your behavior.
So, no one knows how to remedy that, other than you.
Yeah.
It's obviously what you're doing.
So, make a list of everything you do, or you've been doing something that's catching up.
Yeah.
And, you find the structure.
Make a list of everything you're regularly doing, and then what you think you should be doing, and then reverse the list.
Yeah.
But, well, you think you should be doing most of the time, people know.
They'll tell you.
Just like they say, well, where did the year go?
It's December, right?
You know, they're saying it, but they don't have an answer.
Oh, yeah, I know I eat too many hot dogs for breakfast, right?
You know what I mean?
Oh, I know I've been eating too much meat lately.
I know I should be eating less ketchup.
I know I should learn how to cook.
I know I should be using a gas burner instead of an electric stove.
I know people say it all the time, what they should be doing.
They have their answer.
Yeah.
They're answering themselves.
A good way to reset, this has worked with people before, is what's a reset?
You know, if you fully reset a computer, you kind of go back to how it was brand new, isn't it?
Don't you?
I mean, usually.
Let's say you reset it to the point where you have to put, you know, reload the operating system.
Yeah.
Other than what, you know, the hard drive will always mark that it's had stuff on it before, even though you don't see it, right?
Right.
But for all intent and purpose of this, it's reset from the beginning.
Let me ask you, other than when you reset the human, don't you go back to eating baby food?
No.
Right.
I'm not talking about, you know, mother's milk now.
You don't need that.
No.
Even though it would be, you know, the ultimate reset, not necessary though.
I would suggest going back to a baby food type diet.
What does that mean?
Broth, very soft porridges, purees.
Think about it.
Yeah.
And do that for a month.
Watch what happens to your body.
I've told, I remember even myself, I did a vegetable broth diet for just four or five days and I felt renewed.
Right.
Wow.
So, yeah.
Interesting antidote.
And then the scary part is when you go from a baby food, a baby diet, then to adolescent junk food, right?
Yeah.
And no, I'm serious.
You will experience that.
If you do the baby food thing, you'll be craving double, triple cheeseburgers with french fries and melted cheese on it.
Yeah.
Sugars.
But you reset that way.
And, uh, remember also when you told me about that with the sugars that you went to the store that one time to get some ice cream and, oh yeah.
Yeah.
Nobody getting your weight.
I felt that.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
Anyone that I once did the macrobiotic diet thing about 30 years ago.
And, uh, and I still do by the way, but not strict.
I understand the concepts.
Once you understand the concepts, you never go back.
Like once you know that the day starts at noon and the moon is the month you never, even though you may not use it, you'll never, you know, you'll always see a full moon.
Or you'll see noontime.
You're like, oh, it's tomorrow.
You know, even though you see the anomalies.
Sure.
So the same thing, when you do the, when they're very dogmatic, I call them macro neurotics, you know, like you, you look too healthy to be eating health food, you know, kind of thing.
But I did that really, I did a crash on it.
And, uh, it was very athletic at the time.
Brown rice, umabashi plum, uh, dookie beans, seaweed, um, and all this other stuff.
And, uh, uh, I found myself getting up at two in the morning.
Uh, I'll remember.
And I go down the street to the convenience store and I went to the ice cream and the Oreo cookies and the graham crackers and those hit crackers.
It's a dollar for a whole bunch of cookies, a HIT brand from Korea or something.
Sure.
And I opened them all that.
And I sat there, I was eating it online, but I didn't care if I was getting to the register or not, because it was just, you know, I just needed to eat it.
And, you know, I knew I was going to pay for it.
And if anyone got in my way, I would just, I would have been murderous.
That is the drive that I had.
Wow.
That is an intense, intense, uh, emotion behind the food that, and you said you've experienced something like that.
Yeah.
And it was, it was weird.
I kept having these cravings that, you know, oh, you should stop and get a soda or you, you know, you should get this.
And I turned my head, you know, just walk away.
Because your body was, you know, imprinted and used to producing nutrition out of those things internally.
Right.
And it wasn't there.
So I would, so I would suggest, uh, this is the way I suggest people transition diets with, uh, let's say if you want to go from, you know, uh, omnivore in meat to non-meat or, or anything, or vegetarian or any diet change, uh, set up the menu and the ingredients, start acquiring all the ingredients in the menu that you, you, that's your target menu, the way you want to eat in the future, right?
Eat however you're eating now and start incorporating those new foods in there.
And then over time, a few days or weeks, uh, start diminishing what, how you're currently eating and add more of those.
Yeah.
And then eventually you won't notice the difference at all that way.
Right.
Got to kind of work your way out of it.
Transition.
Yeah.
It's like through the spectrum, right?
You go from one aspect of the spectrum through the other, there's no boundary, harsh boundary.
Actually in reality, when you run light through a prism, there are very harsh boundaries, but I'm saying that there's a mellow spectrum trans transition.
You start incorporating what you, what you want to do, and then you start phasing out slowly and gradually at your pace.
Some people can go, can just stop and go.
You have to know yourself.
Yeah.
And if you don't know yourself, you're going to find out.
Well, I did hit it kind of hard, but yeah, I, I, I can realize that more and more and, and it's getting better.
It's a lot of that's worked out and I, I feel a lot better because of it.
Yeah.
Well, good, good.
The, the body will throw you down, um, uh, mechanically, just like if you misuse a car, you know, no matter what kind of a car it is or you don't maintain it, you know, you say, well, I haven't changed the oil in four years.
It's fine.
And then just one day the thing blows and you're like, everything was fine.
It blew, you know?
So you have to know what's required.
And, um, speaking of which we, I think we, I think I've seen Wes.
Yeah.
Wes was one of the guys that brought up the question and, uh, I do look forward to that chat someday there, Wes.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, uh, anything else or, uh, let's see.
Yeah, we can probably do that.
Let's see.
There was one more, uh, however, hasn't it been shown that a person on what they label now as ketogenic diet, uh, will have ketones in their bloodstream after taking a blood sample.
Apparently, well, the body produces that.
Look, it doesn't matter what this, well, look, okay.
That's the diagram that they, okay.
What happens is they've gone off to the extreme point where they're looking, uh, it's the elephant, uh, syndrome thing.
They don't know what they're looking at so that, but they have to produce something.
Okay.
Put a label on it in other words.
Yeah.
Um, for example, if you eat a polyvinyl chloride PVC plastic, you swallow like a game
piece, you know, a plastic checker piece, um, that will not show up in your blood really because
your body doesn't recognize that as something like margarine, your body doesn't recognize
margarine as something you could produce, but it recognizes some of the processes and the energies
in the margarine and start screwing with your system.
Right.
That's why there was no, there was no heart attack or heart epidemic in the U S until they introduced margarine.
Yeah.
It was margarine was injured and also iodized salt.
What was the big thing like that?
Um, you know, there's, uh, go eaters.
Remember that back in the thirties, twenties and you were given iodized salt in the early sixties.
Yeah, no, no.
I, yeah, yeah.
That was, well, these are sick people by the way.
You know, like for example, when you look at the high level medical people or Supreme court judges and, or high level attorneys or high level bankers, all the conspiracy theories you hear about their personal lives in reality, it's 10 times, they're 10 times worse than that.
And you don't have to meet them to know it.
It's obvious, right?
It doesn't matter when you know, you're sharing a few stories on them.
Oh boy.
So, I mean, even recently they have a Supreme court judge that was found at a ranch, you know, died supposedly or whatever.
And yeah, I mean, your mind can go with the conspiracies or whatever.
I'm telling you it's much worse than you've ever imagined.
So don't even go there.
If that's why I think it's best that people don't know the truth about what's going on this planet, because I sleep at night.
That's why I finalize it with the analogy of be thankful.
No one came in and he pulled your liver out of your body when you're sleeping.
That's right at that point right now.
And you don't realize it.
That's good that you don't realize it because it takes a very strong character to be able to, you know, relax into that notion.
So, but when the body absorbs, shows things in what's called blood and all that, that's produced by the body, by influences that have gone through the body, not into the body.
When you eat food, it doesn't go into your body, it passes through the body.
Many, many different things.
Remember old cassette VHS tapes?
Yeah.
There's not, the movie's not like being, it's not jumping off the tape into the VCR drum and into the wire and into the TV.
The movie is always on that tape.
As a matter of fact, if anything comes off of that tape, you lose the integrity of it, you see.
It's induction, you know, that's happening.
It's really mind-boggling when you compare it to what we've been told how things work.
You know what I mean?
Right, right.
So, so what do you do in this case?
You know that, let me, let me just, this might be comforting.
Years ago there was a study, this was done in the 50s, again it was done in the 70s and 80s and they stopped.
I'm not sure if it was the Red Cross, I'm not sure.
I need to one day look this up seriously again, but I put this away because it's not going to help, you know, society at large or even anyone listening because if they're still not going to find out how the body works.
But there was a study done by one of these world health organizations and they, the study was about how centurions live, like people live over a hundred.
So they went and tested, like went to like Hunza, Crete, Okinawa, places where they knew they would find a high concentration of people that lived at 200 or over.
And they're surprised they typically found these people, they were not bedridden, some of them were still getting up every morning and working, you know, in the field, doing agricultural work or smithing or something, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So, so they proceeded to take their vitals, blood sugar, blood pressure, and it was absolutely through the roof.
I mean, we're looking at blood pressures like 170 over 200 and something, you know, it was at 120.
And, and blood sugars that were 15 times acceptable normal level.
And these are people that are 100 and some odd years old still working in the field.
We're not talking about, you know, on their deathbed, right?
Right.
So they, and this was consistent and wherever they went in the world, the vitals of these people, these old people that were still full of vitality had horrible vitals, horrible vitals.
I mean, if you were a Westerner and they read a blood pressure like that, they'd throw you in an ambulance, bring you to the ER or do a sneeze or whatever, right?
Or put you on medication or give you insulin, you know?
So what they did was, yeah, I found this in print a while back and they stopped doing the studies because it went contrary.
Now, this made complete sense to me, because at the time, let's say in bicycling, cycling, there was something called the fit kit.
You see, unlike just a regular bicycle that you jump on, when you get into, just like any sport, whether it's a glove in baseball or a tennis racket or a bicycle or whatever, it has to be fit.
You know, we're not talking off the rack.
So how you set the seat height, the pedal cleat position, the handlebars and all that other stuff, people try to find a standard way.
So what they did was they took the measurements of 100 professional bike racers, okay?
And they averaged them all out, then they try to apply that as a standard fit kit to everyone.
And I'm like, wait a second, that doesn't work because a professional bike racer can nominally spend six to eight hours a day riding the bike, where if you find a local yokel who bought a bike because he thinks it's cool or wants to get into a recreational that rides two hours a month, you can't apply that average to him.
You know what I mean?
So that's what they're doing.
When they're telling you blood sugars and blood pressure, they're averaging out from a study group of people what it should be.
Now if they eat Hot Pockets for lunch every day, I don't care what their blood pressure is, do not compare mine to that, right?
I don't want the magic cuff on me.
That's the magic cuff, by the way.
You know, there's no blood pressure, they put the cuff.
That's the sphigometer.
Yeah.
The sphigometer, yeah.
Sphigometer, which literally means to squeeze and measure.
So, yeah, this is what they're pulling on everyone.
And they're getting away with it because it's not the medicine that they're putting on people.
It's two things.
They're getting away with it because, number one, its efficacy is very low.
And number two, it's a testament to the robustness of the human creature, meaning the creation, how much of a beating and abuse it could take.
Like I said, Midwestans eat at an average American white people family for a week, if you eat good food, and you will be sick.
It's kind of like that movie, oh, a guy ate McDonald's for a month, do you remember that?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like that.
So this is how people eat every day.
That's why when you go, I mean, in public, the way people look and act is because if you go home and eat and live with them for a week, you will be sick.
I will.
And they're sick because of the way they eat and what they think, of course, also.
But there's many levels to this, but the simplest thing is how and when are people going to understand how the body really works, because it's headquarters.
And if you're deceived about headquarters, the only thing that'll go in and out is deception.
So I don't see the possibility of people understanding how the human body works at society at large ever, until this is wrapped up.
But in the meantime, it doesn't mean you can't just speak on it.
And I used to, in private, get into long specifics about it, but ultimately, what works best for everyone is they know what they're doing, they know what they should be doing or could be doing, and that's the easiest way to change one's condition.
The car is a metaphor.
For example, I'll use an engine-driven wagon is what I mean by a car.
I'll use a car for several years before I need brakes done.
And then other people need their brakes done every six months.
And you're like, what's going on here?
And then you get in the car with them and drive, and you see they're accelerating, and then they slam it on this red light, right?
And then here they go again, there's a red light, whoa, hit the brakes again.
Okay, so they're racing to the red lights.
And if you ask them, whoa, yeah, I know I do that, I shouldn't be doing that.
Okay, you get into the car with them six months later, what are they doing?
Still racing the red lights.
They admitted that they shouldn't be doing, but they're still doing it.
Right.
That's why they need a brake job every year, every six months.
Hurry up and stop.
So it's the same thing with the human body.
Yeah.
But it's not completely the same thing, because if you think hot pockets are food, or canned string beans and whatever is food, right?
You probably will never, like you say, well, I eat too much canned corn, maybe I should eat more canned string beans.
No, now you're stuck in the same mode.
You don't that one, you won't be able to help yourself in that, you see.
You get it?
Yes, I do.
Yeah, yeah, Greek, I ate too many canned corn, I didn't go to canned string beans.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no.
See, then discussing this is, then, you know, we have to get more basic.
And then ultimately, you'll find out they don't grasp what life is, the life energy, it's just chemicals.
And then, then you chalk off another one.
Okay, here's another 6,999,000,000 space eaters on the planet.
What's that thing with beers on the wall?
100 beers on the wall?
Yeah, yeah.
And beers on the wall, yeah.
Yeah, 699,000,000,000.
Oh, yeah, another one.
Yeah.
Oh, my.
So, you know, there's many levels.
That's why the specifics don't matter.
When I gave specifics about these things, it was not confusion, but it was a lot to tend to, not a lot of progress.
When I just say, for example, eat seasonally, your body doesn't absorb anything.
If you're not feeling well, it's because of your behavior, change your behavior, what you eat and all that.
I get 100 emails saying, Greek, I tried that, it works.
Right off the bat, simple, great.
I used to get, you know, a sore throat in the winter every year.
I listened to you say, I never got it again.
Very simple.
All right.
Just keep it simple, broad strokes, general, and it works for just about everyone.
And it's simple, and it's amazing how the obviousness of reality, the obviousness of any subject is not out there, not anywhere, really.
You know, that's why, you know, the adversary, he divides, he confuses, he lies, and eventually leads to murder, because he was known as a murderer, right?
Right, right.
Now, if you convince someone to go out and get a gun, and then convince them to shoot themselves, you know, by harsh, you know, standards around them, you're the one that really murdered them, even though they did everything physically themselves, right?
Spiritually, you know.
But legally, in a strict, by operation of law, they committed suicide, you see.
So, right now, humanity is being murdered through suicide, essentially.
But that's, I mean, it's not a surprise.
Again, that's why there's no comprehension of ancient writs, because ancient writs speak very poorly of people, and anyone who tries to reckon that with the mindset that they think that what they see in the world is good, they're never going to comprehend the ancient writ.
But if you say, I'm looking for the truth, and you have two sources of reality, or perception, or information, saying that they're both good, but they're both very, they're opposing to each other, then they're either both wrong, or only one is correct, you see, because they both can't be correct.
So, that's the other thing with the organized religion thing, you know.
They're all wrong.
That's why they're organized.
Okay, anything else?
Well, you see, I think we've pretty much wrapped all of them up.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, all right.
So, you've got plenty of room on the server to load up another one, right?
Plenty of room.
Okay, great.
I just want to thank everyone who's come over to the chat and the emails.
I've gotten about 50 emails the past couple of days, and also donations.
I've gotten a few envelopes this week.
I appreciate all of it, and yeah, it just shows that it's not for naught.
There's some reciprocation, and yeah.
And for all you folks out there, we have another couple of months left here, another month or two, this one and the next.
We'll see how the new year comes around.
It's going to be the start of a new period.
Keep yourself aware of that, and we'll get into more details probably on another Sonic event.
Maybe we'll structure a Sonic event around a subject and keep that going this way.
But the intent for tonight was to have call-ins, which didn't transpire, but that's okay.
It worked out all right.
We got some good answers, I think.
And if you'll notice, no matter what subject, if it's, I like to have a Swiss Army knife approach.
It's just, you know, go back to the basics of it, you know, which is kind of difficult for most people, you know, because of all the distractions.
Right, right.
You know, so.
All right, Bruce, thanks.
Yes, I thank you as always.
I've been enlightened again, and I'm very thankful for it.
Good.
You're welcome, and thanks for doing all your questions out there.
It was much appreciated.
It was an interesting set of topics, and you have yourself a good night, sir, and be well.
Okay, you as well.
Thanks, Bruce.
See you.
See everyone.