There we are, greetings Greek, and greetings everyone, yeah, okay, we're here again, yes,
it's just the first week of the sixth month, right, yes, correct, apparently, yeah, I believe
it's the fifth, if I'm not mistaken, yeah, I think it ends around what they call Thursday,
Thursday, Friday, I think is what they call the day of rest, around there, yeah, so, okay,
any questions in chat, I think you were asking me if I got any response, right, and do you
want to, yeah, a response to, you mean the last sonic event we had with, have you noticed,
yes, you, I believe you want, oh, there was good feedback on that, it was meaning the,
you wanted to get suggestions, topics, subjects, and I was wondering how that panned out, oh,
nothing really, just the usual one paragraph to one page emails that I answer back with
two words or three words, okay, and then I get responses back, they had to think about
my response for a week until they got it, right, I mean, this is planet Earth, you
know, I mean, right, yeah, you know what's going on on this planet, so, yeah, oh, yeah,
yeah, she's not doing it, yeah, no, the planet is fine, it's just, yeah, right, oh, yes,
the planet is beautiful, yeah, well, you know, it's pretty, nature gets pretty wild, so,
but, yeah, all right, if there's nothing in chat, I guess this isn't a very short sonic,
right, yeah, all right, I don't know, I'm not in front of the computer, doing some minor
chores at the moment, right, so, is there anything going on, not much, let's see, just
like I mentioned, one from a person that was in the channel, mentioned about memory,
and improving memory, it's communication, that all has to do with communication, yeah,
and there's many levels to it, and that, I think, is gonna, that's kind of like years
ago, when I was younger, and dumber, and more naive about speaking publicly, you know,
giving at least hints to get into things, so, and that's good, you know, with the possible,
you know, endeavor in mind to expand subjects further, but I don't see that it's necessary
to expand on anything, just give a few hints, and then go with it, well, the memory aspect,
you know, memory only, well, let's just look at it real, basically, it works when you're
conscious, right, and dreams, when you're getting a dream, it doesn't work on memory,
it works on, you're being plugged, right, it's external, that's, even that could get
in, more elaborate into dreams and stuff, but let's just go back to, so what we call
consciousness, and there's, I still get some emails about consciousness, and I stay away
from them, because they're, 99% of the time, if not all the time, the people, morons, I
should say, that approach regarding questions about consciousness is 100% from the new age
mindfuck perspective, and you can't, you can't take that fecal matter and wrap it up in something
and give it to someone as something good, because it's just crap, the new age, right,
stuff, and you know, the ancients talk about the new age being crap, you know, meaning
of the human secular one, right, because there is going to be a new age when the gods rule,
and that's not what I'm talking about, but, so, again, about memory, when you're conscious,
and you're recalling, you typically, you know, it's all external input, right, even the scientists
have looked at it, and said that we don't see where anything in the brain is doing anything,
so again, you're tapping into an external source, but you are given the, let's say, more
than the onus, and more than just the responsibility, the actual mental or spiritual facility to
have retainment of memory, and you know, the brain being an antenna, if you rip off a chunk
of the brain, you might lose that, right, or damage it, just like, anyone who knows
about radio, what happens when you change your antenna once it's been tuned, but nonetheless,
that's like a very basic aspect of let's just talk about what we're talking about, which
is memory, and then the next aspect is how do you improve it, well, first thing is you
have to have good communication, a poor communication is not going to allow one to set things in
priority where good communication allows one to set the priority of that communication,
and I've noticed that most people don't know how to communicate, they just utter, they make
sounds, you know, and other people, and people respond to those sounds, and we think we're
communicating, and that's not really the best, most optimized communication, so once these
communications impart an idea, information, and influence, cognitive, you know, we tend
to recall them using various things, we can call it a trigger, is one aspect, another one
is we, you know, when you file it away, you know, what separates, you know, a file cabinet
from just a big pile of papers, it's really the same thing, you know, it's just ones in
a metal box, maybe ones, you know, if you just took a big metal box and stuffed it with
thousands of pages of paper, you can't really call that a file cabinet, it's more of a storage
area, what makes something a file cabinet is it's broken down by, in some order, you
know, or some form of, you know, when you study categories, indexing, appendices, things
like that, so the way to improve memory is by optimizing that indexing system, and the
easiest way to actually show that is by association, even with indexing, if you're not familiar
with the indexing system, it doesn't make any sense, you still can't find anything,
you have to have the primer, or understand how the indexing system works, like remember
in the old libraries, they had developed what's called the Dewey Decimal System, you actually
had to memorize certain rules, so there are many, up until the, I'd say, 17th, 15th or
16th century, there were many memory schools throughout Europe, and then they were banned,
of course, because the elite, you know, you can't be an educated and well-thought-out
thinking or thought-out person and be controlled, so they started banning all these things, but
one of the more popular things regarding memory was like the memory palace that the Greeks
instilled as one of the basics of the teaching memory, and that's basically by association,
you know, you, when you, let's say you go visit someone's house, or you live in a house,
and you have different rooms, you can actually recall what's in each room, and you know,
and again, even that is a form of indexing, you know, second floor, back room, front room,
things like that, so memory palace is where you basically look at things and you remember
how you're going to remember them, okay?
Another way is by association, when someone is very
familiar with a term, and then you can associate the familiar terms with things that are unfamiliar
by the hominized, when something sounds the same, like that's a very easy way that I just
show people how easy it is to learn, let's say, Hebrew, and I'm not a Hebrew conversationalist,
there's other people that I've encouraged to learn, and they are, they have learned on
their own, but you can do it by association, we could do it real quick, you know, when
I ask someone, do you want to learn how to speak some Hebrew, you mean you already know
some words already, like what's that animal that lives in the desert that has a hump on
its back, a camel, right?
Well, in Hebrew it would be Gamal, with a G instead of a C, right?
Yeah, because they're really good camels there, so they're good camels, so you think of it with a G.
Another one is like, well, how do you say yes in Hebrew?
Well, I'll say, you know that toy, what's the most famous little doll that they give, we're talking about western culture here, girls, it's the Barbie doll, right?
Right.
And Barbie is a ho, so she always says yes to, what's her mate?
Oh, Ken.
Ken, right.
Okay, so she never says, she always says yes to him, so Ken is how you say yes in Hebrew.
Oh my, wow.
So you see how easy it is to remember now?
Yes, yes.
Because Barbie, she's really easy, right?
So she always says yes to who?
Ken.
Okay, there you go.
Okay, when someone says yes, you feel high, but when someone says no, you feel low.
Right, now that's how you say no in Hebrew, is low.
Oh for goodness sakes.
So do you see the associations here?
Yes, yes.
Now these are long, now this
is not necessarily memory per se, but it is, because what we did here is we've fitted
some presumptions and assumptions that you're a westerner, and you're familiar with certain
western things, so I'm giving you western examples, mainstream, that's very easy, that
you won't forget, and actually even if you try to get it out of your mind, you couldn't,
Barbie, you can, right?
Right.
So you make these associations, and you run the person through a short exercise where they actually have a working model of what you're trying to illustrate, and they actually produce and remember the associations as well.
And you do the same thing with memories.
Okay, I just showed the language, so you probably will, how do you say yes in Hebrew?
You just think of Barbie, right?
And her mate.
Because she's easy.
Right, because Barbie is easy, and she never says no to, she always says yes.
And you know, when someone says yes, you feel high, but when they say no, you feel low.
And you could go on and on and on.
You know, like in Spanish, you know, anatomy, for example, you know, like skin, right, you know, skin, you know, when you get a sunburn, what happens after it dries, what does it do?
It peels, right?
So PL, or when you're taking, when you're peeling something, what are you peeling off on a fruit?
The skin.
So that's how you say in Spanish, skin is PL.
But you know, you think of a Spanish accent, right?
Right.
So like, lips are very easy.
What do they call them on a woman's genitalia?
Labios, or labias, right?
Labios, right?
Okay, right.
Okay.
So you go on and on and on with making associations like that.
So, yeah.
Very clever, yes.
Yeah, I mean, you know, like your face is wide, but your nose is narrow, right?
And it's at the end of your face, like the, what's the last letter on the end of the alphabet is Z, and it's narrow.
So nariz, like narrow and with a Z, nariz, you know, it's your nose.
So you can, so what I mean here is these associations are not only for learning, but for memory.
So to actually create an optimum memorization system, you have to have an optimum communication and an optimum learning system, because when you're presented with something or that you decide to retain in memory, you must also learn how you're going to put it in memory.
Just like, for example, if before the Windows systems, when you had worked on old computers and you wanted to put something in memory, you just didn't say, click save.
You had to go through protocols, right?
To put it in memory.
Yeah.
Okay.
And it's still done.
It's just that you don't see it.
Right.
So the same thing where you have to develop the protocols to develop memory, think of it like canning.
You know, you just don't, you know, if you grow a bunch of string means and got more than you'll ever need for a while, you want to can them and preserve them.
You just open a jar and throw them in and put them in the closet, right?
No.
What will happen if you do that?
It will spoil.
Yeah.
And explode.
So you have to learn how to basically put the stuff in a can and canning is a skill.
So in other words, if you get a sense of the various metaphors, there's no free ride here with memory.
There's nothing you can do other than develop the system or the tools to associate good communication with good learning and then storage.
And the storage is the association.
You know, how many times have you heard someone said, you know, I think I have one of those.
I just don't know where it is.
Right.
You have to go look for it.
So what you do is you try to put a logical sequence, you know, when you have, for example, tools that pull and tools that push, you don't want to put the tools that push with the paintbrushes together.
You want to put, you know, tools that grab and squeeze with tools that grab and squeeze, like your C clamps, your vices, your channel locks go together, you know, like your scrapers.
Right.
Something like a chisel.
You know, does it go with woodworking or does it go with scrapers?
Well, you know, you might want to have do you see the dual purpose one purpose, right?
Things that cut well, you have scissors, you're pivoting shears and you have saw stuff with teeth like various saws.
Do you want to put a wood saw with a hacksaw?
Very different.
But you could be working with wood and have a nail that you want the hacksaw for.
Right.
So then you have to make these fine decisions that are personal and also how specialized your memory wants to be.
And then there's there's actually a whole aspect to this that you can there's exercises and all that.
But I think right now I gave a tremendous amount of just ideas in just the introduction to the subject and a skill set.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because in order to discuss these things in a framework where it could be done, you have to really again, I'd have to sit down and think about writing something and like other people have said, well, let's do a podcast and let's structure.
It's just not a matter of doing, you know, I've got to collect myself, maybe take a few days or weeks to put this or at least quite a few hours to assemble this, see what's on the rectangle about it, which is probably a joke and just put, you know, references together also.
And, you know, yeah.
So but at least I think the hint is good enough for now.
Right.
Yeah.
Pretty nice.
What else you got?
Yeah.
Not a lot here.
Not not much in chat.
OK.
Let's take a picture.
Was there some requesting discussion sort of feng shui Greek style about home interior and exterior?
I'm not an interior decorator.
No, that's fine.
It's a it's a valid question.
But you just be glad that you got something that's better than a cardboard box.
It doesn't get soggy when you rain.
You don't have a lot of time right now.
I think you've got 13 years and six months or so.
We never talked about one probably never will, as I'm getting time, the detail on biblical chronology and figure out why I say the things that I think I've been over it before in various sonic events here and there.
But when is the exact within a time frame?
We know we know when the gods will return within three days, like three days before it happens.
You will know for sure.
Three and actually three and a half days.
OK, so that is your your your minimum amount of prep time.
I mean, or maximum, I should say doubt.
There'll come a time in history where there will be at three and a half days before the gods arrive.
There'll be no doubt that they're coming at that time.
So there's a bit, you know, there's a chronology and actually then and then there's another time where we know 40 days.
It'll be 40 days before those three and a half days come.
We could say with 99 percent assurance in 40 days they'll be here.
But when and then, you know, at the 36 and a half day mark rate at that point, then it'll be totally clear that you were really on or off on that 40 days.
You see, if you're right.
And then if you go back, sorry, if you go back from there, you've got three and a half years before they come that you'll be pretty close to saying when they will come.
And then back from there, you could easily say seven years before they come.
And back from there, we could say 13 years and six months, which is right now.
Oh, yeah.
And it's funny when I this kind of discussion makes people very nervous because sometimes they catch them on these nervous twitches.
Sometimes I say, well, Greek, first you said it was this amount of time.
Now it's this.
I said, no, I never said that.
Right.
I'm very sure about it.
I'm very sure about the chronology.
Mm hmm.
It's just that people can't listen to this kind of stuff.
It's just difficult for them.
And they're censored, of course.
It certainly is an eye opener.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
All right.
So in terms of interior, yeah, decorating or whatever.
OK, now anything else?
No, that looks to be the long and short of it.
Greek.
OK, well, let's wrap it up.
Oh, go take a nap.
Was this last one.
Can the relationship between leaving and sin be discussed or leavening?
The what?
Leavening and sin be discussed.
No.
Well, how do you know it's leavening?
That's the New Testament questions.
Anyone asking stuff in the New Testament means that they're an expert in the Bible.
And have pretty good comprehension.
And publicly that doesn't exist.
A little bit of yeast leavens the whole thing, I see.
But what is it about the wheat or the bread?
But here's the thing, that was stuff that the Christ told his disciples and his apostles.
If you think you're in that level, that that's worth discussing.
You know, Euphorus, but just open and I'm telling you, there's no public discourse on that because the people are not at that level yet.
So that's why, for example, when you when you're around what's called the Hebraic or Jewish traditions, they never discuss the New Testament and things like that.
It's not because, oh, it's not part of our religion or this and that, you know, actually, you know, that's the public side.
Right.
But on the private side, these people that are grew up with scripture and actually have a pretty decent comprehension of it, see it as being a very advanced level.
And I don't like getting into when I discuss stuff from the New Testament, it's the premise of who the Christ is to at least go after and get away from the deception and start to get a handle on what his true identity.
But in terms of what the Christ said, forget about it.
That's not for public discourse.
That's kind of arrogant when people come either.
The two types people ask those questions.
One is the the brainwashed moron that is in churchianity or Christianity and has got one foot in that and one foot in the other or in the or in the other one is, I don't know, I was still brainwashed, whatever, is that, you know, they're linked to popular culture, they have no understanding of, of the, of the aspect of what's going on in the New Testament.
So that's, I've brought I've, you know, I'm guilty of volunteering a lot of explanations regarding that, right?
Right.
But when I when I do that, it's not just what about this?
What about that here and there?
It's to underpin the identity of the biblical Christ, the Mashiach that they say in Hebrew, right?
Right.
Because it's their Mashiach, right?
Because why is it because very simply, most of the world was pagan, and they came out of, you
know, various cultures with many, many gods, but the the one of the of Israel, they had always in their
back of the minds, the concept of resurrection and a Mashiach being the one that's going to show them
that no other the Christians don't have that, don't have that, by the way, right, they because they teach
either when you die, you go to heaven or hell, which is pagan, right, right.
And they in the circus and all that there is no church with the Christ at all.
You know, there's no circus with him.
So yeah, I don't I don't like left field.
It's not like they're not it's not appropriate to answer that, by the way, publicly.
Because the background in that is is is.
And it's funny when you go online and try to look up what these things mean that you get the you're going to be swarmed with Christian churchy entity crap, because that's where it belongs.
That's part of the deception.
And not to dissuade or be pejorative to the person who asked that question.
But I think as we get more serious through this society about the crap that's coming, I think that's that's kind of like a brunt of a joke to ask a New Testament question that's like that.
I'd rather ask, you know, say joke, like, what did the squid say to the bagpipe?
I'd fuck you if you took those pajamas off, right?
Yeah.
But anyway.
Oh, my.
Yeah, the whole only thing people got to know when they look at the New Testament is, well, they got to know is very simple.
There's something called the resurrection.
And it's been proven.
You don't have to think about heaven or hell or born again, this or this and that, you know, just basically tells you what happens after you die.
That's all.
It's kind of like when they, you know, they do a nuclear physics or atomic physics, and they're all talking and doing and doing and doing and experimenting.
And then one day they finally do ground zero test site and they blow one up and they're like, OK, we did it.
You know, it's done.
Even though it was just a test, you know, it worked.
Right.
You know, we had all these presumptions before that.
No, if we do it, we'll destroy the whole planet because of the credit chain reaction.
The whole atmosphere will burn.
No, no.
You see.
So all those things are dispelled.
You know, they proved what they did to prove.
Yeah.
That's what the New Testament is.
And the other thing about that is it's monkey business at this point, because the what Christianity has put forward, you know, through the state and through the adversary and all that, through Hollywood and the church, the circus and through tradition.
It is thick out there.
Oh, yeah.
You cannot.
The truth about it is so contrary to that.
Yeah.
You know, because the Christ, if it was the peers, nothing in the New Testament was meant for people to discuss, he would have said so.
Right.
So and and what he what he came to do, he did.
And that was the message that was supposed to go out.
So because also he respected the leasehold that Satan has on this planet.
You ever hear about like tenants have rights?
If you're if you're a landlord, you can't go open and, you know, go into a tenant's house, right?
Right.
Say they have tenants rights.
So so the landlord comes shows humanity or some of the humanity that knew not the ignorant because the Christ hated ignorant people, by the way.
If you don't know that, you could read it yourself.
And he's not going to come as the landlord and start showboating around to the children of the tenant, who is the Nakash or the Satan or the adversary.
This is his children on this planet.
Now, spiritually, you know, right.
So.
Hmm.
Yeah, it's pretty interesting stuff.
People very often, even fortunately, not much, because I give the same answer.
Unless I volunteer the information from the New Testament, don't ask me about it.
All right, because the problem is, you were not talking about the same thing here at all.
Right.
Let's say you're walking on the street, Bruce, and we're let's you and I are a street and someone bus stop, you know, says you're into the Bible and ask me a New Testament question.
Do you think that person knows who the Christ is?
And he knows the chronology of things and knows his purpose?
Anything I say he's gonna that person's gonna have to make it fit into the they're, they're distorted, twisted, you know, church entity, Christian crap.
Right.
And it's not something that doesn't.
You're in the middle of an argument.
Right?
Yeah.
So good.
You know, so the whole thing is to, to wait and study.
And I've been say, if you've heard of my earliest sonic events, there's a graduation, a graduate of order to anything New Testament is graduate level, like you would have kindergarten through 12th grade, undergraduate study, master's and doctorate study.
Right.
So you're at 21 years now in school, you know, from K through 12.
So anything New Testament is graduate level.
So to discuss that properly is to presume that you are past the kindergarten past the grade school past the high school level past the grad, you know, bachelor's and past the graduate level, you're a doctorate level to discuss that some of the New Testament is on a master's level.
But most of it's on the doctorate and master's and above.
Yeah.
So it has nothing to do with people who think, first of all, it has nothing to do with them.
Well, you know, then the people on this planet directly, it's a very indirect thing to show those who know about or yearn to know about what who the gods are and their purpose and interacting with this whole saga, what we're going through, right.
And also what happens after you die.
It's only for those people.
He the Christ even said that he said, I came for the lost of Israel doesn't say lost.
Like, you know, when you lost a sheep, you're lost the horse because the doors open any, you know, when you get lost, you don't have anybody any before GPS.
I don't know where I am.
No, it's not.
The actual word is perished, the ones that have died.
Right.
The one you know, to in other words, because that resurrection has to do with dead people, you can't be resurrected if you're alive.
That's why it born again, Christianity crap is the most ridiculous.
That's like a joke that they put on the people.
And then it stuck.
I can be born again when you're already born.
Right.
Or you haven't died yet.
You know, you know, and then they try to use the metaphor of the spirit.
They don't even know, you know, it's a big man.
Isaiah talked about it.
It's a stumbling block to them.
Hmm.
It's shocking.
You know, here's the other shocking point.
How many people that actually respond to Greek speak and still don't know the identity of the Christ.
They still wrestle with it.
Like, Oh, you mean he wasn't crucified?
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
You know?
senseless.
Yeah.
You're on the humanities on the tail end of a project right now that's about to end violently, because there's no other way.
The gods are very efficient.
So imagine that.
Yeah.
Was it the church lady and Saturday Night Live?
It was a guy Dana Carvey.
Yeah.
Dana.
They need a data Harvey to do the thing.
He was he was quite the fellow.
The only thing people need to really relax and meditate on is things are much worse than they perceive them to be.
And they just don't perceive them.
Because they're normal.
It seems like there's no sense of urgency or alarm.
And there shouldn't be a sense of urgency or alarm because you'll be singled out and you know, as an as a madman, right?
Right.
So no, doesn't mean live on edge.
Really easy to do these days.
Well, that's the modus operandi for the gods when when when you are given something to do, and it's time to take you out, they get the other people around you to take you out, lock you up or whatever.
That's your read that scripture.
Yeah.
By example, you know, even even the king, you know, has some of his family revolt against him temporarily, you know, David, and like Jeremiah was thrown into the dungeon, basically, you know, by his own people.
So yeah, it's a very fine line, you know, well, it's a very fine line with everything, right.
But in terms of discussing the gods, you know, like, again, any biblical question is about the gods, right?
Essentially, because anybody could discuss anything in scripture on different terms and secularly or whatever.
But when you bring up a scriptural question, usually has a context and a subject to it.
And and guess what, whatever the context or subject is, is referred to and what is brought up in scripture is what the gods think of that, not you or someone else, right?
Mm hmm.
So, yeah, the thing is, just wait, there's not much time, you know, think about it like someone like old farts, like I'm in my sixth decade now.
Right.
Mm hmm.
Mid, you know, half a century and half a decade almost.
So, so since my sixth decade, so what I would suggest is, you know, anyone, you know, figure out how long you've been on this planet.
And how long have you been gone without, let's say, biblical knowledge, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know
...
Like what kind of information, what kind of knowledge, you know, the things like that.
Alright.
Most of it most likely, right, actually, I'll be cocky here, but if you haven't heard Greek speak, you probably don't know, you know, you, you might've heard other people discuss it's important, but I'm sure, surely not with accuracy.
So think about how much time you spent on this planet without this any point of view, let's just say, and you only had this point of view or in pursuing whatever you might be pursuing after listening to this kind of stuff for a very short time.
So the remainder of the time that's left might seem kind of long, because you've only been perceiving it for a short time.
But the time that you didn't have this perception is much longer than the time that's left.
So you can balance all that out, you know what I mean?
So I mean, let's take Bruce, for example.
You've had probably half a century without this kind of perception, right?
5.5 centuries.
That's a long time.
Yeah, 0.55 of a century, yeah.
Right.
So now you have, let's say, a couple of years or so of it, and the time that's left is seven times that amount, let's say.
But the time that you went fine without, seemingly fine, was much, much longer.
So these are the things to think about.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you just be aware.
So far, I could tell no one within reach that I know of is being called or chosen to do anything special, or promote anything, or keep it going.
I don't see it.
And I don't mean just the people in chat and emailing or in this, whatever, like Vandy said, the mob.
I'm talking about on the internet completely, too, and in the world.
I just do look up what's going on.
There's no talk.
There's nothing.
It's still very quiet.
I mean, there's like nothing about the Pope's work schedule, or how the body works, or lawful timekeeping, or anything.
Not a word.
Still just, still just, no, not time yet.
Hmm.
Interesting.
But it is rather, from, let's say, geopolitical, it is rather still.
That doesn't mean that there's not much going on.
There's a lot going on if you know what to look for.
So as a matter of fact, you should be concerned when it's quiet like that.
So, I mean, like, I don't know if you remember in the late 90s with Clinton, I think, they said the deficit went to zero and it got really quiet, right, in the 9-11.
Yeah.
I remember the debt clock went to zero in like less than a year.
And it got really quiet.
You know, they did a couple, they blew off, was it the USS Cole, they tried to blame it on some radical group, right.
You notice when they said, yeah, anyway.
That was an introduction, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, and then, yeah, so.
So right now is a quiet time, and I've been talking about this.
This is the time period now to start seeing things be put in place where there will be no doubt that by 2025, around that time, mid-2020s, there will be a Middle East Union in place as a power base.
So this is an interesting quiet period.
For me, it's not quiet at all because I'm contemplating and seeing the timing and I'm seeing really how just by it being quiet doesn't mean that there's not much going on.
The deception and the ignorance is being upheld.
Right.
So there's still nobody talking about, you know, about what the hell's going on, you know, with the most basic stuff that we never looked at before.
So we should.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Yeah.
It'll come.
All right.
Nothing else?
If nothing else, we'll just make it a short one.
Okay.
I don't see anything else there.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's tons of stuff to talk.
Yeah.
Just why volunteer stuff when, you know.
Right.
Just look for where the need is and we'll see what happens.
Okay.
Well, thanks, Bruce.
You're welcome.
And you have yourself a good night.
Yes.
Thank you.
You too.
Take care now.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye-bye.