And greetings folks, and we're live on the air again and got the Greek here.
Greetings.
And, yeah, let's just do a little another impromptu stream.
Right.
Yeah.
So, yeah, let's say anything you want to bring up right off the top of my head.
I was a little concerned about getting everything up proper and everything.
But we do have the call in lines available.
And I'll put that in the chat in just a bit here.
How about you?
Oh, always.
I'm always doing that.
Yeah.
As long as I'm breathing.
I'm doing something that I think is interesting.
So then there was a question in chat that was brought up regarding voltage, electricity and all that.
And is it simple?
We can get a little bit into that.
I wanted what I wanted to bring up.
Essentially, just the impetus is, you know, there's a lot of discussion about Scripture whenever the Greek shows up.
Right.
And last time we did something with Sam, it was kind of good to get off the topic.
But I wanted to just bring up a couple of things that I think surmise things that let's say I were never to speak again.
What would you get out of it?
Right.
To sum up what is going on with that, with that subject?
You know what I mean?
In a nutshell, just like Wes asked in the chat.
Let's see.
The question was something like there's no specific topic yet.
I like to I really like the Greek to go a bit more into depth about the nature of electricity and voltage, more or less, more versus less voltage.
Right.
That was initially the question there.
Well, the thing is, I think I've done that with Scripture.
And I want to do a quick recap on that because it's good to talk about a lot of other things.
And if you pay attention to what I'm going to say now, you can apply it to almost anything.
And the reason I like bringing up Scripture is because it is notably and lawfully a very high priority message, communication.
Not because whether you believe in it or not or know it or not, because it is.
Because if you have a lawful and quote unquote legal mind, there's a prioritization on notices.
Right.
You know, there is such some there's a concept known as a notice.
And a notice could be, you know, curb your dog.
Don't step on the grass or something like that.
Or it could be, you know, we're going to you have to vacate the property in 30 days, you know, and there's various degrees to notices.
And I've never seen any higher notice than that, you see.
But you have to also understand, when you bring up things from a lawful standpoint, you lose 99% of the people.
Well, five nines after the 99 on this planet.
So there's really no one to discuss anything with when it comes to.
Well, I shouldn't say discuss anything with.
There is no audience as one would consider for things that are really based on what they're really based on, you know, like lawful in general.
Right.
And so the way you communicate those things is you just start communicating them publicly.
And eventually, from, let's say, a higher power, if it's meant for those that are meant to hear it, they kind of gather and hear it.
But it's not something that could be packaged and presented to the world at large, if you know what I mean.
That's why when you look at alternative media or anything alternative, the patriot community, you know, you know, the law system is completely corrupt, and they have all these remedies, none of them work, really.
You know, you have the alternative medicine stuff, almost none of it works, you know, on and on and on, right, whatever you want to discuss, because they have no, anyway, no sense of what's lawful and unlawful.
So with that said, what do you think?
Should we just broach on it really quickly or no?
Sure.
I think it's a great idea.
Okay, let's get back on the track with what I wanted to just bring up.
If you were to grade that using the simplicity grade system, what is available to most people is a D minus.
It should be given an F, and I'll tell you why.
It is a D minus because it is an erroneous version of the information that's been held in the earliest copies that we have, right, which is why I suggest go to an interlinear.
Now, because erroneous versions or versions or a story that has so many errors, and it leads to bad doctrine or bad belief or paints a poor or inaccurate picture, it has to be given an F.
In other words, it fails to communicate enough information to consider it viable from the original, you see, what we have is the oldest copies, let's say.
Is that pretty easy to say?
Yeah, and I feel every bit of that that you just said when I first started, yes.
Yeah, so it's a complete failure, catastrophic in the least.
In the most, it's actually – a failure would be like a zero.
What it actually does, what you have, doesn't matter what language it is other than what's preserved in Hebrew, let's say, and Aramaic, and you might even say the Greek.
It's an utter failure, and it's actually – it has promoted most of the things that are considered forbidden or abominable or don't-dos because of such a bad doctrine.
Now, you can say that from a functional point of view.
The reason – as a failure, right?
But if you look at it from the D minus point of view and you actually read, let's say, the King Jimmy, King James, or everything's based on King James, even the Geneva, you have some morons out there saying, well, the King James was a corruption of the Geneva.
I don't really see much of a difference between the two.
And here's the other thing.
I stopped doing it recently because I figured there's a limited group of people listening.
But whenever you hear the biblical topic being brought up, just bringing up verses or what people are familiar with as the Bible, if you don't hear a caveat that even till this date, the present day, we don't have an accurate translation of it, what you're going to be listening to is pretty much looking – a BS, a wholesale BS, and pretty much you're going to be looking for semi-edible corn and poop.
There is no sane individual – sane meaning healthy and collective and rational on any perspective – that will venture on a quote-unquote biblical discussion to the Western world especially without first stating a caveat or a disclaimer that we're going to be discussing the biblical text, but there is no accurate translation in existence.
Period.
This is an important caveat, and caveats are given usually, disclaimers in the beginning.
You hear these legal morons usually.
They say, well, we know we're not attorneys.
We're not here to give legal advice, but we're going to keep going.
You hear that, disclaimers, because they don't even know what that means.
So the disclaimer, if you don't hear that disclaimer, you're pretty much going to be sold or you're going to be buying into a bill of goods that is still part of that spin cycle of crap.
Now, the reason I'm bringing this topic up – I could say these things much simpler, but I want to give the explanation as I bring them up – is because you're going into a time period now prophetically where that's going to change, and it's going to change drastically in its eventuality of the next decade, but it's going to go unnoticed.
Here, what I mean by that, the change will be unnoticed, but if you know this is coming, in other words, what's going to change is people are going to start going away from what they've been thinking is the Bible and start having a sane approach.
Now, what I mean by that is even if you read the King James, if you're paying attention, you will see anomalies in there.
So this doesn't make any sense.
It will say, for example, my name is the Lord, and you know that's not a name.
So then you're going to say, well, there's something wrong here.
But most people don't do that, right?
And then other places you'll read what the laws are, and then actually in other places it tells you there are things happening that are contrary to the law done by people that are keeping the law.
So you're like, okay, something's wrong here.
So it has its – you know, you can – and that will – any rational or sane person will then beg to say, well, maybe I should read the introduction of this piece of crap document, and it'll tell you exactly.
Just a question when you brought that up.
Do you think that people are going to pay more attention to bloodlines?
Yes, but the problem with the bloodlines is – well, it's not a problem.
That is something that is – there's a couple of verses regarding how people will be sifted like you sift grain or, you know, they'll be sorted.
And you know who's going to do the sorting is the gods are going to do it.
What you will see – this is the other thing that Evan brought up.
Ninety-nine percent of the time when countries and places are mentioned geographic, it has to do with the society in that geographic location regardless of who's living there.
So for example, let's say tomorrow you're reading the paper that everyone in Israel left, and everyone in Italy moved to Israel now, right?
What do you mean?
The prophecy still stays true because it's the land of Israel and the people that are there, right?
Okay.
See?
So for example, when you read in Exodus and other places about Egypt and all that, don't think that there were – I would say it was maybe 60 or 50 percent Egyptians.
The rest of the people were immigrants, right, if you took the nation as a whole.
Like even today when you hear something like Rome, later in the later periods of Rome, if you walk down, you know, anywhere in that part of the metropolis, you'd say, where are the Romans?
I see people, you know, we call it Shemitic descent here.
I see northern people.
I see – where are the Romans?
It's like when you go to a coastal city in America, you see Korean, Chinese, black, Latin.
Where are the white people at?
Right, right.
You know what I mean?
I mean, yeah, you still see them, but you know what I mean?
Where are the white people at?
Yeah.
So yeah.
So yeah, I thought America was a white country.
So what's going on?
Or look at the American military.
Yeah.
Especially when they have a presentation of at least a few squadron or, you know, let's say battalions.
Where are the white people at?
I thought America was white.
Where are they at?
I see Latin, black, and everything else, every shade, but white in there.
I mean you still see some white people.
I try to bring them up, especially when they've got a flag carrier or whatever, you know, but – Right, right.
Okay.
So what I mean by when you hear about these things, you'll see the change.
So anyway, what you will see is this change coming, and it will be radical if you know it's coming.
Most people are clueless.
You know, they just go along.
I'll give you a quick example.
In the summer of 2001, I was working for a client.
I was doing some murals, some artwork, a mural in their home, and they happened to be – actually, if I say they're dismantled.
They come from a family that owns some of the largest copper mines in the world in the 50s, 60s, and 70s, and they were busted by President Carter.
I'll give you an example of the background here, right?
And they're always watching the political scene because their fortune was busted.
You know, imagine the government steps in and breaks down Bill Gates into, you know, 15 different companies, and he has to move Microsoft to China and Chile or something, right?
Did you find that rather interesting back in the day when Bill Gates was getting his hand slapped by the government?
All of a sudden, that just went away?
Yeah, it did.
It was really the IRS because they wanted to make sure that – they wanted to teach him a lesson on the money system, and then everything was fine.
Right, right.
Because all of a sudden, that just disappeared overnight.
I was like, wow.
Because most people – and I've met people in the upper crust of society, in the elites and luminatis and all that.
They think there's money.
They don't know that there is no money yet.
So when you get past a certain point, they explain to you how it works, and then they're like, oh, OK, I'll roll with that because I know there's no loan now.
You feel better.
See, like most people think there's money.
If they have a big loan, they sweat it, right?
Oh, I've got to pay back the loan or I'm going to lose this, right?
But if you know there's no money, there's plenty of federal laws written in your favor if you know them.
He also became very helpful to the government shortly after that also.
Exactly, because there is no money.
Right, right.
Yeah.
So if you know the legal system or how it's set up about money, and no one sweat – you won't sweat a loan.
Because there are plenty of laws that will tell you, hey, if anybody – the law actually says it.
If someone comes after you with Dunning and asks you how much – I mean that you owe something, all you've got to do is deny it and say, prove it.
Prove it that you lent me anything.
Prove it.
Right, yeah.
Yeah.
You can't.
Show me where it comes from.
Right.
So he got in there, and he figured out what it meant.
So if he needed to float several billion, he knew – it was all a dog and pony show.
All he had to do was put his signature on a piece of paper.
It runs through the several clearinghouses, and he gets the billion out of his own signature, right?
That's important to know when you're working in this, right?
I'll give you another example regarding money.
I was around some oil tycoons a few years ago, and it was a deal on the $40 million to $50 million.
And they wanted to – instead of using their own money, just go to a bank and use their bank's money, right?
Of course.
That's how you do it, right?
And I was around them in their home, and they were like, oh, a bank called me.
They want me to go down there and sign some checks.
Now, their bank is supposed to lend him money.
And I said, well, what do you mean it called you again?
He says, well, two days ago, they wanted me to go down and sign some checks.
And there were checks for $40 million.
So in other words, the person borrowing the money is signing the checks because then the bank takes the check and deposits it through the Fed and runs your social security number and gets it out of your social security number.
So I said, how many checks did you sign?
He says, oh, this would be like the fourth one.
I said, man, the bank just got like $120 million from you, and they're going to lend you $40 million and tell you that you owe it.
You got to pay it back.
Are you joking?
What's wrong with you people?
He didn't know how the money system worked, by the way.
Right.
He's a billionaire, too, almost.
So I just want to show you how – that's why very often I come out in Enchiladas is a planet full of idiots.
And I'm not talking about the people waiting at the bus stop.
I'm talking about everyone, wholesale.
But anyway, I was doing some mural work for this guy, and I was noticing there was a subtle – going back to what was going on in 2001 in the summer.
And I noticed that the news for about – the television show they call the news and the radio, they kept bringing up this name, Osama bin Laden, from spring and the summer, subtly bringing it back and forth.
There was a bomb – there was a hull blown out of a ship near Yemen a few years before, a couple of years before, and they put it on him.
And the name kept coming up.
And I was having a discussion with a client over a break, and I think we were just socializing really at that point.
And I said, you know, you've got to – this is like June, July of 2001.
And I'm like, you know, this Osama bin Laden character is going to be used in the news.
I mean he's in the news, and they're going to – something is going to happen, and they're going to pin it on him.
Oh, no, that won't happen.
Our biggest problem is China, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Right?
OK.
Do you see how subtle a statement is?
And it's just like – and actually I did confront him after, around October, and I mentioned that he was just totally silent.
He was like – so anyway, also I was around someone who said, well, 9-11 is next month, you know, 9-11, get it, September 11th, emergency month.
And I had another person before that once say to me, how's your credit score, Greek?
And I said, what is that?
What do you mean?
What credit score?
What are you talking about?
He says, well, you make sure you get credit score is really good because there's going to be a lot of security jobs coming up in the future.
And if you've got a really good credit score, you'll get a really good high-ranking position in any kind of private security.
I'm like, what?
What are you talking about security industry?
What security industry?
Right?
You see what I'm saying?
So anyway, you see it.
Are you paying attention in other words, right?
Enough.
How much attention are you going to pay?
It's really simple when someone just tells you what's going on that you can see rationally as well.
So again, very simply with the scripture, you're in that time period.
The other thing about scripture is I want to talk about is the poor doctrine that is – what is – you know, the Christianity, Judaism, Islam even, because they're descendants of Abraham and they attach – and by the way, if you read the Koran, there's not like one consistent story in there.
I mean it – well, one day in – let's see, maybe I promise in a couple of years if I'm still around maybe or somehow get out information on who wrote the Koran, why it was written and all that other crap, right?
So what I want to get into though is because the poor doctrine, the bad doctrine has been cemented with bricks and mortar fixtures like churches and universities, Bible colleges, lots of – you go to a hotel and you see a Bible in there and it's in the television.
It's in the movies.
It's been used as something good or – right?
What has happened is you have a really bad idea, which is a bad concept, the version itself, and it has manifested physically now.
You know what I mean?
So it has manifested physically in the world.
So now you have two things to overcome.
This is again with any bad idea.
We can discuss the medical system is exactly the same.
You know the magic cuff.
Originally, blood pressure was a concept.
If you look at it in the 20s and 30s, some academics were arguing about what that pulse, how it should be measured, and they eventually made it a vital sign, which it can't be, right?
And they built lots of equipment and there are buildings built around that concept.
So you have really bad concepts that have taken foot in society and they have cemented it with brick and mortar and fixtures and real things.
You could touch, right?
Right.
So that's why people can't see and get over it even though they understand there's censorship and they understand that there's a spiritual intangible side that's preventing them from seeing things.
So if you could see all that stuff through all that stuff, now you could transfer what I just said regarding the really, really bad biblical concepts through the medical industry, through the nutrition, through the financial.
Government itself is not operating as it should be lawfully.
None of them are, by the way.
They have the medical industry, religious industry, and the government, the legal society, whatever.
They have the appearance, the food industry has the appearance of being lawful, but they're not.
And it's very difficult to find anything that they're doing that is lawful in anything that you're going to interact with.
So that was the first point.
Well, the world society is like that, for God's sake, Sean.
Right.
And what it is, it's a testament to the robustness of the human condition, meaning your ability to sleep, eat, and avoid catastrophic violence.
Well, these days you're lucky if you can make it through the year without some kind of weird manifestation coming at you.
Even if you're eating lawfully, that usually doesn't happen.
And that's another thing I found interesting.
The priest and what they wore, what they ate.
Do you think this, when it was with the Ark, do you think this was a lot to do with the behaviors, with the inductance of the person, the foods he ate, the specific garments?
It's like if the Ark knew that you weren't pure or following the law.
Yeah, the Ark, the presence of the Ark was symbolic.
Well, it was a symbolic replica of something that was somewhere else.
There was actually an angelic being that was a body double of that particular God.
Oh, okay.
That came, yeah.
You remember how Saddam Hussein had a body double and all this?
Right, right.
Well, the Creator has a body double.
So it knew that you weren't pure.
Of course.
That's what I wanted to bring up.
There's a lot of transmutation in scripture, and one of them is when you touch a dead animal, you're unclean until noon, right?
Well, if you eat animal product or flesh, actually milk wouldn't be that, because milk is not…
You wouldn't be unclean.
Right, you would be unclean, but while it's still in your gut, you can wash before noon, and then after noon you're declared clean, but it's still in your gut.
It's still in your gut, yeah.
But now you're clean, you see, after washing.
Technically.
Technically you're clean, yeah.
So that meat now is clean, even though it's in your body.
You're declared clean.
Oh, okay, okay.
That's what miracles are, it's a form of changing things.
If you look at the root word meanings of the word miracle, look at where it's used, and go look in an interlinear and get a grip on what that means, and it's not what you've been told.
Interesting.
Just like the word forgiveness.
The word forgiveness means to get away from it.
Right.
It doesn't mean, oh, it's okay if you punch me in the nose, no.
If someone punches you in the nose, forgive them, which means get away from it.
Yeah.
So it doesn't happen again, basically.
Right.
Another thing I want to throw in there, I had a discussion recently regarding the law and Christianity, and that's a very short thing I can give, because it could be a very long discussion, it could be a five to eight hour discussion, really, if you're going to start bringing up the 12 beef patty special sauce, you know, each specific verse, right?
You know, no one talks like that, by the way.
I have a disdain and a hate for, you know, show me the verse while you're speaking.
You know, that's why I hate it.
It's because people that do hateful things do it, first of all.
Second of all, no one speaks that way if you're watching a movie.
Do you remember what happened at one hour 36 minutes and 24 seconds?
Do you remember?
What?
You know, or do you remember the scene where he jumps off the building and he flies over to the next building?
Well, give me the time on that.
What do you mean?
It was at one hour 36 minutes and 24 seconds.
No one speaks out, but they've done it with that because these are disturbed people.
But regarding the law, most of the people, just to throw this together, use the writings of Paul.
Now, Paul was – if you look at the writings of Paul, he cites the law over 100 times, you know, issues of the law that are to be followed and considered, you know, as holy writ and to live properly and to be, quote-unquote, set apart.
And to be in good graces with the Creator.
But in other places, there seems to be like a little bit of the – I would say like a falling away kind of sentiment when he discusses the law.
So how can he cite it in a positive way over 100 times, maybe 150 or 200 times?
Really, I'm saying 100 because it's easy to find that.
And then in other parts, be so almost disdainful of it, right?
So it can't be the same law.
What he's really discussing – and I don't like to discuss Paul because it's on a PhD level, and I believe that most of the people at this point that are hearing my voice are on the first or second grade when it comes to scriptural studies.
But what I'm going to state is this.
If you consider the historic relevancy of the time period and the condition of humanity at that point, there was something called the oral law held by the de facto priestly class, which were the Pharisees and the Sadducees.
Pharisees were basically supposed to sit in for the Levites, and the Sadducees were basically supposed to sit in with the Pharisees, but they represented the elite class.
Right?
So they were in the pockets of the elite and the Romans and whoever else conquered, right?
OK.
So they had an oral law.
Now it's known as Talmudic law.
And what they had done is they were using it on the people harshly.
Right?
You get it?
Right.
So most Christians, you'd like to use that.
Now, the Paul saying they don't understand that condition.
Now, the other condition is when Christ had proven that what happens after death with the resurrection, it was a world-changing, there were a lot of interesting things going on through his whole life period that no one could explain, other than there was some interesting individual saying and doing some very interesting things.
And there were many people who didn't know what was going on and were not interested in quote-unquote scripture until those events were transpiring.
And the people that were knowledgeable of this were saying, well, who is this guy?
He says, well, look, you could read about him in the scripture, the Psalms, the prophets and all that.
He's prophesied.
But let me ask you, could you find him anywhere in the oral law that the Sadducees and the Pharisees had?
Nope.
There's nothing to read there.
There's nothing to study because it's just an oral law that they tell people what to do.
Right?
You get the difference?
So what they call the early Christians were essentially not Christians at all because they never called themselves that ever.
It was a derogatory term.
And it was a derogatory term that is difficult to explain because it's beyond any derogation or pejorative that we can conceive of today, if that makes any sense.
So do you want me to give an example of that?
Yes.
Anyway.
Oh, OK.
You know, like, you know, like the Sodomites, they call them faggots.
And if you call a Sodomite a faggot, you'll say that's derogatory.
That's not politically correct.
But, you know, Sodomites call themselves faggots, too, in joking or whatever.
Black people, you know, nigger is a derogatory term, but black people call themselves niggers, too.
But, you see, the term Christian was so derogatory that it could never be used in jest, in joking around.
There is no derogatory term that exists today that could actually show the magnitude of what that really meant.
All right?
Yeah.
That's really, this is what people don't understand today.
Now, at that time, the people that they were calling Christians, which basically came from the Pharisees and the Sadducees, which means Messianite or a zealot, means you're politically dangerous.
You want to make trouble and you're going to get everybody killed because, you know, when the Romans sniffed out if there was going to be a rebellion, they just killed everyone.
Right?
That's what they did.
So anyway, not always, but that was the typical story behind not – they didn't root out a rebellion.
The Romans basically said, well, you better – if you don't – they go to the authorities and said, if you don't take care of it, you're all finished.
You're done.
We'll take 10 percent.
We'll take one out of 10 people.
And then if you don't take care of it, then we'll take another one out of 10 people just randomly.
Right?
So anyway, so what was going on?
There was a movement that people were interested in what was going on, and they knew that this was all written about in the scripture, which the Sadducees and the Pharisees frowned upon because they had their oral law.
So what happened then was these people took an interest in the scripture, and they were stating that we should keep these laws as they were written from Moses.
You see?
Right.
Where the sentiment during the day – even today, this is still going on today.
If you speak to anyone who is religious or non-religious, that is, quote-unquote, Jewish, they – when you say you study or keep the law, they don't know what you're talking about.
They think you're talking about oral tradition, Talmudic, Rabbinic law.
They don't know that you're talking about what's in the Torah.
Right?
OK.
It sounds bizarre, doesn't it?
Yep.
It sounds really bizarre.
It's a really – so these people who had discovered who the Christ was and wanted to study the written word and the law to find out more about him and had proof through good testimony that he was resurrected were the enemies of the authorities.
And those were the ones that were thrown to the lions and all that.
Right.
At the same time that this was going on, just like the 9-11 thing, you have all these different theories out there and conspiracy groups.
Like right now, I think like the one conspiracy group has taken hold on most people's consciousness with the nanothermite.
Right.
Well, the one that – while all this was going on, there was several groups in different parts of the world, of course, and eventually they were agglomerated in different ways.
It's almost like leaderless, but they were supported by the Pharisees and the Sadducees and the Samaritans, who are not good, by the way, but they're called good, and Simon Magus and all these others to create all these stories.
Gnosticism came out of that.
Gnostics would be like the nanothermite or the space energy weapons that took down – just total crap.
But it sounds plausible because you're so ignorant, you need to grab something to satisfy that vacuum of knowledge.
So the people that were called the early Christians in a derogatory term – remember, they never called themselves that.
They ceased to exist by the 2nd century AD.
They were probably all killed off or went underground or ceased to be vocal about it.
So what took hold after that is what you have is basically a conspiracy theory that exists now.
That's why you have Santa Claus in church and the pope and Easter bunnies and hell and you're going to go to hell or heaven or all this stuff that's just erroneous pagan crap.
So what I did right there was I gave you a history to current date of what is going on with that thing you call the Bible, which is essentially an off-the-shelf doorstop.
And you threw in some lineage there, which was very helpful.
Yeah, I threw it in pretty quick, but if anyone wants to go and re-listen to what I just said, you'll get a pretty good grip on what's going on, but you really won't.
In essence, until you meditate and do a little more historical studying because when I mentioned calling someone a Christian was such a deep insult and pejorative term that there are none these days that exist like that.
So yeah, it just shows you how insane everything is.
There's a little bit of talk recently I brought up in a lot of Shemitic languages actually.
If you remove a letter from a name, it means a big deal.
It changes the name, right?
So in that concept, that was done to change many things and it changes it more drastically for a translator as well.
If you remove a letter from a Hebrew word, it changes the meaning of the word, and a translator will no longer see it as a word obviously meaning this with a letter removed, but he'll see it as, oh, this is obviously this word, which is not original.
It gets pretty deep when you start taking letters out of Hebrew.
Or even just one or two letters.
It'll change the entire meaning.
So someone viewing the text from an objective point of view that wants to create a quote unquote translation or attempt one will easily carry over the new meaning because of the missing letter.
In English, it doesn't work that easily.
You can remove a letter from a word in English and you're like, oh man, I should have run spell check.
You know that it's just spelled wrong.
You know there's something missing, right?
So that was just an interesting concept I wanted to bring up.
So in regard to the biblical stuff and the scriptural stuff, where you are today is where I just brought everyone up to speed on what's going on and where you're at.
And the other thing I wanted to bring up, which is quite fantastic, which is really the fantasticness of any subject when you find out what really is going on simply by objectifying it, is you will see that the subject matter in scripture is regarding the society of the gods.
So that is the fantasticness of the whole thing.
Forget about your superheroes and your fiction fantasy stuff.
This is way, way beyond anything.
I always used to say that if anyone wanted to produce an accurate biblical movie on one aspect of the Bible, of course not the whole thing like Noah's Ark or something, Genesis or whatever, right?
Even the Christ, whatever.
No one would understand or recognize anything in there.
That's how deviated it is, right?
So what I'm saying now is based on not only the biblical text.
It has nothing to do with whether you believe it or not, because it has to do with historical texts as well.
And just to go back to a movie, a film of any biblical situation, no one would recognize it.
Let's say you created, there are plenty of sci-fi films out there that are fantasy, right?
Reading the script sounds plausible, you do the movie and it's plausible to watch.
But I'm telling you, anything biblical done that way would not be plausible because of all the bullshit that people have been told.
You could not say that it's biblical.
You'd have to name it something else.
And you could probably keep the original names and no one would recognize them anyway.
Right?
So this is how far removed you are and this is a story about the gods, the most powerful beings in the universe.
And let me just say it in a wholesale way, no one knows what's going on.
Yes, there are people that know what's going on.
But in a wholesale way, if you were to have a map of the galaxy and, for example, put a pin on where no one knows what's going on about the gods, you would easily put a pin on the earth and say, yeah, these people don't know anything about the gods.
Wholesale.
There might be a few down there.
I feel sorry for them if they do.
You see what I mean?
Right.
So this is a situation that you're in right now.
But it's going to change and it's going to be quite interesting.
And the same thing holds true for the medical industry.
If you're out in the galaxy, say, put a pin on all these planets, where these people live, let's say, where they don't know anything about how their own bodies work, put it on the earth.
These people don't know how their bodies work.
No.
Hmm.
Now you're going to have some inkling I brought up the Taoist medicine and the qi and all that.
Yeah, they do.
They do.
But currently, as it is right now, the younger people, everything's becoming centralized, Americanized, Westernized.
Yeah.
I'm not hearkening back to being a romantic fool about days of old because they weren't much better back then either.
Because if they were so much…
You know how they say, well, our great-grandparents were wiser and smarter in the good old days.
Well, if they were so good, how did you end up in the shit right now?
If they were so good?
Yeah.
Stop making excuses.
Stop being a hopeless romantic.
So, that's pretty much it there.
I'll just take a breather.
Anything going on?
Let's see in chat.
Let me walk over here.
Have a seat.
Put on some cheaters.
Get over a few years, more than half a century.
No matter how proud you are of your eyesight, you're going to need some kind of assistance, I think.
Well, they threw me into the deep end of the pool.
They're Greek.
I am a trifocals now.
Oh.
When I work on small things, I work on, let's say, like spark plug development, right?
And it's really like jewelry equipment.
You don't use heavy…
Well, you know, it's working with metal and automobile stuff, but everything is under two and a half or three millimeters.
Right.
Two and a half a millimeter with metal.
And it's going to be subjected to very high temperatures and high voltage, which likes to eat away at things when it's not done properly.
So, I don't see much there.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Spellcasting.
Yeah, the number of chapter verse thing.
Okay.
Naming of chapter verse thing is also a form of spellcasting, I think you said before, Greek.
Directly, no, but it does use that format.
You know, like a lot of chants and songs that people think are original are actually, you know, forms of keys and chords that have carried through humanity for a long time, and some of them could have been used for that.
You know, like I've used various name issues.
Like, you know, you've heard of people calling, using the name Jehovah or Yehovah.
Yeah.
You know, Yehovah means in Hebrew, by the way, I'm going to just use this loosely because there's a more accurate way to define this, but generally it means to bring distress or bring mischief or to bring calamity.
Oh, my.
That's why the Jehovah's Witnesses, right, are in the, you know, so anyway.
It puts a whole different spin on them.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Yeshu means his name will be blotted out.
Right, I remember that.
And that's actually part of a whole verse.
There's a couple of other words, vizikar, you know, which means out of memory.
But, so anyway, yeah, it's interesting.
What it shows is the robust efficiency of the ancient language and how specific you have to be with it.
Yeah, the spell casting thing is interesting.
You know the analogy I give about a trap, which is the best way to avoid a trap is knowledge of its existence, right?
Right.
And spells are very similar.
In other words, if you don't know there's a spell, it's probably going to be more effective.
And I'll tell you, it is.
I mean, just look at the name Jehovah or Jehovah that they're using, right?
And it's really hard to separate it from that part of the world around that time, so it ties back in there.
Yeah, humans are a strange bunch.
They always have been, but they won't always be.
That's a good thing to know.
So, I don't know, should we get into electricity or anything like that?
Back into your capable hands.
Well, the interesting thing about that is, believe it or not, there's a bunch of interesting stuff.
I shouldn't say a bunch, not much.
If you could find it on Tesla.
I can't approve anything, right?
Because remember, you're still eating corn out of poop, right?
So I can't say, go check this.
Right.
But who is it, Jerry Vasilatos, I dropped the link in once.
He did a lot of research on Tesla's stuff while it was still in the library in New York, before they put it all in storage or destroyed it, right?
Right, and government confiscations.
If you could get past the narrow-mindedness and partial schizophrenia of Eric Dollard, he's good to listen to.
He's an interesting fellow.
He's out in your parts of the woods, yeah.
Actually, Northwest.
Yes.
Yeah, I'm not going to say anything about it.
He did have some interesting prospects on many things.
Yes, if you know how to pick it out of poop.
He had done a fascinating subject on a circus that he went to, an old one.
They had a couple of pipe organs in it, and he was talking about, I guess, the aviants.
How it really moved you around inside.
It was very acoustically sound, let's say.
Old choral music, Bach.
He's a big proponent of Bach.
I've always been a big proponent of Bach.
I remember meeting, when I got into metals and stuff like that, a guy says, it helps to play Bach.
I'm like, why?
It helps transmutation.
Then I heard Eric Dollard say the same thing.
It's polyphonic.
I was like, okay.
The tuning of the organs and everything, and how they were very accurate in their placements, and how the sound diffused through the building.
It was quite interesting.
The most impactful part of the sound, just like the light, is the part that you don't see.
They say UV rays and light are destructive.
Infrared is thermal.
You don't really perceive that as much as you do the visible light.
The same with sound.
There are the various chords and various notes in the sound that, when they're isolated where they peak, deliver the quality.
I, being a musician, I can really relate to that.
There's music out there that just will move you.
Then there's some that actually appall me.
Yeah, like the ones that move you, you'll see that they have peaks in A, right?
A sharp.
They'll have soft, I shouldn't say soft peaks, but there'll be a preponderance of that.
The minor chords, yes.
Yeah, when they're in there.
You don't really know they're there.
Once you find out that they're having an effect, you have to seek them out.
You're like, oh wow, what does this have in common?
But no one will say, there's a lot of A sharp in that.
Very rarely, unless you're tuning an instrument.
So, I would suggest that that's a really big topic.
But I don't like giving the analogy of electricity to water, because they're very two distinct things, right?
It's like saying, let's talk about birds, so I'm going to give an analogy with a cow.
It doesn't work too well.
But they both have to eat, and they're both vegetarian predominantly, most of them.
But then it falls apart.
But essentially, you cannot find, and this is a difficult statement for people to hear, but it's true if you research it long enough.
Any time in history where there was a lack of knowledge of what we call electricity today.
You know, this force unseen that manifests through lightning, that manifests through shocks, that manifests through magnetism and all that.
That's always existed, right?
Through man's vernacular, man knowing of it.
And it didn't come until certain societies and people that we're aware of, were able to do experiments and memorialize them and then hand them down.
Like Volta, Galvani, Newton, and all these other people.
But there were people in every society that experimented with it.
The Greeks had a pretty good handle on electrostatics, right?
So they would actually, you know, if you rubbed glass with sheep's wool, a large enough piece of glass and enough sheep's wool, and you had enough slaves dragging that thing, you could send a spark across the room and zap someone, right?
Yeah.
So they would use that and do things.
There's some interesting writings.
Too bad a lot of the stuff that I've discovered is not on the rectangle.
And years ago, I just passed it off.
I figured, oh, great.
You know, I'll find it on the internet.
And I'm looking and looking, and it's not on the internet.
I'm like, oh, okay.
We'll get there eventually.
I think I recently put up something about the mechanisms of the ancient Greeks.
They were fascinated with machines, that steam-powered, water-powered, electrostatic-powered machines.
I think I put something in the chat about how the early churches were using robots.
Yes.
They were animated.
Yes, like a wooden figurine that would be animated, and people would be amazed.
We know a bird, you'd put a coin in a machine, and the wings would move.
It was always about money, of course, and getting the people's attention.
And the reason there was a pull-it-back-to-the-circus, or the churches, the early churches, they were funded because if you got – see, people were always very leery of the political part of their society.
But if you got them to wholeheartedly give their allegiance and trust to the church, then the political side comes from the back door and controls them through the church, right?
Or just today.
Same thing.
Just like I say, if you go – you want to meet dumb people?
Wait every four years when they do an election, or every two years.
It depends on where you are.
And everyone, yes, if you ask them, where are you going?
Say, I'm going to go vote.
That's a real dumb person right there.
They might sound smart.
They might be a doctor, a lawyer, a judge, or even a college professor, but I could show you 15 different ways in five minutes how stupid they are.
And how ignorant they are, I should say.
In general, about the entire workings of society.
They might have a narrow specialized field, like a shoemaker or whatever, but they don't know what's going on within the society that they live in.
And I'll tell you that ants won't know more about their society than humans do.
I'll say it again.
Ants, you know, the little endemic creatures, know more about their society than humans do.
So, I mean, the society that you live in.
So, you know, I mean, look.
How many people say, I'm going to the bank?
You know, like their bank, that's really a bank.
You sure that's a bank?
Right.
I'm going to church.
Are you sure you know what that is?
Are you sure it's what you think it is?
I'm going to the doctor.
Are you sure you know what he is?
What he's doing?
Are you sure about that?
I'm going to the supermarket to get food.
Are you sure they have food there?
Are you sure that's edible?
Just because you can open your mouth, stick it in there and chew and swallow, doesn't mean you should be doing that.
So, anyway, yeah, this goes across the entire board.
Yeah.
So, have fun.
What else is there to do?
Enjoy yourself.
Responsibly, of course.
You know, like the old liquor ads say on TV, drink responsibly.
It might indirectly tie into the concept of hell, which is going to a bad place.
Forget about the hellfire and the demons poking you and all this stuff, right?
Hell is supposed to be a place of discontent.
You're in it, but you don't realize it, in a sense.
And if you actually look at the translation in there, it means the grave, simply.
You know, there are several other words.
You have Sheol, Guana, and they have a generic term for that.
So, it will only get better from here.
And I don't mean within this society either.
So, that's the best part of it.
So, we've got mystic and all that other stuff.
Man, that's really kind of big.
It would be interesting to do it.
I think I have discussed it in the past loosely.
And just for Wes out there who's listening, I know we're discussing spark plugs and things like that, and he's fascinated to see what playing around with, let's say, the gap in a spark plug does in engine performance.
But essentially, just for that, you have two things going on.
You have a current there, and how do I know there's a current?
And there's a voltage there, and how do I know there's a voltage?
Well, the voltage seems to be more obvious because that's what's discussed with the coil discharging the spark, high voltage.
But the current is actually the part that degrades the material.
You know, it smashes the electrons to bits after a while and creates all that internal heat.
When you have a vaporized fuel, let's say, mixed with air, it's not the voltage that ignites it.
It's the current, the part that's more destructive, the part that's ready to just, you know, affect change in material.
So widening the gap to increase the voltage also increases the current because the gap is bigger.
You need more current to jump to associate with the voltage, right?
So the optimum condition would be a shorter gap where the current is lower and more robust.
But also you want a bigger gap for higher voltage because the voltage does not ignite the mixture.
But what does it do for the mixture?
It charges the mixture, right?
You know, like you charge a capacitor with voltage, right?
Let's say, and current.
So there's one side of the spark is voltage.
The other part is current.
The current ignites and the voltage charges.
So there you go.
So you'll have a faster ignition with a smaller gap but less of a charged mixture.
If you go with a bigger voltage, you'll have more of a charge in the mixture, but then the ignition becomes iffy or not as consistent.
So actually, I personally here, I've figured out a way to overcome both of those about 75% of the way.
In the industry, it's not even 5%.
So, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just you got to look at it objectively.
Look, it's not difficult to go into an emergency room, ICU, intensive care unit, and have about a third of the people go home the next day.
I'm not talking about a regular hospital room now if you know how the human body works.
I'm talking about ICU.
When you're in ICU, they usually stick you after a week or a few days in there, they put you in a hospital bed for a month to six months.
Where because of health care, they usually kick you out the door within about a day or two now.
And you heal at home.
But your time of healing is still the same either way.
But it's the opposite.
It's not because...
They're a bank, the hospital.
I always tell people, if you go to the bank, anything you sign or whatever, you want to speak to someone in the administration, and you would like a cash receipt for the document you just signed.
Because if you talk to the idiot that deals with the public, I want to speak to someone in administration.
And you wait, they could produce that moron in five minutes or five hours, I don't know.
And you have this long form or short form, anything that says...
I have copies here, I signed this, this and that for you guys.
I'd like a cash receipt.
Do you know what I mean by that?
These documents that I signed have a cash value.
And when I say cash value, I'm talking with five to six to seven zeros behind each one.
Per person.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
These guys...
Don't believe what I just said.
Go look up, if you know a hospital, look up the stats on Manto or any of these business sites, how much they earn a year.
Even in a small city, a billion a year.
A small hospital.
A big hospital in New York can do 15, 20 billion a year earnings.
Billy with a B, right?
Wow.
Yeah, look it up.
You'll be surprised.
Where do they get all that?
Credit card swipes, insurance?
Nah.
That too, that's double dipping.
All that stuff goes offshore and is used for money laundering.
Money laundering.
Find out who owns these hospitals.
You'll be surprised.
I'm not going to say that because it varies, but it has nothing to do with medicine.
It has to do with finance.
Here's another thing, concept, guys.
If you have a general, a military general or admiral in your neighborhood, meaning in the country, they usually have a Wikipedia page or some history of this guy.
They're weaponized, you know what?
Look at their history of all these generals and admirals and all that and look at their schooling.
What do they all major in pretty much?
They go to a military school, of course, but what did they major in, almost all of them?
What do they have degrees in?
Yes, economics, finance.
That's right.
Why?
Because it's about money and there is no money.
It's about how they're going to convince people to know if you want to know.
Actually not.
Most people say they want to know when they find out if they don't like what they're hearing, it's no good.
I used to do radio with others and I had one guy always tell me, I don't agree with that or I agree with that.
And I was like, you agree with that?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on a second.
I hear that a lot.
So let me just interpret what you just said.
You agree with me.
If you didn't agree with what I said, because you agree with what I'm saying, it makes it true.
This is how people roll in the world.
Oh, I don't like that.
I don't agree with him.
Why?
Well, I don't like the way he parts his hair.
So what he says can't be true.
It's a standard.
God.
I hear that all the time on the Rectangle.
If I catch an interview or someone sends me a link on something, I hear the idiot host and the moron guest.
Oh, I agree with you.
At least I would give the host the benefit of the doubt until he said I agree with the stupidity that the guy was saying.
I said, oh, no, you're both morons.
Click, all right, off.
It's just, you know, and it sounds short-tempered like in a way that I wouldn't.
Maybe there's some corn in there.
I'm like, you know what?
I don't want it.
I'd rather be ignorant of that subject if they have anything good at this point because I just can't get past their stupidity.
It's a way of information gathering and it's always been that way, believe it or not.
Another thing, just as a little caption on the whole thing, even when you read historians from the ancient days, they were very subjective, by the way.
They get into self-praise and praise of the subject that they're writing about if they find it favorable.
And they do the opposite if they don't find the subject favorable and then to top that off, I'm talking about ancient historians now, is that who knows how many times their works have been redacted or changed and translated into English.
Right?
So if you're going to read Herodotus or you're going to read any of this stuff, yeah, see if the subject matter is interesting but then try to get it in the original language.
Watch what happens.
It's very different.
Or you'll see three paragraphs in the original language and only one in English.
Yeah.
And usually it's the opposite.
Usually you'll see one paragraph in the original language and three paragraphs in English to explain it.
So you're like, oh, why did they leave those other things out?
So, yeah.
Oh, no, they wouldn't redact or leave stuff out, would they?
So that's why it's really important to know for anyone that studies history, what I find to be important is what is important that can be known, salient stuff, information that really pertains to where you are now so you can actually use it so you don't score high on a trivia board game, but you know you have enough accurate history at least to explain where you're at right now.
It's like navigating a ship.
You ever see the old-fashioned big sailboats?
They have diesels on them too.
You've got all these rolls of paper and all this navigation stuff, but you're only using a little bit of it for the trip.
You don't need all that other stuff, all those maps and all that.
Right, right.
Because it doesn't pertain to this particular journey that you're setting out to do this week.
So that's basically the suggestions that I give to people when they study is get a handle or figure out where you are now, what your interests are, and find out if there's anything that would help you along if you knew about it, of course from the past.
Speaking of interesting things, this morning in chat, somebody threw out that link about the Arizona TV station when it was taken hostage.
Oh.
Yeah, that was an interesting thing out of history.
Really?
Yeah.
It was an article?
Apparently they interrupted a live broadcast, had this nutcase that was holding a gun.
I believe he fired the shot, and they forced this anchor to sit back and read off this dissertation by this nutter who was sitting there with a gun.
Nutter?
You mean like the Pope?
No.
He didn't have the clothes on.
Yeah, it was I think a five-hour ordeal.
It was quite the interesting thing.
It was way from the 19, I want to say late 50s?
Somewhere in that area.
The black and white?
Yeah, the old black and white.
It was a cool TV.
I think it was Arizona, if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah.
No, no, I'm not familiar, but those things happen.
Again, when you talk about the news, there's a lot of stuff happening.
Most of the stuff that happens that could be interesting never makes it to the news.
The stuff that's usually in the news is the stuff that's there as part of the agenda, and it sounds kind of conspiratorial.
Of course, there'll be an event and they'll put it in there but yeah, there's a lot of crazy stuff happening all over the place.
Of course, when I say the news, I mean what they put in front of everyone for a day or two or three, but because of the rectangle and the quote-unquote independent journalists, if you have a smartphone you could go out and be a journalist.
Just like back in the days, I knew several people that were independent writers and photographers and you put your story or your stuff together and the New York Times at 4 in the morning opens up, anyone has anything interesting to bring in or whatever, or you call a TV station for an interview.
That doesn't have to go that way anymore because when they have material they just do a website or a blog and they put it up themselves.
Also, the major news concerns, UPI and AP and all the other ones, independent reporters, if there's something that's noteworthy for them to use and you're there and you have a cell phone video of it, New York Times will buy it from you.
They'll buy the rights from you even though you're just somebody out there with a cell phone.
So that still happens.
Very seldom do you have any real journalism where you're actually going out and looking at things anymore like they used to.
Well, the thing about nutters,
let me just throw this in,
if you've ever known anyone
that worked in EMS,
the paramedics,
those guys,
if you ever hung around with them
or whatever,
they have stories on and on and on
and very often,
back in the day,
they took Polaroid shots of things
that they were called to check out
and that was some of the most
just freakish,
nutter-based stuff you can imagine
that never made it to the news.
Oh, yeah.
That would be the kind of, like if you were to write a horror movie or an X-Files, and you needed material, you'd want to go befriend or recruit a retired EMS person and ask them, either him or his buddies or whatever, for access to their portfolios or private portfolios of all the things they'd seen that were weird in their career.
And you would have enough to do at least four or five episodes of X-Files and maybe three or four horror movies.
Maybe a few seasons.
Yeah.
Anyway.
This nutter that I was speaking about was claiming something about Islam and controlling people, quoted something out of Ezekiel, I believe it was 37 or 38, and how Johnny Cash and all these other singers were prophets and some weird...
It was really out there.
We started off by saying today that really bad versions create really bad doctrines and beliefs, don't they?
Exactly.
Yes.
Yes, we did.
And again, just to go back to what I was saying earlier, the people that were around the first century, the early, quote-unquote, I'm not going to use the term, you know, Ishtans, this rhymes with Ishtans, with a C-H, I'll just say it, Christians, what they dubbed in a derogatory sense, they did what they did, I guess it was meant for them to do it, but they did it the wrong way.
They wanted to make a mark in society and establish the rule of the law as it's written in scripture and not what the Sadducees and the Pharisees and the Rabbinics were doing, because they were the predominant religious, spiritual people in that part of the world, right?
Right.
They failed to acknowledge one small little detail, that this world is being run by the adversary, or Satan.
Well, just failed to mention that, yeah.
Well, they failed to live by that truth.
Almost a vanity kind of thing, then, you know, rather vain.
Yeah, it was rather vain, and they got it.
But if you met them and you say, well, yeah, what you're saying is correct, obviously, just like, not because it's a matter of what religion you are, it's like, for example, if you met an attorney and you saw what he's doing, you're like, wait a second, dude, here's your law book, it's not like that.
But if you met these people back then, you'd say, yeah, that's correct, so you know what's going on, you're living in this unique time, and also, what you're saying is correct according to the writ, but, like I say, who are you going to tell this to?
Look around you.
Crazy.
A planet full of idiots, and they're cosmically censored, and the only reason the Pharisees and the Sadducees are like that is to accommodate the evilness of the rest, so shut up, sit down, if you're going to do it, do it, this is not a friendly place.
No, they try to make a mark,
you had the concept of communes,
even today,
where people physically separate themselves,
the true separatists,
that separate themselves
and form a commune out in the wilderness,
or whatever,
that time is over,
so you separate being right in it,
just like you could be in the middle of a sewer,
but just don't be skinny dipping
and drinking the water,
you need protection, right?
Right, right.
Asthma, breathing, so if you're in this shit society, which is what it is, no matter where you go now, it's a matter of, do you want to drink the stuff they drink?
Do you want to breathe the stuff they breathe?
You know, because they thrive on it.
That old Persian tale that you talked about, they thrive on the crap, you don't have to thrive on it, you can still find something, and if it's not good, you try to make it good.
Make your day good, you don't have to be a part of their thinking, actions or anything, no.
That's right, and if they're in the condition that they're in, in a wholesale market, and they sell away, meaning everyone around you, it's not, after a while, you have to throw up your hands and say, they have nothing to do with it, they're just participating, this has been set up for them and they fell for it.
They can't change it.
No, no.
Now there are many times in history where there's an apparent change instigated by the people, yes, it does happen on occasion, on the big early ships, if you had overloaded to capacity the ship with people and there was a whale or something on one side of the ship and everyone went to one side, the ship was in danger of flipping over, if you had that many people.
And a lot did.
Yes, some in the Great Lakes did, with cargo and things.
Some of the largest ships to ever go down are in the Great Lakes, you'd think it would be the Atlantic or the Pacific, for reasons like that.
Shifted loads.
That could happen, and it has happened in a small way throughout society, apparently, but I wouldn't put too much weight in it, no pun intended.
So, that's why, again, the truth, how many times have you heard the truth is still a secret about anything?
You hear people discussing wrong, they'll just spout out whatever they're told in school, or whatever, biblical stuff, wrong, medical stuff, wrong, it's just, what are you talking about?
It's like, who was your first president?
Yeah, well actually, just even recent history, past 50 years, I have no idea what's going on.
Oh, easily, easily.
I'm interested in political stuff.
This is a very quick way to judge the wheat from the chaff, the stuff that should be thrown away or the stuff that should be consumed.
Whenever you're looking at any
political issue,
especially when it's going to change over
at an election,
when they're making all their promises,
if you have anyone political,
and if they don't stand up and say,
this is not because I'm saying it,
this is the veracity of the truth of the matter,
if they don't stand up and say that
we've been bankrupt for about
75 or 80 years now,
it's about time we get some lawful money
so we can operate lawfully.
Do you have anyone discussing that?
No, and they can't.
So it's all crap.
So, alright, anything else going on?
Otherwise we're on for about an hour or so, right?
Yeah, we passed about the hour, 20 some-ish, somewhere in there.
Oh yeah, I see here, someone's putting, a conservative in Australia is socially acceptable and encouraged.
Yeah, that's the new age stuff.
They don't even know what the truth means.
Just say that's very nice.
Their truth is very nice.
Yeah, very nice.
Yeah, but you've got to understand too, I mean, there's still, you know, it's good to profile, good to be stereotypical out of efficiency.
It's not good to profile and use stereotypes if it's in vanity.
You know what I mean?
So, the stereotype and the profile for Australia is that it was basically, I don't know, when did they discover Australia?
1988?
When did it become a country?
I'm just joking.
It was set up as a spillover by the Dutch and the English and all that.
And not because nothing good can go there.
I mean, of course you have some good that can go there.
And you said you were going there.
You were disencouraged because of that initial fact that it was a spillover, a penal colony, a place where they sent crazy people or criminals or black market or people on the run.
You know what I mean?
So, it's kind of like growing up in parts of New York City and you're a white boy and you say, I'm going up to Harlem.
Oh, no, you can't go there.
You'll get hurt.
They'll kill you.
I'm like, no, that's not true, obviously.
But a lot of people have been discouraged from going up to Harlem because of stuff like that.
You see what I mean?
Of the stereotype and the profile of that.
Going to the red light district.
You don't go to that part of town.
Many people are discouraged just from a simple statement like that.
You see?
I see.
Wes just asked, are ether and electricity completely independent of each other?
No, they're not.
No, because electricity, let's just use electricity in the common way that people speak and use it.
That is the byproduct of the ether.
Just like, let's just say you would have, the ether would be the humidity in the air and the condensate you see off of a cold plate dripping off, that would be the water which is the electricity.
It's a condensed form of ether.
And when I mean that, I mean literally.
It is a concentration of a degraded form, the one that most people are using because it's coming off of chemical decomposition.
You know, batteries that are chemically decomposing, coal, nuclear, hydroelectric plants, you know, the way the transformers are wired and all that.
Just like the medical industry.
They study, that's all based on dead people.
Well, how could you say that, Greek, very simple.
What do they base their anatomy on?
Dabber.
They don't know what a living kidney looks like.
They might know what a living kidney looks like when they first cut it out of a person, but by the time they get to examine it and catalog it and illustrate it, it's quite dead.
Right?
Oh, yeah.
They don't know what, that's why the early Gray's anatomy, whenever they brought up a body part, it said it always, it usually appears like this.
It doesn't say it looks like this.
It appears like this, right?
The heart appears to have a ventricle here.
And you see, this renal gland appears to be, you see, they always were very safe that way.
So, this is actually, these are grunts.
These academics, these professors, these people in the professional fields, they've done all the grunt work.
You know, it's like, let's say you have a beautiful structure you want to build, you need the foundation dug.
The architect and the engineer and the artist or whatever is not going to, you know, the master carpenter is not going to dig the foundation.
The grunts are.
Sorry, and if you dig foundations, one of the aspects of getting the big chunk of something ready is grunt work.
And when you go to any of these institutional training facilities known as universities or in programming facilities or whatever, that's all grunt stuff.
And I always challenge people if they challenge me on the aspect of that.
Very simple.
Go to your Ivy League schools, which are online right now.
Depending on what school, university, you know, or particular field in the university and look up the curriculum for undergraduate and graduate studies and actually list all the classes and courses you take, right?
Pretty much like Harvard, Yale, Princeton, upstate, downstate, medical, Berkeley, USC, whatever, you know, Northeast, Northwestern University, whatever you want to look at and whatever field you want to look at.
Look at the curriculum objectively.
And all that other stuff, NYU, whatever.
Do they teach any law in their undergraduate or graduate?
And the answer is no.
They don't.
Right?
When you look at all of the medical universities and colleges, do they teach anything about how the body heals and how the body really works?
No, they don't.
I tested that theory with my daughter who was trying to become an RN and had a couple of experiments with her.
Not a clue.
The RNs, they do a lot of microbiology, you know, like inside cells and chemical, basic chemical stuff, you know, biology.
Basically, it's a biochem study is what she's doing and cell studies.
You have to memorize all this useless stuff.
And half of it doesn't even exist, by the way, in the real world.
Right, right.
I got to look through some of her stuff and paperwork.
You won't find any real photographs.
It's all drawings too and artist renderings.
Simularities.
And they don't exist.
Those are good.
Maybe finish off with something.
You know, when you go to these quote-unquote supermarkets, they have a pharmacy department.
And usually within the pharmacy department, they have a blood pressure machine.
And when it's not busy, and I see the pharmacists are just, you know, bored out of their skull, and I mean that, you know, like they're angry about their lives being there.
They know deep down inside they're doing the wrong thing, but they have no other way to function because that's the path they're on.
Anyway, when I notice they're just like staring into space with those little trays and stuff, especially if they make eye contact with me while I'm looking at them and looking at the area, I say to them, I say, hey, this blood pressure machine here, where can I get one of these?
Or is this something I could get from you guys?
And they're like, oh, no, no, we just rent the space for it or whatever.
I say, why do you want one of these blood pressure machines?
This is like the kind you put the coin in, you know?
Mm-hmm.
I said, why are you interested in one?
I said, oh, glad you should ask.
See, I'm starting, I'm starting a museum on medical quackery and fakery and I wanted this to be one of the primary exhibits.
And they kind of stare at you.
Yeah.
Get that look in their eye.
Yeah, and one guy, I remember it was near closing and I said that to him and then on the way out he was leaving and he says, why did you say that?
I explained it to him.
He says, yeah, you know, I have a suspicion about that.
He was an older guy too.
I have a suspicion about that blood pressure stuff is all garbage.
And right there in a lawful society you take them out back and shoot them because he's been responsible for, well, he's been responsible by how much prescription medication and just like the certain people, they said, why did you put all these people in this camp?
I was just following orders, right?
After a while, those people got hung.
For just following orders, didn't they?
Yeah, this guy is multiple.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, and it's in a lawful society that will not exist.
So in a sense, you have these reminders constantly, you know.
I mean, I've been in, back to the legal society and meetings with attorneys with other people and they're discussing and the attorney doesn't know the law at all.
We brought up some laws once in one situation.
He was befuddled and he was just frantically looking through the book and the book, I said, how long have you had these books?
He said, I've had them for about 20 years.
They look brand new, never touched, right?
And then he got frustrated.
He couldn't find it.
He said, oh, here it is.
Oh, no, this is not it.
I said, no, that's not it.
And he puts it aside and he says, listen, just do what the judge tells you to do.
I'm like, what, excuse us?
Excuse me?
Right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Take care of that.
Yeah, go take care of that.
That's another guy that you would take out back.
if you keep doing that, you lose half the society, you know, and then the other half that's left are sad.
You know, it doesn't work this way.
The gods have to do it.
There has never been a situation where any, whether it was through peaceful or violent means that have changed this core rottenness in human society you know that, right?
Right.
There have been violent dictators that have tried eliminating groups of people.
Did it work?
No, it didn't work.
Because eventually they were gone and they turned the system around and if you go to places like the Soviet Union, China, they have just as many idiots, pharmacists, attorneys, whatever, you want to go down the line, fake food.
I mean, in China, didn't they produce a whole bunch of fake milk out of melamine and poisoned, you know, 100,000 people, babies, right?
Yeah, that was a big thing there, what, 10 years ago?
Yeah, maybe 4 or 5, maybe 10, yeah.
So this goes on everywhere, and then you have a place called, the Europeans were tired of justice so they came and formed America, right?
Make it better.
What did they get?
They tried to do it once, on the other side they tried to do it peaceably, and where did it end up?
Nowhere, it's the same.
So the situation, the evil that persists, when I say evil, I'm talking about it's in the ones that you trust, I'm not saying don't trust anyone and be paranoid, I'm just saying you're not objective enough to know what trust is, let's say, right?
For most people.
And you know what?
They will.
That's why, you know, I was looking earlier, there was something in chat about the book of Revelation and it's scary, and I'm like, well, yeah, book of Revelation is really a hands-off kind of book, anyone can read it, how can it be hands-off, right?
Anyone has access to it, because there's a very small specific group of people in the situation that you're in, right?
That's all it is.
And that book will not be comprehended if you don't fit in the description of that first verse.
I'm not saying the person who posted that in chat is or isn't, I'm just giving that as a general statement.
The other aspect of anything that's in scripture is, of course, the caveat.
It hasn't been translated yet.
We mostly just have it in Greek, which is not good.
A limited version of Greek.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We need to get some, because none of those guys back there did anything in Greek.
Anything you see in Greek was, at minimum, 150 years later.
And it was not one of the earlier writings, you know.
It was just a certain amount of pages too, wasn't it?
Not so much.
Well, again, there's a lot of speculation that one can go into because we don't have anything that can show us better.
So you have to do the best with what you've got.
Just like I was saying earlier, if you just had the King James and it says somewhere, like, my name is the Lord, you're like, we know that that's not a name.
We know that's a title.
We know that it's a poor title because it doesn't even have a sequence of things in that version that you could start piecing it together.
But you will leave, if you just have the King James, you will leave with a very bad idea of what went on.
That's why when you go to, things like the King James, the Geneva Bible, and other translations, have created really bad doctrine and really bad religion.
For example, if you go to the American Midwest they have formed a religion around that Bible.
Not around the scripture.
They think that is the Bible.
They think that's what was given to the prophets.
They think that what's in there is, you know...
Oh, it's a vanity aspect.
Yeah, and they've actually created a religion around a false document.
Like bell-bottoms or something.
So that's why I'm saying when you see the religiosity the only solution for those that are in that is extraction, which could be viewed as poaching.
You don't go there and say, hey listen, leave this place, whatever, you know.
But they're usually unreparable.
They've already done unreparable damage.
Not because they've just created a religion out of a really bad document or bad version or bad information.
It's because not only now but always the state of society has been so unstable that that's where they find their maximum stability.
So if you show them where they find their maximum stability it's really not worth it at all.
Now you've pulled the rug completely from under them.
It's kind of like the magician or the trick, it actually takes a lot of finesse to pull the tablecloth from under the place setting and China wearing everything on the floor also when you do that for them.
Because they don't understand where else to go.
Right, well they're left empty then, yes.
Completely empty, yeah.
So that's why I'm saying they just walk away and it's a very solo path.
Sam often reminds us about that.
He'll say, well I don't care about them, I just care about myself.
Now it might sound self-centered, narcissistic or selfish, but I think he's trying to make a point that just get it out there and whoever can use it will use it and don't bother.
And I'm just interpreting that.
We had one perhaps, can we wait for another show, any info worth sharing about the so-called dark ages around 10 to 12 AD?
You said this time period was heavily censored.
What was it?
10th or 12th century, yeah.
It is very heavily censored.
You're not going to remember it.
That's post-imperial Rome, formal imperial Rome, way post-imperial Rome.
That is a time of tremendous meddling of all the cultures of the earth.
It was also a time where about 75% of all the people on the planet were wiped out due to natural disasters, cataclysms and things.
The Greek mentioned, I was practicing information regarding the cataclysms, right?
Yep.
There's records you can do, you could do a strenuous study.
You will find that during that time period, like between 6 or 800 AD to 1100 AD around there, about 90% of the population in Europe was wiped out due to plague and natural disasters and astronomical events.
Strange phenomena, stuff we've never seen.
I always used to throw in an opinion which I don't like to put out, but apparently what happened there around the year 4000, around the year when the 1st century AD was a de facto end of the world scenario, mankind should have ended right there.
I think the spirits that are poised to do that in Hmm.
Yeah, because you see right now there's nothing else to prove.
Everything that mankind needed to have accomplished about mankind was accomplished around the early part of the 1st century.
This is all filler time.
This is the time where you've already got your tooth filled at the dentist and you're walking out of what you were in earlier.
Right, and you've got anesthesia going.
Yeah, and you're just walking, either waving or you're like, oh man, I've got to get home now.
Now you're walking back out.
See, before you were in the waiting room, 1st century was when they operated and now you're, I'm just giving a western analogy, and now you're walking through the waiting room again.
Yeah, there's nothing going on.
There hasn't been.
Laughing gas is still good.
Yeah, yeah, nitrous.
Yeah, so I would say that, yeah, I would say that just be patient, educate yourself, get informed.
Well, it's about the only way you can do it.
Okay, Dark Ages 5 to 900.
Yeah, that was the time when most of the stuff, 10th to 12th century, getting into the Middle Ages.
We have a lot of heraldry.
There was a boom in heraldry and a revival of the late imperial Roman way of doing things in Europe.
You know, when you see all the knights and King Arthur and Beowulf and Grendel and the art came out from that time period and later from that part of the world, you know how England got more prominent and all that?
Right.
Well, they did, but they were just doing what the Romans had done, just like the Romans had done what the Greeks had done before them.
That was that whole time of like the King Arthur days, the Camelot, Middle Ages.
Repeating, repeating, repeating.
Castles, that was just repeating.
The height of the Roman,
well, not the height,
prior to its
gradual, you know,
imperial collapse,
let's say,
which it didn't really
collapse all of a sudden,
it was just,
it's kind of like
saying it got overrun
and changed
and
they just revived that
in the 10th or 12th century,
but what's unique about
like from the years
like 450 to 900,
especially around
the years like 600 to 800
is when you had the majority
of the people on the planet
wiped out.
When I say 75 percent, that's a majority, let's say.
Holy smokes.
Yeah, and there's no information on that.
And that's also where you have a lot of the legends of the flying carpets and the Vamanas and all that, you know, flying machines.
I remember you saying that, yeah.
Yeah, you know, sometimes people will look at documents and they're told these are thousands, you know, like Sanskrit is 20,000 years ago.
I'm like, nah, it's like 600 B.C., dude.
You know, it's not that far, you know.
The pyramids are 15,000 years old.
Nah, not really.
They're like 3,500 years, man.
You know, but you can't, you know, that's their truth, right?
Right, right.
They've got plenty of dummy loading they can get involved in to figure out what they want to believe in.
Oh, it's a divine thing to do.
Yeah, and the other thing, the thing about the truth, again, none of that matters really at this point.
Well, I shouldn't say, it's very, it's good to know, if you're getting, if you're not getting, if you're not getting corn out of poop, but.
Yeah, but what, in terms of a social perspective, none of that matters, because you're, none of it will be able to be implemented, unless you know when the gods are going to implement what level of, level of truth, you know, the low level or medium or high at certain points, you know.
But there are simple truths, which are which I like to discuss, usually, and so, whoever listens to, let's say, a short or long single event, can walk away with something.
Right.
And I think maybe
in the future,
I'll be discussing
a little bit more,
I mean,
five or ten years ago,
sometimes I'd say
I would never say this
in public,
and I find myself
saying certain things
now in public,
but never say,
and right now,
let's say I'm thinking,
oh,
there may be some things
I need to say
in the future,
and I might be saying
them sooner,
like,
you know,
I'm not going to bring up
what topics they are
because people are going
to start hitting me up
on them,
you know,
so I don't want to
start too much curiosity,
I'm not teasing anyone,
I'm just saying
it's not nothing
that anyone else
can't figure out,
I'm just,
and it's not that
I figured it out,
I can just give a report
if there's a difference,
you know,
there's no figuring on it,
I mean,
there's always figuring,
in other words,
how deep you want to go,
and how much more,
but what kind of reporting,
and that's what I always
used to say
in the early days,
I'm not here
to teach anyone,
or get anyone to,
or anything,
I'm just giving a report,
you know,
strictly because it's become
very,
these subjects have become
almost non-existent,
you know,
in the way they can
be discussed,
and so,
and it sounds,
a lot of things
I like to bring up
sound ultra-rarified,
but they're not,
they always have to do
with something
you're already engaging in.
And you can tangibly check it if you take your time to do so, you know, I always encourage check it out, you know.
Yeah, yeah, it's not that difficult, unfortunately, I have to watch, if I'm going to ponder something I'm going to speak on, I like to, see if I could couch it within the rectangle, you know, I want to, hey, you know, I want to maybe talk about this, I'm going to see what's online about it.
I'm like, if I don't find anything online, I'm not going to talk about it too much.
I'll bring it up, I'll say, this is not online, but I want you to consider these things, you know.
But if it is online, I'll just keep going quickly through it, you know, and, because anyone later on who wants to go through it might find some stuff on it, right?
But there's a lot of stuff.
It does seem like we are getting more and more into the digital book-burning era.
Information seems to vanish, not to appear again, which is very interesting to watch.
I looked at stuff that when I first got my first computer way back in the day, and stuff that I looked up and archived and try to look for it now, I mean, there's a lot that I didn't Right, and it's not even on the archives, it's not in the way back machine.
Yeah.
There is a site, by the way, I've lost all bookmarks.
No.
I use Maxton, M-A-X-T-H-O-N.
Yeah.
You know, but anyway, it's about like how to destroy an account as a website.
If you have an account and you want to destroy an email account and don't want it anymore, or a Skype account or whatever, you just I had that bookmark.
I gave it to some people that have used it.
I've never used it, but the reason, yeah, I think it was yesterday or this morning, I turned on the computer and it went through this process of upgrading and no bookmarks, all right, at all.
Yeah, yeah, so, well, but I, as a young person or young man, I remember having a tutor that kept slapping the pencil out of my hand and because when it's really important, you shouldn't have to write it down, you should commit it to memory, right?
Right, right.
But then again, notes are very important.
Bookmarks can be important.
I got wise and always started archiving all my bookmarks and I periodically would update every couple months or so.
Okay.
That saved my keystore a couple times already.
I'm using
a
old English versus modern English and with the digital format you can with an
upgrade over a period of six months to a year all of the designers getting
together and changing stuff can do more change than there was that in other
words the change between the old English the way it was pronounced written and
understood to modern English which took several hundred years that could happen
within months or years now with a digital format right oh easily easily
even shorter I would think yes yeah yeah so you so gradually this is an
interesting thing within the next few years the entire language will be
changed because oh yeah so you catch people doing it now you know they
incorporate some of those certain emojis into their vernacular and and the
appearance also of the language like the letter a may not mean the letter a
anymore there's something I'm not saying it's going to happen and I don't think
it will teach they don't teach a script a cursive anymore none of that yeah for
sure for sure there's the penmanship is atrocious declined they don't even know
mail a letter for God's sakes yeah which isn't yeah what which is a whole
other convention it's all done point-and-click you know I'm done
yeah it's a yeah it's a completely different convention but but but they
will have their their online stuff delivered in pot and parcel correct
boxers yeah but they won't be able to read the label yeah or write the label
by hand I should say right label you know but I have this suggestion that I
made regarding the language change may or may not happen that quickly but I
wouldn't be surprised if it is you know the actual yeah yeah we can kind of
gauge it in media how they're they're changing their scripting and approach
it's subtle it's very subtle mm-hmm well to me it's not subtle though no no it
to the to the morons at large yeah it is yeah they don't they don't know it's
happening or they realize it's okay like the Android the Apple phone the smartphone
platform regardless of the the operating system I can't I I always like to be
around I will usurp the opportunity well if I'd like to be around people that
have them when I'm out in the field oh and I just tell them look this up for me
but if you had me the thing to do it I just want to smash it oh you said one
time it's a nine-year-old girl how true how true I raised one so yes
you're spot-on oh yes yeah because that's what I perceive it to be if you
see it that's that's what I perceive as well so I mean I can't say having raised
a girl definitely definitely very true all right let's what do you think
anything else sir we've been on for let's see two hours waiting about Skype
okay yeah these things are okay people think they're free they're not they're
using credit you're the credit that was given to you to operate just on a
closing thought perhaps another closing thought right there's a big to-do in
what they call America because there's a very high credit rating right with
what's called illegals and I'm not talking about sick birds you know an
eagle that's sick and it's you constantly see legislation on that from
one hand I'll tell you why it's a big deal it's never going to be discussed
and it hasn't been discussed it can't be discussed because the people that are in
the legislature presidents Congress they don't know this either I mean
they're so compartmentalized some of them do if you bring it up they'll say
yeah I know it but they can't articulate it and I'm going to articulate it for
everyone here listening when you have someone that comes over to this
jurisdiction known as America and the various jurisdictions there in the
various political subdivisions and they start performing in society whether it's
labor jobs or job trying to buy or sell something there is no money to do that
lawfully so the liability on the government is huge huge you could
literally take down the government if you knew how the legal system really
worked if you were if you're a wetback that came over here worked for a week
and you knew how really the system work you could you could leave a billionaire
or be taken care of for the rest of you they probably kill you though before
that because there is no money to pay you you've got some serious beef so so
what is going on is when when you're branded in illegal do you have to hurry
up and get papers it has nothing let me repeat nothing to do with identifying
you for God's sake you know yes it has everything it has everything to do with
you identifying with a credit line to operate which is vis-a-vis let's say the
Social Security number is the easiest one there are other numbers too but even
someone that has a temporary green card or whatever gets a Social Security
number yeah there's what they have to do and once you operate or accept that
because supposed to be voluntary right now you have now waived all of your
rights to go after them for lawful currency or lawful compensation in this
country because now hey they could say hey you got a credit line asshole but
they never let you they never tell you what it is yeah yeah they do yeah the
funniest thing is when I was an economics professor type guy had a
daughter's is all she's only 16 she doesn't have any credit I'm like what an
idiot what an idiot this guy teaches economics right so and they're all like
that by the way because if you're an economics professor and you know how the
money system works and you talked about it you will find yourself eating out of a
garbage can in about a year and they know that well they do or worse yeah so
that's a pretty general statement that holds true across the board with any
field so there are people that know it and don't and promote the other stuff
like the Sadducees so that's why they're sad you see right sad they're
sad you see so anyway I would say I would say that's that's probably enough
for tonight almost about two hours and it's more or just driver yeah yeah okay
well a pleasure as always sir thank you yeah another sonic to put away in the
box a lot of information room to ponder through and I want to thank everybody
for chiming in and listening and any last words or Greek nope that's it until the
next time thanks thanks for all the gathering of this stuff Bruce thank you
problem you're just approaching the $200 mark on all the sonic episodes so a lot
to ponder through there folks enjoy mr.
yeah I'll be up on the server in just a little bit and you take care of Greek you be well and you have yourself a great evening thanks to you as well bye okay bye bye