And good evening folks, we're live with the Greek and how are you doing tonight, sir?
Greetings.
Okay.
Well, yeah, we're doing another sonic what they call Totten's day or death day or Tuesday.
Yeah Yeah Sure, so our all of Satan's sons and daughters on this planet doing for you know, that's the question sometimes, isn't it?
That's too stark of a question.
You know what?
I mean sons and daughters.
It's who's William
Actually doing
You know, so and some people actually come back when I explain this to them like well, it ain't so bad
Is it and I said no, it's not I guess
so
That's that's the mindset
It's really a harsh reality, but is it so harsh if you it's if that's all you know, so yeah
Yeah, but the pricks I
Like to call them pricks or scumbags or morons the average human and it sounds misanthropic, but it's actually quite accurate
It's very objective
They're going to be you know going to the next level which we don't after they're taken out
Which is why I think you said there was a question in the chat about post-resurrection
Yeah, and I don't know if there was any other there's I posted earlier just a few minutes ago or a half hour hour ago
Someone put about veganism.
Do you want to start with the veganism one?
And then we'll get into post-resurrection Touch base on a few things Okay, give a little bit of a formal introduction if people understand that's a of the Hindi or Hindu culture If you're familiar with the old Prakrit Pali Mahabharata Rick Vidas the there was an emergence of a culture that anything that anyone that kills anything is a murderer and even if you You know do it for food.
You're still a murderer and if you buy Food that has been an animal and killed you're partaking in murder.
They're a very extreme group not well liked at all
in ancient times
But this was also contrary to the people
Which are discussing veganism now, which which is basically no animal products whatsoever
And the question was something about you know is it is it good or bad as it's definitely not good
But that doesn't mean that the concept is not
But let's so but
Contrary to the cult of the vegans or the or actually I say the Vedic's I should say which is where it came from
There was an occult it were actually the priesthood.
I have a certain
Group that had said that any animal product is not to be taken by man for spiritual reasons
That is a completely different thing that the V the vegans are not familiar with at all
Most of them are not there a couple old guys maybe that do but most of the it's an urban phenomenon
I think I put down in the
chat, it's a vegan usually
Some underprivileged people find something to latch on to whether it's 5% or
vegan
Communist Party
You know you just go on and on you know there's always a group emergent for those that feel disenfranchised, right?
Yes, so that's the sodomites the lesbians all that you know there's always
Some something for everyone, so that's really where it how it holds its own right now the true understanding of it is lacking
Amongst those that consider themselves vegan, and I'll tell you what it is very simply and I learned this maybe 30 40 years ago
Speaking to someone who was an old Krishna guy
And he was explaining to me the purpose of the food not having any animal is to elevate the spirit of the man basically
You eating something that is so unique that only men would eat not anything else
Like he gave the example like if you were if prepared a proper meal with no animal product
It wasn't that it was just lacking animal product
It was it was spiced a certain way
to elevate your mind and your spirit and your being and if you're eating that meal let's say on the beach and
You threw your meal on the ground
The seagulls wouldn't come and eat it the crabs wouldn't eat it the dogs wouldn't eat it and only you would eat it you see
It was very unique
Flavored and spiced and tailored so only a human would eat it.
Let's say you understand
Yeah, we're right now if you took like what these vegans call whatever and you threw it on the beach
You know the crabs would eat it the seagulls would come down pick it up and go so this is this is a different level
Of it, which is not no very interesting concept
Right and then there's the other I was like, you know, no onion, you know, they got into more stuff because onion is to base
No, you know, it brings your spirit down.
So they had this thing called hin
H I n which is a substitute for onion flavor, you know
This is this is all lacking in the in the urban vegan community and I put in the chat
Yeah, it's it's it's just a thing that you see a dummy load and in one of the comments I put there under vegan rules
If a baby is suckling on its mother a newborn is suckling on its mother's
Breast for milk is that vegan and the answer is no because right?
So where's the option?
They don't understand what?
They don't know what they're just like anyone, you know ask so a Democrat.
What does that mean?
They don't know if you ask a you know, Russia Soviet, you know back in the day.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
That's a Christian.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
It's a Right ask a vegan out.
Oh, it's just animal.
It's bad.
You don't know you don't know Right now your scripture is very clear That the dead flesh makes you unclean drinking milk It doesn't make you unclean scripturally Because it's not dead right right now, of course, they come back and say well the milk is poison.
The cows are mistreated That's not the point If I have a pet cow outside that I love and adore and treat Well as a cow should be and drink its milk.
Is that vegan?
No Stupid is what right?
So there's a whole other level to it, you know, well, then again, I would rather have sheep or goat milk so Right.
So either way Because of there's many reasons for it not necessarily Fully, you know Applicable because cows milk doesn't harm but is you know a smaller animal better?
Yes, that's still a clean animal So the whole thing about the veganism, can it be usable abuse?
Yeah.
Well anything will be used I mean, we don't know for sure, but I would say I would put it on the list as a dogmatic Behavior that could be manipulated towards people.
I think that what will go beyond vegan is in the future They'll be feeding people to people likes member Charlton Heston Soylent Green.
He's like Soylent Green is people, right?
They're doing that now And if I say they're doing it now, it's a Greek.
Where's the proof?
I say we'll just sit back you if you're a pork eater.
You wouldn't matter to you anyway so Because it wouldn't you wouldn't couldn't tell the difference now, you know madness that sets in is different So the vegan movement any any unacknowledged?
See the only thing like if you look at veganism what's acknowledged about it is that it's very different and it's very good But when you start to question your typical vegan why they do it The reasons they give you again are very contemporary and politically and socially motivated You know, yeah That's the 99% of them now.
There's a small percentage that don't consider the sums vegan that do practice That type of eating because let's say they found that if they didn't if they ate Food that was completely devoid of any animal product their cancer went away the cancer they had were diagnosed with diminished or vanished Right, right So and that's very true.
Like there's a dr.
Gerson a Gersen and if anyone knows about him, they killed him.
They tried to kill him a couple of times.
I finally succeeded He basically said you got cancer just eat raw foods and do coffee enemas and cancer goes away and in 90% of the people it did They and he moved to European.
He moved to New York and they killed him in New York, right?
19 this is 1950s.
He killed him So and the purpose of the coffee enemas is the the coffee coming in the backside like that stimulates the gallbladder which releases certain hormones and Enzymes that inhibits inhibits tumor growth or an unusual growth in the body You see so right yeah, so that from there and I know from direct experience if you go with a Non animal based diet you you you know, everything improves.
I mean physiologically for sure.
That's without a doubt
Especially if you understand how to tailor your intake with your activity like there's people that say raw food
Well, if you sit at an office desk all day and you eat raw food, you're going to be miserable
Because you look at the animals eat raw food they jump around and play and run and those like a sloth
that doesn't jump around and play and run that it's only one specific type of
Raw food that it is very specifically
Adjusted to eating and aggressively digests it, right?
But typically apples that eat raw are very active so someone that's a UPS driver a postman a construction worker a Full-time athlete can eat raw.
They'll be fine.
They'll have a little time adjusting But if you're an office worker or sedentary type individual, whatever, you know, you'll be miserable eating just raw All right, so you have to incorporate Right some cooked food.
That's why for example in traditions when someone isn't feeling well, they make a soup or a stew You ever notice that why because it's already booked down and broken down so the body can induct it induce it much quicker Right because they're not active when you're not feeling well, you're sedentary.
You see where people that are very active.
They prefer salads and fresh food.
So The the vegan aspect of it.
I know there's someone in the chat that I'm fond of And if a correspondence who does profess being vegan and this is not directed what I'm saying the negative aspect of it directly to them Some of it might be but it's not directed towards them.
That's okay.
I think they're part of their
Journey of developing their themselves and their character anyway as we all are hopefully
But I'm that's just the hard truth, you know
I'm just dropping the truth and doing giving you the math behind it
The other thing I put in the chat is typically I've noticed for 30 years
People who can't cook and but have a desire to but are too lazy and stubborn to learn how to cook and prepare good tasting
food usually adopt veganism
So when they taunt and try to stuff their crappy food to people and they say this food tastes terrible they say it's because it's vegan
Right, so it's it's fun for years.
I'd go to health food stores and I'm like, why is this cookie taste so bad?
It's vegan.
That's why what's wrong with you.
Don't you know?
Like what do you talk?
Whoa vegan the vegan food diet is delicious It's usually why I say why people that want to cook and taunt people they switch to veganism So now they have an excuse why they're so lousy at at performing the culinary skills, right?
Yeah, and usually most people I run into that are vegan don't know anything about cook Usually or how to prepare and construct meals or the flavors and all that Usually not all of them But actually all of them that I've met in the past 10 or 20 years other than the old You know the Krishnas from back in the days that I knew some of them they knew how to prepare food So it's not a good thing.
No, it's not veganism
I would avoid it as a whole as a philosophy as an ideology and avoid the vegans themselves
Because you're you're not dealing with rational people usually
Why would you just say, you know, why would you say I'm vegan would just say I don't take on animal product
You know, but you get they people are always trying to brand someone like when I'd go out and you know restaurants
I said, well, I don't dig on swine anything about pork and like what are you Jewish?
I'm like, no, I just don't dig on swine.
Right, you know, you see they can't they always have to pigeonhole you and You know, whatever So they don't know So if you consider yourself a vegan that means you fell for the pigeonhole get yourself out of it If you got any substance left to you Otherwise, you'll be you'll be dressing up in the vegan substance, which is crap.
So That's my part on that.
I think some of it sounds a little opinionated
but if you look up what I've said and are objectively noticing and looking at everything you will find that
What I said is true, unfortunately or fortunately
Not to discount the benefits of a non animal based diet just to throw in a you know
You can always make fun of people for their stupidity whether they're vegans communists Christians Jews Muslims, whatever, you know, you could go Republicans
Doctors lawyers you could always make fun of anyone.
So after you get that out of your system You know if you want to be sarcastic or snide or you know Get that out of your system you realize the best thing to do is nothing just sit back and just go the other way a Little bit, you know if you can if it takes too much energy to avoid these types And obviously you're gonna have to do a slight encounter, right?
so Because you can't avoid the idiot on the on this planet.
That's just the nature of it right now.
It's what comes natural But again, I want to bring up another point.
I was at a vegan restaurant, New York City quite a while back and Lady the waitress says welcome.
There's a new restaurant, you know, we're vegan.
I'm like, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah So there's no animal product in here at all whatsoever.
I let her go on and on and on I said the more she's saying the more rope she's gonna give me I'm gonna hang this idiot, right?
And she goes I said, well, this is a new building.
She stopped speaking and I'm like, okay, this is new Isn't a new construction.
She goes.
Oh, yeah.
I said is this drywall or like plaster?
She was always dry Well, I said, you know that drywall has animal glue in it It's animal byproducts in it All their walls are coated in animal byproducts.
You got leather shoes on How are you talking about And the food wasn't that good either and when I complained about I wasn't good.
She's was vegan bunch of white people can't cook Yeah, so it's really not good.
It's really it's a bad situation Anything with a label on it, you know, it's kind of like years ago people, you know, I talk about scriptures They you're too religious.
I'm like what makes you do all yeah, maybe but not what you think
You know like the Christian people thought I was Jews and the Jews thought I was messianic and
You know, they can't they don't understand
so for those that need the pigeonhole the the simple idiot definition call yourself a communist a Democrat a vegan a
Jew a Christian a Muslim whatever if you need that well, obviously if a shoe fits wear it
But I'm telling you it's not nothing good will come out of it
Because all it can be it'll be used as an ideological tool when necessary and
the reason I say nothing good will come out of it from a social point of view is because it'll be used as an
Ideology to go after those that are mistreating animals or how it's this and that you see it's not gonna be you know
It's not going to be fashioned as something
That can benefit, you know any any group, you know
I wouldn't say elevate because you're not going to get elevated here unless you got an elevator, but
the
The no, it's not a good.
It's another ism And most people again like Christians don't know anything about their Christianity or what they profess to know vegans Don't know anything about food or what they profess to know really?
There's just it's a political thing
And you know, maybe I'm harping a little bit too much on it
But I assure you that you'll find it to be true if you're awake and aware and looking at things objectively
not-good any ism
You know and the thing about the ism and and not only the vegans but most vegetarians if you ask them about
From whether it's cosmic or secular psychosis means dumb to me
They don't know why they're vegetarian.
They just say well, it's Animal look good to eat animal meat, you know, whatever.
That's about as far as they go or they'll pull some
You know tradition or of a religion or something, but they really don't know the lawful aspects to it
and then of course you have the aspect of
The which is a very effective
You could say the underpinning
Fact that most cancers can be reversed or eliminated through, you know vegetable based diet
Vegetable and grain that's a fact that's well quite well known for many many years
But then again, you're like well, why do you do it because I don't want cancer.
I mean my cancer go Oh, why are you talking about in such context, right?
Oh That's a cancer-free diet.
That sounds so appetizing, doesn't it?
right Not really So there's nothing good really out of it other than what you make of it if you can if you take something Let's say again the concept of being a vegan which is no animal product and you can use it in a joyful Way and in a lawful way.
Yeah, of course, it's good But what I'm discussing is the group as a whole as an ism as an ideology.
No, it's pretty foul like any other thing right So and the the farmers that are cruel to the animals don't give a shit about how many vegans there are I don't care about you.
Just like the Democrats don't care about the caught the Republicans.
They'll fight with you
That's not gonna stop them from doing anything
so anyway
that's what I have to say about that and
The part that rubs me the worst about the vegans is they don't know how to cook and they lack finesse and skill
Not all of them, but just about all of them
I mean, I'm sure there's some vegans out there know how to cook, but I haven't seen any
Or tasted anyone's food other than the old old Christian is from back in the day 30 years ago
You know or some Indian place, right?
So It's just another ism Not good now, is it going to be used?
Yeah, it can be but I would suggest that it's People are so vile That if you're going to push veganism on them, it's not vile enough I think what will be pushed on people is a deception that their food is good when it's actually other people You know or baby parts or you know what?
I mean, right?
That's that's more in line with the human Human what do you call it experience?
right, so And again just to wrap up on the vegans.
I have personally given and created more recipes and Suggestions to vegans and they've ever given to me and I'm not a vegan.
So what does that tell you?
anyway
in other words vegans come to me for
For and have for developing flavor and developing recipes and I've never gone to a vegan for anything
What does that tell you and I'm not even a you know in that business of food
So it's not good
So in other words
They're trying with our whole life and they can't come up with crap and I'm not trying on
Veganism and I come up with more stuff than they do.
What does that tell you?
Yeah It's it just doesn't make any sense.
So
All right, what else have we got
I
Think I might have commented on that I think
Now what people you know, I attribute everything to the gods
I recently got off a conversation regarding that what we can't just contribute all to the gods
But you know at the moment I'm like, yeah, but you have to but either way
One thing that people forget is, you know when you read something in Scripture, you know
Look a demon for example cause stuttering
But then you have other people that it wasn't attributed to a demon, but it was it's just that the anatomy was changed
Like for example, let's say, you know, there's a god of the sunflower.
There's a god of the cabbage There's a god of the mountain.
There's a god of the river.
There's a god for stuttering There's a god for every aspect of human behavior The Greeks are quite good at that back us Dionysus, right?
Very those are the various balls or Lords of various human behaviors.
The Hindus always did that
You know when you we did something bad, they said well, it really wasn't you
You're appeasing the God of doing that that day, but you have to do penances
I've said we're gonna charge you with a social debt put you in a prison
That's why you know, the prisoners are an orange, you know, they wear the Hindu garb of orange
anyway
So
There's a spirit behind it
But the thing is is there always a spirit behind it not necessarily after the fact because they could actually change and rewire you
Whether it's from the womb or later to be stuttering you see
So it could be mechanical
right
In mechanical meaning nervous muscular
Physiological anatomical, right
Well, either way it has to be addressed from the spiritual side to acknowledge that you know
There is a overall primacy to everything and then move down the line
There's several ways to look at it.
One is there's the conventional way
I you know, whatever they discuss, you know in the conventional idiot, you know, the average medical technician or academic
whatever they've researched go on the
Whether it's a mini television or the stupid rectangle computer or whatever see what they talk about it avoid
of course anything pharmaceutical or anything that the medics say regarding any kind of
Treatment that they consider conventional because obviously there's still people stuttering some of the stuff doesn't work, right?
All right, so you can look into something that's more evolved And other than that, I really haven't researched it and I can't make any suggestions on mitigating a stuttering you know condition Had a friend of mine that had that problem and hummed.
He loved to hum and it seemed to help him Especially if he was If he was listening to an audiobook he would kind of mimic with humming The actual kind of like retraining oneself to rebuild that You know something that we take for granted Like a tone producing a tone, correct and and it went into farther things like that where he had like a Slight tone in the ear and it seemed to help a bit too.
And then finally he overcame a lot of it
there would be
Occasional times the thing I found interesting is it would it came and it left it came and it left
That's how he was kind of describing it when I was so so that could be
So it's a it's of the mind or you know
If it's if you don't if you let's say did a cat scan or an x-ray didn't see he had a deformity
You know in the actual body and anatomical then it would be a spiritual thing of the mind, correct?
I think the person also put it in the chat that they tried speaking with their mouth shut or many other techniques or whatever
Yes, there there is an aspect to
Making efforts and exercises that are known to improve
And at the same time, I don't like to use this word because most people don't know what it means is the concept of prayer
Right because that's my word that's been hijacked by many religious groups, but asking
Especially if you can go high up the ladder
For it to be mitigated.
Now.
One thing I didn't mention is the other side of it
Is that that might be your quote-unquote, you know cross beam to bear in this life to learn from it or to show others
You know, right, so I'd say make the best of it, you know
And always practice but but if it's easy, yeah
Sure, but you know the words you're gonna see someone that is stuttering that's trying to figure out how not to stutter is gonna learn
More about it than someone who does it.
Oh correct.
So so in that aspect, you know well, I guess we're all learning about it, but I would suggest there's there is a Supernatural divine nature to it and that has to be addressed first at least that'll bring peace to the mind so you don't have worry and Right worry and stress and whatever the doubt In other words, you should be without any doubt that there's a spirit behind it Period that's for sure.
And most people of course would balk at that.
That's what most most people though.
So And then take it from there.
So you should not worry about it or stress whatever There's the you know and ask for help and say if it's meant for if it's the will The most high for you to stutter then make you know, make everything else Accommodate for that, right?
There's many so many things to do it you one might consider it a handicap, you know I don't know how bad it is.
Like some people just can't get a word out Yeah, and other people it comes in like you said the guy who was humming so either way There's a primacy to it But that now that was the one that he brought anything else.
I Don't see anything else since then.
No Actually been very quiet Well the first question One of the first question you said what happens after the resurrection the post-resurrection?
Yes post-resurrection.
Well, there's post-resurrection And there's post-resurrection.
Well, which one right this post-resurrection post-resurrection is the first resurrection
Which is when the gods right become overt
You know and then there's the resurrection in a thousand years or nine hundred and some odd, you know
980 something year X 70 something years now
There's going to be the second resurrection for everyone and then the earth gets cleaned up and really seriously terraformed
You know, there'll be no oceans.
No mountains as such, right?
There'll be enough landmass to support trillions of people, you know thousands of billions, which is trillions Quite harmoniously versus the satanic Concept or ideology that the earth is overpopulated, you know, what is it?
Less than 5% of the usable landmass is being used at the moment.
Yeah something like that Yeah usable not unusable rate, right correct.
So yeah, so these are just another satanic thing You know adversarial to what is true So, uh, so I didn't get to that what happens after the resurrection Well, what does scripture have to say about it is all we have then you could venture off and study any other ancient witness I you know was a way to call it right the ancient witnesses, right?
What's written down and try to See if it's bullshit or not because for example you go into Gnosticism That's straight-up bullshit right or a Mormonism or whatever, you know, but they do you know because the subject matter of that is Regarding the gods, you know to some people Gnosticism and Mormonism and whatever other doctrine you see out There is not bullshit.
So how can you say it's bullshit Greek?
Well, then you have to go into hierarchy of order and the highest order again is the scriptures, right?
Which by the way is still a secret There is no one place you can go and get the lowdown on who the Christ is or anything About anything like that without being drifted off into some other thing because you know, we've discussed why past But essentially when people call it, you know the day of the Elohim, you know Lord for the Christians or when the Christ returns and all that.
Yeah, they call it, but I'll tell you what it really is
That that the end of days what's known as the end of days or when the rest the first resurrection starts actually the first
In mass resurrection because the first resurrection already took place with Christ the prototype and that one counts the most
But it's not counted as when the resurrection start you see, let me tell you really what's coming
Whether the for many religious point of view or there to what's really coming, okay?
I mean the real reality of it not whatever what people want to call it the end of days or whatever the return of the Christ or no, no, no, that's not what it is.
The real reality of what's coming is the overt Versus covert the overt presence of the gods on earth.
Let me say that again in case you missed it What is referred to as the end times the beginning of the resurrection the return of the Christ the all these things is none of that Because it's some of that but none of that none of that meaning you can't just pin it on one thing But I'll tell you what it is.
It is the overt presence of the gods on earth Period Because when the you could take one thing at the end of days, what do you mean?
Like there isn't going to be any day No, of course, it's the end of the days that were given on the lease that was given to Satan All right, his days are up right right the return of the Christ.
Well Yeah, you could say that also, but does he come alone?
No comes with all the other gods Right, and it's overt Right end of days the day of the Elohim or the day of the Lord is the idiot it's a Well, yes, because the time is up of a certain period right but what's interesting From that period on there will be no atheists anymore Right, there'll be no argument.
In other words, there'll be an overt presence of the gods on earth where it never has happened Well, I if you go back to the days of Abraham, it was fairly overt Right, right, you know what?
I mean the days of Noah would suggest in all that back to the page It was pretty back to the time of the recreation of the earth.
That was fairly overt to most
But what's interesting about but you see that was still under the auspices of Satan
the lease of the earth and this
reality given over to him
We're now oh, it's and it stopped and you know, of course, you know, if you understand some aspects of Scripture
Supposedly he's brought back to and then humanity rejects him completely because they're aware
right
So that's what the end of day is about the overt presence of the gods and I've said this many times
I've never emphasized it, you know, some people want to say it's the end of days the last day is the return of the Christ
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever
It's not really the return of Christ because he doesn't come along
You can't just say that
Right, right
Comes with it with an entourage of millions of spiritual beings
So it's basically the overt presence of the gods on earth and one of the promises that was made
to mankind if not the promise is what happens after you die, which is the resurrection and
Post resurrection at that time after that happened with the gods are over
They have the the resurrection of the patriarchs and the early people
that you read about in Scripture right and the
Apostles right and many others that are not whose names are not written to us but are written in the book of life
Let's say right and they will rule the earth
Which will still be a bunch of 5% of the population is left is not going to be
The surviving people that are on the planet are not because they're worthy of it.
They're just a representative sample
They're just going to be just as evil as you know, the rest are
right, and they're going to be ruled over and
You have a lot of things changing
In nature, so life human life on earth will no longer be the same even just the over presence of the gods
Cannot you know, you won't need fighter jets or nuclear bombs and electricity and there won't be any grid
Right satellites and all that stuff, right?
It's going to be very different Because you want to go to space you don't build a spaceship you go with the God he takes you there you see, right?
Anyway, anyway, you want to light up a house.
You don't need a wire bringing electricity Right you the God you see lights it up for you.
So we very different world But what's interesting?
I've stopped looking at it for a little while Which I'd like to resume is the actual technical aspects that we know That a group of people is led out of the Levant Back into the wilderness, you know, like for example, the Exodus scenario is revisited and They're held for a generation 40 years and trained and let's say I'm using paraphrasing here, right?
Yeah, that's when you read in the Psalms.
I will not fear as I pass the valley of the shadow of death is behind me Right.
Mm-hmm.
It's a shut, you know, they're seeing the shadow.
So there's the that's the lake of fire, which is the Dead sea, right that will be ignited all right, so they're gonna pass that and they're gonna so we're talking about 40 years of coping with Post-destruction earth society You know, what would be on a quote-unquote used in modern Hollywood terms apocalyptic scenario, correct?
You know the other day I brought up but there will be no roofs He is a house a house, but doesn't have a roof on it.
Or is it just a bunch of walls you see, right?
So
so what you're going to see is
If you survive it is basically a 40-year period of what the hell happened here
that's how drastic and devastating it will be and
then you you you
You can imagine the over presence of the gods filler fulfilling human requirements
right
Because the idea is not to completely wipe out humanity or torture humanity, but to sustain them
Right, so, you know, you won't need water pumps the gods will provide water.
I know it sounds kind of crazy, right?
So but I just needed to voice that out and it's right again what the purpose of declaring something as the return of the Christ or the end of days or the day of the Elohim or all this is not that at all.
It's the overt presence of The gods on earth is what it really is It's like does the Christ exist in a spiritual form and as the head deity right now, of course, oh, yeah Show me prove it to me Right.
I guess it's a matter of belief now, isn't it?
It is You know, where are all the gods, you know, they can do anything or I prove it to me Well, I guess it's a matter of belief now, right?
You see the difference mm-hmm when it's overt no one's gonna ask prove it to me
in your face
They'll be in your face
That's what happens after the resurrection
So after the resurrection if you are one of the first to be resurrected you will be amongst all of this and you will be like
a god
Essentially, I don't know how else to say it
And that's pretty much it in other words if you want a physical body
You shall have one if you want to sit down and eat with people, you know
Look the King James says you want to sup with them, you know
What a ridiculous document by the way King James or people actually
Still think it's the what they call the Bible and it is the Bible, but you know, it's not the scriptures, right?
But if you want to sit around let's say you Some people that have not been resurrected and survived this and you want to be around them Well, you might want to take on a physical body and eat some Hebrew national hot dogs with them or something.
I don't know if you're white people You probably eaten some tuna casserole or whatever, right?
But anyway and string bean casserole but anyway Yeah, you might want a physical body you may not and it's your will hmm, you see all right and These people that are resurrected, you know, we can go down the line who they are you get anyone can it's for sure the prophets and the patriarchs and the Apostles right and those that were that were Considered in what's called the book of life, right?
Sephirot I am right.
That's in Hebrew would be the scroll of life.
So so so You have a group of people that are now dead that the first waking the next thing other than them remembering they had died the next moment is Consciousness of being resurrected or you know the resurrection So Like Woody Allen says if dying is so bad How come no one has come back to complain about it, right, right?
So Adam the next, you know, whatever last memory he had the next memory he has Is the resurrection and there is no memory of death being dead for so long You see so then you now you're God you have godlike powers and if you want to understand Well, you know how to say people are fallible.
You still are even at the resurrection One of the scenarios is in the book of Zechariah where the high priest is held and his mouth is shut You know, that's why I keep saying at the resurrection.
Just keep your mouth shut It doesn't say in Scripture keep your mouth shut at the resurrection It implies that very strongly and it shows examples of it So but I don't know why people haven't pieced that together and tell the public at large that it behooves Anyone to wonder how stupid?
Any any kind of discourse on Scripture has been For so long.
I think time for that kind of ridiculous Discourse is over.
It's why I sometimes dare say like to speak on these things.
Well, just essentially historical looks at history Wow Where do you know the history is written by the winners and what if the winner wants to be written as a loser?
Because there's benefits into being a loser.
Yeah, just like yeah, you know Like people do that on what they call so-called tax forms put on you have more dependence You know, I want to look like I'm in bad shape, right?
Right Proforma accounting makes you look either good or bad depending on what benefits you book in the book Yeah, so the books are cooked That's why I say lately for a couple years.
I say why bother do nothing Do nothing just get out of their way They want to live in paradise tomorrow and create a paradise they can do it That's fine with me if they want to just kill each other for no reason.
That's fine with me either way I want to stay away from them You know in the state that they're in right, right.
There's no benefit in anything here So anyway back to the resurrection I think in the past five ten minutes about that I've painted more of a picture than you've seen anywhere ever ever.
I hate to be arrogant about it You're spot-on, buddy If you study scripture and look at the intent This is what I just said in the past ten minutes has never been said before in this way.
So succinctly And it's sad to say that it's pathetic It just makes me think like why don't I just get off the stream right now and make a delicious dinner You know and throw my feet up on the air and watch some Netflix for four hours.
Why bother, you know, even though You know, I mean, I'm just an example actually, I've got plenty of stuff to do but Mm-hmm, my list grows, too Yeah, so so Post resurrection is not going to be all that honky-dory, you know, like they say it's a little white people phrase.
Yeah, I would suggest that The best way to go as stated in scriptures to be part of the first resurrection Right.
Oh you're speaking about Zachariah in the mouth shut Yeah, yeah The priest was You could read that yeah, I don't like to get into what I like to paraphrase because you know Most people still don't want to study scripture.
They're they're censored.
They can't they look at it
That's whatever, you know, unless it's a laundry list of stuff
They like to listen to what other people have to say about it, which is fine
That's just the condition of man right now because if everyone was able to study scripture and comprehend it
It might be enough to screw up the plan you see I'm not saying that I
Study scripture and comprehend it
you know, haha, so that sarcastically but
Because to say that sounds kind of arrogant to most morons, but if if you have a propensity for studying
By the way, not only other people
Try to say scripture don't comprehend it because they're censored
But from a cultural point of view it is written in a way that they are not
Able to handle like people don't speak like that people don't think like that anymore
Because you're you know, you think in the manner of a slave or a serf
Mm-hmm, you see
see if you look at old depictions of
human society in the Western world 500 years ago the slaves and the serfs or the you know, the
whatever the
plebeians were never
Considered highly and even if you read any old literature, they want to slave a serf or a plebeian speaks
It's like blue blue blue blue blue, right and they were never thinking of highly at all
Right because it's like the brains have been garbled up
And this is the norm
now
When you're reading a works of the ancient witnesses to the gods
You're reading
Something that is a highly ordered mind
You know and I've maybe met two people in the past 10 or 15 years that have a highly ordered mind
right
So you're not it's not gonna you know, so forget it.
That's why I said don't why bother studying scripture?
You're not gonna understand it and I've never really gotten into why other than well just now You're censored.
It's not meant because if if it was too many did it the plan would get screwed up And the other thing is you you were raised in the manner in a culture and tradition of a serf or of an idiot of a plebeian You can't think clearly enough for that.
It's way beyond your pay scale as they say right So and also I think I've mentioned many times in the past when you read scripture, it's what the gods are writing the those Most of scripture if not all of it.
I should say I could say all of it is is Dictation given to quote-unquote scribes or prophets and which who had scribes Dictation they were it's all dictation, right?
It wasn't written on their own behest.
It wasn't written.
It wasn't creative writing Right, you know what?
I mean?
So it's what the gods think of you and what the gods are seeing and what matters to them.
It's about the gods really I mean, that's what it's obvious To see why there's no airplanes and rockets and power grids and stuff in there You don't have any talk about any human inventions in there other than all things were and they just Memory of them has been forgotten.
You know, there's nothing new under the Sun, you know implying, you know reference to these things, but there's no
Fascination of anything that we're fascinated about in there because it's just basically a very rote dictation from the gods
Especially the most high
it's really the Christ who's doing it, but the one that's
dictated by
The Christ from directly from the father is the last book
Right, which is the first book.
Mm-hmm so As you noticed I've lost my as time goes on I lose more of my enthusiasm to explain these things For obvious reasons, but right Yeah, they've been said already.
So if you don't know what I'm talking about, it's tough shit, but on the other hand Again just to stick to the topic Post resurrection It will be a tough period for sure for 40 years or so though.
You will have the teachers pet Who is we were called call them the Israelites they are the teachers pet That they're called the chosen people because they're chosen with a laundry list of deeds and acts and things that are going to happen around these people so you have a Reference or a time clock to watch right?
Mm-hmm, and they're the teachers pet Doesn't mean when you say teachers pet that should evoke the concept of a classroom also, it doesn't it or it does The teachers pet if the teacher has only one then it's not the teachers pet It's just the only student but if they're not they are the favored ones, but it doesn't mean that the rest of the class is not Addressed either, right?
So
so the
Survivors or the chosen of the chosen people will be the ones that go into a let's say
crash course
training of roughly 40 years as they did
You know
before
You know, I was in a conversation recently about speaking just a little bit about the patriarchs
And what one day I'll get into it more, but I just give a little bit because I'm very weary of
Discussing scripture you have to be you have to really want to do it publicly.
I'll do it privately but publicly I I don't think there's much reason for it anymore because I think I'm waiting for to see signs that Something called the New Testament or the writings of the witness the ancient witness to the Christ on earth will be provided somehow You know instead of their ridiculous New Testaments that you see out there now, right?
I'm always looking for you know Is there a project to bring it forward what was really said and start discounting all the ridiculous notions that are around that?
So and that's not happening yet.
So I don't see it right now so there's no reason to start talking about scripture in detail, but a Little bit.
I do like to give a little bit of things that I've meditated on and contemplated that are in scripture And one of the things that I brought up recently in conversation regarding the patriarchs since I brought up, you know, the Israelites if you were example got into the mindset of Noah or Abraham and you presented Which happened much later the exodus?
Which was the Israelite slaves?
leaving Egypt Okay, if you presented that them let's say in that state to Abraham or Noah.
They would come back and say Those are Israelites.
Those are just a bunch of Egyptian slaves You get it, right?
Okay.
Yeah Because let me just put it this way.
Let's say your fourth generation German Swedish Swiss German Swiss, let's say Italian in America, you know, they emigrated here in the 1800s Right now if you presented this third fourth generation American To someone, you know, you know other than that would say this is just an American You're not gonna say oh, this is a German Swiss, whatever.
No, they're not.
Let's say this is an American ugly American, right?
Look at him, you know, the Europeans used to say, you know, they're American You could hear him from a block away and they got terrible dressing Sense, they they look terrible.
You know, they wear sneakers.
They don't know how to dress their fat They they're obnoxious loud.
You always you always come uninvited in and stay too long Yeah, that's also yeah, they have no sense of hospitality, you know was it all no no Greek you're off because they're German you see They emigrated here yet.
No.
Well, okay so if we if you in the mindset of the patriarchs and you saw who came out of Exodus or Egypt is Nothing more than a bunch of Egyptian.
What?
Not plebeians Egyptian slaves Talking ghetto Okay.
Mm-hmm When you go to the American ghettos that are mostly black I assure you whether you thought of that or heard of this or not.
That is still the same slave mentality from the 19th century Mixed in with the prison drug rape population mentality The fashion the style of speaking food the culture they have not recovered from that slave shit That's I mean, I know some people industry that are older black people.
I bring up the word slavery.
They freak out It's like a very touchy subject, right?
Yeah, they can't handle it because they think it pertains to them only, you know But I'm saying if you the modern American black ghetto is is this if you go back pre-civil war There's no difference other than radios and and Nikes Same mentality.
Yeah You see they're not it's not that's not a quote-unquote African Negro If you go to the continent of Africa all the various countries, they're very very different Those are people.
Let's say that if we're not and did not have that slave Mentality, right?
You see what I mean?
And also they've been given this see fortunately I was exposed at a young age Semi-culturally, I say we're not as prejudiced as others Like for example, the Greek culture is not prejudiced against black people like other cultures are believe it or not, right?
But but let me just say it this way if you Let's say they've been given a bad rap like 3040 years ago.
I remember going to black neighborhoods that were middle class and upper middle class and like in places like Queens New York City and northern parts of new northern New York and parts of what's called Long Island.
They were middle-class black Predominantly black like black and predominantly like it was all black really Middle class and upper class and they were there for many many years So this the bad rap about quote-unquote the African American Negro ghetto is a very bad rap It's a very negative almost rat when you what do you call it when you rational when you when you?
Marginalize someone.
Mm-hmm.
It is not true.
There have always been affluent Negro Why a black American You know of African descent communities in America always Have been those types of communities, but they no one in the popular movement and the popular mindset does not consider it That's why when I said earlier when you look at the modern culture of the black culture That is prevailed in the American mind in the Western mind.
It is not that culture
It is the slave culture the prison culture
the with the sneakers and the music and the those that you see
Okay, there are of course there have been prejudices and and marginalization and all that but that's not what I'm addressing here
I want to go back to addressing what the patriarchs how they would have you viewed the Israelites as
Nothing more than a bunch of Egyptian slaves
Yes
The blood that's running through their veins the majority of them also were Israelite
But not all of them because it says a great multitude also left, right?
So you had Greeks and Philistines and you know Canaanites and others that left to right right Egypt Would be Keftari.
Let's say what they were called They were not called Greeks or Hellenes then but let's just sum it up as it was a mixed group of people but if you had the mindset for example of Noah or Abraham or any of the patriarchs and You viewed, you know hundreds of years later who left Egypt that would be an indiscernible from any typical Egyptian slave.
So Go back to post-resurrection the people that would be brought into The wilderness again to be reworked.
These are survivors now not resurrected people To be reworked To be leaders in this new social order on earth with an overt presence of the gods They will be viewed as just nothing but Satan's slaves Satan's children that need to be reworked and retrained you see Because the if you look at the majority of people that call themselves Israelites today, they have no clue of what's going on.
They they're they're
spiritually culturally and traditionally they're in a part of their
down to the bone satanic
In virtue, you know, they've been beaten down by different books just like everybody else
It's the culture and tradition cultures traditions
Yeah, in other words the people the Israelites now they are only familiar with the current world culture
Whether it's a world culture Western Eastern or where particular country and that is downright satanic.
Yeah, you know, this is Satan's I'm you can't escape it.
That's why I've said many times If you're passing through this in a starship the earth and you point and say this is where Satan rules and everyone on there is his children and his sons and daughters.
That's very accurate There might be some exceptions, right?
Mm-hmm Meaning the Sun and or meaning that's that's where you get your direction from, you know, not your biological Right, so we're in a very very sad state of affairs But you know most people don't see it because that's all they know again just to go harken back to Jack Fresco's analogies with culture Yeah, does it upset you?
You know, I mean, yeah, of course, they're gonna be upset cuz they don't have enough shrunken heads
So it's the same here now
So, you know, it's gonna be a harsh reality, but I guess I don't know hope that I
don't know if I performed an answer or performed a thought on the question about post-resurrection life because
The resurrection is the promise to mankind about what happens after death and
What that doesn't happen until there's an overt presence of the gods led by the Christ and the angelic beings
Right, and it's not only to quote-unquote like many people might think which is not incorrect to defeat Satan.
It's not He was ever in a position to win.
Anyway, this was a lease that was given to him So when a landlord comes to evict or clean up a place that was let's say the one-year lease is over a tenant Does he defeating the tenant?
No, there's no defeat there.
The lease is over That's why if you look in Scripture very closely Satan knows what his time is what up?
Coming to an end doesn't anyone who is renting an apartment know?
Well, my lease is up in a week or a month.
How many times do you have you heard that right?
All right, I got to find some place to live you hear it's a very it caught they're very cognizant of what's going on
There is no battle between the Most High and Satan is a joking just like there's no battle
I mean actually there might be a battle between a tenant and the landlord, but this is not this is even beyond that
It would be the difference between a battle of a landlord and a little tiny ant on the front lawn
There's no battle there
You see, yeah, I mean could a landlord lease a building or a place to a little ant
Yeah, sure in a Disney kind of concept may you can't but is there ever gonna be a battle?
No, I just squash him There's no battle there So we are we looking at the clues?
No, we're not I mean generally as a whole as I don't want myself into the way it's ridiculous to think that even for one's own well-being you want to separate yourself, but You know He knows his time is up His time is up.
Well, there's no fight It's just a matter of you were given dominion over a certain amount of time even the Christ respected that When he came here how he was here in secret Right, right the price didn't you know have Fanfare around him all the time.
No, it was unrecognizable The only and so as well, what about the people that came to listen to him at the with the crowds You know at the thousands of people by gal, you know, they wouldn't that wouldn't have happened if he didn't have his followers They recognized his followers You know what?
I mean, right?
You're like who's that?
Well, those are the followers of the Christ.
Okay, that means he's here You see.
Mm-hmm.
So and there's no discussion of any of this yet It's sad but true, so I would suggest that When you consider something about the resurrection, it's good to know about it.
The promises will be fulfilled
The ones that are resurrected when the gods make their overt presence will be as gods
you know the words you will have all the power that a god does and
It's going to be pretty crappy place to be on the planet because it'll be like a post
War scenario, that'll just there won't be enough people and resources to rebuild it
You're gonna have to rely on the gods to do it
You see
So you're seeing the films where people come out of there was a famous film action
I don't know if it's all famous, but I'd seen it several times.
I still can't remember the name.
I have to look it up it was in Europe and people were in a it's a little movies about them being in a bomb shelter overnight and That towards the end of the movie, you know, they come they come out and they're walking through the city Everything's blowing up and they're in like they're in shock, you know, they're physically unharmed, you know, but they're in charge a Complete shock.
Well, that's how it's going to be for you know, quite a few decades after the gods appear
So anyway, there's a roundabout
Just drop drop in the hat kind of explanation of it
But the the most honorable thing that gods can bestow on a human is the first resurrection by the way
The highest honor right now everyone will get the honor of being resurrected but the highest honor is the first resurrection
And sometimes if you're if someone in some cases I should say not sometimes but in some cases
If you are chosen to partake in the first generation and you are alive as the gods are returning
They will take you up with them.
And as you go up you will be killed like Enoch was Right, and you will be resurrected immediately It'll be and then you know, then you have a resurrected body.
You're in the sky.
Well, it's no big deal It's not like you're gonna fall, you know, because you can choose to fly or whatever Yeah, there's also a thing that still the people don't understand that it's people think Enoch and Moses and these guys are alive No, they're not Enoch was taken up, but it doesn't say he was resurrected No, no, it doesn't say he's still alive.
As a matter of fact in later writings.
It says Enoch was and now he isn't Whenever you see that means that he's dead, right?
The only reason he was taken up and spared He was very well liked to be spared death by the flood Because he wasn't to be in part of in in the in the boat with Noah, let's say in the ark You see the gods don't have any privacy people are afraid of death And all that the gods are not afraid of that.
I mean unless it's to them, but they're not afraid for you You know if they like you and they're like man, we like you a lot, you know, you know Why do you have to hang around for the stupid bull?
Come here.
Come up with us I'll just kill you on the spot.
You'll be you'll be spared the stupid bull or the next election or this plague or whatever, you know Right, they have no problem.
That's no big deal.
You of course you have no choice, but to go along with it.
I'm sure that there's a
the possibility of negotiation like Abraham did regarding the survive
You know sparing Sodom and Gomorrah that you can negotiate with the gods to a certain extent
But if it gets extreme and if it's definitely determined is they have no problem killing you
And he did try
Yeah, yeah, well Abraham did but the yeah, we're going to get over the thing about death
The gods don't see that as any as any.
I don't know how you'd say it They don't view it like we do Because they know that you're going to be resurrected.
It's like no big deal.
It's just we like this guy Let's just kill him on the spot.
You know, the next thing he's gonna know is yeah the next thing he's just gonna know is gonna be a Resurrected, you know save the poor poor guy, you know Satan's Whatever fun, you know Why should we subject them to the satanic world?
Very interesting Yeah, I've got to go out and grab something I'll be out of reach I'll be back in 30 seconds.
If you want to maybe take up a few minutes be right back.
Okay?
Well, I don't know about you folks, but that was a whole interesting Bit of Conversation there And as always if anybody ever wants to call in we have all the information in the chat feel free All right, I'm back, okay Okay So what I miss Nothing much.
Just mentioning that if anybody wanted to call in they could feel free What an interesting and precise Yeah, the interesting thing is This is very very rarefied this information again.
Most people that are interested in this
Cannot and will not or won't for many reasons study scripture to get it out of it
the other thing is they're looking to other people historically have written about it and you're going to have that mixed with a lot of poop and
Omission
And yeah, so that's the biggest tool that they have is the omission
in the rewriting of
History or they include or they include too much.
They might use a Christian perspective.
Then I you just ruined the whole thing right there
You know, they'll tell you this is the good Christian thing or this is the you know, this is the whatever
Or an academic might say well, there's a mythology, you know, or mm-hmm
There's always some flavor with some tag
Yeah, you know, you're gonna get poo and corn pie
So it was it's like succotash or something like that
You're gonna get when you see the word Christian or they use the Jesus name
Yeah, or you know, as soon as you see that it's poop.
This is that's might sound dogmatic But if you hear a Christian or God or Jesus that is shit sh ITT Now You're going into shit and you better find some edible corn.
These are people that are out for the culture
They'll also find
Most of the people in the Western world that do use the Jesus and the Christian way to teach what's in Scripture
condone or actually they praise
constitutional republics and
You know leaders so-called political leaders and science hand-in-hand
Yeah, and the current scientific stuff backing up what's in the Bible, which it doesn't by the way
Very little of it other than a little bit of biology does
So you'll always find all that and it's just bizarre and it's been going on for a very long time
Actually only in the late 20th cent mid to late 20th century in the 19th century
It was more about leaning towards the what the secret societies adopted as deism that you know
There's a cover
Let's say the owners of the sovereign states use that as a cover deism like the American
On the dollar bill and God we trust and the GOD.
That's all deism.
That's a public Cover for in private.
They're all Satanists, you know, meaning not Satanists.
I'm just using that should have retracted that but
Because most people people are Satanists
But they are doing the ancient occulted rituals out of Egypt and the Druids the ball where you know, the Canaanite rituals
You know child sacrifice and all that
but
in every case
Yeah, like the American founding fathers were deists they basically say there is a creator architect of the universe, but he's hands-off
It's up to us.
That is the cover for them You know, they're pretty vile like when you look at the monarchies and the what they call the American founding fathers and You can look this up on your own Haven't researched it in over a decade.
But if you look at it's pretty overt.
It's not hidden It's in other words mainstream knowledge.
If you look at the lives of the what they call the American founding fathers Many people would call them Satanic like they would have pet names called Satan and they would do all these rituals and all that You know, they're pretty sick a bunch of people.
Yeah, but you know and and they were not well liked by the way They're only well liked hundreds of years later They were very well disliked because they knew what they were doing to the country So one of your hints you see in a lot of the popular quote-unquote Christian movements is to praise the Constitution And the founding fathers and all that and right away.
That's like, you know really bad poop So you want to venture off?
There's lots of movements.
There's lots of websites through history that are supposedly
Telling you what's in the Bible and I just can't stomach it
I have got a lot of those books here that were given to me by others and after a beam from the beginning of my
study I was like this is just
Garbage but there has to be something good in it, you know, so you to save you time and
This has been going on
More in the American side in the European, you know, they're mostly Catholic
So, you know forget it, you know, we're Protestant.
There's no knowledge.
That's just That's like the bottom of the barrel.
That's where you know, they need to put
You know how you go into a Walmart or a Target they have a McDonald's in the lobby, you know
That's that's the same, you know, it's McDonald's
They're just there to socialize and if you try to speak on anything
I just like not to use the word scholarly
But edifying to a Catholic or Protestant or whatever they they don't want to hear this say well that goes against the tradition
You see and the culture
Recently, I was looking up some stuff and I came across some
Christian stuff and some people doing research in let's say Aramaic texts and finding different stuff and saying oh, this is very scholarly
But it sounds anti-christian so we can't accept that.
You know what you're saying about the ancient scrolls, you know So that people are still stuck in that crap It's very and anything biblical is anti-christian anything in the Koran is and I French awesome Culture and tradition.
Yeah Those are the satanic masses That people will never see as as they should or could because of the censorship Yeah, so in short humans are a very vile bunch offensive and vile and all that.
That's why it's very hard for them to reckon Scriptural knowledge with sec, you know, they're stupid secular knowledge because in order to do that You have to be able to objectify the state or status of humanity and they never will they never can they still?
Go around telling each other.
They say this is a good person.
There are good people You know me times you heard that or he's a very good per, you know, no, there are no good people.
Sorry You've got really bad.
You've got shit people and you've got really shitty people, right?
So this is a general rule on the planet, you know Yeah Yeah, yeah, you're only good if you're made good You're inherently born into you know, evil You know You know still people complaining about political educational health systems.
It's your own parents that messed you up You know get to it so And then you have the biological parents and mess up then you have the spiritual parent right which is the leaseholder the leaseholder.
Yes So, you know, how can you expect how can you be optimistic the the most optimistic thing you could do is when is this going to end It's like being in the dentist's chair What's their optimistic about it?
Well when it ends, right?
What's so optimistic about getting your tooth drilled or capped or whatever?
There's nothing good about that.
Actually even when they're doing it in the dentist's chair What if the power goes out and they have to stop right there?
Yeah You're worse off than you were before they started you bet you little more anesthesia Well, yeah in the dark.
Yeah, so well Little nature's oxide Yeah, and if the lights don't come back on in a month, you're screwed.
So you're screwed So this is yeah, this is a really bad scenario, but it's a you could rest assured It's been planned and thought out for a very long time By super efficient super of a benevolent beings.
You don't see it because you lack the knowledge most people So what it's called tolerance and suffering to suffer something means you do it willingly Well, I don't have a choice.
Well, if you know trace and go jump off a bridge Right.
Yeah Yeah, of course you have a choice you suffer it So that's pretty much it Right.
What else you got?
What's else going on?
I have nothing in chat whatsoever.
No Collins We've pretty much just And Well, we've been speaking to a few there's a a bunch in the channel listening or I mean in the stream They're hearing things.
I don't know who's listening.
We really don't know who's listening yeah, this we've a number just as they're possibly hearing it, which is a series of tones and and sounds Yeah, that's you know what?
I mean?
This is you know, I said recently when I'm in public I you know, I know there's a conversation of Greek speak is going to ensue.
The first thing I asked the victim Is have you been on this planet for more than 15 minutes?
Then you're probably and you should they should have noticed what I'm about to tell you yeah, you know Because you're a victim.
I don't think there are any more
if you're partaking in Greek speak, you're a victim of it at this point because
the
The rationale to say how many people really understand what's what I'm saying
What's being said is so small and rare that you you're just actually sometimes I would say dare say this
You're probably better off not hearing it
You know, yeah, all right, so let's see
All right, that's it let's wrap it up I'm gonna go make some some
Some supper and we'll do it again next week.
Yeah.
Well, thank you very much for for everything Thanks for doing outstanding job that you did done this one Okay, that's well, that's wasn't even trying but thanks actually, but let me I'm gonna log on to the email to see if there's an email Okay in the meantime This is nothing like doing it live, right?
Well, yeah, I know it's being put into a can right?
It was it uncommon sense radio, I think I'm common sense radio one at gmail.com and Let's see if anything pops up on the emails Usually if you send an email probably get back to you and then a week or so.
Oh Here I got a whole bunch.
Okay live stream.
What's going on?
Credit system.
Okay.
I've got three emails from someone sent in the past few minutes, I think What's up with the way people I don't know man tell me in a casserole Who is the Christ?
Mr. Greek is another one.
This guy's funny What part of the credit system will play in the Middle East Union?
Yeah.
Well, it's credit Think about it.
Yeah, and who is the Christ?
It's a secret.
I mean if I've never met him.
I was not on the earth when he was here All I can do is do I have access to what everyone else has access to?
Which is what the ancient witness is what they've written But you have to do it with discernment, right if you watch What's that ridiculous Hollywood guy makes movies of passion movies Gibson already, you know Gibson, you know, it's Catholic.
Yeah No, you're misled.
There's a church.
All of the churches are wrong.
Not some of them all of them How do I know because if they were right, there wouldn't be a church They wouldn't exist.
No, they also make also you're gonna make yourself a subject to Satan big-time You know so Credit system is very interesting because Let me just say before we go years ago when I started doing the research on the credit system I'd say what they call 2005 2006 on the Pope's work schedule.
I was quite dynamic and active about how trying to have correspondence with the Treasury the Comptroller of Currency Federal Reserve, right?
Right and Literally you it takes about a year because I wanted to do it orally whenever you send an email you get a form letter Back or no response, right?
So I wanted to get a live person on the phone and record them which I didn't record because I realized that this was beyond Ridiculous the reality of it, right?
so It took it took about a year to get to the Treasury and the Comptroller of Currency Federal Reserve It took about a week a year of being on hold In other words you call the numbers and you ask you ask about these questions and they shuffle you around and then they put you On hold literally for four hours and you have a charger and all that and you hang up and you try again next week Right.
Well with the Comptroller of Currency and the US Treasury when I did get through to someone and I knew I got through to Someone not just like when you call a government agency you ask what's your give me your employee number?
They give you like this 14 or 20 digit number, right, right?
This person says I don't need an employee number.
They were pretty high up also someone high up in the IRS Okay.
Well, I explained to them.
This is credit and basically it's a social security number The banks don't lend money the whole spiel, you know when bank transfers are done.
They're not transferring They're basically need the signature the Federal Reserve note title toll check for one is illegal, you know, not lawful to use So, what do we do?
And you know what?
They all said to me the Treasury the Comptroller of Currency Federal Reserve just denied and lied just like they did They said well then don't use it then Social Security I say well the banks are not really lending money.
There is says well, then don't use it
In other words, you're saying it's okay to be criminal
In other words, it's that's why I use the analogy with Ocelli bags when the hot dog
manufacturers the Frankfurt manufacturers in the US
When they were getting health inspections and they found it was rat feces in all of them
Well, they couldn't shut down all of them because there'd be another American Revolution, right?
No hot dogs.
Are you joking?
So people are fueled on So they said well, let's just change the standard and allow more of rat feces in the hot dogs you see And they jacked up the values.
Yeah, so the entire system whether it's the religious system scientific system.
The money system is so criminal
That asking what to do
the only answer is don't use it avoid it because in other words the US Treasury the Comptroller of Currency of
Arizona and the US their offices and other people and Social Security other that I've spoken to
Admit by not saying it, but they admit then yes, we know what you're saying
But so then don't use it in other words
Then it's not okay to use it.
If someone tells you then don't use it, right?
But this is the norm If you understand scripture, it goes back to why this destruction see I don't call it a lot of people call it about the destruction of the it's not the destruction I don't never really say it's destruction of society.
It's what the mop-up crew It's the cleaning up of it So when you do when you call the Treasury in the Comptroller of Currency of Arizona and you explain to them what you found out They don't deny it.
They just say well, yeah, basically it is a criminal society
You're living in if you know about it
You have two options one is be a criminal like them or don't don't use it
Right and just say this is an observation
I want to take notes on like happenings not like a diary, but historically give an example when I was on
AFR and we were asking for donations raised on the average about 400 a week
right for AFR
But after that I said well if their donations you have to send it in the mail
There's like nothing coming in.
I know you sent Bruce and a couple other people sure, right?
Why Because it everyone even listeners to this are used to oh, I have a card I could do it electronically digitally I like what the group is saying.
I like you know, I don't care about the system.
I'm just going to use it right Danny Afr was like man, we've got like it was like third week over a thousand bucks from you, you know coming in You know, I'm just saying, you know, whatever, you know, it kept going up and up as are you getting it?
He's well, just you know, there's using the electronically, right?
So how many people actually listening to Greek speak that are you know, it's like they don't care no one cares
Yeah, I know for sure
Not for sure because it hasn't happened
But if I had a PayPal and all that stuff saying asking for donations, I'd be doing that
you know for cigarettes and coffee and all that but because because the people have to actually if they want to donate a
Contribute they actually have to get go to the post office
Sometimes it doesn't happen right because just show you how entrenched
Society as a whole is even the quote-unquote people have professed Greek speak, you know, it's it's what why bother
right, by the way, I want to thank
someone out in Oregon who sent a
Kilo and a half of some super premium coffee and a 36 page letter
single spaced
Well, I don't know if you've ever any writing before but it's 18 pages double printed printed on both sides single space very dense
Yeah, so
Anyway
I've started reading it and and the coffee is very much appreciated if you're listening.
Thank you very much We did I've never had anything from you know lost in the mail or anything But again, how easy would it be to go quote-unquote get a bank account start at PayPal and ask for donations?
So I could at least get coffee and cigarette money, right?
Very simple and very simple, but I don't do it because I've been told by the authorities don't use it then right and you tried Unsuccessfully PayPal Well, I know how to be.
Yeah, I know how to be successful by just being an idiot or more or one of these other people You know, which is I'm not idiot.
I'm not saying you're an idiot for using the banks I'm just saying I can't go back.
In other words people who Work in sausage factories Can't eat sausages.
I mean you go to a party where everyone's eating sausages enjoying them You look at you look you're like, oh, that's so gross.
Yeah, that is so gross, dude Like what do you mean?
It tastes good You know, yeah This is not a but I'm not trying to guilt-trip anyone for using BAM I mean you do but do because you know, whatever but I'm just saying as an example in The past when asking for AFR donations, everyone was quite happy to do it electronically But when it comes to putting something in the mail, yeah We don't like that We want to do what Satan set up for us.
We're not talking about people that profess to like Greek speak now, right?
Right.
So why bother?
Yeah, why bother?
Okay.
Well, that's pretty much it for now and Very much.
Thank you.
Yeah, hopefully given some really good fresh corn Before you do and you got the yep good and you got the rest of the week to sift Corn out of poop because that's all that's out there guarantee like we say down so That's all you're gonna get for sure.
I know that for sure.
You just can't oh, yeah put up with it and till next week Maybe we'll put out some fresh corn in the trough Set of the pig swallow that you guys usually get okay Thanks.
Thank you very much.
We'll see you next week.
Thanks that you take care now.
Bye.
Bye