And greetings everyone, this is Live with the
Greek, and I think you've got a phone
call.
Yeah, it sounds like it, right?
Yeah, that's the old-fashioned sound there, I
like that.
Yeah, yeah, well it's a small flip phone,
I'm still not using anything like a miniature
television, you know, anything that looks like a
mini TV or anything.
And in the beginning I felt like I
was resisting it, now I'm glad I don't
have it.
Personally, I like that everyone else around me
has it, you know, like if I'm out
doing commerce, people are very gracious usually.
Let's say I'm out in the field and
I need, let's say I want to scan
a barcode and see what, you know, or
something.
I say, can you scan that for me?
And Tommy goes, oh sure, I'll do it
for you, you know.
Yeah, I'll do it, sure.
Yeah, they're accommodating.
Yeah, they are, yeah, they're good.
They're bipedal cattle, they're fine.
So I noticed the world's been in mediocrity
lately.
Not too many false flags or stuff to
keep things exciting.
I noticed that there's not much going on,
seemingly.
Yeah, the flooding down south, and we just
got dealt with a good batch of some
rain, which brought the whole city into a
rather frenzy of some sort in their media.
It was quite interesting.
I was wondering about the subtle changes and
that kind of stuff, when you mentioned that
before, especially with that video, that was something.
Oh, that heifer?
Yeah.
Oh, my, my, my.
It sounds respectful.
Actually, it's about as respectful as you could
get for humans.
They're just fools.
And what happens is, you know, you could
look at the animal or the creature, the
being, from creation on, the design and all
that, and you see how it's being used,
or how it performs, and it's just pathetic.
I mean, it's the deplorable humankind.
And here's the irony of it, you know.
It's kind of like this old man who
rescued a cat, but he yelled at the
guy, and he's like, you know, I hate
people, not animals, you know.
Right.
Just because you tell it like it is
doesn't mean that you don't like the thing
that you're telling about.
But you can have hate for the way
that it is.
Years ago, I had a pretty fancy exotic
car.
I'm not going to say what it is
or whatever, but it's the kind of car
that people mention when they're bragging.
And I hated it because it didn't function
correctly, and I noticed it was a prank,
you know.
To make a long story short, kind of
like certain high-end, finicky, esoteric equipment, regardless
if it's audio equipment, cars, tools, you know,
things like that, things that get on the
fringe.
You know, that's why, you know, for example,
is a Maserati a good value?
No.
It's not a good value.
Right.
I just said I wasn't going to mention
names.
But here on the other hand, is a
Bugatti Veyron that's two million bucks a good
value?
Yes, it is.
It is a good value at two million.
Why?
Because it goes from zero to 60 miles
per hour back to zero in less than
five seconds.
Ouch.
I was telling this to someone.
And they're like, that's not a big deal.
I said, you're not listening to me.
It goes from zero to 60 back to
zero in five seconds.
Not zero to 60.
Zero to 60.
See, everyone thinks how fast something goes makes
it good.
No.
In reality, the real engineering mind is more
curious in how it stops.
Right.
You know, back in the days in the
70s, we were souping up like the Z
Camaros and the even Ford Falcons with the
straight six.
Yeah.
We put in a truck engine, right?
We didn't have to cast iron head.
You couldn't close the hood, you know.
And they were really fast.
And they had that, you know, leaf spring
suspension all around with the first, you know,
struts in the front.
It had, you know, the shocks in the
front.
Right.
The coils and the truck suspension.
Garbage.
And the thing is, I noticed after playing
around with cars, I was, you know, my
early teens, that I got a little tired
of the go.
I was more curious in the stop because
we had a lot of run-ins where
we couldn't really safely, you know, just barely
by the skin of our teeth made it
because we couldn't stop.
Barely stop.
Holy smokes.
So the thing is, how fast can you
stop and how safely and comfortably can you
stop is more important than the go.
The go doesn't mean nothing if you can't
stop her.
Or control it, yeah.
Right, right.
Right.
So with that said, it's exactly what the
topic of any conversation can be.
To what end?
How do you get to the end that
it's going to come to?
And the subtle stuff, it's all subtle.
Here's the thing.
You know, we just had a little conversation
about Christians before.
Right.
The thing that people don't realize, regardless if
it's, I think most people listening might have
heard of Dmitriy Kozov.
He recently did some videos on state religions,
basically saying the same thing.
If you've ever heard any Greek speak from
10 years ago, I'm saying like, well, if
you read the Koran, it tells you to
do the laws of Moses, right?
Right.
It's very clear.
There's 10 places, 10 references, maybe 15 to
Moses.
And all this says, it's not a, you
know, what people think.
It's a post, I don't know what you'd
call it, post-Christian era document.
But to make a point with all this
stuff is that anyone studying anything truthfully or
objectively, no matter who you are, where you
are, when you are, you always come to
the same conclusions.
Right.
And what people will not be able to
conclude is because anything, is because they don't
study.
They're stuck in trends.
What they do is they eliminate the ability
that their faculties grant them.
You know, like your faculties would be your
perception, your touch, smell, sight, hearing, sound.
But they don't know what to do with
the impulses, right?
Or they don't know how to control it.
One example would be, I, in the past,
and even currently speak to people that are
into Greek speak.
And when someone asks them to explain what
I'm talking about, they have no authentic dialogue.
They just repeat what I say.
Right.
It's no different than, you know, the people
in public.
You know, what's going on?
Well, they just repeat what they heard on
Fox News.
There's no authentic dialogue.
It's lacking.
So, to what end is very simple.
Like, all of the religions, again, are state
religions.
In other words, they're promoted by the state,
meaning they're permitted to exist by the state
because it makes people docile and compliant to
the state, which is a complex apparatus.
But it's simplified as, you know, commercial apparatus,
right?
Well, it's almost a tool, huh?
Yes, yes.
So, we understand why there are different countries,
if you understand.
Well, like I've been saying for many years,
a decade and a half almost, there's a
patron or matron deity or a god behind
each nation.
And that's, you could study that, you know,
on your own.
And these gods are hostile to man, but
they want to be, in order to be
successfully hostile, you have to appear as a
friend, right?
Right.
Or have to appear as, yeah.
Okay, so that's why when you hear all
this stuff about adversarialism in politics, whatever, they're
not really adversaries because they're not pulling punches
like they were.
Or, I mean, they are pulling punches like
they're friends, not throwing punches like they're adversaries.
But essentially, going back to what is going
on and where people get their input from,
is designed on the notion that people will
always put their faith before their knowledge.
Like most people say, oh, I like the
way that sounds, I believe in that.
You know, years ago, I was on a
Skype, this person, believe it or not, had
an alternative media radio, they were a host.
And they were listening to me on a
Skype call, and they were like, you know,
Greek, I think I'm going to follow you.
Do I like what you're saying?
I'm going to follow you.
I was like, no, please don't.
You're an idiot.
What you need to do is get an
orange vest and a plastic broom and wear
yourself out, is what you need to do.
So, yeah, so in other words, what has
been, humans, you know, are stupid, and they're
reliably so.
But here's the thing.
Now, inherently, they're not stupid, but they seem
like they are because it just keeps, you
know, being so prevalent.
But what they're, the powers that be, spiritual
and physical, rely on humans believing and grasping
onto something before they know anything about it.
Even a little bit about it.
But in other words, the absolute minimum is
shown as all there is to know.
Like, for example, if you go on the
internet, you'll see the browsers or the ads.
What you need, everything you need to know
about this going to Bermuda.
Everything you need to know about this hurricane.
Everything you need to know about this.
No, that's bullshit.
There's nothing there.
They're not telling you anything.
Okay.
So most people work on the, you know,
I feel good, why?
Because you're touching yourself kind of thing?
You know?
What do you mean, feel good?
Right?
Yeah.
It's that self-absorbed crap.
So people, everything that people inherently lean to
as part of their faith, what they believe
to, what they desire, is based on the
impulse that, you know, is put out in
the world.
In other words, find something to believe in
and believe in it.
Instant gratification.
Right.
Never any discussion.
Study it well.
And all this other stuff.
It's like they ask children, what do you
want to be when you grow up?
It's like, what do you want to be
when you grow up, I would ask.
Right?
Because you're an idiot.
Grandpa or whatever.
You know?
So the point is, when you put the
belief system and you grasp onto some bullshit,
which is either all religion, science, political, sports,
whatever, without any knowledge, this is how you,
this explains really the way society functions, all
of it.
Now, what happens if most of us have
fallen for that?
Right?
Most.
Now, what happens when you start to say,
wait a second, I need to gain some
knowledge, and you already establish the faith, the
knowledge will push against the faith like the
horse against the cart.
So you're doing the believing in something or
liking something before you study is putting the
horse in front of the cart.
The horse is designed and made to pull,
not push.
You could make it to push, you know,
but the horse doesn't have shoulders like an
ox, you know?
It doesn't like it.
So it's going to be hard to get
it to push.
So what will happen is that the knowledge
and the faith will be contrary to each
other.
And you have two options.
One is the individual will be looking at
other individuals and how happy they are in
believing in basically nothing, and say, do I
want to be happy or do I want
to have two struggles?
One with these people around me that are
happy, the other one internally because I have
to now admit to myself and others I
no longer believe in that because of X,
Y, Z, but they don't care about X,
Y, Z, you see?
Right, the old Persian water story.
Sure.
Yeah, that's a way where the natural environment
is controlled.
So, yeah, there are many stories that could
be told about this concept.
You know, hurry up and believe something.
Like if you ask most people why they
believe in, let's say, in the religious sense
what they do, it's because my parents did
or it's the country.
If you speak to someone in Greece about
this stuff, they say, oh, no, the two
most important things to a Greek is his
religion and his family.
I said, that's why you're going to lose
those two things.
That's why you're so screwed up, right?
And the same thing if you talk to
people of any quote-unquote national faith or
mainstream, they don't know why or, you know,
especially in America, they have to quickly decide.
Just like, for example, you may not be
a football fan, but when the stupid ball
comes around, you immediately latch onto a team
because it's, you know, you're really left out
if you don't, right?
Or the World Series and baseball come around,
you're not a baseball fan, but it's the
World Series, so let's just pick a team,
you know, we're not into this, you know.
So what most people do in America is
because, again, just the same thing they do
in other countries, it's whatever ideology they have.
And what you're being told from a young
child is to hurry up and believe in
something.
Hurry up and make a snap decision because
that's the way society is run.
No one's really thinking.
We have people thinking for us, right?
Doctors, lawyers, priests, right?
So what that means immediately is that the
population is too primitive and too irresponsible to
deal with anything.
You know, last week I mentioned the number
one priority.
By the way, the number one priority of
any government in the world right now is
how to get their military to go after
their civilian population.
Every country in the world wants that.
Not the actual government itself, the state, but
the people who control that government, you know?
That is the number one priority, and I've
gotten this from several sources already in the
past year.
I'm just finally listening.
Of every government in the world.
I'm not speaking out against them.
I'm just reporting on what they're up to.
Now, if you go, for example, in the
American military, if you're hanging around in halls
of Congress and Pentagon or DOD, what the
older guys are telling the younger people is
that the gods of old are coming back.
And these are not religious people.
These are not even people that know what
that means.
That's been said now for the past year
also.
The gods of old are returning.
Yeah, in the military they're saying that.
Not the snotty recruits.
Yeah, yeah, so there's a movement.
But here's the interesting part, which is not
interesting.
Remember, the number one priority of any state
right now is how to get their military
force, which is not even their military force.
It belongs to the private owners, just like
police.
To go after their population without any, what
do you call it, without any mercy or
whatever, if they have to.
I was having a short discussion with an
American moron.
And he's saying, oh, that won't work because
posse comitatus.
I say, well, let's just reduce posse comitatus
because there was no police back then.
Posse comitatus says the American military can't shoot
American citizens or civilians, but the police have
no problem legally to do it.
So why is that?
What's different with the police?
Well, guess what?
There is no police in a republic.
There are no police.
The only time police show up is when
the banks form districts.
For example, like the United States, talk about
state rights, federal rights.
That's all bullshit.
The country has been sold out and divided
into districts.
You ever, right, there's a post office like
Kentucky's KY.
You know, that's where they spread that on
their toast there.
Right.
It's right.
They have, you know, Iowa's IO or Hawaii
is whatever age.
Those are not natural grammatical abbreviations.
That's to show you that you're using all
these, you know, there are 12 Federal Reserve
districts.
That's all.
There's no state.
All the rest is for public consumption.
Yeah, there's state rights, this and that.
Oh, this guy's in trouble.
He won his case over the state.
Yeah, that's just a show.
No one cares about.
No, you know, this is they still have
to upkeep.
So again, the main priority is how do
you get your implemented forces of destruction to
go against the civilian population?
I didn't finish the thought last week or
even now.
It's a long conversation on this.
It's not just all the Greek says this.
I don't believe it.
Screw you.
This is the main thing.
How do you do that?
Once a country facilitates that type of aggression
against its own, quote unquote, slaves or citizens
or residents, that's not the problem.
That's easy to do.
But the thing is, how do you maintain
that the remnant, the survivors, the ones that
are left are in harmony with it?
They'll go back to work the next day.
Like right now, if they got, let's say,
in Kansas, the military to go in there
and wipe out like 90% of the
population, right?
I don't think the people are going to
go to work tomorrow.
Probably not.
There'll be outrage, right?
So the problem is not getting rid of
the 90% of the population using the
military.
That's simple.
That's a chemical, physical thing to do.
I mean, there's high-speed chemistry, explosives, nukes,
bullets, poisoning, whatever.
That's easy to do.
Many things in their toolbox.
Yeah, many things in their toolbox.
The hard part is how do you do
that without not having severe consequences in the
aftermath?
In other words, they want to figure out
a way to do it, and then everyone
the next day says, oh, that's fine.
It's just natural.
Let's go back to work.
Nothing to see here.
Right.
You see, that's the part that's the kicker.
That's the part, if you figure that out
now, you know exactly what's coming, you see.
Right.
A little spiritually and physically.
Just for example, a lot of people discuss
in the ancient writs, regardless of what prophecy,
some will say, well, how do you always
get stuck on the Bible?
I'm like, no, give me any work, any
literary work or anything that's been memorialized even
that makes sense and adds up, I'm into
it.
This doesn't have to be scripture.
Right?
Although it's prioritized also, you know.
I'm into anything that's good, not crap, you
know.
Diversification.
Sure, but even the more you diversify, the
more you come to the center anyway.
Right, right.
It's the same spot, which is the truth
and how things really work.
So, again, the subtlety, like everyone knows, go
into a public space.
Whoever knows about the Antichrist, raise your hand.
They all raise their hands.
Well, if everyone's so smart about it, aren't
they going to cry foul when he shows
up?
Of course.
Yeah, so guess what?
No one's going to figure it out.
Well, I mean, you have to know how
the mechanism works.
So when you look at all these things,
they're going to be so subtle.
And, again, it's very easy for any state
to destroy its own population.
The thing is the aftermath, the blowback, the
reaction, you know, you want everything to be
normal.
You still want people to go to open
Starbucks and McDonald's and Walmart and work at
the water utility and work at the power
station and pick up the garbage.
But you just don't want it.
You just only want one out of ten
people.
You don't need the rest, you know.
Right.
Because, actually, from an objective point of view,
a causal point of view, they're pretty useless
anyway.
They're just filler.
But how do you get to that point
where you've eliminated the majority of the population
and the remainder still acts normally and also
is susceptible to the changes you want to
implement?
That is the, in other words, that's what
you're looking for, right?
Right.
That's what you're looking for, the reasoning behind
that, right?
Yeah.
The how-to.
See, the thing is, there's a very simple
way to look at it.
It has to be done by consent and
by permissions.
Everything is by permission and consent, from both
ways.
See, they give you the illusion that you
have to consent, but no, they're actually just
giving you permission.
Like, for example, with the homosexuals and the
gay rights, there is no such thing as
gay rights.
All they're saying is the state now is
permitting this.
Right.
That's all.
That's all they're saying.
We are permitting this.
So, in other words, the minds behind the
state, they're not talking about politicians, like, for
example, the Congress and President and all that.
That's irrelevant.
Congress doesn't even, people, if you know how
to read, they won't let you in Congress.
You have to be illiterate.
I mean, no comprehension.
Right.
Right?
They never wrote a law.
They never read a law.
Nothing.
They're just there, you know, because the Constitution
says Congress assembled as Congress, not showing up
and attending, you see.
The President, okay, since Nixon and starting with
Kennedy and maybe before that, they were always
giving the President a hard time in the
people's minds.
The people say, oh, it's important they have
a President no matter who it is.
We have to be behind them.
That's being patriotic.
Well, they've been working for a long time
to diminish that office to irrelevancy.
Why?
Because you don't need one.
Because there are no states.
There is no government.
You're just 12 districts.
You're a commercial entity, and you're privately owned.
As a matter of fact, all of North
America, believe it or not, except for Paraguay,
is the same owner.
Paraguay is connected differently because you have to
study how the post office works.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Did I say Paraguay?
Yeah.
I didn't mean Paraguay.
Uruguay.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So it's very interesting, you know, how these
things work.
But this is not for public consumption.
Right.
In other words, the bullshit that you see
that's going on politically with presidents, Congress, laws,
and all, is the same bullshit that you
see when Christmas comes around, or Halloween, or
Fourth of July.
None of that exists, but people are enthralled
by it.
So at this point, it seems like getting
rid of what they call the structure of
the American government is going to be just
as resistive as getting rid of Christmas.
I think they're both going to go together,
you see.
You know how they put a lot of
resistance against Christmas in America about a decade
ago, and people kind of pushed back a
little, and they stopped.
Well, they're pushing back against officers in the
American government.
Like, for example, here, I don't want to
mention the position of local government.
Someone that I know, and they've been in
there for 35 years, even though they're supposed
to be reelected every four, right?
Right.
Everybody here knows it's a corporation.
None of that stuff is true that they
tell the public.
And this is someone official in the government.
I'm not going to say who it is.
Okay.
Right?
Yeah.
And I'm not talking about you call them
up, they're going to deny that, but once
you get to know them, you'll see, right?
Sure.
The same with the military.
There's a movie, Jarhead, by the way.
I don't know if you've seen it, about
the Marines and all that.
Sounds familiar.
The best part is when they're watching videotapes
and the guy's girlfriend says, Hi, baby, I
just want to show you, I'm tired of
your ass, and she's having sex with the
neighbor on a videotape.
Just to show you, this is how these
pagans are, you know?
They don't even know why they're together.
That's why very often I hear about people
getting divorced.
I'm like, why were you together?
You didn't even know why you were together,
so you just have to make up something
to break up because you never knew why
you were together anyway.
That's how pagans operate.
So, again, back to the way the structures
work.
The irrelevancy, okay, what's subtle is this.
This is what people are not watching.
How things are being made irrelevant or attempted
to be made irrelevant, not because that's when
the change will happen, but just to be
in alignment with reality.
So going back to, let's say, the concept
of the state, the reality of the state,
like Dimitri says, is a privately owned corporation.
You can look at it.
That was in 1871 for America.
They changed it, put it on the credit
system in 1933.
It's irrelevant.
Anything they tell you about constitution, patriotism, president,
Congress, it's all irrelevant.
It's just as relevant as saying, if I
say Starbucks is privately owned, yes, yes.
Okay, Walmart's privately owned, yes, yes.
Okay, well, Walmart sells all this stuff and
Starbucks sells all this other stuff.
Okay, yes, they're very different, aren't they, right?
But they're still privately owned, you see.
Right.
Just like it doesn't matter, well, this state,
they do this.
So what?
That's because they don't know how to change
your mind to give up this stupid thing
about patriotism, right?
Right.
So they're trying to discredit the presidency.
They've already got rid of Congress, by the
way, in most people's minds.
Yeah.
Because Congress has less than a 20%
approval rating.
That's great.
I mean, fine.
You see, they can't be honest.
They're shameless.
Those that are controlling those can't come out
and say, look, we own you.
You're our property.
Sorry.
You have a problem with us and you
shouldn't.
You should have a problem with your great
-great-grandparents.
They voted for it, basically, by not doing
anything.
Right.
You know, if you have a problem, go
shit on their graves, piss on their graves,
whatever.
It's not us.
Sorry.
Right.
And you've got no say, but we have
to let you, because you need, it's like
this.
Listen, people of the world, you're just our
private chattel, our property, you, your children, everything.
You don't own anything.
You have credit to get what you want.
Yeah, the attorneys screw with you, telling you
there's such a thing as a debt, this
and the other, which there isn't, but that's
okay.
Get used to it.
You're being screwed with.
You'll be fine.
But they can't tell that to the people.
Okay, so Congress has been made irrelevant pretty
much.
Now they're going after the presidency, not to
go after the presidency.
The presidency is finished a long time ago.
Right.
A long time ago.
That's over.
What they're doing is going after it so
you get it out of your mind that
it matters, because it doesn't matter.
It's a show, and when they show any
presidentiary leader doing something significant, it's a show.
Just like the courts railroad everybody.
They ignore everything.
And then occasionally they'll be fair with someone,
and that one makes the news.
Oh, yeah, this guy is fair.
Oh, see, it's a fair system.
It's total bullshit.
See, what the people, again, Christianity is the
same thing.
They will not look at the Bibles, even
the piss-poor thing called whatever version they
give you in English, without an interlinear even
or whatever.
If you really read it with comprehension, you're
going to say, wait a second, they're pranking
me here, first of all.
Second of all, it's nothing like their religion.
Even if you read the King James, by
the way, as it is, you're going to
see it's a very anti-Christian document.
New Oral Testament, it doesn't matter.
As it is.
Either way.
Just like the Koran is very anti-Muslim,
as it is.
And what they call the Old Testament is
very anti-Jewish, for example.
Even the very furry Jews with the hats
that you see.
The ones with the beards, they call them
the furry ones.
They have varieties.
Then you've got the secular, whatever.
So there's no honesty.
It's all just shamelessly, ridiculously a lie.
In your face, no problem.
But the people are holding on to beliefs
of certain things, via their religion, via patriotism,
via whatever other ideology they have.
The media has really stepped up on that,
as far as subtle.
People turn to that automatically.
Whatever news site is out there, here's where
you get the real stuff, or whatever the
case may be.
That's another way to lure you in.
Exactly.
Look at all the things that are being
discredited.
For example, good food and water is discredited.
There was a little bit of a boost
in the 80s and 90s, where they had
all these health companies.
Smith & Wesson, the gun company, bought Hain,
which was a natural food producer.
H-A-I-N.
What does that tell you?
They're not going to invest in something that
has no growth.
The thing is, where you're going to see
the subtle changes is not in what's going
to change, but change people's mindset towards it.
How come there are people floating around the
Pentagon, old senior people, telling people they're witnessing
the return of the old gods?
What does that mean?
Exactly that.
Why is the A-1 priority of all
the owners of all the states or governments
to get rid of 90% of the
population using whatever?
Water, food, military.
Why is it there?
Because it's long overdue in their minds.
This is the same thing as cattle.
If you know anything about cattle ranching, I
did a study on ranching cattle a while
back.
That's why very often when I hear about
anthrax, I have to laugh.
Threatening people with powder and anthrax and all
that stuff.
That is a very common thing that happens
all over America, especially the southwest in places
like California where they had ranching where it
was very dry.
Horses and cattle got that.
The way you remedy that, by the way,
is to actually take notes on this.
What they did, this guy Joe Blankenship, actually
he's passed away now.
Whenever there was an anthrax outbreak, he would
just show up with a double axle truck.
Let's see, 10 wheels, right?
Double axle.
Sure.
With about 10 or 15 55-gallon drums
and a single piston diesel pump.
They would put iodine, just regular iodine, that
red shit, in the water and spray it
over all the animals.
Iodine, diluted iodine, not full strength, but diluted
iodine over the area gets rid of it.
Wow.
So does colloidal silver, but the iodine is
a readily available thing.
There's many commercial sources for it.
It doesn't even have to be food grade.
People are like, oh, there's nothing.
Just iodine gets rid of it.
Even the iodized salt, there's enough iodine in
there to get rid of it.
Anyway, there's no intelligent life on this planet.
Again, with the ranching, some of the ranches
were developed with a carrying capacity of so
many.
When stuff grows naturally, you know from experience
and statistics what grows on the land can
carry a certain capacity of cattle.
Now, if you double or triple the amount
of cattle, they run out of food and
that has to be open and the ranch
becomes very tenuous.
You could have disease.
Right?
Now, with the people, the humans, it's different.
There's plenty of food.
The reason they're messing with the food is
to prevent starvation.
Now, this is an interesting study I did
a while back.
There is enough land on just the highway
medians in America, where the highway median is
a narrow strip.
If you just shut down all the farms
and grew food only on the land in
the highway medians, that would be enough to
feed the whole country.
I know it sounds crazy, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're going to get some tailpipe pollution
and all that.
Sure.
Okay, so there's no starvation.
During Jeremy Carter years, they were paying farmers
to burn the wheat.
Yeah, that's right.
They would rather them burn the wheat than
get a negative price on it.
Because it actually would go to zero and
then go negative.
Right?
Right.
It would go to zero.
So, you're talking about a sick bunch of
people.
The people that own, there are people and
there are certain demonic beings behind them that
own all of the countries now.
They want to get rid of the people
because they're just tired of your stupid asses.
There's plenty of water.
Water, like oil, is made underground, just like
the vegans.
Vegan means no animal.
Okay, but it's wrapped in plastic.
And isn't plastic dinosaur animal product?
They always freeze up when I say that.
Because none of these vegan idiots ever came
to me and said, Well, it's really not
dinosaur fossil fuel.
It's abiotic.
It's created by the earth.
No one.
That's how stupid they are as a general
group.
Right.
But it's easy to pull that.
And you don't want to mess with stupid
people.
It's like you don't pick on retarded kids.
Anyway.
Right.
So, the powers that be are just tired
of your stupid asses, right?
And your children and your parents and all
that.
The whole group is just like, you know,
we've had enough of them.
We've been running these people for 150 years,
most of the world for 100.
And absolutely the whole world now for at
least 30.
Except for one or two countries, maybe recently.
And it's no fun.
It's kind of played out.
You know, like if someone likes fishing, and
they don't catch a lot of fish, but
they're really into fishing.
If you provide them with a few barrels
of fish to go fishing in, they get
real excited.
Finally, I'm catching fish, right?
Right.
But I assure you, no matter how much
they like fishing, after like a year of
that, or two years, or five years, or
ten years of that, they're like, oh, screw
the fish.
This sucks.
Right?
Belly up to the bore.
So, this is the subtle thing.
Anything they're telling you, not enough water, bad
weather, starvation, population the earth can't support, is
total bullshit.
The subtlety is coming from the point that
what you believe in, what you hold on
to as being your faith, needs to be
changed in order to accept the reality they
want to put.
So, all of you idiots out there, that
think anything in any of your governments, doesn't
matter if it's Erdogan, Trump, Putin, doesn't matter,
even a monarch, Netanyahu in Israel, those people
there have nothing there but functionaries and position.
There are leaders behind there.
So, when the scripture is talking about leader
of a people, it's talking about the leader
of the people.
Now, for example, if you had a leader
of a country, let's say like Dimitri gives
Iran as an example with Ayatollah Khomeini, he
was really the leader of a people.
He cleared out, he got rid of the
influence, the background influence, for a short while,
right?
You see?
Right.
Okay, so he would be a leader.
So, for example, Trump is not a leader.
He is the agent for the leader.
But even, not even like an agent for
a leader, he is more like an agent
to tell you what you are used to
hearing, and to tell you things that you...
Same with Putin.
He is part of the show.
He is putting on a show, and also
they are changing what they are saying.
So, same with Netanyahu, same with all of
them.
Even the cannibalistic African leaders, the ones that
they celebrate by eating human liver, right?
Right.
Those guys are still puppets.
At this point right now, because they have
a credit-based economy, right?
So, this is the insanity of it.
Like the Pope is another one.
The Pope is just a...
Rhymes with P-U-P-P-E-T.
Right.
There is a leader in the Vatican, I
assure you that.
It's not the Pope, and it's not the
Jesuits either.
No.
None of those guys.
There is a leader of the United States
of America, but I'm sure it's not the
jokers you see on TV.
That's for sure.
For 150% sure, not just 100%.
Yeah, that's a good one.
You see?
So, when the Scripture is talking about leaders,
and you factor it into a certain time,
you have to understand, is he really the
leader or not?
So, when you look at the leader of
a people, let's say, 2500 years ago in
the area of Babylon, Nebuchadnezzar, yes, he was
the leader of the people.
They didn't have a sovereign corporate state, as
you do now.
You see?
David was a leader.
Hezekiah was a leader.
Right.
Because the Scriptures, in any ancient text, is
blatantly honest.
For example, if during the kingdom of Judah
and Israel, there was a sovereign corporation or
whatever, it would state that.
It would tell you it's a corporation, and
they have this puppet called David, or a
puppet called Hezekiah, or whatever.
Scripture is blatantly clear.
It doesn't hide stuff like that.
Right.
You see?
So, who is the leader of what they
call Russia?
We don't know.
But we know it has a leader, you
see?
Right.
You see how the subtleties are working?
And what these leaders are saying, it doesn't
matter, even industry, when you look at this
Elon Musk idiot, or Bill Gates, or Steve
Jobs who passed away, those guys, they're puppets.
They have no...
They're very...
If you've ever seen...
I learned this a long time ago, back
east.
There was a couple of industrialists I saw
giving a speech.
And I was working in lighting and sound
and all that stuff.
Right.
And you get to see them off stage.
And this one guy was being crowded by
three people, and they were in his face.
You know when someone is speaking to a
child and they're angry at them?
Their mouth is just two inches from their
face, and the person's looking down at the
floor and they're nodding the whole time?
Right.
Imagine the body language.
Imagine Bill Gates standing there.
I'll just say it.
Bill Gates is standing there, and he's staring
at his shoes, and he's nodding like he's
one of those bobbing head dolls.
Up and down, up and down, up and
down, up and down.
And there's two guys an inch away from
his face, looking like they're almost ready to
yell at him.
And this is going on for five minutes,
or three minutes, or one minute could be
like five minutes.
And he's just nodding his head up and
down like a little boy.
Wow.
And that's the head of your Microsoft?
Come on.
Give me a break.
You know?
So when you, again, the leaders of the
people, this keeps coming up, the kings of
the north, the king of the south, the
king from here.
Yeah.
You have to learn to discern the nature
of the state.
Right?
Hmm.
Okay, the other thing is, regarding food and
water.
Okay, oil and water are made in the
earth, period.
Period.
That's just like you make pee and poo.
You'll be doing it until the day you
die, most likely.
The earth is going to be making water
and oil.
Somebody was telling me, oh, the flood, this,
flood, that.
Like, flood was not the oceans.
The flood, the primary water from the underground
and the rain.
It wasn't the oceans, you know?
Right.
Because they talk about in Genesis how the
water will not exceed its boundaries.
So it couldn't have been a worldwide flood.
I said, well, but the cause of the
flood was not specifically the oceans.
It was specifically the fountains of the deep
and the sky.
So it doesn't break the Genesis rule of
the waters will not exceed their boundaries to
the land.
See, so it's like no one has no
comprehension.
Anyway, so your food, basically food, water, air
are unlimited because the earth perpetually produces it,
recycles it, renews it.
So anything you hear about water shortage, food
shortage, it's total bullshit.
It's just like saying you owe a debt.
Yeah, if you agree to it.
Now look, if they tell you that global
warming and the bad weather and the starvation
go away and you agree to it, well
then that's the reality that you want to
pursue.
Remember, even scripture is voluntary.
The law is voluntary.
You can't force someone to do it.
Right?
So these are the subtle things.
You have to establish what's called the common
denominators, right?
Right.
To discuss the subtleties, like for example, if
you, like people are not good at math,
if you show them like the movie Good
Will Hunting, which is like a chalkboard full
of mathematical equations, it's blatant in their face
they can't figure it out.
And to get the result or solve the
equation is very subtle.
Right?
When you see a huge, let's say derivative
or calculus or like 15 quadratic equations, the
way you figure it out is subtle.
The opposite would be if you showed your
common person a big letter 2 and then
the plus sign, I mean number 2, and
again an equal sign, that's not so subtle.
That's in your face.
That's easy.
We could hit that.
Boom.
That's 4.
2 plus 2 is 4.
I think most people know that.
Okay.
So from that point of view, that's not
subtle.
You see?
The subtle parts are understanding the underlying structure
and does the information that you're getting or
trying to solve fit the underlying structure or
the substrate.
Right.
For example, in the beginning we started discussing
how people accept faith before knowledge.
And then they don't want, they can't look
at knowledge.
Now it's too late.
And if they do, it's contrary socially.
Okay.
That's part of the cosmic censorship.
The way you censor, I'll start to, you
know, Sam asked me about some cosmic censorship.
I've written some stuff about it a while
back, but it's technical.
Not that no one can comprehend it, but
yeah, no one can comprehend it.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
It's not like no one can comprehend it,
but at this point, I don't think there's,
it can be comprehended without looking at it
from a, you know, what it really is.
And not that I fully understand cosmic censorship,
but we can, we have made a line,
a list of line items on what, why
society is so fucked up.
And if you look at it, whether it's
on the individual or social level, it shows,
well, this is cosmic censorship.
You see?
And part of the cosmic censorship is to
put on people the desire to believe in
something, even though they know nothing about it.
Now you're stuck.
Because you don't know what it means.
That's groupthink then.
Groupthink, yeah, is cosmic censorship.
Yeah.
The other part of cosmic is seeking pleasure
at any cost or without any discernment.
You know, the typical thing, if you, like
with Christians especially, because this is a Christian
society, if you ask them about why you're
doing Christmas or New Year's or Halloween, oh,
come on, you just don't know how to
have a good time.
That's their answer.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So if you're living in a society of
cannibals, why are you eating that baby?
Oh, you don't know how to have a
good time.
Right.
You see?
What do you do with people?
How sorry would you be if their leaders
wanted to reduce them down to only one
out of ten?
You wouldn't feel so sorry for a society.
Oh, do you feel bad that they got
rid of 90% of the headhunters?
Do you feel bad?
No, you don't.
Oh, there are people, too.
Okay, well, why did you call them headhunters
if there were people?
Just call them people.
Right.
You see?
All right, so the subtleties are very subtle,
but they're not once you understand does the
information match?
if you go into a crowd of people
anywhere in the world and you ask them,
anyone who's ever heard of the Antichrist, raise
your hand, if almost everybody raises their hand,
how is it going to happen?
Very subtly.
You know, these people don't, so the subtleties
that are happening is the truth behind the
matter.
Because everything that everyone is discussing is bullshit.
Very simple.
How do you know it's bullshit?
Because most things that people discuss and get
involved with is open to one's acceptance or
one's interest based on their, you know, selective
nature.
Some type of pleasure, yeah.
Yeah, like, oh, I don't want to talk
about that.
I don't like talking about that.
That means it's a bullshit subject.
Or, if you're coming to them with it's
not bullshit, it doesn't resonate with them because
it's not bullshit.
See, if you give me some bullshit, I'll
take it when I feel like it because
that's what I'm used to getting, you know?
Talk about how the Republicans are screwing stuff
up, right?
When there is no Republic, there's no such
thing that the whole thing is a bad,
bad show.
It's like our happy days, Fonzie and who
was it?
Richie.
I need some joy.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Yeah.
Yeah, and it ain't going anywhere and you're
not going anywhere unless you understand the substrate
behind what is and what's coming.
You can't overlap it just, you know, on
face value.
You can take, if you comprehend prophecy and
you have a good handle on what's being
said, you can overlay that on what's going
on but what, not what you think is
going on but what's really going on.
Right.
You see, there's a big difference there.
You know, how many times you look on
the internet rectangle, there's a prophecy being fulfilled
and they give you some bullshit political thing
going on.
It's like, oh no.
Yeah.
You see, so it's very, very subtle.
The Antichrist analogy is the best one that
I can give.
Most people have heard about it and if
they're so smart and they know about it
then how is it going to take place?
Doesn't work that way, sorry.
So, you know, all of this stuff, it's
just, it's, how many times have you heard
me say that the being's in control of
an IQ of 2 million?
You're not going to outsmart them.
You're not even going to perceive that they're
doing anything.
That's how smart they are.
Like, the best thieves are the best, are
the, are masters of disguise.
Yeah.
So, anyway, I would suggest that you have
to study both sides.
You know, I mean, nowhere, like when you
study scripture, nowhere in scripture does it fully
disqualify secular knowledge.
It kind of pokes fun at the scribes
changing things and philosophy as being the be
-all end-all, let's say, man's philosophy or
man's law, but it doesn't say you shouldn't
know about it.
Right?
Right.
So, keep yourself aware.
And the workings of it, it's mature, you
know, it's a, most people, again, they have,
they've stopped developing, you know, what's interesting, I'm
starting to see on the rectangle, more Greek
-speak topics come up out of the blue,
so to speak.
Like, for example, there was a commentary about,
like most people, this guy hasn't matured beyond
eight years old.
Well, where have you heard that before, you
know?
Right.
Most people, it's not possible to mature beyond
that.
When you look at the parents, like Jack
Fresco says, you give the child a book,
the cow goes moo, and the lamb goes
baa.
Yeah.
Well, guess what?
When you go to get a PhD in
physics, it's the same thing, you know?
It's just a slightly different wording.
It's the same mentality, same mindset.
You know?
You know, do you ever see a dog
or a cat or a deer or an
elephant raise its young, like, or show it
something that's contrary to what it's going to
need as an adult?
No.
Not at all.
They're preparing you.
So, look at how the society educates their
children.
That means, that's the follow through.
Go look at a high school textbook, college
textbook.
When I open it, even if it's physics
or whatever, all I see is the cow
goes moo and the lamb goes, you know,
baa, and the dog goes bark and the
cat goes meow.
Yeah.
That's the same mindset.
Obviously, you know, the topics are different.
Sure.
And they're wording it differently, but they still
got you in that mindset.
So, whoever heard of the Antichrist raised your
hand.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
You're hearing things now.
They don't get it.
Right?
So, and the other subtle thing is this.
Be very careful because right now, actually, it's
been, when I say right now, I mean
in this past century and especially now that
times have ended, because remember, time ended 20
plus years ago.
Right.
So, whatever is good is considered evil and
whatever is evil is considered good or permissible.
Like, whatever is haram is not tawd.
Right?
And like haram in Arabic is not permissible
and halal is permissible.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
So, what is now, what is becoming permissible,
again, going back to the sodomites or the
lesbians or whatever, they're not giving them any
rights.
Who wants rights anyway?
You know, that's, that means that you're in
trouble and you're given a right.
Great.
You're presumed to be a criminal.
Yeah, there's no law, discussion of law.
All they're doing is making it permissible and
then if you don't like that, now you're
interfering with them, you see.
Mm-hmm.
It's not, yeah, you see, it's interference and
permission is what the entire society is based
on and they don't know this, by the
way.
And very subtly done.
Yeah, if you look at some older, not
now, like past 30 years or so, legal
documents for a bank robbery or not bank
robbery, a store robbery, let's say a convenience
store or a store.
Sure.
It wasn't really robbery, it was interfering with
the state's ability to collect taxes was the
charge.
Interesting.
Because how's the state going to collect taxes
if the guy's interfering with a gun and
a mask?
Right, But you see, that's beyond, even the
attorneys getting out of Harvard, they don't, they're
like, who, who, who?
You know, they don't understand that.
You see, so, yeah, yeah, it's really, it's,
yeah.
So on the bright side, you know, have
you had a good meal lately?
And if you haven't, or you, let's say
you have on the bright side, do you
know how to, did you prepare it and
can you have another good meal?
Right, you see?
Are your shoes comfortable?
Are your clothes comfortable?
Do you have someone around or are you
or imagine that there's someone around that you
can speak to, even, right?
Right, right.
Okay, is the air reasonably clean where you
are?
Is your bed reasonably comfortable and is where
you dwell reasonably comfortable?
Anything outside of that is superficial.
Those are the main things.
Yeah.
I'm serious.
Good food, good clothes, good people.
Some conversation, yeah.
yeah.
Good water.
Yeah.
Because once you know both the gods and
man are fixing on getting rid of 90
% of the earth's population, you know that
now.
It's not whether you're afraid of it or
want it or it's good or bad, it's
going to happen, period, you're done.
Get over it.
Move that to the side.
So that means that you're living on a
momentary basis, daily basis, weekly basis.
There's a prayer in scripture, does it say
give us our yearly bread or our monthly
bread or my 401k?
Or does it say daily, right?
Yeah.
Because it's that bad.
Like all these states, they all are under
what's called state of emergency.
Every year, every month, every day, every government's
under state of emergency.
That's been going on for quite some time.
Oh yeah.
They know.
Yeah.
But you don't because you don't, you know,
it's too subtle maybe.
So the fall, the breaking down period is
now and it's quiet.
Yeah.
It's quiet but for the, in other words,
the noisemakers aren't spinning.
It doesn't mean that there isn't a party.
You see?
Just because there's no noise doesn't mean that
the group, you know, there isn't anything going
on.
The punch bowl is still full.
You know?
And don't drink from it because someone pissed
in it, right?
So anyway, hmm, the host pissed in it.
Right.
And he gets off on watching you guys
drink out of it with pleasure.
So anyway, there's a lot going on and
where do you start?
Well, if you have, you have to understand
the substrates.
What's happening is there's a posture being set
when it's quiet.
Okay.
There's some people that might appreciate this.
When it's quiet, you know, imagine all the
topics that you've seen in the media, good
or bad.
I mean, there's not much good but, right?
I mean, what can people do that's generally,
you know, objectified as good?
Very little.
They just do.
And hopefully, they don't do too much damage.
That's good.
Right?
Now, to give an example, have you heard
of any plagues, any pestilence, any kind of
scare of epidemics in the past?
Whatever.
it's funny you should bring that up.
You know, I go to a, that map
that shows all the different things that's supposed
to be in real time.
It's free and yes, there is biological hazards,
epidemic hazards that always seems to pop up
at least daily.
Daily, but on what scale?
You know, pretty much always localized.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
All the different countries except, well, Australia wasn't
in there.
Well, I don't know how that would be
quantified.
Like, for example, if some, if there's a
neighborhood that has a hamburger shop and all
the patrons get sick from the cold.
Right, something like that.
Yeah, like local.
Sure.
Okay, so let's say what you've used to
your whole life seeing, you know, you have
the, let's say the epidemics.
Bring that up right now.
Yeah, there isn't anything like that.
Guess what?
They're working on it.
Okay?
Right.
So when that comes up, when it comes
up, you'll see how it's been structured because
it was worked on while it was quiet.
The next thing is a geopolitical thing.
It's kind of being resolved in the Middle
East a little bit, but guess what they're
working on?
You know a country called Jordan?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, that little short guy.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you're going to see some serious stuff
going on there like you ain't seen before
when that shit hits the fan.
Okay, so watch that, right?
If you've been watching, Iraq hasn't been in
the news, but if you really are watching
what's going on in Iraq, it's, what is
the main, if you deduce the main thing
that's going on in Iraq right now, especially
for the past six months, is decentralization.
In other words, there's a growing majority of
people in what they call the country of
Iraq don't want the country to be like
a country of Iraq.
They want it in different sections.
This has been going on a bit.
I've discussed becoming a new Assyria.
Okay, you know, what else is going on?
You know, bad weather.
Well, we're working on that.
Next subject.
The thing, you'll get that for sure.
You'll see.
The other thing is economics.
You know, it was 2008.
That was not a crash at all.
That was just a reset.
It was a wonderful thing to happen.
It proved many things.
It proved how stupid people are, you know,
and it proved that the credit system can
recover.
It was an orchestrated deal.
Of course.
It's kind of like when you test a
car tire, they have a course for testing
car tires.
You know, and part of the course is
when the tire does fail, how quickly can
you recover with a spare?
It was all a success.
You see, people say, the tire failed, but
look, the car still drove off.
that was a big success.
So, when you look at these things, you
know, and by the way, the way the
economic system was reset allegedly on the crash
of 2008 is going to make it more
difficult to rearrange it the next time.
That's another explanation why.
Right?
Yeah.
Because no matter what they do to recover
the next credit economy folly is going to
be very obvious that what the credit system
really is.
People still don't know what it is.
Right?
So, it's kind of like the story of
the old caveman, you know, who wants to
live in the cave.
He sends one of his children and he
doesn't come out, so he has to send
another child who doesn't come out.
Then he sees a lion come out, the
lion goes back and he still doesn't know
what's going on so he sends another child
and the child doesn't come out.
I mean, this is how oblivious the people
are when it comes to the economy or
anything, or even the health field or anything.
So, you start imagining what could be in
the news or what could be noisy and
is not and that's what's being worked on
because it's all a show right now.
Right.
The main thing, again, is how do you
reduce the population down to 10% of
what it is?
This is a secular and divine thing.
It's a big thing.
I'm not stressing it as the be-all
end-all, but this is something that people
scream about, you know, population reduction, this, that,
and the other, but they don't know that
it's going to happen for sure.
They don't know that.
Right.
And they don't know how it's going to
happen.
A lot of it is based on that
and I think we've had a discussion about
that audio or about The New Barbarians, right?
Oh yeah, Dr. D.
Yeah.
For example, they talked about how all the
cars will look alike.
That's true.
I mean, if you go out, I can't
tell right now if a minivan or a
compact car is a BMW, a Kia, or
a Toyota.
I can't tell.
So those many things, you know, they already
gave the gays and the lesbians or the
homos rights, you know, that was a lot
of things, but a lot of things that
were mentioned there were not put in order
yet.
That's a really good secular guideline.
You know, a lot of things have not
been done yet.
Right.
You know, like, where's the demise pill?
You know, when someone gets tired and they
go to an office and they check out,
they say, I'm done with here, okay, fine,
lay down, we'll give you an injection, take
the pill, you're done.
That hasn't come around yet.
That's being worked on, I'm sure.
I mean, the thing is, how do you
get people to accept it?
Well, Gavorkian started up a little bit there,
but that faded out real quick.
They slapped him down too quickly, I think.
I think they could have kept it around
and people would have gotten used to it.
Right?
Yeah, if it was in the face more
positively spun.
Right.
Here's another, when it comes to, you know,
the subject of war, because the three things
that are going on with human society is
very, very simple.
The first thing is entertainment, in this order,
believe it or not, and I'll explain why.
The second thing is food, which is food,
clothing, shelter, and the third thing is how
you kill, war, you know, how do you
kill each other?
Those are the three things about human society.
Why is it the first thing, entertainment?
Well, it should be obvious, but we can
discuss it briefly.
Entertainment includes marketing, what you're, when you engage
in television, radio, film, written, you know, pulp
or electronic media, that's how you find out
what you're going to eat and if it's
okay to kill people too, right?
You know, if you look at the Syrian
war, they say, oh yeah, Assad is, we
need to go kill, you know, so if
Assad's so bad, just take him out, why
do you have to kill a million Syrians,
right?
So the entertainment justifies, you know, let's say
9-11, entertainment justifies, because the news is
entertainment, don't think it's the news, right?
I mean, whatever news is new.
It's like what movie is new is the
news, right?
So the entertainment is first for humans, believe
it or not.
What do you think the churches are?
And your synagogues and your mosques and all
that?
What do you think that is?
Entertainment first for humans, period.
Second is food, clothing, shelter.
We're talking about this society now.
Food.
How do you know what's good to eat
or not?
How many times do you hear people saying
they don't want to eat this and where
did you get that information?
Oh, from the doc, what doc, on TV,
right?
Okay.
Have you heard of like Atkins diet or
paleo diet?
Oh, God, yes.
Where do people get these ideas?
That's entertainment.
How about clothing?
How are you going to know what to
wear?
Entertainment is where you learn what to wear,
what's trending, what's fashionable.
And shelter, that's also entertainment.
You know, oh, yeah, I want to get
a tiny house.
Why?
I saw it on the internet.
I like it.
Oh, really?
Entertainment, right?
Entertainment dictates what you're going to eat, what
you're going to wear, and how you're going
to live.
And the third part is how to kill
humans.
Entertainment dictates that.
Oh, yeah, they blew down the towers.
We have to go get those countries.
Perfect, yeah.
Wasn't it you that, yeah, I think you
mentioned something one time about how they tried
to get more enlistments at one time and
all they did was made a movie with
some soldiers.
Japanese.
right.
Yeah, and Frank Capra, that asshole who did
that other Christmas movie.
Right, right.
Did it, yeah.
He said, oh, we'll just make a movie
with people dressed up like Japanese soldiers raping
white women, white Christian women, and the enlistment
went up.
They tried to do stuff like that for
Vietnam also and other things like that, yeah.
Yeah, they had the anti-war thing going
on at that time.
Oh, yeah.
You know, if that anti-war stuff didn't
go on, I bet you that would have
worked a heck of a lot better.
I bet it would have.
Oh, yeah.
There was more anti-war.
The most anti-war there ever was was
for World War II, but you don't hear
anything about it.
No, no.
Right, just like the history books tell you
still it's Arabs and airplanes.
There were no Arabs and there were no
airplanes.
I mean, there were airplanes, but they were
landed at an Air Force base, you know.
Right, right.
Right, so, yeah.
Yeah, so again, entertainment will tell you who
it's okay to kill and it, yeah, you
see, right?
All shaking hands with each other, yeah.
Entertainment will dictate your food, clothing, shelter, and
it'll dictate when it's okay to go kill
a whole bunch of people.
Yep, yeah.
Very simple.
And if you know, if you understand things
that are true, or the truth, or the
truth of the matter, because, you know, each
matter has its own structure, substrates, and history,
and condition, you know, what state it's in,
right?
Like, if we talked about the hat industry,
it's very different discussing it before the 1960s
than now.
Right now, it's just baseball caps, basically, and
ski hats, right?
Yeah.
It wasn't so, you know, if you go
back turn of the century, it was more,
you know, the richer you were, the shinier
and taller your top hat was, right?
Mm-hmm.
So, but hats are a pass, and, you
know, how does that come, entertainment again?
You know, so, You had to tell them.
Yeah, again, religion, same thing, entertainment, and the
people take entertainment very, very seriously.
Oh, yeah.
I know, I wasn't going to talk about
this, but, I got kicked out of my
first Christian channel.
Yeah.
Well, the Christian channel, not yours.
yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And, Well, let's, but here's the thing, you
know, if they come out, those people are
deprived.
They're in depravity.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not that they're Christian, or Muslim, or
Jewish, or Hindu, or Buddhist, or whatever.
They know nothing about nothing to go for
that.
You see?
Well, you know, and knowing what I know
now, and I was, and I did more
listening than I did any kind of engagement,
and it was all Mithra, Asclepius, brother me,
brother that, and sister, and, And it was,
let me ask you this, though, let's get
more down to the root of it.
Okay.
In case one of these idiots are listening.
Right.
It's important for them to get this.
Are they mostly American, would you say?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I think there was a couple of, there
was a couple of Spanish ones in there,
yes.
Okay, but they were most likely that not
going directly for Mithra, let's just say, but
yes, a derivative of, of derivative, yes.
Well, I could tell you directly what they
were going for.
Directly, they're going for the American Jesus and
the American God.
Exactly.
Based on the American Bible.
Yep.
As what, and the American Church.
Now, if this was a group in England,
it would be the England, English Jesus.
If it were, if it was a group
out of Yes.
Italy, it would be the Italian Jesus.
Yeah.
You see.
Entertainment.
The same with Buddhism, and the same with
Islam.
Right.
It would be, yeah, it would be, because
each country has its own, what, how difficult
would it be for the God that's behind
America to be okay to have people organized
under the J-E-S-U-S label,
or G-O-D?
Totally fine.
Oh, yeah.
How would the God in Italy, for example,
or Spain, be okay with the people being
organized, as long as it was a lie,
under their form, of J-E-S-U
-S or G-O-D?
Totally fine.
Mm-hmm.
As long as you follow the party line,
you know?
Right.
Because it's political.
They don't know this.
You know?
Mm-hmm.
Who was it?
It was something that the greatest Americans that
ever lived was John Wayne, Barry Manilow, and
Jesus Christ himself.
Those were the greatest Americans that ever lived.
No, literally.
This is what people think.
Mm-hmm.
Or how about this one?
The King James Bible is the true word
of God.
It was good enough for the Apostle Paul.
It was good enough for me.
It's like saying, you know, the iPhone is
the best GPS.
It was good enough for Christopher Columbus.
It was good enough for me.
Right?
That's right.
There's no...
You can't...
You ever hear take a number?
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what these people are, take a
number.
The waiting room.
take a number.
Yep.
Your number 6,953,000 in the minus
mark, whatever.
Just stand here.
We got 70 years.
You can graze and eat and poop, breathe
the air, and then you're out.
Boom.
That number is satisfied.
Next.
Yeah.
Right.
This is serious cosmic talk.
You don't get that.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No one could touch this at all, this
kind of talk, because they don't think.
And I'll tell you what, if I know
for sure, 100% sure, that people that
do know this and have meditated and know
that it's true aren't speaking.
So...
Yeah, it's...
But, you know, the Muslims are a funny
bunch and the Buddhists are a real funny
bunch.
I mean, they're all just as ignorant.
You know, the Jews are a real funny
bunch too, but you could have more fun
with the Jews because at least you could
make scriptural references and they have heard of
it.
They don't understand it or don't know much
or they'll bring up a point of view
and they'll find out that it's really not
what they think it is, you know.
So you could have a lot of fun
with the Jews on that.
I like to spell it J-O-O
-Z so it doesn't get picked up.
I like to change that because it sounds
the same and it actually emphasizes the phonetic
aspect of it.
And it's...
Yeah, it works.
Yeah, it does work.
Yeah, it does.
Because no one...
Yeah, who cares?
Yeah, so with the Jews you will get
a little more...
you'll have a little more fun if you
study scripture because at least you'll feel that
they're not trying to push something completely foreign
on you.
They will usually admit occurrences in the Old
Testament as being significant where no one else
does.
You know, none of the...
Buddhist, Christians, Hindus or Satanists or whatever are
all the same.
You know, they're not going to...
You know, you can have more fun with
the Jews in a more relaxing way.
It's like I'd rather have a drink with
a Jew than a Christian any day.
You know, if we're going to talk about
scripture you know, the Christians are just finished,
you know.
Right.
And there's a thing going on now.
I've noticed on the rectangle...
it's been going on for a couple of
years.
Christian academics.
If you listen to them very carefully though
they are usurping your attention.
Meaning, what they're doing is they're coming in
from the priest...
they're trying to be your priest by the
way.
Because...
what does that mean?
Very often people would ask me some pretty
deep questions to resolve things for them scripturally.
I'm like, you have to remember I'm not
your priest.
I can't tell you what to do because
I'm not a priest.
Right.
Because the priest had the knowledge and the
priest had the dictum to do that, you
know.
So what I would say is these academics...
like recently I heard something about an academic
and talking about another one and someone said
well, that guy sounds stupid and the other
academic says yeah, but don't call him stupid.
Right?
Because it's a priesthood.
Right.
So don't fall for these idiots.
Because they're all idiots by the way.
Now it doesn't mean that an idiot can't,
you know, hit his hand with a hammer
and say something truthful.
Like, oh shit.
A lot of these academics could go through
the poop and pull out the corn and
wash it off.
But remember, do you want to eat the
corn that's been cleaned off of somebody's poo?
You know?
But you still can approach what they've done
if it's a lot of work to save
you work.
If, you know.
If it's worthy.
Or just to show another parallel thing.
Here, I'll...
not toot my own horn, but toot toot.
I've been looking at stuff and hearing people
lately and I noticed more Greek-speak type
subjects are popping up here and there.
That's why I put the YouTube with that
heifer.
Right.
The Asian heifer on there.
She actually said well see, September means the
seventh month but whatever.
Let's go back to our being our little
LSD trip here.
American Christian stuff, you know.
American Jesus is great.
The gospel, right?
Those of you who know what that means.
Oh yeah.
I mean, there's a whole plethora of idiocy.
I mean, you can take...
You know like ice cream how they have
different flavors mixed with...
You know, they mix flavors of like chocolate
and other things to make a new flavor,
right?
Right, right.
And they just mix things.
You can mix pretty much any flavor that's
out there to make a new flavor, right?
But I'll tell you what's not going to
change.
That whenever you see a flavor, whatever stupidity
because that's all you're going to get from
humans anyway, coming out of somewhere, make sure
that you get a geographical marker on it.
Why?
Because they're being influenced by that geography.
Right?
Okay.
So let's say you land on a video
about Christianity and the origin, let's say the
speaker, the audience and all that is from,
let's say, I don't know, pick a country,
Armenia.
That's going to be the Armenian J-E
-S-U-S and God he's talking about.
No matter how many references he makes to
the biblical text, unless they qualify it by
first saying even though the text has never
been translated and what we have given in
the New Testament is pretty much erroneous, is
not worth looking at really until it's organized
a little better.
The irony of it is the most important
thing to look at, by the way, is
the New Testament.
That's why it's in the most disheveled condition.
The other thing is unless they start giving
you the caveats, you know, we want to
talk about Scripture but it's going to be
difficult because you guys don't know what's in
it.
Nobody knows what's in it unless you do
the study.
None of them talk like that.
So they're going to give you the crap
that they're getting from that God that's in
their nationality.
I'm serious about this.
The entertainment over there, yes.
Yes, right.
The entertainment that they're giving there, yes.
The same with medicine, the same with science,
the same with all this other stuff.
Right.
Yes.
The return of the old gods.
Ah, that's...
That is interesting.
Yes.
Yes, but you know, it's the return of
the old gods being more overt on the
scene.
In other words, the bizarreness.
Right, right.
You see, if you hung out with some
mobsters, right, other than what you see on
TV, some of the Goodfellas is pretty accurate,
and the Sopranos might have been pretty accurate.
If you hang out with some mobsters, let's
say for a couple of days, and you
really live with them for a few days,
let's say from where they normally live to
their vacation house, how they do business, you
will find it to be in great opposition
and very contrary, almost bizarre to what's considered
normal, but yet they do have a visage
of being normal and likable, even.
Just like anyone would have a characteristic that's
likable.
But they're very, very strange.
Because they're operating with a certain character and
a certain power level that they control their
environment.
Right.
If you ever hang around powerful people that
control their environment, they don't act like your
average Joe Schmoe, by the way.
They're very quirky, they have, you know, I've
seen, I've been around some very wealthy people,
and no matter how much you like them
or like them, you always see the really
strange sublime weird stuff and the real mean
streaks come out more than you've seen in
your common people.
Right?
Because they can get away with it.
Right.
You know, like for example, if Joe Schmoe
puts out a mean streak on another Joe
Schmoe, the other Joe Schmoes will kick your
ass.
You say that again.
But if you have, I'm not going to
mention names here, someone who's a billionaire put
a mean streak on someone, a maintenance person,
he's going to put his head down and
say, I'm sorry, yes, I'll do it right
away.
Right.
Right?
Big difference.
And they get, because they're always being accommodated,
that mean streak is cultivated, I call it
a mean streak, it's kind of a childish
thing to say, but you know, from a
position of power, they're not apologetic.
In other words, they don't have to tell
you why they want it, when they want
it, you just better do it.
And not even or else.
Yeah, not even or else.
The or else is unspoken.
Yeah.
You just do it.
You see, the commoners don't have that in
their thing.
Okay, so why did I bring this up?
Because the gods that are behind the nations
are like that.
When they make things happen, it's bizarre, it's
going to happen no matter what, even though
it shouldn't be happening.
Right.
based on common logic.
Watch out for that.
Okay.
Use scripture.
I found some very good sources other than
scripture, and that would be understanding the real
natural sciences, how things really work.
You know, so when you hear of a
storm and the power goes out, do you
know why?
Not because the force of the wind or
whatever knocked the power line down.
No, it has nothing to do with that
at all, but they don't accurately report that
to people.
Structurally, everything could be fine and all of
a sudden the transformer explodes, right?
Right.
They don't know why.
It's electrons.
Yeah, right.
So you have to, okay, water.
So how does, you know, how does weather
really work?
You see, so when you comprehend that, yeah.
How does food really work?
What, you know, carrying, carrying, you know, the
carry and consumption ratios, you know, in other
words, if you, you know, how does that
work?
You know, if you're going to maintain the
population of adults, you need one pound minimum
per person per food a day.
You need one pound of food and two
pounds of water, 32 ounces of water, I
mean, yeah, two pounds of, of liquid and
one pound of food per person per day.
So if you, let's say you were to
open a prison and you needed to maintain
the population of adults, it would be, you
would have to be able to supply a
minimum of one pound of food and two
pounds of liquid to each prisoner per day.
That's the minimum.
Right.
To, to stay alive and maintain, you know,
if you're fatty and you like overeating, no,
you're not going to, that's, because if you
did three meals, that's a third of a
pound, you know, it's not much.
Right.
But you need a pound per, if you're
doing a survival thing, by the way, it's
a pound of food per adult per day
and two pounds of liquid per day.
Minimum a pound, 16 ounces, right, of water
per day, minimum.
But depending on the environment.
Mm-hmm.
You see, that's, that's your ratio.
So a year's supply would be 365 pounds
of food and 700 pounds of water.
Yeah.
I'm saying, you know, there's eight, eight pounds
per gallon, right?
Mm-hmm.
It's eight and a half depending on the
dissolved solids.
It could be up to nine and a
half if you have very heavy mineral water.
Right.
Those are the real, so once you understand
these capacities, you see, you start to get
more comprehension on what's going on.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you know, it's amazing, I was talking
to someone, an old guy, he's about 80
something now and he's into food storage since
the Y2K.
He still goes on and off about it.
He didn't know the one pound per person
per day and two pounds of liquid.
He's been into it for 20 years and
he doesn't, he didn't even know that ratio.
Oh, Simple, yeah.
Talk about not, it's like go to a
local pastor or minister, ask them anything in
the Bible.
Oh, it doesn't matter what that says, it
doesn't matter what, just have faith, my son.
Yeah.
And just relax because we're going to give
you some lubricant.
Yeah.
Just relax.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Why do you have both your hands on
my shoulder?
Yeah.
Sick people, man.
Oh, yeah.
Not some of them, all of them because
the ones that you think are good are
part of a system that is inherently evil
so you go figure out how you're going
to sort your, so the people that think
that there are good pastors and ministers and
priests or whatever or rabbis or gurus or
whatever, just don't forget that they're part of
a group that condones abuse and evil.
Right?
Tie that into your patriotism.
I have a friend who is a Nazi,
you know.
He's a nice guy, right?
Yeah, but he's part of a group that
sounds really bad that everyone's been taught to
hate because of it, right?
Whether it's true or not, that's the idea.
So when I hear that he's a pastor
or minister, I'm like, oh, his friend's a
Nazi.
What's the difference?
Cosmically, they represent the enemy.
And even though your priest, pastor, minister, priest
or whatever is not directly related to representing
Satan in his mind, he is directly representing
the god of your nation, for sure.
That, you know, the J-E-S-U
-S, the American J-E-S-U-S
or the Russian or the Mexican or the
Canadian J-E-S-U-S, whichever, whatever
they say, it doesn't matter.
They can change it on a dime.
And sometimes they do.
And they do, yeah.
They're pretty evil.
Years ago, I was on a roundtable and
I said, pretty much one-third of the
population is just fixed on evil.
Can't be changed.
They'd rather die before they...
Then if you put a gun to their
head and said, stop being evil, I'll pull
the trigger, they wouldn't know what you're talking
about, most of them.
But cosmically and objectively, they are.
The other third is, another third is they're
victims and the other thirds are just along
for the ride.
They can go either way.
They're just cannon fodder.
Useless.
So what do you do?
How do you sort that out?
This is your world population.
Right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's not very good.
No.
This is cosmic talk.
Most people can't handle it, man.
At all.
That's okay.
And you know that people say, it's not
my problem.
Oh, it will be.
Remember Yoda?
Maybe Skywalker?
I'm not afraid.
Oh, you will be.
It will be your problem, all right.
But you know what the best part of
it being their problem is?
They're not going to realize that it is.
Yeah.
They're going to go with it all the
way.
Even at the resurrection, they're still going to
be talking shit.
Yeah.
I'm telling you, man.
Okay.
I don't know if there's any questions or
anything else.
We did have one guy.
Hi, Greek.
Appreciate it when you talk about improving water
quality.
Do you have any recommendations on how to
improve air quality?
Same.
Best way to do it is to...
Are you ready for this?
Create an artificial sun, which does...
The sun is not a light bulb, by
the way.
It could be invisible.
That allows the air to move where you
have a rarefied rising cold and a descending
heat, just like it is on the earth
within a living space.
That's the best.
The second best is to have good convection
that is not air forced through ducts.
You know what I mean about convection?
You open the top window, open the bottom
window, the bottom of the window, the hot
air, right?
Better rise, yeah.
The other thing about air quality that people
should know, especially those that are structurally minded,
is depending on the interior space, depending on
what it's made of, is going to be
dependent on how much dust you have.
If you have a dirt floor, you're probably
going to have more dust around than if
you have a marble floor.
Right?
Yeah.
So keep it clean.
Carpets are notorious dust collectors.
Here in the southwest where I am, the
population since I've been here has more than
doubled.
And the car engines have more than, amount
of combustion engines have more than doubled, but
the pollution has gone down almost 70 or
80%.
And it's not because of the EPA.
It's because I've been running, you know, devices
that clear the air and prevent pollution from
forming.
Right?
So if you understand how the ether works,
you can make a small rotating device.
Some of them are the size of a
coffee mug.
I have a guy in Australia that's been
experimenting with coffee mug size ambient ethereal translators
for a couple of years now with great
success.
You can go into any place, any pollution,
place that has bad air quality, increased air
quality within three weeks and maintain it forever
that way with a small coffee, you know,
coffee mug size device that rotates.
That's the other thing.
That's what I'm employing and I enjoy it.
I remember when I first moved here to
the southwest, there was always an inversion layer
and they had air warnings on the news.
Don't breathe the air tomorrow.
Oh, how are you going to avoid that?
Right.
You'd approach the city from a distance, let's
say 30 kilometers out or 15 miles out,
and you'd see the city and you'd see
the sky and about, just hovering above the
city was a thin band of brown.
Right?
And you'd see blue below and above it.
Right.
Ever since I've been employing the rotating translators,
that has not occurred ever here.
That's impressive.
Yeah, that's the truth.
Yeah.
And it's simple to do.
The other thing is we can also change
weather air quality at a distance.
I've done several, I don't know, let's just
not get into specifics, but, you know, international
ones at a distance.
I believe you mentioned about China one time,
yes.
Yes, yes.
Somebody says, oh, did you get permission from
them to do it?
I said, no, I said, well, you could
create an international incident.
I said, that would be like the best
thing I would go, if I knew I
created an international incident between the Americans and
the Chinese over that, man, oh, what an
accomplishment if I had children and grandchildren.
I'd say, my granddad did that, you know,
started World War III, you know, or whatever.
By cleaning the air.
Like, who's that, the bullshit story that they
gave you who started World War I was
killing the ambassador Ferdinand, King Ferdinand, the assassination.
Yeah.
Which he wasn't really assassinated, his own people
assassinated.
They shot at him, the guy ran, he
missed, and then his own people shot him
twice or something.
Anyway.
Yeah, that's pretty, I'd say the medical term
cover your ears, fucked up if you ask
me.
You got that right.
So, or snafu, or whatever, what's it, or
in the military, FUBAR, yeah, FUBAR.
FUBAR.
FUBAR, and they've got in the army, those
idiots, they got us saying soup sandwich when
something's really messed up.
Yeah.
That's a soup sandwich, you know, you pour,
yeah, so.
So, that's our army rangers that do high
lows and hey ho's, and I don't know
what else they do, but, you know, paratrooping.
So, yeah, yeah.
All right, if there's nothing else, we'll call
it.
It's been a long night, just thought we'd
come on, say hello and goodbye.
Yeah, yeah.
Subtleties are, are there.
Again, just to wrap it up again, repeat
a few salient points.
Sure.
Get over the, get over your daily grind,
your weekly, monthly, yearly grind.
Get over that you live to 60, 70,
80, 90, or whatever.
Get over that.
Some of these things that the gods are
engaging in are multi-generational.
Like Dougreek, I know that, I've heard that.
No, yeah, you might have heard, but have
you internalized it?
Right?
Do you really know what that means?
Mm-hmm.
You know, are you able to fathom a
plan that, whether you want to call them
the global elite or the gods, they take
hundreds of years to implement.
Can you fathom that?
And if you say yes, you're lying, because
you can't fathom it.
How?
Yeah.
How can you see what it takes?
No one can really see it unless you've
lived that long or been around that long.
The best you can do is start to
rationalize what it takes to do that.
Begin to rationalize.
Well, yeah, okay, so if it took 75
years to implement this, that means grandma was
born when they started, and now that she's
old, you see, so you can start rationalizing
it that way and saying, well, look at
the rationale here.
Look, this, you know how many things change
over 75 years on a trend level?
Many, many things.
Right.
How the entertainment has changed in those generations
and what's been passed down and entertaining and...
And what most people are affected by is
trends.
It's like, have you ever heard of Atkins
diet or paleo diet?
It's like the dumbest shit in the world
until the next dumb shit comes out.
You know, that's why very often I go
on a Skype call.
They're like, oh, the Greek, he's not going
to like it.
He's not going to like it before they
even tell me what it is, you know.
But why does it matter if I like
it or not?
Is it true?
Is it bullshit?
Well, you know, Greek, we need something to
talk about.
See ya.
Yeah.
Don't forget to get those orange vests and
plastic brooms, guys.
I have no qualms and problems in calling
people stupid or moronic or did your mother
have any children that lived kind of thing,
you know.
Right, right.
Because at least, you know, that's the more
truth that they're going to Doctor lied about
dropping you on the head, huh?
Yeah, your doctor lied and your friends lied
that you actually, yeah, dropped you on the
head.
They picked you up and gave you back
to your mom and told you he'll be
alright.
Eh, he's fine.
He'll be fine.
Dust him off.
Yeah, that's right.
That's how it goes, man.
Oh, yeah.
It's very nothing else.
Ah, thank you, Greek.
I appreciate it.
It was very enlightening.
Yeah, great.
Not so subtle about the subtle, right?
Okay.
You gotta be.
Gotta be, yeah.
Okay, thanks, Bruce.
We'll do it next week if you can.
Take care.
See you, man.
Okay, bye.