and most people will take their body as precedent over the other two and in a
way they should because neither the soul or the spirit could be animated without
it right so that when I say they don't the gods don't care about you that's
what I'm referring to they have no problem you know it's like you know if
they have like the news on you know the television show called the news on in
heaven how many humans died yesterday 80 million okay let me know when some you
know some real shit starts going on right so that's not the point the point
is are you looking at the obvious you know again people have asked the
question why does God allow all this suffering and murder and all that stuff
and death because they don't care about your physical state they care about your
spiritual state right how many times in prayer do you know you ask for physical
things or spiritual things Solomon asked for spiritual things wisdom and other
things have been asked but essentially it's a spiritual connection to spirit
beings your physical interest is secondary to them as a matter of fact if
you study some of the prophets they had been put through a living hell you know
parentheses you know right even Jeremiah if you if you're real slick you're
talking about reading the Bible getting a hang on the Hebrews handle mmm on the
Hebrew excuse me right before we got on something to do with Hebrew or Japanese
or Chinese or English has to do with are you are you paying attention you know is
it possible to have a roadblock I'm not a roadblock is it probably a robot or a
speed bump you know how the standard speed bumps are in Brazil and other
countries that call them turtles in their language right or increase okay
well is it possible to have a speed bump that's so small that you don't notice
but does affect the speed of the vehicle yeah it's called it's called a
rough road you know you ever go on you like when I travel around because I am
familiar with civil engineering and worked in that field whenever I get on a
road and I have people in the car I'm there oh this they rolled this up this
asphalt pretty good people like what you know or this right they use to course of
a grag aggregate on this asphalt like people in New Mexico they have a shit
crap specifications not all in Mexico most of it they use too large of a
gravel so wherever you're going you're gonna have more rolling resistance and
vibration right except for the big federal roads right certain places back
east it's really it's depends on how you mix the sand and the gravel to get a
really smooth and also if the asphalt is too hot you're gonna get washboard
effect bumpy ride if it's yeah right if it's too cold you're gonna get that
effect when they roll it if the roller is too heavy you know the roll out the
asphalt for the thickness of the asphalt it's going to be uneven so if you get
everything right you have a very smooth road right right but every road can be
criticized for its imperfections and that's that's what I mean it can be the
whatever state of imperfection you might be all the way to just a you know
completely deformed person on life support right is the whole scale but to
go back to what I was saying before if you look at reading it carefully in the
book of Jeremiah at one point he said he had an abominable an abominable thing or
an unclean thing that he asked to be healed and it wasn't I'm paraphrasing
here this is towards the middle of the the book and it doesn't go into it and
anything else or whatever and then after that he says that you know you're
like he tells the most high you're like a stream that doesn't flow your drive
oh and then he says well take it back you know because he's saying that in
front of other people right right so I'm not yeah I'm not discounting the power
of the most high or the hierarchy but essentially what I'm telling you is
they don't care about your state that you're in right now unless it's
predetermined to be rich or healthier or whatever or you pray and have it
mediated or you're just going to suffer with it or it's put on you you see so
very often in times in scripture especially what they call the New
Testament which you should avoid and I don't think there's I've only met a
handful of people in the past 15 years that I believe are competent to read the
New Testament the only reason why is because it's cumulative right the New
Testament would be like master PhD level I'm not you know so if you just
started reading scripture a few years ago that means you're in the third grade
you're not going to go to you know fourth sixth seventh year college right
away right and if you do go there they're not going to start at the
beginning you know I've said this many times if you took like graduate level
mathematics do you think your first day in class you're gonna say okay everybody
this is a class 408 of abstract geometry we're gonna obviously start with the
basics 2 plus 2 class is what you know 6 divided by 3 is what they're gonna do
that in graduate level of college you think nope right you should have done
that are wise words those are wise right so when you get to the New Testament
you'll be wrapped around the axle you I assure you you will not comprehend or
understand anything being said other than articles and words like the and is
up-down hot-cold and you will only be able to use anything that you're
reading in the New Testament are over like an icing over a cake or a
superficial garment over a large body of mental modeling that's been done to you
through society church TV cartoons hearsay urban legend right so and if you
want to double on that I was doing some research on the King James because I was
actually talking to someone was pretty respectable the community yesterday and
there's a start of their Christian to go to church and just starting to learn the
Hebrew and it's painful to them because they notice that the discrepancies of
what they've been taught Christianity and what's in the King James is huge and
they don't know how to reckon with it right and and you can't it's just like
finding out like your parents are not your parents or you find out what you
know what's really in sausages or something right or you know those those
pork loins that they serve over at that restaurant is not really made of pork
but the homeless people that are no longer a hoops did I just say that okay
so yeah I'm not discouraging anyone I'm just saying hurry up and hurry up and
get to graduate-level thinking graduate-level comprehension of
scripture there there is no shortcut but there you can compress it so it is
like a shortcut right you know like one of the things I talked about I don't
really get into because more on the I don't want to sound pedantic use big
Greek using big words man you got to keep it simple you know people don't
know like for you know I talked to people and they think hamburgers made out
of ham and I'm I mean that's how you know people are right so but in
heuristics which is a methodology of having like a tool set of things you
apply to solve problems very quickly versus going you know starting from
scratch right and like one thing in heuristics is when you're trying to
invent something you want to have as many failures as possible because that
just tells you how you shouldn't do it you know people typical people say when
they have a failure discourages them right but when you're on a research
project and you have a short timeline they encourage failure so like when
they're going to make something that hasn't been made before or designed to
be made and is not comprehended they actually welcome they hired twice as or
three times or four times as many people as they need and they just give them the
basics and they said start building this thing and the more failures they have
the happier they are because they're cataloging all of them and
documenting them as ways not to do it you see this is the opposite of how
people operate right but you know when you certain times old companies they get
to a point where all they want is failures because if they do succeed then
they they're cut their money their funding gets cut off right so what
happens with heuristics here would be fail as many times as possible and
and you welcome it meaning when you study scripture the actual failure itself
is understanding the misunderstandings that you've had you see but it's very
difficult right you know like I tend to be irreverent when when I can be and
when it's allowed like you know usually like with someone I was speaking with
recently I explained you know the different men and I said when Adam was
alone was either just jerking off in the garden he says oh he couldn't that's a
sin I said that deliberately I knew you know it would it would poke him the
wrong way because of his Christian background and I said no no no it's not
a sin I mean and I explained what sinning is and he's like okay now he was
he wasn't imploding but in a sense you know and it wasn't even asking the time
and telling him how to build a watch it was like imagine going to the kitchen
faucet and turning it on and it's like a fire hydrant right yeah so so I don't
know if anyone's here has ever worked with a three inch or two inch water main
it doesn't sound very big but it puts out a lot so so the the actually the
aspect can you fail studying scripture yeah of course you know so you need to
go through it now tie it back to what you were saying Bruce about the Hebrew
it's not about Hebrew what you can do for example is when you discover an error
a word meaning like for example sin in the New Testament doesn't mean what the
Christians think it means it means to miss the mark right so let's just put it
in this way if you had no desires can you sin and put it this way if you had no
desires and you sat in front of a TV and the remote never failed nothing ever
failed like your TV your beer your popcorn and and you slept there and you
had a toilet nearby nothing everything an endless roll of toilet paper there was
no way anything could run out whatever it could you sin no because you'd never
miss the mark right all right if you had no if you had no desires and didn't do
anything and everything was as expected and never attempted to do anything that
didn't work out can you sin no that's how simple it is right so it's another one
so another one is the concept of hell hell is the grave right and then there's
another place that's for spiritual beings or post-resurrected beings let's
say right which would be thrown in fire you know so those are different concepts
but 99% of the time when you see the word hell in scripture means the grave
now how many people do you run in the world and you say hell they think it's
you know this don't like this it like Satan's in hell right now you know and
all this crap right so just correcting that in your mind you know right so
you're correcting errors and so now when you're reprogramming yeah so the
deprogramming is where the mistakes are found and corrected and even though you
let's say get a handful probably a third of what you're still reading is
incorrect so you bite it you chip at it a little bit every day like when I used
to do restoration of architectural sculpture we get this real intricate
cornice piece would remove it make a model of it and it was really intricate
and I was like man I really you know this thing needs to be touched up in a
model to be made and I knew I had discipline that you don't sit there in
front of it for 12 hours a day for a month you just tell the client will be
ready in four or five months you do two hours or three hours a day on it right
right and you extend it out so you know because you're not a machine so the
mistakes on it right right because of what's gonna make you burn out his
emotions if if you were raised from a young child to do that for 14 hours a
day every day in and out yeah it wouldn't be no problem all that stuff
comes from the mental models and the image training and the culture you're
from remember the headhunter analogy right now so you know it's like when
people discuss politics I was scooting around a little bit on the internet I'm
not gonna mention any names but Ocelli I was gonna go into chat you know he's
always dishing dissing Trump and I was like why you upset at Trump because he
has more shrunken heads than you do anyway in other words it's like saying
you're all you're the same you're the same you know same culture you all keep
time the same way you eat the same stuff you have the same gods you have the
same interests you believe the same stuff I mean so what's wrong with the
guy you know he has more shrunken heads obviously right so you see there's no
way I don't see anything on the internet and and that's viable that I can
recommend to anyone even Jack Fresco which I find enlightening you know in
terms of his perspective being around so long basically you have you heard his 30
minute or there's a 30 minute YouTube where he's in England and he's real old
and he's saying take your Norman American which means fucked up and
that one that's really funny no no yeah I also drop a link and he got he's got
it as he got older he realized it wasn't going anywhere like Trevor Trevor at 91
it's funny I bring up Trevor because I pulled out a box and have all the stuff
that he sent me it's notes I got about an inch and a half thick of unpublished
and some of it published in original photographs and designs from Trevor you
can tell he's real old and he's on some kind of medication because when he's
writing his return address and his name it's on an angle right and then the
other times on different but anyway we've talked about chemistry does that
when I first started discussing things with Trevor is like no no no you can't
do that because it might cause some bad weather well like three years later he's
like screw it man I told me no through a tornado down here took out the county
40 to 30 tornadoes and he's like good boy you know so it because he changed
because he realized you know I saw him in three years go for him oh you have to
be very careful in public interviews to private being asked through these people
they're evil they're shit they're crap you know you bring them yeah if you
bring a cure to cancer they'll kill you and they'll ignore you right but if you
tell him you're looking for a cure of cancer they'll they'll have all the
middle-aged people running out you know and donating right right
see Jack Jack you know so he's you know much shitheads on this planet so anyway
this is the majority now I'm not you know the exception is so few it's not
even when I say morons shithead scumbags on this planet it's everyone and there's
a small minority that's an exception but they're so small it's not even worth
mentioning right it's like you have a building that's 500 feet tall and the
next one next to it is 500 feet in one inch can you say they're the same size
yeah you can't you can't see the difference without a laser beam or you
know a very accurate water level they look the same you see what I mean
there's no it was very very look even Jack Fresco talked about there's no way
you can change into ways and society has to collapse or go away or whatever and
still you know someone sent me a link and somebody says all these false flags
need to go away so go back to a harmonious world is that oh what an
idiot I can't work with someone go back to a harmonious world since when did you
have a harmonious world when you've been in the shithole with the gods the
gods you know you're in the shit with the gods right the good ones and the
bad ones you know you know what I mean so so here's the bottom line work China
was gonna be investigating weather modification in order to take care of
fires we got a few years ago more of four years ago and there might even be
some people listening that can that know this is true someone had some
contacts because I used to work with someone work with John Arava part of his
trust made like stealth materials out of nothing basically you know like Israel
got the paint put it on some 50 year old 40 year old jets and now they had still
planes you know I mean right it's basically if I could give you the
it's very easy to get some magnesium oxide with some silicone and various
other things but make a long story short this person John Arava's ex-wife was or
what he died his wife was a Chinese who had used to have tea with high-level
politicians in China and it ended up being she knew the current president of
China's wife and someone else that did business in Malaysia and China also knew
one of the cabinet people in the current government of China's three years ago
and we did a short synopsis on we did a couple of demonstrations on clearing
certain target cities that they gave us from here and we succeeded I actually
have all the reports State Department and all that right but it was a State
Department does a I'm sorry from the State Department website they do a air
monitoring for cities and we use that because it was more of a reference you
know as opposed to a private company you know so we took it from 900 parts
per mil per cubic meter or whatever the particular matter down to below 50 you
know anything below a hundred it's rare yeah so and then and then we stopped
within 24 hours I went back up to where it was you know and then we did it again
to show that it was not a fluke and it you know so anyway well the report got
on the current president China's desk and he looked at it about doing this
weather work and he says I'm not interested and he looked at the cabinet
people's but if you're interested you can do it I get it yeah okay let me
explain this for the people who are not too smart okay when you're a president
in a communist country or whatever and you're the king let's say and you say
I'm not interested in it but you guys in my cabinet one of you might be
interested the minute one of those guys picks it up it's treason indirectly not
directly because even if he picks it up says well then I'll do it well isn't he
he didn't say don't do it but you're showing right that you're being a little
too ambitious here you see you know I mean mm-hmm that's like a Sun Tzu move
right so it didn't happen so now they're people no no because he actually did say
I don't want to do it but if you want to do it and that just shows who's gonna be
overly ambitious and they don't like like Stalin said always surround yourself
with stupid people so you can sleep because if you had smart people around
him you know you couldn't sleep right who's gonna kill me right make up a
story so so what they're doing now in China is there they picked a mountain
range and they're gonna use chemicals and I discussed this with Trevor a while
back says oh they're never gonna go for it I said I know but let's try it anyway
and he's correct you're not gonna get a cure for cancer you're not gonna get real
weather work that that makes the planet good let's say good conditions you're
never gonna get flying jetpacks you're never gonna go into space you're never
gonna get a hotel on the moon you're never gonna get free energy you work
because that was around 50 years ago and you know you know I mean Newman and other
things I don't Ernesto dropped a bunch of links and I saw in the chat today I
think he dropped them in yesterday and I looked at those I said man how did he
hack into my bookmarks so I had the same things book you know I was like oh no he
hacked into my bookmarks I went to check the computer you know because I have a
resource sniffer on it you know what I mean yeah sure yeah so I was just joking
yeah and then I dropped that image in if you're gonna copy my homework change
it a little bit shows the Quran in the Bible right you know most people are so
moronic they don't even know that the Quran was written by rabbis still you
know you know if someone asked you for the proof you know it's like well if I
say Mickey Mouse is a fictional character you need proof you get it
right anyway but anyway so you know because here look you got a guy that's
admittedly illiterate and the document was written 150 years later after he
died and about 90% of in it that has any lawful references direct directly from a
rabbinical commentary anyway okay so that's why I put it in there because it
had the Quran and the Bible I found a couple of other things on the rectangle
I put in King James Version inaccurate couple of interesting scholarly papers
done where the one guy says I've located 14,800 errors in the King James and I'm
like that's pretty good because I got about 5,000 personal ones and then I
estimate 27,000 you know errors in it right so it's it floats or it doesn't
matter to doors but here's the thing make mistakes but make the mistakes
knowing that you use them as a step on a ladder right no one builds a little you
know like no one no one by no one bought wants to buy a drill bit right why do
people dry build bits drill bits to make holes so if you're a drill bit company
and you want to promote your drill bit you don't promote the drill bit you know
it's coding it's technique you know it's quality because no one cares about
drill bits but if you have a drill bit company and you promote a better hole and
by the way you get it done with the show but then people will buy it you see what
I mean right right no one wants to read and study everyone wants to know the
gist of it I do but I found out I told you in the beginning when I hung out
with the Ernest L Martin crowd those old farts and the Armstrong farts and
the guys who came up with the Dead Sea Scrolls what's the keep forgetting
there are one of the guys here is in the they started the foundation in the 50s
when they found the Dead Sea Scrolls they didn't take interest the full
bright or all bright or something like that all these people that you know what
they're assholes I'm not afraid of saying it why because when what they do
is it's like the alternative media which is all a bunch of assholes anyway what
they do is like that oh yeah the mainstream is lying to us but we're not
going to do real journalism we're just going to grab press releases and repeat
them based on what somebody else said you know they don't know anything about
how many times you alternative media cry about vaccines and ask them how does the
body work was it you know what are you talking about they don't know anything
none of them right so what happens with these people in the alternative
biblical study thing they grab a couple of concepts like the Hebraic roots or or
something you know we got you know whatever right you know the dark you
know the moon but it's got to be the new moon that the astronomical you know the
dark moon right or whatever they grab some stuff and they get a following and
it supports them you see and then they realize that as they're learning if they
change the following will go to pot right that's what I was told when I
approached a couple of old heads from the Ernest L Martin group and the
Armstrong group I said look there's no Pope's I didn't call Pope's work
schedule and I said the moon has got to be full because you can't measure in the
dark moon it's got to be noon look and they're like oh no no no you can't tell
people that because it divides them I've said this before right it divides
them and they and then we're not gonna they're not gonna want to listen anymore
so it's better for them to listen to the stuff they're familiar with and gently
give them I said gently gently these these are like baby seals ready to be
clubbed by the gods and you want to be gentle you know what I mean the gods are
ready to stop you like a roach right if you don't believe me it just wait 14
years and see or not even so I think the time for what is it kid kid glove
and you know as they go Greek a you know people think you're an ass you know you
get more flies with honey I said asshole I don't want any flies I want people if
I want to collect flies why would I be you know talking right right you see the
analogies that are given so I think right now if anyone's looking there's a
segue again so make mistakes but the thing is we'll get into the news of the
thing is you could read if you had a lifespan of 500 years and you read the
scriptures every day there's a possibility you still won't understand
jack shit in it right possible right slim you'll be able to cite it but you
want to be able to push it together right so ultimately it's a communication
debate can you have an accurate translation strictly in Chinese without
in other words make an accurate translation Chinese and then destroy all
the Hebrew and Greek that never exists on the planet you still have the
scriptures yes you do because it's accurately translated in Chinese but that
doesn't help you does it okay so it's translated into Bulgarian and then
destroy so the only record of the scriptures on this planet is accurately
in Bulgarian is it is it valid yeah sure it is you know you see because the
message is retained you see it doesn't matter what language so well the back
going back to the failure aspect of it I would suggest that get a methodology
that you know when there's an error in the King James or anything you're
reading in English you know there's a pattern where these errors show up you
ever notice that you ever notice the patterns yeah but they're ready well
shit well over your eyes with them Christian or Jewish crap right so
there's not gonna find any Muslim influence in it right because I was
way later and you know anyway the story the bottom line of the story is you have
two societies the things you see and things you don't see and perceive and
they made you and you got a 6,000 year plan and then you're gonna go to the
next level and too bad basically in between just tough shit and they don't
care about you sorry they only care about their own you ever read in
scriptures my people will know my name for example in the book of John he says I
want you to protect these of my own I mean my flock right so that's how it
goes sorry I'm not making this up but would you rather I made up some bullshit
and told you God loves you like in their language I'm going to tell you the truth
right there's plenty of places that anybody can go and say oh yeah the gods
love you the Elohim loves you know they don't that's obvious they're doing they
love in terms of doing the right thing which is not disturbing the plan and
making sure 6,000 years go by that's where the love is you see because love
like Jack Fresco said love is bullshit you don't even know what it means you
don't even know you're right would you be in love with yourself you know I'm not
meaning from a narcissistic but would you be with yourself right you know how
people separate in relationships right so are we still on the air Bruce yes we
are yes okay so you notice I'm not in the family hour mode anymore now I'm in
the right this street back alley modes and I think this is how it's going to be
from now on because pussyfooting around when you have seven billion people with
targets on their backs you know I mean and you're all a target until they take
the target off you know you ever see these to play pranks years ago on the
child they say hey they pat you on the back and what they did was they put us
thing that said kick me on it you know or hit me yeah yeah oh or you know if
you're in the Midwest you got sucker tattooed on white on your forehead right
or wherever if you're an afro that's tattooed in black or you see I mean
there's these things have been put on people and you're you're up Schitt's
Creek with or without a paddle it doesn't matter so the point here is this
is buck up man up you know they say man up whatever and enjoy the ride because
what you are going to be experiencing from here on out is you're still going
to have an availability of food water place to sleep you know I'm talking about
you know the general consensus you know relative amount of peace relative amount
of wealth and all that and cosmic censorship going up you're not going to
be suffering anymore any less than you are now you see what I mean so once so
just make the best of it you know if you're gonna you know make a meal and
you know you can make it better by spending 10% or 20% more time or even
twice the time do it so you get used to it you know and all that so in other
words it's kind of like if you had to go back would you do it all over again you
do it the same way I do it a little better so why don't you start doing a
little better right now you get it right whatever it is you know if you're gonna
do laundry you know there's a stain on that shirt just take the time and get
the stain off so when after you do laundry sales day didn't come out well
you knew there was a stain there asshole make sure it's off before it goes in the
wash right don't count on the wash taking it out is what I'm trying to say
don't hope for the best do the best so bad going back to your studies and
getting a hang on the Hebrew what I would suggest is doing a cumulative
report if you've ever known any mid-level management or worked in
mid-level management other than the people that you know you're managing and
the people above you one of the things that their mid-level management managers
are tasked with is to write reports familiar with that you know when all the
employees go home okay so all right so we're not going to say anything you
haven't worked mid-level management I mean you know what you you're making
six figures and and you know you got a minimum of 50 to 100 people under you
the upper they have reports that they have to put together to see that
comparatively to the reports are written before where you know how they're going
right and and now it's gotten to when everything is so rigged and screwed up
that no one reads them anymore so what you do is when you read scripture take
notes and write a report on what you've learned even if it's just a few phrases
every time you study don't rely on your memory alone because when you go back to
three or four or six months after you've been taking notes you're like I don't
remember writing that oh yeah I need to remind myself of that point you see
right a lot very often people say I'm going to take notes on the on the show
you know the sonic events and I see that some of some people's you know
courteously sent me that I'm like that's not what I said that's totally
jibber-jabber would mean a part of it was what I said but that's not the point
you see mm-hmm that's a very good good point just take so what you read like a
lot of these old heads when I say oh yeah I get a wide margin borrowed Bible so
you could put the notes in the corner no don't do that because if you give the
lose the book you lose you know keep them separate you know you can do I
remember I didn't really get into it years ago I had a personal recorder I
just made recordings you know I'll just talk to him and listen to it with those
little micro cassettes are kind of annoying you know they cost like nine
bucks for a little tiny remember those little tiny things it was like a size of
match yeah so take notes I mean I've got a lot of notes but the problem with the
notes that I have is they change subject because I've worked with you know
acoustic reproduction water or petroleum restoration work construction
automotive ignition systems high voltage stuff studying scripture doing mining so
when I have notes for scripture guess what else is in there all that other
stuff right so people say we look at you know so yeah you're not gonna understand
them anyway I don't even understand them I mean I do but you know for scripture I
have to sift through it right so you take your own personal notes and here's the
thing from I'm not altruistic you know hope for the best or whatever but you
know if I think I've gone through enough summaries of what scripture is and the
gods and all that in less than a few minutes or an hour even in the past right
so you have the the picture of the jigsaw puzzle if you got a 1 million
piece jigsaw puzzle you still need that picture right right to help you you
don't really need it because what if all the pieces were white and they're
not and if all the pieces were white there's only after a certain matter of
time you're gonna see the patterns repeat anyway it'll make it really
difficult so when you the reason you use the photograph or the image on the cover
of the jigsaw puzzle as a reference is for fielding what I call fielding right
right so if you have a blue sky with a white cap mountain and the mountains
black and then a green grass the minute you see all the green pieces or parts of
you start fielding you start grouping them together all the white goes the blue
goes together right and then when you have the a piece that's let's say black
and then green you know while that the green is towards the bottom and the
black is towards the mountain and then you have black and white all that goes
up you see and you start gent your first thing is you start grouping your major
things and then you right fitting it together now one thing what do you hear
me talk the first thing I'd like to bring up in conversation even I did with
them I can mention names Ocelli the last time I brought up the guy nailed to a
cross wearing a diaper if you ever hear me speak that's the first thing I bring
up when we discuss scripture why because he's the one that's going to explain
and he's the center figure and in the center lampstand is that's where the
center of the book is him I don't know like you know I got I think someone put
in the chat Thomas or someone that mentioned book of Joshua you know well
who's the king who's the head of the hosts you know is the angel of the
Christ right you see so he so now when you understand the Christ is not this
thing that the church has put in front of you the sigil or whatever crap and you
understand that is the main spiritual being when it comes to in you know
inter interceding with man not the main hierarchy but the main interceder right
when you see things happening like who put the order on Jericho for the walls
coming down people think it was sound they're still idiots that even a history
channel a built a big speaker trying to knock a brick wall down it did at 170
decibels right and yeah stupid stuff it doesn't superscripture doesn't say that
the sound knocked the walls down the Elohim knocked the walls down anyway you
know it's like there's no burning bush I think you're familiar with that right
mm-hmm so right yeah yeah okay so you have to know who the Christ is if you
always forget it you're not going to understand scripture that's assured oh
how many people think the guy who nailed to a cross wearing a diaper is really the
Christ Oh most people right and how many out of those most how many understand
scripture none none doesn't matter what lip service you get they don't so don't
be one of them go through it quick you know so the shorthand on the fast way to
slap someone around get them out of their stupor if they survive it or you
survive it is identifying the real Christ right which is the the the largest
identity theft in the universe right or cosmic the identity of the Christ is
subject on one hand to the largest identity theft known to man but on the
other hand guess what how was he able to walk through people walk in front of a
crowd that wanted through a crowd and escape a crowd that wanted to throw him
over a cliff I saw a minute before he has the ability like men in black right
invisibility if you see if you see if you sat down if you knocked on your door
right now Bruce and he came and sat down here for three hours and he left and he
said you know what he looked like well I don't know he looked like a man right
that's it no other detail how tall was he well he wasn't too tall but he wasn't
short okay that's really detailed not you won't be able to you see so is it
to interrupt his presence in the mind or whatever form and never really does
speak about that either oh yeah you mean of course technique or whatever was no
the technique well put it let's put it this way other than having a phaser here
wouldn't you want to be invisible or you know not invisible to where if you're
not paying it not invisible to the point where if you actually if you're invisible
you can't see because you need that fleshy eye but to be like a memory you
know to be a really vague oh it sounds like what I want to be sometimes you
know because after a while you say why bother that's my thing from now on is
why bother you know and most people just sit there like lackeys by the way look
up the definition of lackey l-a-c-k-e-y and read it either at a mall just put it
in a search and the regular dictionary is fine yeah because we don't need to
know if it's French or German or Bulgarian or a baby seal or whatever but
you know I used to be I used to use that word a lot in the 80s when we used to
assemble crews of people and train them as though they'll be fine because you
know you work with them supervise them for weeks and months and you leave for
like half a day and you come back and everything's gone to shit you're like
how could it be how could it be they were doing great for six months and you
leave you know what I mean mm-hmm it's not bringing me l-a-c-k-y okay try that
one yeah it didn't work l-a-c-k-l-a-c-k-e-y or l-a-c-k-e-y yeah let's try
you only see there we go read it and you're running footman valet from middle
French l'acquiesce foot soldier footman servant a word of unknown origin perhaps
the old Provencal lackey see gluten covetous if you put it in a regular if
you okay hold on for a second if you just I also look at if you put it in a
regular browser search I'm let's see I'll just put in lackey and they usually
throw a Merriam-Webster definition a servant especially liveried for man
servant and then it gets more into it behave servile to you wait upon a lack
of somewhere lackey someone is not who does mental tasks or or menial tasks or
runs errands for another a server follower needs a boss right yeah yeah
so it's actually you you don't want to be what are they called the poppy
syndrome right which is you stand up you know the English say that mm-hmm and
you don't want to be when the world of hammers you don't want to be a nail but
the thing is essentially you're pretty much done for and it's so obvious what's
going to be coming in the next decade and a half or less right you might
capture yourself once in a while say well how come nobody else sees it right
but then you have to catch yourself again you know what I mean you catch
yourself again and you say no one else even sees how you don't absorb through
the intestines no one else is talking about how calories are absolutely
meaningless they tell you you know your body fuel you know like your body burns
up calories where mm-hmm you know stupid poop and travel aria yeah yeah
they don't know anything about the money system at all they just say well it's
fiat right it's not based on anything right well it's based on what I think of
the Persian water story every time they don't know how the weather works you
know they say the rains bring the the clouds are bring the rains but the
how they do the range in the cloud right yeah so 200,000 tons of water in the
cloud you know what happens when you have water vapor the gravity pulls it
down it's called fog there's no water in the clouds I mean they don't know
anything you mentioned that about watching a thunderstorm roll and I do
that every time I can you if you have if you have the right kind of polarized
glasses or polarized lenses I mean before they went mass production there's
a guy I knew who had a decommissioned military surplus yard and they actually
pulled apart an SR-71 I have some I shouldn't say what what I have from it
but I had some interesting optics right okay and you know like a you know like an
a six or eight inch lens that's finally ground for a spy plane I was tossing it
around the guys like you know that's thirty thousand bucks for that piece of
glass there I'm like oh okay but anyway so yeah so you know when you when you
have let's say a piece of glass that's polarized you know like mil-spec if you
hold that at the cloud or if you can get some really good aviators glasses that
are true polarization you know like not the cheap stuff right you'll see when
you look at the cloud you'll see no matter what color it is there is a dark
layer like I said you know as the clouds have a silver lining it literally looks
like a metallic shimmer underneath the cloud and there's a little dark sandwich
layer like mill of whatever thin it's almost unperceptible unless you're
someone tells you it's there and the what that's where the water is actually
forming just like a magician would do it you know but a magician is ledger domain
you know I'm not talking wasn't there someplace at the beginning in Genesis
where the mist rose up from the earth right I think yeah this is before that's
different oh okay oh this is for the plants yeah yeah yeah yeah that's before
the sixth day right yes so yes and then after also it's mentioned I was speaking
of someone also about there's a dark cloud surrounding the earth in the book
of Job I think it's called the NAFA off on off but anyway so basically you're
typical and even atypical you're exquisitely you know entitled classes
your professors your industry engineers scientists there don't know either any of
these things that we mentioned and there's the short list is a thousand
items by the way the long list you could say pretty much anything people are
interacting with are not familiar right with it so if there are so oblivious and
so central to everything quote-unquote everything with very little exception
right how the hell are they going to know prophecy it's not possible not
possible this is divine intervention which is coming which is possible by the
way and probable and going to be happening because there are places in
scripture where certain people are going to be given visions of certain things
you know with clarity right hmm so so yeah I think that the level of like no
more family our talk you know once Sam says oh you know you sound like a
Philistine now you curse a lot you're not polite you know look when I used to
listen to you like Shelley in the Greek you're older stuff and would Seth you
were really about I was like yeah so what you know it's all an act you know I
could what do you want me to be right right right you know this is war it's a
theater of war you know I'm not at war but you know you're in you know what do
you want me to say how do you want me to say it right I think when you're talking
to people that are going to be stomped like a roach in less than a decade and a
half yeah I think it's time to give them a little reality check you know yeah so
yeah but that but they have no sense of reality and they won't because of the
censorship they can't right it's not possible I've actually been around
people that teach a university and their feet in their own fields and I bring up
some points that are just obvious like an eight-year-old you know whether it's
chemistry whether it's a human body physics and they freak out I was once in
a parking lot speaking to some academics oh I was gonna I'm gonna
lecture on Saturday at the University of oh and I said well how about this this
and that oh no it's the Greek I gotta run to the car you know yeah yeah I'm
serious Wow so yeah I think getting stepped on is gonna be well-deserved
but but here's the interesting thing about all of this you ready think about
what I said earlier and this is the best advice you can get whatever you do do it
the best you can do it if you got a stain in your laundry don't wait for the
don't hope for it to come up remove it make sure and then do the laundry right
right yeah you know if you're gonna cook a meal and you hope that it comes out
well no just take a moment and make it come out well right you know if you're
gonna wax let's say a dark colored car and you look at your wax and it's white
and the car is dark look at some liquid shoe polish the liquid or pin drop it
in the wax and mix it up make it dark you know then polish the dark car with
the dark wax and watch what happens it looks like that just got painted you
know when I do a wax car I tone the wax and then people say oh is that a brand
new car no it's 15 years old you know it looks shinier than a brand new car right
because you know so you see what I mean it's just a point you know just a little
better yeah you know it's called toning so right anything you do yeah and don't
look for approval stop seeking approval you know if you have to have to ask
someone is it good or bad or how did I do it or whatever you're missing the
point you know because you that means that if you from the beginning you had
never considered that you were going to improve the the situation like you know
I can with Ocelli I said I try to leave people better off than I found them
right give them a little extra thing to think about or do or apply which is like
only three or four people can do anyway maybe it's like at the campsite you
always leave it looking better than when you came that's right yeah so you
do that anyway and then you don't need approval because if your help if you
know that the people don't know this and you can impart something whether it's
sonically or physically or even emotionally do it you know don't like
Jack Frisco says telling someone something is wrong doesn't tell them
anything right just evaluate it you go over and even what I tell people this is
not right I don't just say that walk away I say well this is you know right I give
an outline of what was discussed or how it should be or evaluate what was what
they're doing and show what was done correct and then and then what was
incorrect show them how to make it correct and then then there's no feeling
that they did anything wrong they just needed to do a little more and there's
no inadequacy or change the way to do it yeah right but if you're cosmically
here's the other thing I notice if you're censored cosmically whether it's
a little bit or a lot of Greek speak you're gonna run away you can't stand it
it's like those you know those insect repellents I think they're 27 K or 30 K
plug in the wall makes the high frequency you can't hear it yeah to the
typical human asshole the Greek speak is like that's like that repellent they got
to run away ah right so which is fine I actually that's that's a reality so the
the aspect of making mistakes understanding the Bible understanding
where you are at seeing how obvious the head it's so flipping obviously you know
what's coming and how it's going to come right but how can it be obvious when you
can't even pour piss out of a boot with instructions on the heel right that's
an old Texas saying right now because if you're looking for the instructions by
the time you just accessing the instructions the job is done you get it
it's one of those things so this is the majority of the people on the planet
it's a you know I don't think telling people God loves them where everything
is going to be all right is is righteous or proper anymore and it
hasn't been for a long time by the way so I'll tell you what God loves you
they're dug in pretty deep yeah the word love instead and the word yes the word
like God by the I mean the word love by the way I'm using God for anybody else
tuning in you know the word love means to do the right thing even when you don't
feel like it all right and how many people say well I don't feel like doing
this I'm not going to do it where's the love right like you ever see even in
Hollywood you know the guy who you know saves the lifeboat you know so the and
he drowns or whatever do you think he feels like drowning no you know he's
doing the right thing so next time you hear the word love just imagine it's
doing the right thing even if it inconveniences you or it's not your
desire you see that's what it means and that's what that's why you know people
say you know God loves you I mean they can't even define that they don't even
of course he does because otherwise it wouldn't be stomping you and putting you
through whatever but you're not going to if you start asking questions why is
there so much suffering war why is a newborn baby thrown in a hefty bag in
the dumpster how can you don't understand what's going on here you see and those
questions by the way I've been asked by many people I've even heard of people
being in prison camps Oh where's God allow this it's like oh you need to
study you know so he does it to his prophets as well so because you're in a
physical state but essentially anything else anything else pop up on that chat
or anything else you want to get into Bruce or otherwise I could do what Sam
calls a little Greek rant I'm gonna let you take it for a ride nothing in
chanting I'm I'm just fascinated by the information that you're you're giving
and I'd rather remain silent and listen well that's fine but I brought up the
news earlier have you been watching international news and especially the
Middle East and anywhere else it's all the you know all tied together now right
you notice in Jordan almost on time Jordan is having not yet but they're
having they're firing the Prime Minister and because they have a king right
basically they have a king that you know perpetuity to that family rules Jordan
and he appoints a government you know you can appoint a parliament whatever
you know sections of government legislative bodies judicial whatever so
he's starting to fire and and you know do you remember any discussions we spoke
about Jordan being broken up right yes in the past yeah no start watching
Jordan Hezbollah in Lebanon is making moves as various types of Hezbollah
there's a you know there's a Saudi Hezbollah there's a Lebanese one you
know they're different regions but they're they're going to have an
interesting ride Israel is going to walk through that place and pretty much hold
on to it most people are not familiar that all there was a actually an
occupation of Syria the current president of Syria now his father and I
had occupied Lebanon for many many years was kind of brutal there as well
and pulled out mostly are you familiar with the occupation of Lebanon by Syria
no no yeah okay well so Lebanon is one of these places always been occupied
anyway and not always but predominantly right in the past century or so is very
hard time you know if you lived in Lebanon there's various groups they have
the Christian group the Muslim group and various groups in there and you know
Syria was in there till the 70s they're supposed to pull out they didn't they
were kind of I wouldn't say high-level brutality but you know they you know
anyway so now it's going to be Israel it's going to go up through there and
Turkey is going to keep moving tearing up that area you know Syria Iraq right
all these things are past the springtime going into the summer growth
pattern and then we're going to see in the fall what gets torn down right if
you're going to have anything coming this fall it's going to be you know tear
down break down right so we'll see you know we'll see how it goes but I assure
you in the three and a half to five years that it'll be very different
political scene and all that very grim I would suggest because if you say well
Israel is going to go through March through Lebanon and stay there right or
they could actually influence a different legislative body or government
political body you know that's more favorable right you know but all this
influence that's going to be the expansion of Israel I'm not talking
about the greater Israel plan that they you know have been talking the Zionists
I've been talking about for a while this is different and also the breakup
of Jordan and still looking for a Syria to come one of the things that made me
go mm-hmm about a Syria was the US is the US military knows lackeys they're
putting up a bunch of temporary military bases on the Nineveh Plains without
permission they just showed up you know with their macaroni and cheese and
chicken ala King and their humvees and they started making some impromptu you
know just military bases in Nineveh recently and they asked the Iraqi
government what are they doing there well don't worry because they can't set
up a base unless they get our permission but did they get your permission no you
know it's kind of like one of those all lackeys in there right now they're all
just censored and the they're all going to be like finger puppets to the gods
right that are sent down to do what they have to do so things to watch yeah
on the rest of the front you know here's the thing like I told the wife every so
often you know the food qualities no matter how much good food we try to get
is going down down down recently I got a Trader Joe's organic rice that you know
just on a pinch I usually try to buy it in bulk I couldn't cook it in other
words I so I think there's like it was hard as if it wasn't cooked then I cooked
it again it still didn't cook as if it was made out of plastic and then the
next time I soaked it for an hour and cooked it was still uncooked I was like
this rice is uncookable what did they do shift to like a non-human grade rice
strand a straight strain or something Oh you see and so I don't know if I'm very
sensitive to things like that not peculiarly sensitive like allergies were
but I noticed changes a quality quality changes and I just say well a
couple of years it's gonna start getting rough on the quality and you know it's
interesting as you know that I rebroadcast the past sonic events on on
the stream one when we're not doing live and I had the fringe on in one of your
old sonic events and they were talking about the laboratory meat and I think it
was I think it was a fringe but it was a show where he started out by discussing
laboratory meats now being created and most likely in the markets and it just
kind of sparked my memory when you're talking about the race is like oh my oh
yeah it'll be you look start getting it'll get to the point where life will
start to become difficult for everyone but acceptable and noticeable by some
when I say some like three or four people yeah so yeah so what else in the
news you know I think I've spoken about animal attacks we know that's on the
rise more than it's it's there are more animal attacks than are duly being
reported if you know what I mean if you know how to if you know how to and no
one is it grab that bull by the horns upon attended and said look there's a
rise of animal attacks right right but there is and the other thing is you know
there's a volcanoes going off yeah yeah that shows just getting in your mind
there's asteroids comets hitting the earth or asteroids recently yeah that's
in your mind just get used to it it's going to be another thing reported on
that interestingly yeah I was like a five it was a 10-foot asteroid yeah yeah
I think it was it might have been reduced even smaller than that they
just estimated the 10 probably but still you get used to it you've already been
primed back in 2011 2012 with the Ellen in and the excuse me the other ones
that's already in the back of your mind it's going to be more and more normal to
me it's none of it is normal because I know what's coming I don't know how it's
coming I don't know exactly when but I do know that the the the times that are
broken up it's going to get more intense as we get towards the end right and and
people will be so modeled mentally or spiritually into everything's going to
be okay right that no matter what happens at that point those they're still
going to be hopeful of course hmm so again I wanted to touch back if to the
jigsaw puzzle and the picture on the on the on the box as a reference right when
you get a jigsaw puzzle when you're studying scripture and your grab let's
grappling for or trying to reach for definitions are you not not you Bruce
but in general is a rhetorical question are you you feel victorious when you
learn what a word means or do you feel victorious when you get more meaning to
the overall story is the question you see because there are people by the way
who are Hebrew reader Hebrew speaking educated in Hebrew who can't still get
the meaning of scripture for example I seldom speak with someone who's from
Israel I actually frequently not seldom about once a week or every other week
and they had not read scripture and since they heard some Greek speak a
year or two ago they started they picked it up say I could read Hebrew I could
just read it straight out of the Tanakh you know and because they were raised
secular right I think you guys are familiar with the story in Israel if
you're religious rabbi runs your life so most people say I'd rather be secular
keep those assholes away you know what I mean right they're not holy men they're
little Nazis no pun intended you know but the and I mean that more truly in a
sense because they are Nazis were not fascist it was socialists right right so
so you know most of these people that are religious leaders are socialist
right because they get a group together you know it's group groupthink as long
as they're at the top but when this person was reading scripture they come
back to me you know in our conversations yeah it's basically just like you say
yeah the the Elohim you know the gods basically say this is what you want you
to do if you agree to it then you do it if you don't do it we'll tell you you're
not doing it will give you plenty of time to straighten up and if you don't
then well you know the rest is on you because I'm gonna you know nail you with
it now right that's what that's what I hear coming back to people that are
familiar with the original they could read you know not the interlinear they
read the script straight up Hebrew but they still don't get the story you know
the connections and all that but they you know completely because they have
to meditate on it once they download it you see I hope that was a inspirational
example because here's someone whose native tongue is Hebrew and comprehends
reading it but they still don't get the full import of what's going on because
it needs to be discussed in to meditate on it they need to do read more I said
what about this so I need to read more to discuss that you know so what do I
keep saying go through it as fast as you can to get it all downloaded you ever
want to download something on the computer and you see the progress bar
right come on already download already you know what I mean
yeah so I can use it not now but later so get it in you as or past you know you
ever go on a road trip for the first time and the second time you have to do
it even if it's a long road trip you're like that's not so bad because you're
familiar with the road right and once it's a regular commute truck drivers are
interesting that way you know if you hang around with truck driver and you
want to do a two-hour drive to them it's like just like going around the
block right so it's a matter of what you're used to but essentially again
just to recap the gods have a plan to keep humanity within its own let's just
say human gestures influenced by certain entities that are not your friends but
will always portray to be your friends how many times have you heard people say
I thought he was my friend right and you your biggest limitation believe it
or not other than your censorship and how moronic people are is your physical
body and when you once you get the emotional part which is impossible to
have the emotions that you do without a physical body right mixed with the
physical body and you start asking questions again I'm repeating this theme
tonight why is there so much suffering war and harm to the physical body you
need to start putting it together that maybe the gods don't care about that too
much did you ever stop and think about that asshole I tell people you know
because they don't care about your condition right now you have to go
through a certain amount of time yes you can pray for help yes you and it's
exactly what will be happening you'll be praying for help you get it doesn't mean
you're going to get it right so you're you're kind of like in a situation where
people in general and have been for thousands of years where there is the not
just the river in Egypt denial but combine that with the censorship I can
combine that with the various cultures right and you have humanity as you do
and it's the end of humanity 1.0 or 1.5 I should say but nonetheless I would
suggest that when you run into any body of information get to handle the all
information in context by understanding the conclusion right you're gonna read a
scientific document on what viruses are and it's a thousand pages long well you
should peek at the conclusion because the conclusion says even after all this
experimentation we still don't know don't think you're gonna read the whole thing
and know you see right that means it's a waste of time if you're looking for the
solution you can read it for the experience I remember we talked about
failures and but the thing is you're always going to fail researching viruses
because they don't exist as their as your you know they've been categorized
anyone can do a slight search and find that virology is part of toxicology and
toxicology is liver function it's basically your liver you ever take the
garbage out and and you have a hole in the bag and you take the guy you come
back to this drip all over is that all the bag was leaking from all that beer
that was in there whatever you know I mean you gotta mop it up that's what
viruses that's what they're calling viruses essentially so when you get to
the conclusion and you find out who what the main aspects are of any body of work
while you're dealing with the body of work or thinking about that subject you
have a better more realistic handle on the subject matter
when I run into college students in their textbooks I'm like so what do you
think of that Phil I don't know I'm only about a quarter of the way through the
book said asshole on the weekend don't you just grab one textbook and page
through the whole thing read the whole textbook not read it directly but page
through all of it go look at all of it so you know what's coming you might want
to drop out of that class like this will get some credits fool right right they
don't do that anyway but you know so the the understanding basically is when we
talk about the scriptures of the Bible or whatever can be unsurmountable
because you have the various aspects of going back to the original text which is
not even it's been also the original text has been adulterated slightly right
but then you have all this information because it's one of the most popular
subjects on earth that you have to undo in your own mind right because you've
been loaded up with bullshit right and then you might want to study the
interlinear and you see that it's not your language but you're familiar with
right but even with all that work you still may not get anything out here's
proof of it by the way I used to seek out biblical scholars you know I figured
when I wanted to get into scripture 1516 years ago so this is easy just like
anything you seek an expert in the field use them for mentorship for a
little while to put you on the right track right wrong boy like I said they
might have something they worked on for 50 years that they share with you and
book that just saved you you say thank you very much
you know I mean and you move on but essentially I have I thrown in the part
about the cosmic censorship is going to be lifted but then it's going to be so
thick meaning very specifically so everyone follows what the Antichrist and
his crew is saying and you're going to fall for that deception yes you do yeah
yeah okay so in other words right now that hasn't hit yet so right now there
could be discussions but when this young fellow he's in his early 20s about 20
something or one or so in the 21st year when he rises to prominence anyone I
assure you anyone and everyone listening to me will fall for it right so right
you know so there'll be absolutely no reason to be speaking then or before the
even slightly before then that's how powerful this is going to be right that's
yeah yeah I was even a recent conversation I said if I you know how to
go bet in Las Vegas who's going to fall for the Antichrist I bet everyone that I
know everything I had is going to fall for it that's a very safe bet how do I
know well that's what it says I might even fall for it right you have to be
really really aware and also you have to be given a few ounces of insight you
know cosmically into it right because it says even the very elect might even fall
for it that's how convincing it'll be right Wow so the Greek speak lackeys
that sit back and like what the Greek is saying and all that you don't do a lot
of homework are definitely going to fall for it you know because here you're
going to have a world system that's going to be talking about being lawful
and using biblical law right so you know so oh that's great I've been looking for
non-mixed fiber socks finally great this guy's great who's the Greco that
asshole now we got the real thing now look right you see what I mean right
there's gonna be a real real yeah you're gonna have to the thing is you'll be
able to enjoy most of the things that are being said and perhaps done I
wouldn't say all of them until it starts really getting buck wild like they say
down south and yeah everyone's going to fall for it and that's what I'm talking
about now is like 2025 2026 2027 right yeah oh that's so far away no it's not
blink twice it'll be summertime I'll be end of summer quick oh look at them you
know look at all of you and I are I went by oh yeah years ago years ago
someone says it's gonna take about two years like oh that long now it's a two
years oh that's fine yeah that's just right around the corner now hmm ten
years ago I remember like a year ago right what you call the Pope's work
schedule 2008 in the summer I could tell you exactly what I was doing where I was
what up what projects I was on what I was thinking what I was eating what I
was wearing everything like it was a you not even a year ago right so even 20
years ago I have you know extreme detail why because it doesn't seem like the
distant past at all does it seem to you ten years ago distant past blue no it
doesn't even seem distant right it seems like well within reach of your cognitive
memory maybe a couple weeks sometimes yeah but yeah exactly yeah so that's why
you know recent you say like Sam saying man I don't know Greek you're getting a
little brash and crass and Philistine like I'm like yeah screw it what I
haven't gotten much support or just a couple of pats if I got any pats on the
back for Greek speak it's because I did it myself I mean I do appreciate whoever's
contributed for cigarettes and coffee and the kind words and all that about
seven eight hundred emails and all that but you know that and two dollars get
you on the New York City subway right basically if I had it if I had to rely on
donations for subway fare I'd be walking right so clearly this kind of talk or
advancement of this kind of subject matter is not wanted right because if it
was for every moron that was listening to me would tell ten other morons and
they would tell another ten and we'd have something going where we could
actually form not a group or an organization but form a place where
resources can be pooled and things can be advanced you know something like an
order because these groups and organizations usually say that it's
usually something that has a head right you want to have a guy honest with you I
can't find one person that'll that would take the time to even listen we're just
you know and I'm thinking of this hypothetic you know just if I were
supposed to do it or want it to do it yeah they're not right no it's cosmic
yeah it's cosmic I'm not blaming the people that are listening or whatever
this stuff is so poignant and so true that when I say it's cosmic and it's
beyond human culture beyond human control there's your proof mm-hmm
because I you know I have considered it many times but then I just kind of sit
back and think well well here's the thing cognitively cognitively and
intuitively I know this would never work I mean on a scale where it would grow
not now no and I've also I've also prayed on it and cast lots and every
time I did it it was no if I cast lots 50 times it was no every time right you
see so I'm not stupid I'm not naive you know sometimes Sam will tell the people
say oh you thought you were so optimistic well yeah that was an act you
why is it an act well because you know when you're going out in public you want
to look like a slob right now not that I want to look like a slob now but I think
people need to be hit across the head with a wet newspaper a little bit more
than they have been in their daily lives so and I know you're getting hit across
the head from your ignorance based on whatever personal relationships career
out there in the street and at home whatever I know you're getting hit
across the head left and right but in terms of this subject matter there's no
pull you know it's just like you know either get it or you don't if you don't
get it just screw you and if you get it screw you too yeah yeah mm-hmm
it's harsh you know it's like oh what is God love so much suffering okay so
it's pretty evident that the gods don't mind a hundred million dead in these
world wars or in America five to ten million outwardly killed by attorneys
and doctors right and no one's saying anything I mean they're saying but no
you know there's no you know anything direction to curb that right so why do
the gods allow it because what are they killing what are they destroying physical
stuff you're gonna be brought back later chill man relax you'll be fine yeah but
it hurts now and your emotions about that are contrary to the cognitive or
the knowledge of that because you have a physical body no matter how much of a
good mood you're in if you get up at 3 in the morning and get a glass of water
and you hit your big toe on the kitchen chair it hurts your emotion you're
gonna not gonna be so happy at that moment you know because you're
physically attached to it your physical body I mean why do you think people do
drugs because it affects the physical which then affects the mind and like
fresco says and I've been saying for a long time I can't do drugs because it I
find it to be painful you know if I take a hit off of what they call cannabis or
marijuana I'm like oh shit why did I do that ah now I got to wait like four
hours to feel good again so it's crap to wear off you know I mean no so but the
the aspect of knowing what's coming doesn't mean that you're going to be
better off what makes you better off because of you knowing of knowing what's
coming is that you you'll be better off now because what you're going to be
doing is striving for doing the best that you can right now in that capacity
you see in other words don't put aside don't say like oh well this is how I
always do things and it works out sometimes sometimes it doesn't know take
a break and see how you can make it work out favorably for you and everyone else
around you every time and you'll notice that it doesn't take that much more
effort in the beginning it might just like going to the gym right so what am I
talking about food clothing shelter food clothing shelter better food better
clothing better shelter you see and in order to maintain better food better
clothing better shelter however you're gaining the credits that you're gaining
you might have to be more efficient at that you know get more credits per hour
or however whatever agreement you have right so you can have the better food
and clothing and more free time to do those things right you know I mean right
yeah and in terms of health that ties in also in terms of health ultimately just
pray that your death is quick swift and painless but the longevity aspect I mean
what are you gonna you're gonna want to be around for the next 14 years that's
fine if you want to but you you're not you're not if you're 30 now you're not
going to be old right you might actually here's the thing 10% might survive in
actually 10% might survive what's coming and live in the next 30 or 40
years until the entropy begins to be reversed right but it's going to be you
know how they say hell on earth for 30 or 40 years after they were the Elohim
after the gods show up I never got into details on that I don't have many
details but what is given is enough I mean there it's not going to be like the
magic hour when they show up there's gonna be a lot of destruction and
they're not gonna fix it once they destroy it doesn't say anywhere they're
gonna rebuild anything does it no right it's gonna be like anyone who does
survive is gonna be in shell shock for about 30 or 40 years so yeah that's
sobering moment I don't want I don't want anyone to believe what I'm saying
at all unless they unless they could start validating the data and the
information and then you file it away as a known possibility and that's it and it
is a good belief if the information is good right correct you have the bus
schedule and it says the bus will be here in an hour well it's a pretty good
belief to say the bus will be here an hour because it's on the schedule and
they tend to be reliable is it here now nope did I see the bus nope anyone else
know about the bus see the bus nope doesn't matter you got the information
you know it's just data information that's years ago I saw people even on
consulting I say listen just this is the information ABCD or whatever is sorted
well you know it's communicated on an eighth grade level or less file it away
for later right how many times you heard me say that file it away for later can't
use it now what you can use now is food clothing shelter up it you don't get
start to eat better start to think better be lawful find out what God you
get your law from you know these kind of stuff right that's what you do right now
whatever you're interested in find out really what it's about here's the other
thing um you let's just a little segue you want to really you want to do this
Bruce you want to really have a laugh okay you want to I want you to go to
your browser and put in MIT Massachusetts Institute of Technology
just MIT nuclear physics curriculum and I want you to read it and just a preface
before you get it's going to be quantum this quantum that Schrodinger's
principles you know Schrodinger these guys were mystics right getting high on
acid and opium and talking about occult mysticism right I'm serious you know
bumping particles and quantum bullshit right you know you ever notice their
stuff electron proton gluon muon moron how it all rhymes you know anyway
morons in training go to the MIT I'm not so we're not going to mention any names
here just MIT nuclear physics curriculum see if you could find this I want you to
read off the courses and we're gonna have a good laugh okay because years ago
they say it's not rocket science you know it's kind of like a double you know
thing but if you tell any of these idiots that are on the planet today that
you are a nuclear physicist from MIT they go oh he's so smart right so let's go
let's let's go read their curriculum nuclear nuclear physics curriculum yeah
graduate or undergraduate doesn't matter it's all the same you want to go to PhD
yeah it doesn't matter go undergraduate first or graduate courses yeah we'll try
master of science yeah that's fine okay let's get to overview the object of the
master's degree program is to give the student as thorough knowledge of some
so just read the curriculum do they have bullet points for the curriculum so with
a number next to it you they do not this I know okay
here we go yeah nuclear reactor physics one engineering of nuclear reactors
probability and its applications to reliability and quality control and risk
assessment modern physical metallurgy or radiation damage and effects in nuclear
materials introduction to plasma physics MHD theory of fusion systems fusion
energy engineering principles for fusion reactors principles of plasma
diagnostics nuclear technology plasma is essentially high plasma is essentially
ionization yeah yeah and by the way when it says nuclear nuclear reactor design
is do you have a tea kettle right you know the concept of a tea kettle how you
heat water yeah that's all it is good yeah see managing nuclear technology
nuclear non-proliferation nuclear science and engineering laboratory
quantum theory and radiation interactions radiation biophysics
non-invasive imaging and biology and medicine nuclear science and engineering
laboratory and then we're into thesis research department regulations for
thesis yeah that's pretty much into that so the undergraduate though I
believe is you know when you first get your feet wet in there here we go under
undergraduate went freshman they're going to probably they get into quantum
physics morons gluons prove you know morons and they get into Schrodinger and
they get all mysticism stuff that in other words the people that all that
everything that you have that's useful from a hairdryer to airplane engines all
that has nothing to do with what they're teaching that everything that you have
that's useful in the world even today that's being developed was developed by
people like Tesla people like Steinmetz you know not Einstein not quantum
nothing that's why nothing is happening but go to the undergraduate so because I
just I just burst out laughing looking at Stanford looking at MIT here we go
there was Chicago thermal fluid engineering one physics to calculus is
the introduction to computer science we're really at the beginning here this
freshman year let's get down to the juicy stuff physics three physics to
calculus different equations you're talking to new equations like mother
nature like mother nature as a calculator yeah go ahead right social
problems of nuclear energy electronic signal and measurements applied nuclear
physics nuclear system design projects neuron and science and reactor physics
yeah so tea kettle how to heat up water yeah how to heat up water yeah
probabilistic systems analysis complex variables and applications let's get
into some juicy stuff here thermal fluids radiation biophysics nuclear
asking why a bucket ask them why a bucket of water weighs more than a
bucket of air right anyway you know we're just get mostly nuclear analysis
stuff quantum theory radiation interactions is that the one with the
Schrodinger yeah yeah yeah anyway you rock whatever that is yeah when you get
into the meat of what they're outlining like when you go to nuclear physics for
this or whatever and you start looking into it a little deeper you're like what
a crock of crap no wonder they're not getting anything done what they're doing
is looking at the plants that were built 50 years ago and painting and making
them a different shape and color they cannot develop new technology it's kind
of like the car theory then you know mm-hmm
develop a new car every year have you know there's a guy I was I was going to
be introduced to him by someone that knows him personally is so he's out in
California I was not interested because I know none of this stuff because these
are people want to do stuff to make the world a better place when I hear that I
go away the opposite direction and I'll go home and rearrange clip my nails and
take a bath and rearrange a sock drawer then go look at what they're doing or
but I will be familiar with it here's something called the tiny but mighty
engine so it's the T what you know tiny but mighty it's a Hispanic extraction is
his name he has a small rotary motor I mean you could basically pick it up it
doesn't look bigger than I don't like a round cylinder let's say we have a foot
and a half in diameter and he has it next to a you know eight foot long diesel
engine it's the same power right because it's it's like a rotary engine
but it's not based on the rotary principle of the road of the wine kill
rotary it's based on another thing and this is designed to do went around almost
somewhat like in a triangle or something yeah well the rotary is like that yeah
yeah wine kill has that shape but this is similar to that and the problem this
was developed and or thought of 75 years ago but they didn't know how to do the
timing on it and he came up with the timing on it right so and it's
perfected it's ready to go but no manufacturer will touch it right because
if you brought the reason there's several reasons why by the way anyone in
any field that's in dimension the manufacturers go moot moot when they see
a vast improvement the other reason why it's called NIH not in-house development
and they don't want to do patents but I'm going to give you a have a I wish I
could get if it was 15 years ago I'm going to tell you just remind me what I
would done 15 years ago regarding patents but the other thing is if you
bring in this newer stuff to the people that were trained at MIT and all these
other you they don't they look at there they don't know what to do with it
there it's beyond it's outside of the scope of what they've been trained you
see you know I mean because that's why you when you read that curriculum like
the people who really design like nuclear devices for engineering or
weaponry they don't use any of the stuff that they've learned in school at
all you can't it doesn't work right the the the handling and the development of
the materials you know the radioactive materials they don't use any of the
stuff at all that was in the schools you see you know this all so don't the
patents again let's sorry this is how you mess up the industry in a good way
what happens is just you if you have an idea get into a publisher in the trade
magazine or whatever and have them write about it even though it hasn't been
developed yet and if someone a corporation wants to patent it they're
not going to give them the patent because it's that idea has been
published before not patented people I'm familiar with the patent office how
they work okay so let's say you invent okay yeah they tell you if you read the
patent law it's not what people think as a major well everything is
misunderstood but this is how patents are misunderstood also if you have an
idea of you know a thing that you know is a can opener remote control and a
and a beard trimmer and it doesn't exist if you get someone in like the
Washington Post to put a little blurb or you put an ad for it even though it's
imaginary if someone wants to go patent it later they're not going to grant it
because you had made it public prior there's several examples of that like a
digital loudspeaker guy wrote an article about that in the 80s and there
are people that wanted the patent office will not grant because they're citing
this article from like 1986 and he says I totally screwed them up and no company
will invest in developing it if they're not going to get a patent on it so what
it's about time that anyone or the thing is that not anyone has ideas but what I
wanted to do was start a website and plug it so it has high visibility you
know what I mean anyone that has any idea just start publishing on the website
and you know make sure the patent office knows about your website to totally put
the damper on this patent madness that companies do because they're not going
to issue them a patent if it's already been published right so if you got any
cockamamie ideas technological or otherwise let's start publishing them so
like the scumbags of GM or Apple or whatever want to go and get a patent
they're gonna say no you can't because it's already been published you see what
I mean at least everyone has access to it now right so I know some inventors
and they're all scumbags by the way every single one of them that I've ever
met the only reason I associate with them is to help them develop their
products because I think they have merit but if you want to talk about poor
character greedy assholes if you know anyone who's gotten a I was just gonna
ask that if how much greed but and they and all none of them I've never met of it
that knows anything about how money works or even the general field of what
they're patented I'm serious and this is without exception so I think it's time
that I mean some of these industries and these knowledge-based things get kicked
in the shins so if you got some strange idea whoever is listening whoever go to
a centralized place that is well-known could create it and publish it online
right and get it so you know people see it is there a margin of how many people
have to see this in order to be considered published if the pot and I
think but the example that I gave anyone could look this up digital loudspeaker
there's a guy wrote an article in the 80s and he says no no company will be
issued a patent because he really screwed it up because he was just joking
when he did it and no company's gonna spend all this investment if they can't
get a patent on it they're not because anybody could do it right because they're
greedy assholes right now it's not because they're greedy assholes like I'm
pointing a finger it's the culture it's like I'm not gonna mention names and I
went to a Shelley's chat room earlier tonight he's talking about about Trump I
like why what's wrong why are you mad at Trump because he has more shrunken heads
than you you see they don't people don't see what's going on they're all dick
heads so the whole thing is if it's that simple to throw a monkey wrench
into this bullshit industry of that humanity has created do it you got a
crazy idea something that was you know a dildo of vibrators trims your beard
washes your carp and it's semi reasonable go ahead and publish it so
these guys later can't get a patent on it right so at least it's it's open at
open source you know I mean right anyway but you tell again it's like the
MIT I go to physics degree at a physics degree at MIT yeah right yeah in my book
you're qualified you know I'd have to watch you washing the car you know
because you're just a moron in training but but the thing is when you when you
make it all open source like that it you know it has it's a double-edged sword
also because it won't come into development right but on the second
hand it's open sourced already you see you know you don't have this restriction
see when people get patents and you know anybody if you go to the patent
office by the way you can copy anything for yourself you just can't put it into
commerce you can't manufacture it and sell it right and mass-produce it or
whatever right but you can make one yourself there's no infringement there
now some people have the misunderstanding that there is I've
looked at some forums regardless very so you can't do it because it's patent is
not sure oh yeah you're right I can't oh yes you can asshole you can do it you
just can't go into business with it you see so anyway the aspect of of doing
patents is limiting the accessibility to that for everyone right how many times
like for example Apple if you have a good idea and you patent it Apple will
will not use it unless they take over the patent they don't do little royalties
there was a big that which there's a small company that makes compute computer
speakers only that small company there there's a few of them they're very
popular those guys tell me was that the one with the cell phone no they what
they did is they came up with the iPod before the iPod the mp3 on a without any
rotating moving devices you basically you know stationary memory on a chip for
music great great and Apple said that they did it first and there was like no
way because these guys have done it first on Apple rewarded they got a four
hundred and fifty million dollar reward from Apple because they have Apple lost
to them so it's just a bunch of guys and they got 450 and a half a billion from
Apple or something and now they just make computer speakers it's one of the
computer speaker companies that are popular
Wow that's all yeah so these are these are treacherous people you know people
don't know I mean occasionally the it gets out you know like here's a I saw a
clip with Trump this is just an example because I give political and apolitical
examples what during the debate someone had asked Trump you know you had
bankruptcy three times what about you know responsibility there Trump says
that's okay because these financial people they're killers they're you're
ruthless people and he shut up right away you know yeah you think Apple and
Microsoft all these people take over industries and do what they're in Google
because they're kind and nice you know in the British sense you know or
whatever no they're ruthless you know downright cutthroat yeah yeah and
getting an understanding of so not to go off on the patent as we're getting an
understanding of what is controlling people because you see the word patent
that there's a controlling element to it doesn't it oh we can't do this
patented bullshit you know you can't do it commercially and actually you can if
you understand how to go around the patent there are people you know and you
should because there shouldn't be you know if there's a beneficial technology
it should not be limited it should be open-sourced right right and yeah and a
lot of people that I have discussions with that are inventors I said well you
know I can help you improve or we just have discussions but you know you really
should be oh no no it's Pat it's patented it's under license like yeah
whatever so this is how people are getting rid of greed aspect to you know
that's never gonna happen yeah I mean I want more I want the most
shrunken heads is what I hear them saying exactly yeah the the same thing
as with the Bible there's someone had once sent me there was an audio clip or
YouTube or written one of the Kings in England when you know the Church of
England broke away from the Catholic Church so they can Henry can get a
divorce as the story goes and paraphrasing and when the King James and
other Bibles were made available to the public and they were read he says
remember this Bible is copy written by the King and the Church of England it's
only there to inform your conscience in other words you can't use it right all
right for yourself you know you can't go out and do what you want to do with it on
it for start your own groups or whatever with it so but anyway did I ever discuss
the shorthand of what the purpose of Scripture is because it's not futile
it's meant to be comprehended but it's not to be comprehended by everyone you
know what the sole purpose of that is by the way I'm suggesting here this is not
an opinion it's a strong suggestion is so that later on after the resurrection
there's no excuse no one can say we never had access on what your intentions
were yeah right yeah because if the gods wanted you to know and everyone to
believe in them they can just show up every hundred years on a global level
tell everyone on your knees where your masters will be back in a hundred years
do the law you get it how easy would it be for them to do that wouldn't be it
would be no effort for them because they would do it by proxy they could create a
whole other set of beings that would be their doubles to come and do it you see
which is lawful by the way as long as they come in their name right yeah right
yeah and can prove and can prove it how do you prove it well you see that village
over there boom pink blue light and they're all vaporized okay yeah you come
in his name because that's what people understand right Wow so you know or turn
water into wine right right mm-hmm so there you go and I think just you know
harken back to the Greek speak it's not Greek speak is this is not a this is a
leaderless concept in other words anyone can say what I say however they
want to say it and make it their own I'd prefer they do that because you know you
really have to be able to do it forward and backward otherwise you fall flat on
your face right like sometimes I ask from Ed can you speak on Queen of Heaven
Queen of Heaven well the Queen of Heaven is a prop was a problem for the
Israelites big-time Queen of Heaven was something mentioned it's actually
mentioned as Queen of Heaven in the book of Jeremiah I think it's mentioned
somewhere else there are other attributes to her like the asterod a
start day which is the Cleopatra's needle he also says in one of the books
why do you put that up my nose are you familiar with that verse no I'm not no
okay that is associated you'll see it in full blast I can't say specifically
it's the justice people you know the justice crew you know the the goddess
but I can tell you specifically outright the Catholics call a rena de cielo
especially in the lat which literally means the Queen of Heaven that's what
you see the Virgin Mary or that she's the mother of God
sky goddess worship throughout the Mediterranean yeah right and that's the
current Catholic chief deity by the way yeah and now if you go back to the text
and I believe it's Yirmeyahu Jeremiah the Israel had worshiped or had that as
a chief deity within the locales of Judea and parts of Israel Israel had
gone away pagan way before Judea did but and they would light fires for her
and bake cakes for her for hundreds of years during the time of judges and even
the Kings and they said we prospered under her now you're telling us that
we're going to be sacked by the you know Babylonians we don't believe it you see
I would suggest she's still around now there's a multitude of goddesses it's
it's not complex but it's not singular in the book of Zechariah there is more
than one female spiritual figure one of them is specifically carried to Babylon
or Shinar in a basket are you familiar with that no no right and we know that
most angels are male so here we have several female several meaning three
portrayed that and one of them is put in a basket and carried by birds let's
say but there are other of these you see female entities that straight that man
goes after now the thing about that you could say is how predominant is the
Catholic Church pretty predominant right actually it's funny listening to
Christians Christians who argue that they're not Catholic I'm like what a
dummy what do you think all that stuff came from you'll have the same holidays
the same concept you know the guy nailed to a cross wearing a diaper right the
same does Pope's work schedule so how are you different you know okay you're
not your vanilla and chocolate chip instead of chocolate okay but you still
ice cream you see so there are one of the things is prosperity and and that
reigns over has been given to have because how much prosperity and power
does the Catholic Church have as having her as a key chief deity quite a bit as
a matter of fact that you heard of the Jesuits and the bat is not
conspiratorial this is actually easily accessible all be it being on the
conspiratorial and that the Jesuits have influence in world government and
intelligence agencies right you familiar with that maybe maybe not they're
Catholic that's the Pope's army so you see that their chief God is this Queen
of Heaven so that's what I could say about that I started going when I
started just like anyone when you get into a topic of spiritual you want to
look at everything right like the spiritual world right you look at
everything but then when you notice that there's a hierarchy and the difference
between the high-level stuff and the low-level stuff is so far apart that you
don't want to dwell on the low-level stuff and you want to get to know more
about the high-level stuff right because when you dwell on the low-level stuff you
fall for the mental modeling that you get out there like how many people speak
badly against Catholicism but yet still think they go to heaven or hell when they
die or think that that you know the Christ is this guy nailed to a cross
wearing a diaper right or was born on Christmas most of them still do so it's
futile when you get stuck in that low-level stuff right you're not going
to you're not going to get the truth there's people all over the internet
that are bad-mouthing the papacy and the you know the the entire aspect of
Catholicism and they have no other than this stuff that they make up or they
look at each other what they're going to say next none of it is you know viable
for research the none of them know them you know how the the the higher
level stuff works you know the ones that are get stuck in the the study of you
know the Catholicism and the you know what I mean so I found out with my own
my own personal decision not to get into it too much and become an expert on the
Queen of Heaven or Astaroth and all that other stuff because the only people that
feel like they would benefit from that are a bunch of Muppets like do you would
you feel let's say personally Bruce let's just have a personal thing here
for a moment would you feel more benefit from talking about the Most High's ways
or the Astaroth's ways of Queen of Heaven's ways it's a no-brainer I'd be
up on that's no brainer exactly so why would you spend a lot of time on that
because in other words the the world is the there's such a much wider and deeper
wider and deeper body of knowledge to gain from the higher aspects of the
spiritual world in the lower aspects again it don't trust what I'm saying go
ahead and research people that are quote-unquote experts on the occult
mystical they're pretty dumb not to mention names I'm not going to get into
it I was going to you know who they are the classic ones you know they got the
granddaddy of them Jordan Maxwell and the before him the Blavatsky's and all
they're all idiots ask them to define you know anything you know money the
soul the spirit time anything they can't because they're there they've been put
here to satisfy a need which is the people find out about something they
don't want to go along with it they want to find more and they stay in the low
level crap right the David Ike's the you know what I mean right no project
Camelot's the all that low-level crap let me ask you are there more five-star
restaurants or there are more McDonald's yeah and why why because is it is it in
balance yes it's accommodating the people don't want the better restaurant
they want the McDonald's how do I know well duh that's a fact now you might
pull a standard to a human asshole aside and say hey I see obviously you guys
want the McDonald's better than the rest was no we don't know we don't know we
don't know we do bullshit because if you didn't you wouldn't go there and it
wouldn't exist you see you know I mean don't listen to what they say watch what
they do what else pretty much in on that one pretty quiet hmm that's fine so
there's about 10 to 15 seconds to get down the stream so that's fine also to
Sam said he might be interested in doing something tomorrow he's gonna get
some more internet access if you're available tomorrow know what your
schedule is like I think he had a couple of things you wanted to mull over see
tomorrow I go in late and then I'd be up early somewhat early I could probably
squeeze in a couple hours easy that's no big deal yeah I think take it we took a
couple of months off I did I was actually involved with things that and I
actually sat back and see what you know if anyone's gonna not hopefully
hopefully someone was gonna do something no one really did anything with it so I
just go seasonally you know this is getting into the middle of summer watch
how things are growing you know and just let out some information a little bit
more every time slightly different so personally everybody cover your ears I'm
just gonna tell Bruce the public at large even these streams chat whatever
people email me are not ready for more stuff that's my decision you know
somebody wants to tell me what people want you just say it anyway and let the
people decide I said nah it's still operating on a real low level the whole
the whole thing and even if I were to die tomorrow and it didn't speak anymore
I'd be quite satisfied because I've said a thousand times more than anyone
else has period at all on all these subjects on the and yeah my being cocky
that's your problem if you think I am somebody said a condescending or whatever
if you has the interesting thing I got a comment about being condescending if you
feel like this kind of talk is condescending well maybe because you're
one of the morons you know what I mean they always get offended you know what I
mean I remember by the way when I wanted to learn and people were kind of
rough around the edges giving the information I was quite happy to get the
information and the morons that were not interested in information found to be
condescending they couldn't be there right right so that tells me a lot you
know like one time just to be sure you got over $200 of events and oh yeah and
that's 200 hours more than yeah than anything else it's pathetic to say that
by the way because there's so many people that are supposedly well-versed
and there are different subjects that have internet access can get it out
there even on a searchable query you know and it doesn't exist it's just
what's going on and you know that it's even more pathetic is the people that
work in the fields the entitled classes you know the doctors the attorneys the
MIT idiots where we're not coming on saying hey this is bullshit you guys
there are been told you know there is some of that going on there is enough
to enough to say that yeah it's not correct to say no one is but they don't
have it together you know they don't they just think it's one little thing
and we just fix this and we'll make the world better again no sorry I had a kind
of laugh today I went to these suspicious observers YouTube thing and
he was actually mentioned something about the 18-hour day and that's the
same place that I found out about the China in weather modification whether
he's he's a little against that when he mentioned that about the 18-hour day I
caught my eye right away as you know huh you know believe it or not I had not
gone to him in about a month and I went there today and there's something about
the moon making the day longer yeah right yeah and I when these idiots say
18-hour day they're talking about 18 hours of daylight not the 12 hours of
daylight six hours of night okay okay the time date I think he was up in a
million so I was like oh wow that's you know that's so good oh yeah because the
thing is when you're dealing with a human you have to assume that there are
more on and then you just wait a little bit and they prove it right yeah they
did and then then you then you're not you're not hopeful you don't have this
ooh you know the only thing you should be hopeful in is like let's say you're
not good at making rice you know most white people you tell them to make rice
they're terrified you know they'd rather run around the block 4,000 times because
they know if they try to cook rice are gonna get a big lump of starch right so
if you're a white person and you want to learn how to make rice learn how to make
rice and that's where you're hopeful in because you're gonna make better food
now you see what I mean or you want to get lawful clothing and make better
living environment you see that's what let's hope that they haven't taken the
cookable rice and made that a permanent staple now god that was scary what yeah
it is it is scary I I think what I'm gonna do is I have a there's a market
that's a good 10 miles from here that's a huge market and they have some real
high-end rice I'm gonna experiment I'm gonna get a small batch of high-end rice
and they're giving example a high and it costs what beef costs you know in pound
you know and it's Japanese and other varieties I'm gonna try a little bit of
that because that's your good measure like you know if you get into a Maybach
or a Lamborghini or Ferrari and it's a piece of crap you're not gonna your
chances of getting into a Ford and it being good is you know your expectation
should be lowered you know you go for the best stuff right right so it's a gauge
but not always because I've driven by the way at a high-end super cars or
whatever and you go over a certain number speed and you're like oh I'd
rather prefer you know 1978 Caprice classic was smoother you know because
they feel like they're gonna fall apart right they're not forward to your report
that's for sure yeah yeah yeah so I'm gonna get into a rice investigation but
I I tell people around me the food you know like for example recently a few
maybe a month ago I said to someone we're not going to be you know in less
than two years are probably not going to be eating any animal products you know
like a steak or chicken or fish or whatever I mean that's how much the
quality is going to go down if you are paying attention you know I mean mm-hmm
because the animals are not going to want to spiritually give up their bodies
anymore for the for nutrition it'll be toxic when you eat it this is this is
something else very nice you know there's there's the backtalk you know
stuff that I've explained to people and they you know they come to me like man
it's just like you said I said yeah you know well you shouldn't be surprised
because we talked about it five years ago right you know so now how about how
about you know instead of telling me it's just like you said Greek how about
you know it's just like I said you know why don't you say that once you start
looking further down the line you know I recently from this is just a little a
shout out I think it was six one eight whatever he private mailed me about he
wanted to find out more about the circus split in the church and the clowns of
anything online I said I don't go look online the really good libraries in
print I don't you know been to one in a while but they have stuff on ancient
cultures and if you start looking at descriptive diagrams of ancient culture
their temples they were just like the clowns of modern-day you know you could
look at it yourself look at something where they were actually both
interacting well not only yeah and they used magicians like the Orthodox what
became the Eastern Church they used magicians and contraptions where you put
a coin in and they had robotics I think a while back I dropped some links
about the Greek church was yeah the church was investing in that yeah it's
the same crap today look at the whether it's evangelical or any any denomination
whatever demon they take some under their wing to inspire them to do that
crap it's a circus it's a show people bounce around clapping hollering you
know bingo yeah it's just a show it's a circus and it really you don't have to
drop a ton of bricks on them if someone goes to church on with the circus but as
I start looking up what that word really means if you read the scripture without
watching the TV and what they tell you can see something different maybe don't
get your hopes up on that boy you know the thing is I think anything with
Greek speak or anything that's along this line even with fresco whatever file
it away you really can't use any of this stuff outside of food clothing and
shelter and the proof is earlier like we said you know try to tell other people
right like you know I gave the hypothetical thing how come there's no
support for this and why isn't everyone listening getting 10 other people to
listen right I know that's not going to happen because I'm not you know I've
been on this planet more than 15 minutes right there is a time when
specifically the identity and let's not be confused you know a lot of Christians
I've had personal phone calls okay I call you on the phone I give them the
phone number to bring their buddies on and they say well you know is this
gospel to go to the whole world and basically they don't even know what
they're talking they think it's what they're doing has to go to the whole
world Christians are doing right when you actually look at the meaning of
what's being said there what it was about twofold one was at that time the
people who knew who the Christ was in his purpose and now to any information
about that to come out to go against the misidentity right who the real Christ is
in other words right because people don't know you know that's one of the
examples I'm giving is if they wanted even a small semblance of accuracy they
should call him Joshua not Jesus because his name is Joshua like the book of
Joshua the sixth book of the Bible why did they have to make up the Jesus because
it's completely different creature right so there so Satan or the adversaries
forces as we can't call him Joshua like the book of Joshua that's his name if
we're going to use the letter J we have to make it a different creature
completely so later on if they're going to put our feet to the fire and say we
never said it was Joshua's it was Jesus which is not in there anyway but that's
not going to be enough to let him go you see they're just trying to lawyer
their way out of it you see so what's happening is remember the whole purpose
why is scripture so difficult to comprehend for most it's because it
doesn't matter if you could it's not because it's not meant to be
comprehended like some Christian circles tell you that's your
interpretation sorry I don't like it now it's so later on no one can say that I
didn't know it existed you see so know what the only reason you have scripture
is so later on it'll you'll be everyone will be without excuse the last thing
gods or angels want is some sniveling human scumbag saying well you didn't
know sure of course you knew you know so the battery die we still here we saw
no we're still going we're still going okay I was just taking all this in and a
wealth of information again well I don't know about the wealth because it's it
doesn't have any currency value to it didn't the knowledge yeah well remember
you increase knowledge put an equal sign on the other side of the equal sign
you know the little smiley face turn the smile upside down until you learn how to
handle it you know for example when you go to the gym okay let's say you go to
the gym and you're just an observer do the people look like they're having a
good time no right it's like a torture chamber isn't it you know as I've what
do they call one of those Roku things and Netflix yeah I do sign in on our own
stuff yeah but I was watching a film pumping iron with Schwarzenegger and
used to do bodybuilding and I remember reading his books and all that in the
70s right and I was telling someone I went in the other room I said it sounds
like a torture chamber in there you know lifting weights so it's no
different than people being tortured but is it beneficial yes it is beneficial
for the body getting knowledge for the spirit is it beneficial for the spirit
yes but does it sound like a torture chamber yes you know it's anybody happy
no well that doesn't stop me from wanting to learn right because the
reward you end up learning the highest the knowledge itself is its reward you
see and because it's the adversaries world it takes a form of currency when
you turn it around and twist it and make it devious that's when it becomes like
MIT right or now churches or the various political groups when they twist it
around and make it devious that's when it becomes gainfully you know currency
knowledge you know many times you say oh yeah you know I have a best-selling book
I said I don't want to read no best-selling book because who well why
not Greek well because who the hell's reading it if a million people read it
and they like it it can't be good right you know what King James is an example
millions of people have read it they like it can't be good am I right or
wrong you're right hmm who's hitting me on scarcity okay not much yeah so the
the interesting thing is that the the the basics of it is like we mentioned
earlier I'm not a relativist or anything you know how we you and I mentioned as
you get older how fast time goes by mm-hmm right you know I I have like you
know ten years now is not no big deal but when you're five years old a year is
an eternity you can hardly wait until you're a teenager or you're not five
years old anymore it seems like you're five forever right right or so whoever's
yeah yeah and they don't like young the children don't want to be called babies
right that's how you discourage them right and adults don't want to be called
children or vice versa you know it gets to the point where no one knows why they
are where they are and why they want what they want to do and why it's just
bizarre so how fast time goes by that the amount of time that is left this is
from an informational point no one should be I shouldn't say foolish but
should be jumped to the point say well because the Greek says we only have 14
years that's it and that now you know we're in trouble no that's not how it
should be what you should do is is separate the Greek from and say I'm
getting information why there's 14 years left you see and whether it's good
information or not is up to me to decide by through validation verification
study or just emotional I don't like this guy so his information can't be
good or I really like him so his information has to be good you see the
point is that it's put out there no one later can say that it hadn't been put
out but those that are taking heed to what is being said and comprehend it in
addition to if you are older or approaching half a century old that
decade and a half will come by like tomorrow not tomorrow but maybe the day
after or feel like you know next week hey it'll be like if you have a haircut
appointment in two weeks that's how fast it'll come you'll be getting your hair
cut and the asteroids will be hitting that's how that's how it'll fear feel you
know or you or by then you're gonna feel that you have a thousand actually
know for most people listening you'll be getting your haircutting appointment
and be dreaming about the next perfect thousand years that you're being told is
going to happen right yeah so anyway so this is a very very quick thing and now
here just to recap the point is very interesting is although the thought was
almost fleeting the very interesting point would be that if it's going to
happen so quickly how come others don't see it with such specifics well because
others don't see anything with specifics ask anyone what day it is a pope work
schedule do your intestines absorb yes do you do calories yes what you know all
these subjects that have been discussed right they don't see anything what's the
money base oh it's just fiat no it's not it's a bond it's a mortgage can you
trade mortgages of course you do it's done all the time do you want to be
subject to that no it's all private you see they think the church is a good
thing they think you know what I mean right it's Bruce okay since you've been
listening since you've been listening to this stuff and you've we've touched
on I'd say at least 10 different core heavy core subjects I know me core
subjects meaning that I affect people on this planet have you tried to discuss it
with other people and seemingly draw a blank or they've never heard of it and
they're all obvious they're all all obvious so okay so if they don't you
know what this has given me it's given me much more clarity as to what I'm
looking at and shocking you know just how much the censorship is there and
it's stuck it's just not gonna let up on them yes because the reason why is
because they're stuck here's another reason why is because they're you know
I say carnal you know the carnal mind you know carny meaning flesh because
they're stuck in the material world they're stuck and you see when someone
if it's blatantly obvious that the for example the intestines don't absorb
anything that's blatantly obvious in any item anatomical reference right but
they're stuck in believing and won't lift a finger even the people working in
the field to see that it doesn't say anything that means that you're stuck so
much in the material world that being able to cognitively rationalize what is
physically going on is not possible that's how bad off you are it's like
someone that is so drunk they can't walk three feet but they want to go to the
store to get more alcohol because the the level of drunkenness they have is
not enough it ain't gonna happen either and their desires are busy so you know
like once I think go with Ocelli I said that even the people that are called
materialists don't know anything about the material world they don't so when you
start putting at this bizarre perplexing condition that humans are in
all because of the gods by the way we don't care about you by the way when I
say that I mean the great majority I'm not talking about the elect and the ones
that are tasked to do things right right this is the generals you know all you
know I'm talking about all the talking about the beach and and all the grains
of sand not the ones that get stuck in your shoe you know and here you know you
can have a million people go into the beach and they all bring some sand home
the beach will still be there you get it how many people have gone to Coney
Island or big beaches in Malibu whatever and for a century now and brought some
sand home in their panties or their pants or their sandwich cooler bag at
home and the beach is still there you think after all those millions and
hundreds of millions of people go to the beach over a century would have
depleted all the sand you see what I'm saying right so scripture says you know
the poor will always be with you I'm telling the morons will always be with
you so when you're when you're dealing with a reality as such on this planet
and remember this is planet wide right yeah they can't see anything how are they
going to see something like that you know prophecy or what's coming next not
possible and the ones that do see it what can you do about it nothing because
how many times have I said if it's so explicit and let's say the book of
revelation which we shouldn't read anyway you're not gonna understand it in
its proper context but a book revelation it's so obvious that all these things
are happening if if so many millions of people have access to it if they
understand on how to put it in its proper place aren't they gonna cry foul
when it's happening yeah does it say anyone's gonna cry foul no there are a
few of the elect that do and they're put down very quickly beheaded and all this
right but it doesn't change anything I mean how many people go to medical
school that stay you know in the field and say your body doesn't absorb
anything none now you know the dropout rate in medical school is very high
right and you understand why yes that's a someone drops out of medical school
that you should take that as a success and a moral lawful and ethical success
by the way to stay in that and continue is a failure it's I don't same with law
school someone to drop out of law school it should be considered a success so
anyway I'm perfectly content with my my knowledge and getting better with my
knowledge if I don't have to say it to another person because of their
stiff-headedness so be it right but they're censored also and what happens
is if you push against the censorship the other side can turn them into a
werewolf an animal type thing tear you apart I mean physically and emotionally
or spiritually yes yes remember the fact is this World War one hundred and
something million people died right from the plague that the Americans
engineered the Spanish flu World War two 150 million and we have about 20 or 30
million people throughout the world every year I'd say about 15 million
conservatively half of them if not more in the US being taken out by the medical
industry chemicals and all that maybe more and and where that why aren't the
gods stopping them well because the fact is they're not stopping it now let's
just look at the facts you want to look at the facts now cold facts right not
what you think or what you want or whatever do the gods know this is going
on yes are they doing anything about it no so someone knows something is going
on that's bad and not doing anything about it this does not tell you like they
don't care you get it or you could say they are do something about it Greek if
they didn't there would be 300 million dead instead of a hundred million that's
not the point the point is you are getting that you see 50 million hundred
million whatever it is you see and the reason why they don't care is because of
the carnal nature it's physical how many times have you read in Scripture
you're just dust anyway right get over it now here's the thing no matter how
sore people are and the reason I'm bringing this up at the way that I am
this way is because I've heard this several times every time you heard me
say if I hear something two or three times with an interim I'll do I'll talk
about it on a sonic because it's like a little message being sent you know like
maybe you should talk about this right when you hear from different sources so I
did it recently a past week or two I've been hearing oh why does you know God
allow this to happen I was okay that's it enough of this and I need to balance
out the equation not because it's going to make anything better but just because
you have to write it's kind of like the janitor solving the big problem at night
you know that the physicist couldn't you just fills it in and walks away you
don't want to take credit for it but essentially the carnal nature and how
bad it seems because you are emotionally attached to it because of the physical
if I were to say that the reward post-resurrection and when the gods
return to sort things out will be so great that will not only compensate for
all this misery that humanity's been through but it will also overcompensate
would you believe that and that would be a good belief by the way you know it
would be it would be like giving you guys is a example I knew a bass player
and he got a bicycle and he got hit by a car he left the bike shop and he fell
down and he broke his thumb now for an ordinary person that would be you know
ten twenty thirty thousand dollars right fifty thousand but but he's a bass
player he needs it's for his livelihood right so he got three point something
million from the insurance right okay because he was a bass player it took
like five years you know they offered him like a quarter of a million he said
no it was you know there's a quarter of a million in the first year or you just
kept going right so imagine that you get a paper cut so that that's like you
know because that's that's like something that makes sense right okay
you can't work anybody could but okay so imagine you get a paper cut and you get
a billion for a paper cut that would be more of an analogy of after the
resurrection the compensation that everyone will get everyone right and of
course that doesn't make a good analogy because if you think it through if
everyone got a billion a loaf of bread will be 500 million right so because of
you know how the economics model works but I'm just saying all of this stuff
that people are asking and questioning and doubting and even though I come out
cold-heartedly and say because the gods don't care about you the compensation
what I need to fill in the balance is the compensation later when they do come
and take control and are at the top overtly because they're at the top now
covertly when they're over the compensation for all of humanity will
be beyond compensation for all of the misery and shit that's happened that so
much that you would even forget and not even see all the bad stuff that's ever
happened to humanity is being bad because of the powers and the privileges and the
what you'll be enabled to do later and this is not like some hokey stuff will
you have course it always sounds good when it's going to happen later what
about now we've spent quite a bit time discussing what about now you know what
I mean and can't even realize the obvious what about now there is no now
you're living in a fog in a dream but it's not you know not don't go that
route that it's a fog or a dream either using it as a metaphor you know it's
just would behoove anyone to study any field very quickly objectively with
discernment and you can approach any of the entitled classes in any field and
and render them to bits you know so so let's say that's that's our sonic for
now it's I'd say it's approaching midsummer we still have a I have to go I
haven't been as diligent I need to also if I do a posting on a on the chat or an
email on the date on the day not today I need to double check myself because
sometimes I put up some wrong I've been doing it for so long that I haven't been
taking measurements I just do a sighting I'm like okay I'll remember that and I
don't you know and I'm often sometimes so I need to be more accurate not because
not only for my sake actually it's good to be accurate but for others that ask
you know or if I'm gonna throw what I what day I think it is so I just want to
defend my inadequacy will be more adequate in the future hopefully in terms
of you you weren't alone on that last one well it's it's interesting it is
good you know how the people you've seen the deserted island or the guy in jail
he scratches on the wall right you know how many days I've been here you know
how they do that mm-hmm yeah just start scratching what's good is a dry erase
board on the fridge chalkboards are really good by the way I actually from
messing around with the dry erase marker boards I do prefer the chalk I you know I
think dollar stores get chalk now and all that right mm-hmm there's something
about the tactile feeling you know there's something neater and cleaner and
more sanitary about a chalkboard a real chalkboard than the dry erase markers
too I don't I don't know maybe it's just me yeah yeah maybe I'm just old-school
so or a pad a notepad that you don't keep in a horizontal was personal
experiences now if you have a notepad make a hole in it somehow it doesn't and
hang it from a string instead of keeping it on a desk or a drawer because it's
there you know what I mean you're not going to use it for other stuff and when
the moon comes or you could have the Pope's work schedule and you know where
the lines are on the Pope's work schedule the boxes the day actually
starts in the middle of the line you know so so in other words wherever there's a
line on the Pope's work schedule calendar the printed calendar that's
that's the that's the day see so the the day starts in the middle of the box
right I'm sorry right mm-hmm right the middle of the box is when the day starts
the line is the middle of the night and the middle of the next box is the next
day so you almost have to put another set of lines through the lines that they
have right or a little dash or a dot you get it no because the the box
delineation the vertical lines of the brakes are midnight which is the middle
of the day you know the you know in terms of time span till the from noon to
noon right mm-hmm so that's the other simple way to look at it and you can
still use that as a because you're going to communicate for example if you mark
up a calendar a Pope's work schedule calendar and let's say you go in a chat
you're going to look at the Pope's work schedule because on each chat line the
they do supply the date and time and that's not lawful they do it on the Pope's
work schedule so you marking up a calendar is actually even more
expeditious you know I don't even think they have the old plumbers catalog
calendars with the women in scampi skimpy clothes anymore do they they still
do those mechanics calendars and things remember that you know what I that
started in the 40s oh yes yeah yeah yeah yeah I bet it'd be funny because yeah
yeah going into the mechanic shops and all that these guys all have silly
phones you know so they probably yeah yeah they probably do like snap on or
whatever I think I think I recently saw a snap on a reason maybe a year or two
ago and they just show a tool a chrome socket or something right that you know
anyway strange world of advertisements so I know the office supply places have
calendars and all that now the ones that could be not very useful are the
ones that you peel off remember the old-school ones that they those little
pieces of paper you peeled off Oh sticky nose it yes yeah those are not it so
timekeeping so there you go and we know we're in the the fourth month and we're
in the second week of the fourth month now so I think the we're in the what is
it the ninth day now or something yes no no one is lining up pretty good now
yeah I was off there for a while yeah let me see I'll double check my work here
six 90 that's around the 10th 10th yeah 10th okay well I think it's a yeah the
Sabbath was over at noon today I think right or something yeah either way yeah
yeah and also I think I've mentioned before and people have guessed that
eventually you won't be able to keep time at all right right right right yeah
and you really won't want to keep time when the Sun goes really hot because
you'll be just no you know yeah you'll be cooking in it yeah so you'll be
keeping time with a convection oven essentially yes yeah not a lot of time
left I mean I hate to hate to say it in a way that people have to believe it but
I have to say it in a way that people should hear it and if you you know just
like I used to tell the young people if you're if you're not if you're not
disgusted with humanity you're not paying attention you're believing some
kind of mental model that people are good and things will be all right and
all that and they're not and the only reason the only way all this what I'm
saying is going to be passed off as being good or okay is because it's a
deception just like you know anything toxic yeah I guess that key word would
be toxic and all the ways around it yeah there's still a lot of going going on I
would say and we're going to get off here shortly we've been quite a few
hours or maybe two hours something when you hear people saying we need to make
the world a better place by the way now you know past few years and now and we
need to fix this so it gets better and all that that's not just like fainting
feigning altruism you know to make things better right now when you hear
those positive remarks about improvement and all that you know what that really
is if you put it in context that's the set I that's the setup for the
pseudo-perfect society that you're going to be taught is coming you're being set
up for that as well you know what I mean mm-hmm so the people that are saying we
need to make the world a better place and all this other stuff that is not that
is very different now than the apologetics or the altruism that you
heard in the past now it's going to be attached to the fervor of this and
instead of or anti-christ figure that's going to be coming that will usher in
that sentiment you see that's another flavor yeah so the making the world a
better place in the perfect society and look at all these improvements whether
it's political scientific medical religious or whatever is not just your
run-of-the-mill stuff that people have been seeking it's this part of the setup
for this specific section that's coming in the mid 2020s so it's not to be
negated by the way you know very often say oh yeah I didn't want to go see that
guy because it was the engine because you want to make the world a better
place that was a decade ago now the people that are doing that are going to
be crying ha see I told you later you see the difference yes because later when
they get the big deception the ones that are spiking the interest in hope of a
better future will be satisfied will be granted that but not the real one
they'll be granted that through the Antichrist you see so that's another
level of discussion all together because you'll start hearing more of
that so you may not want to from let's say an indirect ounce of advice would be
if you heard Greek speak you know avoid this crap about making the world a
better place whatever but when you start seeing the majority or let's say a third
of the people saying that and if you start saying well it's not they're gonna
kind of want to kick you in the nuts and knock your teeth out for saying it's not
you see what I mean oh yeah because because they're going to be accommodated
by the Antichrist on that so you might want to not now is no there's no nothing
like that now but in the future when you start seeing that talk more and more I
wouldn't I wouldn't I'd stay seated on that and just watch it you know what I
mean all right don't want to be the tall nail no no the tall poppy syndrome or
anything like that so so that you should do the you remember the book for
dummies they don't really have that anymore because the internet killed them
over those yellow books how to computer programming for dummies internet book of
for dummies or something yeah yeah I think the internet killed that because
not people could search specifically right or they still exist I don't know
you need to do the end time for dummies you know they have the character the
figure guy it's a yellow and black go I know I know you already got the streams
you've been very diligent behind the scenes but someone else out there you
have to be more of a lackey because you're gonna have to do something is put
to find out the template for the dummies for dummies thing and submit and times
for dummies and time scenario for dummies anyway I think they have one
already on biblical stuff for dummies of course it's all yes I think yeah I
think they do think for every subject in the under the Sun pretty much so
anyway they still have the book out the internet book for dummies yeah right I
was discussing something for some reason we should do the inertial principles for
dummies this at all I think the internet killed that and I kind of believed him I
said yeah it makes sense because you know back 25 30 years ago I would have
sought out one of those at a bookstore use bookstore you know where I did look
at them they've been around for a long time mm-hmm there's not much you can
still get your copy for $2 here's and all the way up to 13 yeah oh my goodness
yeah in credits yeah now it's regarding economics you can get a pretty good
grip on what things are costing by looking at the price of silver and then
the previous cost of things explain that if you want to make a determination on
the price of gasoline right go back to the silver cost and you can look up spot
silver right go historical back to when it was near a dollar like a dollar 12 or
something in the 70s or 60s right and look at the price of gas then what the
price of gas was when the silver was close to a dollar so what you do now is
you look at the price of gas for example gasoline and the cost of silver now and
you do the math so if silver is at 15 you take the price of gas now and divide
it by 15 and then go back to when the silver was a dollar what was the gas and
you'll see that the gas is actually cheaper now right okay like for example
when silver was a dollar gasoline was about 30 35 cents a gallon you have
something like right now right now gas is about $3 a gallon and silver is at 15
16 so that means that if it was a parity it would be 450 a gallon I'm not talking
about California now right California it's always 450 or $5 trendsetter you
see so in other words gasoline is in terms of lawful to silver remember
silver is the money for people mm-hmm gold is the money for royalty and kings
and barter is for peasants right correct anyway yeah so so gasoline is about 30 or
40 percent cheaper now than it was in the 60s and 70s do you see what I mean
do the same thing with a gallon of milk you find out what a gallon of milk is
now and if it's less than 15 times what it was in the 70s it's cheaper now if
it's more than 15 times what it was in the 70s it's more expensive but you can
do this at any time in history but silver an ounce of silver is a dollar
period whether it was a 500 years ago or 200 years ago when they started that you
know in 17 the Treasury Act right they determined that or you'll find that you
know pieces of silver are very close everywhere in the world was a day's
wages was a piece of silver $15 most people make more than $15 in a day now
I'm using the credit analogy right right but you were three times that at minimum
wage so you so the average worker now makes two or three times of the average
worker let's say 500 years ago so economically you're a lot better off
do you may not like certain things about the economy you know we can't afford the
rent let's say or the bills or you don't understand you see that I'm not talking
about that I'm talking about price to value index strictly you know and this
is a very simple way to look at it no one's talking about it you know so
that's another thing having a I found in private a few years ago I just started
having economic discussions and we kept meeting after a while I said these
people are really quiet I'm going to start quizzing them on what we talked
about they didn't remember anything so if they're not adding or taking away
from the conversation and they don't remember any previous conversations I
kept asking myself what am I doing here why am I talking right so you know I
told you when you're doing a public speaking especially when there's
question-and-answer at the end I look at everybody's faces and their look in
their eyes when is this asshole gonna shut up and sit down so I can get the
microphone and quote-unquote there are people that have moat when you have
hosts and guests even I hear it a lot on the internet and listen much but when I
inquire any show I notice that the guests not listening the host the host
not listening to the guests you ever notice that if you're listening to
internet the alternative medium ones mm-hmm because they're all waiting oh
when is this guy gonna shut up so I could say what I want to say you know
this is human you know this is not really human nature but this is how
humans have been raised and they are inspired or censored or all that other
stuff the headhunters yeah so yeah there's no reason to get into depth in
many things before if anyone wants to reach me they can go to the uncommon
sense or uncommon radio there's the email on there just go to the uncommon
radio it's the first site that comes up you contact me I had gotten a contact by
the way for someone wanting a water project it was an international project
and see how I so see how that goes yeah it's a foreign country it's pretty I
wouldn't say as high as corporate government and hmm I usually don't
mention I try to keep these things covered but the reason I'm bringing up
because nothing will come out of it not because I'm because I know what will
happen the moment you get in there and make real improvements and changes it's
it steps on too many toes in other words if you if you're doing ears this is for
anyone that's I don't know many people working consulting or you can put you
know have extraordinary stuff to help other people with if you get contacted
by let's say a well you know high net worth or well it financially endowed
group to join them or help or consult if they have more than three or five
people it's not going to work out if you're doing really got the goods
because you're going to step on their toes because of the ego and all the
other the conformity and all that but if it's less than three to five people
chances are you might go you might actually develop something because
there's not that many people to step on right so let's say this is let's say get
to Greek we want to know about but your water stuff we this is our problem and
their problem is pretty big it's not you know it's a large-scale stuff if they've
got 50 people 100 people in the in the brain trust you know the people at
engineers and all that and you start pulling shit like why does a bucket of
war water way more than a bucket of air and you have a hundred people saying we
can't be that stupid it's better off getting rid of this guy than admitting
we're stupid right yeah this is how they do it they'd rather sink the ship then
but if you got three or three four or five people and they all admit they're
stupid they're like okay we're not you know we didn't admit it to everyone no
you don't learn something new so yeah so yeah so maybe maybe we should keep
going but I'm telling you this is a lifelong experience folks anybody out
there doesn't matter what it is any field yeah imagine going to the a large
hospital in a city with hundreds or thousands of doctors and saying the
intestines don't absorb we need to absorb re-examine this methodology you're
gonna get booted so fast you're you know you may not even you it'll be like three
minutes before you land on the sidewalk that's how fast they're gonna throw you
but if you go to let's say some backwoods place with three doctors or
five doctors and you tell them that they might say wow you know we should
consider that you see what I mean yes right you get it yeah yeah yeah and
that's how it works Wow but you know I think you remember in the the new order
of barbarians the whole thing is about industrialized medicine now institution
and I was watching a Star Trek the other night I've been trying to because I
don't do drugs so I need something to just dumb you know a chemical
lobotomy watching right here and there and they had an ad there said do you
ever have an intuition or whatever you know there's gonna be two million people
added to the health industry in the next five years don't you want to be a
part of it like whoo that sounds like major institutional shit like we've
been hearing about you know yeah Wow anyway yeah it's it's it's so
unpredictable I mean you know let's say before I go let's say in a hypothetical
world that's really far off imaginary you know how I give the analogy of the
Kevlar underwear because of the thumbtacks on the seats right mm-hmm
let's say you were turned into a mouse or a rat not not to put down mice or
rats they've done anything wrong and you were stuck in that world with what you
know now what the hell are you gonna do right think about it or how about you
want to end it right here there's a certain there's something called a dung
beetle you know why they call them a dung beetle because they eat dung they
actually stand up on their rear quarters and they roll the dung into their nest so
let's imagine now you know what you know now and you were turned into a dung
beetle coprophagia in living with other dung beetles what are you gonna do now
hopefully the tractor will run you over and squash you as quickly as possible so
you don't have to put up with it and this is what it's like to be on planet
earth sorry guys I say I hate to break it to you but if that's news if you're
older than six years old or eight and that's news to you I'm really sorry so
anyway well thank you yeah it's just Sam comes around I'll yeah tomorrow maybe
for double or whatever it doesn't sure sure it's coming up the middle of
summer I think everyone got a pretty good taste of what happened in the
springtime and what to expect and the next big changes are to be viewed in the
fall and then eat this reason then we've got a few more years to see how
things fall together well I got it yeah yep so sorry about the dog that's yeah
and and of course get knowledge it's reward and learn how to pray because they
they you know the the gods especially the most high he does he does watch the
back of those that are his own and he I'm not saying it because I'm saying it
I'm just reporting for careful what you pray for you know yes get it yes you
might get it or even if you don't get it that's big that's okay too right that's
the other but this is the thing that people have fall amiss there is no such
thing as why does God do that there are gods and the thing to remember is that
he does take care of the most high does in the Christ do take care of their own
and if you're not being taken care of and you feel like you're out of touch
guess what you ain't one of his right now that's okay too you know what I mean
this is real talk people are not used to this kind of bullshit I mean this kind of
the kind of bullshit that they hear it does not conform or does jive well with
this kind of talk you know when you read scripture he says these are my people or
my people will know this or that if if you don't qualify you ain't one of his
people I'm sorry and the proof is all the misery in the world so so it's okay
either way everyone here's the point that you should always communicate if
even if you just had a moment all of humanity anyone that's ever been born
lived and died and will be born is going to be rewarded so when the gods are
finally settled in and overtly at the top and and again the reward will not
only compensate for all the evil and the misery and the sadness it'll over
compensate if that makes any sense mm-hmm so that's what you look forward
to but in the meantime the reason I speak the way I have been lately is
because you ever you ever go to a party or a group of people and they're all
drunk but they're not just buzzed they're drunk drunk and you can't
rationalize with them and you tell the guy you know the bathrooms over there
and he's going the opposite way and he starts peeing and you know in the
hallway you got it yeah you got to physically grab him and take some of his
weight and bring him you know to the you know because they can't rationalize
anymore you know it doesn't doesn't mean that you couldn't always rationalize
with them but they're stone drunk now you see now it's purely beat him up sock
him up knock him down get away or whatever cuz they're drunk you see and
this is the condition of mankind always and this is the way I will be talking to
people probably pretty much from now on as if they're just a bunch of drunks
don't pee in the plant don't pee in the pot right go to the right and you
shouldn't have been so drunk in the first place so you know or sleep it
over you know it's gonna hangover in the morning so and boy they're gonna have a
hangover yes yeah yeah yeah and again just to be apologetic to defend the way
the style that I've been incorporating and speaking publicly is you don't have a
lot of time left so you know when you know how people again when they're
getting drunk you know they play all nice and nice they have a drink they're
like I think you're an asshole right right yeah you know how people do that
get him drunk so he tells you what he really thinks well I'll tell people what
I really think you're all bunch of jerks well nothing personal but you know what
I mean it's just humanity you know so get over it then what are you gonna do
now food clothing shelter study like Bruce says you say even if no one
listens to you when you know you know right and that's the reward itself that's
the reward in itself yeah I am rather comfortable with just that aspect of it
yeah because I tell you I made the rarity it just ain't there that's just
nothing you could do so right I'll sit back and enjoy the comfort of
understanding right food clothing shelter so the piss-poor pathetic lives
and good water you gotta throw that good water in there oh yeah that's part of
food and it's also part of clothing and it's part of shelter you know like the
way for example I do water here if you put the tiniest amount I LG Trom except
no substitute by the way you know what I'm talking about LG's a company they
make a washing machine they don't stop making that's called Trom they have
other ones but it's a front loader and if you if you modify it so it doesn't do
the water conservation which actually uses more water remember the water
conservation toilets you flush two or three times so where's the water
conservation the way to do water conservation there is you know you have
the sink water going to the toilet you see so instead of telling people to
conserve water you make you make it so they can only but anyway when the water
here like the way the soaps are now if I use the tiniest amount of soap it's like
super sudsy and you go to someone else's you know because they haven't
modified the water condition of the water they pour all this soap you see
because you know when you're when you're washing you want the water to carry away
you know so if you know how to modify water so it does that you a better water
will clean better right clean clothes better clean your car better clean your
body better right real clean right and having good water running through the
house changes the vibe like if you ever go to a like hospitals have the worst
quality water I had you know and changes the the vibe for very various reasons
yeah but like you said the water as well and all of that food clothing shelter
it's all attached yeah yeah so 14 years man keep saying it pretty soon it'll be
13 and then 12 and yeah I don't know how much I'll be discussing or doing
anything anymore much after that we'll see I'd you know I don't think I'm not
gonna say now I need my words later but I don't think after 2020 I'll be around
to say anything I mean if I am around I won't be talking you know I mean I think
it's best to sit back and watch the train wreck which is not gonna look like
a train wreck at all it's gonna look like a brand new supersonic jet coming
out of its hangar everybody want to take a ride right right Wow all right watch
what I'd suggest is you got till now to the fall you got um watch Jordan watch
Assyria watch Lebanon it's not this year next year and you got three and a
half to five years before the discussion we had regarding the cities mm-hmm to
look up in the scriptures all the cities that are I think it was a Wikipedia was
just as good as anything else right yeah I mean you can't fudge too much I mean
I'm sure there's a few errors and some of the names I've noticed I was looking
at my chicken scratch I have to relook the city because you know spelt it wrong
maybe I was taking it off of an interlinear off the Hebrew letters but I
would say get a list of all the cities and the ones that have to have any
involvement to biblical cities between judges Joshua judges Chronicles Kings
that's yep you get the point right we've discussed before that's where Israel is
going to be and I think I dropped the map or maybe I didn't is go do an online
search under maps or just do a browser browser search map of Israel during time
of judges and then go to images and what you're going to see is quote-unquote
tribes of Israel over the Jordan River on the other side of the Jordan River the
eastern side what's that now that's Jordan now isn't it so yeah have fun and
that's that's how it's that's how it's going to come that's how it's going to
be right I'm gonna I actually have to run attend to some things I just realized
what time it is to Bruce I appreciate the all the behind-the-scenes stuff I'm
going to do a one-handed clap for you and yeah I'm actually if you didn't do
that because I'll tell you sure sure is whatever I'm not doing it I haven't
archived anything I neither do I care I don't have anything if you any of the
computers that I use I don't have anything archived or whatever if
someone asked me send me an audio of whatever I don't have anything yeah I'd
have to go to archives and AFR what you're doing right right it's like
someone says I don't even before I keep all this every all the past sonic events
streaming 24-7 and I catch myself I'd rather listen to that than have that
crap that's out on the net you know they're all a bunch of assholes yeah the
whole is a whole they're all assholes out there you know I'm not mincing words
anymore no no they're all assholes I mean not not only do they have assholes
they are assholes the entire internet thing and yeah and even when you try to
brush them up in your own mind you know like fresco and these other guys they
say good stuff you're like wait a second there's no way this is going to work
without so much more you know none of it is it's just it's just a freaking dump
but look it's the same thing you know if we went back to when the printing
presses or even before that people were bad-mouthing the monks you know they're
writing all this bullshit you know this is you know a hundred thousand years ago
right mm-hmm it's still it's been going on for for the longest time you know the
even if you go back to biblical days first century the Sadducee men that
perishing the fat Pharisees and the Sadducees they were not liked our mixed
feelings you know the rich people like them because they could wield power with
them you know so they were all it's all been messed up and if you even if you go
back with Israel left Egypt they're in the wilderness within the presence of
the Most High's proxy and they got used to it to the point where they were still
making pagan altars and sacrifices to pagan gods right there when when it
would that you see right so it's never been the scripture does say a fool
romanticizes about the past right this year this is the best this is the best
time right now because it's almost over is that when you go on a long what's the
best part of the long road trip is the arrive right before you get to where
you're going right right is the best part of the road trip so okay so again we'll
stay in touch and thanks for what you do on the archiving okay okay guys take care
you take care good night good night