Greetings folks, we're live with the Greek.
And how are you doing tonight, Greek?
Greetings.
Okay, pretty good, I guess.
Good, good.
We were just talking about a hurricane remediation,
I think, before we started the stream.
People in the southwest are wondering, and I
said, well, I just popped a translator in
a tree, which is basically, it's a four
-foot plastic tube with a double mirror on
the end, which is, you know, two compact
mirrors, you know, the mirrors women use in
their makeup cases.
Sure.
You just put the mirrors back to back,
so, you know, you look at the mirror
and you flip it and it's another mirror.
That goes on the end, because that tends
to periodically and sort of momentarily reflect the
ether.
Yes.
Outside of time, you can't put a time
function on it.
Right, right.
And inside the four-foot plastic tube, which
is about three inches in diameter, there is
a galvanized metal tube that's about a foot
and a half long, and there's an air
gap of a quarter inch between the metal
tube and the plastic tube, and that's filled
with silk.
And that's it, that's a basic translator.
And that was enough to sort of jar
things and stop the, you know, the jet
stream and whatever, and just pause it a
little, drop it from a four to a
two, which I don't know if it really
did.
But I was going to break it.
I have two large guns.
I call them the intercontinental guns, and they're
three pieces and they kind of go together.
And I took them out.
I was cleaning them.
I was like, ah, that's a lot of
work, man.
And by the time I set up the
ground and it's like, do I really?
And when you set it up, you have
to man them because everything is moving constantly.
And if you focus on an area for
more than 20 minutes, it gets ignored.
I've never discussed the blind points.
So it's like, why?
I mean, I've done so many, and it's
like there's no reason to do it.
It's not like anybody is in danger, and
if they were, that's okay too, I guess.
I mean, there's danger all the time.
There's worse danger.
So I don't know.
But I think the big hurricane mitigation days
are over.
I think it can be done as a
real project where funding comes in and it's
used for whatever to develop it.
But that's not going to happen.
It's not going to happen in this society.
Yeah.
All right.
So it's what they call seven days since
the last time we were around.
I'm reckoning it's the first run to the
‑‑ I lost the day count, but I
know the full moon was about less than
a week ago.
I've got the ‑‑ I'm keeping track of
this here.
Yeah, it's the first, I think it actually
is the first Sabbath.
Ninth day of the eighth month, yeah.
Yeah, roughly, yeah, we just had a day
off.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I got, yeah, roughly.
You can feel it even if you don't,
you know, are aware of it.
People tend to ignore how they feel about
things, and I don't mean about emotionally and
what crap goes into their minds.
I'm talking about the body relation, you know,
gauging the body.
But, again, that's kind of difficult because if
you eat what most people eat, your body
feels like crap all the time.
You just get used to it.
But you do feel a little slowing down
around these times every seven days, you know,
count the eighth day after the full moon
or whatever.
All right, I'm looking at the chat.
I see go back, there's not much to
‑‑ I just opened the email, there's not
much.
I want to thank someone from Alabama.
I got your envelope.
Thank you.
And there's a question, or let's actually have
you notice ‑‑ you want to read that?
I'm going to go to the kitchen and
get some coffee.
Okay.
Having you notice posted something about a coroner,
I read it earlier, about someone admitting an
official off record capacity that the brain is
under a vacuum, but, you know, it just
happens to escape them after that, right?
Right.
So, yeah.
You know, that was interesting.
I was having a conversation, medical, what's called
medical.
He said what could be done, I mean,
you can't fix this society.
It's not possible.
I mean, the way you fix it is
by, you know, redoing it completely.
You have to scrap everything that's here and
start all over.
But the approach would be, if you had
to fix it, is you'd get like every
‑‑ out of all the millions of people
that work in the, quote, unquote, health industry,
you get two or three per million, or
it might be maybe less than .001%
that you can work with, you know?
Right.
And train them.
And they will admit what you, in other
words, when you, all you do is train
them to accommodate the body, the vacuum in
the body, now you have a proper perspective
on how to approach medical treatment or, you
know, any form of treatment to the human
body, and then put them back into the
system, right?
Right.
And then let them, you know, teach others.
And it's not like you're teaching something new.
You're basically just explaining why things happen.
It's already ‑‑ everyone already knows.
Anyone who has any training in anatomy or
the medical whatever already knows.
In other words, they've already observed the reactions
or the vacuum condition, right?
Like when something heals properly, it gets sucked
into the body.
Right.
Right?
You know, there's ‑‑ and when something is
infected, it's pushed away.
There's swelling, right, and heat.
Right.
So when something heals well, it gets sucked
in, and it's cool, right, relative to the
surroundings.
So, yeah, it's quite interesting how there's not
much training.
It's just admission and acknowledgement.
You know, like when I used to speak
to doctors, they used to walk out, and
I'd say, well, I'd see them later.
I'd say, why'd you walk out?
Well, I can't acknowledge what you're saying.
They didn't say what I was saying wasn't
correct.
They just said I can't acknowledge it, and
I understand why.
Right.
It's a fraud.
You know, like recently I was at an
auto parts store, and I was telling the
guy, you know, the whole society is based
on constructive fraud, meaning it's constantly being repaired
and built up.
You know, more fraud is being built up,
right?
And he didn't understand it.
I said, well, everybody is doing that.
I said, it doesn't matter.
I didn't say ‑‑ I didn't give a
quantity.
I gave a quality.
It doesn't matter if one person in society
is living a fraudulent life, or all of
them are.
The fact is that there's constructive fraud eminent
throughout the entire society in everything.
Oh, God, yeah.
Most people, like, they like to hide behind
the plausibility.
Well, everybody does it, so I'll do it
too, right?
Well, that's not the point.
That's not why facts are stated, you know,
unless they're quantitative facts, you know, giving a
statistic of how many people, right?
But once you get into the plausibility aspect,
then you don't have to do that because
everyone does it.
So there you go.
So there's that.
And that's my story, and I'm sticking to
it.
Right.
You know, when you were talking about one
person teaching another in that profession, you know,
you start, well, then they're caught in a
nasty position where, you know, they're looking at
the legal system, the administrations, and all that
kind of stuff, and they have to make
a decision whether they want to carry on
with the fraud or move on.
What an awful, rude awakening.
It is because you're on your own when
that happens because everyone around you is supporting
you in that scheme, right?
And then when you want to break out,
you have to, your friend's family, well, you
want to explain why you're leaving, but you
can't, so you just give a couple of
pat answers.
No, you can't.
I feel I can accredit myself to having
a couple of attorneys and doctors quit their
professions from after having discussions with them.
Not because I say this.
They came back and said, listen, I heard
you, and I considered it.
It took me a couple of years, but
I did it, and I'm glad I'm out
of there.
Yeah, yeah.
And I feel that's like a really good
accomplishment.
It is.
They got lawyers and doctors and stuff to
quit their profession.
It's not going to make much of a
difference, but you get one or two to
quit.
To them personally, yes.
A start would be like most of them
quit and put on a barge and sunk,
but that would be a good start, but
that's not going to happen.
The reason why you put them on a
barge and sink it is because they're unrehabilitatable.
They won't be able to fit in again.
So either way, that's just the way this
is.
Exiled in their own mind.
Well, the thing is, the benefits of this
is of understanding what's going on is you
still have the air is relatively sweet, and
so is the water.
In other words, when you breathe the air,
it's not accurate, and you have to wear
a gas mask, and the water is still
relatively okay.
I mean, not drinking tap water.
They deliberately keep the tap water in bad
shape, and even if they didn't, you've got
straight pipes, so it's going to diminish in
quality.
But you generally can still seek out things
that are pleasant, generally, not all the time.
You still can seek out pleasantries and things
that are affirming to why life should go
on.
But the majority of the systems and things
that are put in place by man and
also nature's catching up are leading towards utter
destruction.
And I don't mean that generally.
I could be specific.
In other words, nature is going to also
start showing why this can't go on, which
is okay.
Because it just can't go on.
It's like pulling off a band-aid.
You can't just leave it on.
It has to come off.
It has to come off sometime.
Yep.
So, yeah.
And the thing is, one thing I was
having a discussion with someone recently is why
isn't there, like, one specific place?
You know, I think they somehow found out
a way to get over to the servers
you've got going on there.
Oh, okay.
And it was like, well, there's not one
introductory.
Actually, the question is, you know, why isn't
there an introductory Greek speak going over all
the points in the beginning?
Whoa.
Yeah, it's a lot because it's everything, a
little bit of everything.
How do you purpose something like this?
Well, it's a mindset.
Just be objective and look at what things
are based on and try to find the
history of that thing.
That's it.
Right.
Yeah.
Some of the best way to find that
is if you find, like, an initial interview.
If I have done an initial interview with
someone, I usually start off with a recap
of some very obvious points.
Oh, by the way, great job with Chuck
this last time.
You packed a lot of information in there
again.
Yeah, Chuck is pretty harmless.
And the thing is I did someone left
a comment.
He didn't really throw up too many roadblocks
or easy to get around because, you know,
Chuck is very mainstream.
Yes, he is.
He doesn't think he is, but he is
very mainstream.
So I don't find great joy in discussing
these things that way.
Like, I have to start from the base.
Yeah.
But even if you want to be more
elaborate, you still have to refer to basic
things.
And also, you know, I got to send
appreciation or thanks because he put up with
me doing the Ocelli and the Greek, and
that put out some really good stuff for
quite a few people.
Quite a few could be anywhere between one
to 20 that kind of get it and
can move on with, you know, the mindset.
So, but yeah, you said good job, I
guess.
Why was it a good?
Let me just ask you when people say,
when I ask people, how was this?
It's good.
So why is it good?
You captured a lot of different subjects with
history involved.
You moved through it very, very flawlessly.
You hit many, many topics that I think
were necessary.
Okay.
In that respect, it was in general, I
guess I want to say, as a complete
package.
It was good to hear.
And I think it will do, hopefully it
will do somebody well.
Well, there may be.
But to see that, see, first I started
calling people unaware and then I call them
morons and idiots and then space heaters.
And now they're livestock.
And most people just possibly focus on that.
Right.
So there's an evolution in terms there as
well.
Yeah, there's an evolution in terms that I'm
using.
But eventually we'll go back to unaware and
moron.
And here's the thing.
You can't, at this point, it's a little
way, I should say, way past the line
where plausibility can be used.
Meaning where you can say, well, they don't
know.
They were misled.
That's total bullshit at this point.
Because they have access.
They can see it.
They use it.
They speak it.
So they can't be that blinded by this
authority.
You know, what they consider authority, you know,
government, university, doctors, priests, rabbis.
They can't be that blind, are they?
I would have to say yes.
I mean, looking back where I was a
way long time before ever coming across any
of this, there was no reason to look
at history.
There was no reason to move on past
what was thrown at me throughout my life.
And I guess that's what, I guess, really
bugged me when I first started looking into
history.
I was like, how in the hell did
I never get any of this?
Where was it?
Well, it's false as well, the history that
they put up.
But even with the false history, let's say,
take JFK with the magic bullet.
Sure.
I mean, at one point they say, you
know, there's no such thing as a magic
bullet.
So then you could say, wow, they're just
basically, they think so little of the public
that they're putting out bullshit and getting away
with it.
So that's part of that.
The bullshit is part of the history.
I mean, like 9-11 or any of
the events, Pearl Harbor.
You can actually include what's called the official
story or the plausibility as part of the
history to show how ridiculous the people and
the authorities really are, both sides.
So even the false history is part of
the history.
Right, right.
And it's really, really pushed and it's absorbed
by everybody and changes their way.
It's amazing.
I deal with that every day.
And I just walk away by just shaking
my head and just, oh, well, you know,
sorry to see that.
Well, it is.
It's even worse than sorry that we're here.
You know, if you do realize these things,
if you read ancient writs, it's like you
should be sorry that you're here.
I mean, it tells you not to worry.
It tells you don't, you know, don't get
mixed up with them.
Set yourself apart.
Don't, you know, there's no reason to get
anything organized to change anything because it ain't
going to happen.
Changes will happen, but you have to, and,
you know, it's interesting, ancient writs kind of,
you do catch up on the changes quickly.
They tell you, you know, what the changes
will be in society.
And if you understand how to keep time
or put them in proper placement, you'll know
whether it's in your lifetime or not.
And other than that, it's lamenting that you
were born here is actually one of the
greatest realizations anyone can have.
There's no reason to find any joy or
happiness in being born here, you see.
Once you realize that sad aspect that you
were brought into this world, then you seek
joy and happiness because you're here.
But being born here and coming here is
actually a terrible thing for a spirit and
a soul, you know, to be a spirit
with a soul and a body.
Not initially, but now it is, and it
has been for thousands of years.
So once you find yourself in that calamity,
just being born here, you can then seek
joy and happiness best you can, you see.
But the people do the opposite.
They find joy and happiness in being born.
That's a sad thing.
But now that you're here, make the best
of it, right?
So it's kind of backwards.
Yeah, but it works.
If you can make it work, yeah.
Keep it simple.
Don't complicate yourself.
If you start learning things and you can
prove them out, there's no reason to jump
in there with both feet, eyes closed again.
You might have to enter those situations or
those institutions or people or societies or whatever,
but you keep yourself guarded.
Yes, yes.
And you actually appreciate being in a minimalist
setting, a social setting, meaning a minimalist social
setting.
You know, there was a study.
I used to look a lot at the
psychology and psychiatry stuff they put out.
And you could find, because they spend their
lives researching this, you could find some good
statistical stuff, whether it's been adjusted or played
with or not.
You'll have to look at the supporting evidence.
And if the evidence looks bunk, it's probably
made up.
But what's interesting is no matter one of
the things I got out of studying this
is one of actually quite a few, just
for comparative analysis, quantitatively, is no matter whether
you grew up in a small town or
a big city or went to a big
college or a small college or exposed to
a lot of people or a few people,
your own personal group is still roughly the
same number of people.
So someone growing up in a small town
in Ohio will probably have the same number
of acquaintances and friends in their small social
group as someone who grew up in New
York City.
Let me see.
OK.
Yeah.
So there's no – in other words, you
make the – well, in other words, even
when people aren't deciding, there tends to be
a gravitational field that attracts X amount of
people on average and that's it, right?
So in a small town, you might have
four or five acquaintances and two or three
friends, the same as if you're in New
York City.
And we're not talking about passerbys that you're
familiar with and all that.
But even then, passerbys – I remember living
in big cities and the passerbys that you
greeted were still about the same as if
when I was in a small city based
on occurrence.
If you're in a small city and it's
an empty road and there's no one there,
well, of course not.
But I mean when people were around.
So – and someone put 97.25%
of statistical data is bullshit.
That's right.
It is.
That's why you've got – when they give
you statistics, they've got to show you how
they came across it and the evidence.
And that's what you study.
See, the statistics is bullshit usually because they
– that's why they've developed that system to
hide the bullshit or pass it through.
So you look at how they came across
it, right?
I mean I use statistics typically if I'm,
let's say, working on certain things and it's
repetitive statistically.
You know, when I do a – when
I apply a procedure to something and it
has to be repeated, I see that if
I repeat that procedure, do I get the
exact same results?
And what are the variables?
Right.
And then I could develop a statistic saying,
well, maybe I need to either accept the
variable, the inconsistencies, or do I change my
procedure, you see, to – Right, right.
In other words, does the variable affect the
outcome?
Right.
I mean actually scripture is statistical, believe it
or not.
Let's see what that word means.
I'll look it up real quick.
Do I even have etymology?
I got – by the way, it's a
minor inconvenience and I like it when it
happens.
I somehow accepted a Maxthon, which is a
browser I use, M-A-X-T-H
-O-N, upgrade and it wiped the bookmarks.
Oh no.
So it's kind of like going on someone
– you know, just a library computer.
Sure.
So I've got to do everything longhand.
That's why sometimes I might ask you for
a link or someone else, you know, on
Skype, just drop, do you have a link
for this?
Please drop it in, you know, or whatever.
Right.
Like this chat, I had to do a
longhand search for it.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, that's pretty – can you uninstall and
get your stuff back or are you pretty
much poached?
Yeah, it's up on a cloud somewhere.
Oh.
It's a cloud server.
Sure.
And you have to log in and it
somehow wants me to log in using something
I'm not familiar with, so.
Oh.
Yeah.
And also – I see a statistic, one
numeral statistic from 1939.
Etymology.
Yeah, in reference to a person considered as
nothing more than an example of something measured
quantity.
Right, it's quantitative.
Statistics, let's do it here.
It was just statistics.
Science dealing with data about condition, state, or
community.
From German, Statistik, popularized and perhaps coined by
German.
The science of Gottfried Aschenwald.
Okay, statistician, statistical from statistics.
Oh, click on it.
Oh, that goes back a ways there, holy
smokes.
Oh yeah.
1719, wow.
Well, that's pre-Victorian.
Yeah.
I think I discussed – there's many things
to discuss.
You know, I've been going through some notes
I've had for over a decade and I
found – I did some study on the
Victorian era, which was quite interesting because she
was like a queen and an anti-queen
at the same time, right?
Right, right.
I don't want to discuss things that people
are not familiar with because I've asked so
many people, are you familiar with the Victorian
era?
And they say, well, I've heard of it,
but I don't know anything about it.
And if you ask like a hundred people
over a year and no one knows anything
about it, you know you're not going to
– it's not a popular water cooler topic
or Skype topic.
Right, right.
So I don't discuss it.
But it's an interesting time period because that's
when a lot of the changes that you
see today have been – were made firm.
Right.
The 1880s was a big experimentation time on
human society.
So let's see.
Yeah, basically it is math.
Well, they're accrediting it more to certain people
that elevated it to, you know, whatever it's
known today, more than the use of the
word in general terms.
So it's basically bean counting, bookkeeping.
Yep.
I enjoy it because it's objective.
You know, when you're talking about – It
improves on more things, yep.
Yeah, because you can just – and most
of the Greek-speak stuff is not quantitative.
It's qualitative, I'd say.
Right.
The purpose of focusing on qualitative aspects is
because they've been abandoned generally.
So, I mean, you know, like people look
at – for years, movies, when they report
a new movie, it's how much it earned
that weekend.
That's what makes it a good movie, right?
Or a bad movie.
Right.
So I started noticing early on in life
how it didn't matter.
The quantities were a joke in terms of
what can be perceived.
It's – you're being pranked, basically.
That's another – Well, even if you get
a million dollar doll hairs to come and
watch some poor movie, and based on that
they say it's good, you know, the movies
still suck, you know.
Oh, and the entertainment industry is just crap.
Oh, God, yes.
And I have a right to say it.
I know people in there.
I mean, I have – I won't say
it.
A relative was the CEO of a major
– two major movie houses.
And I know people in the – years
ago, especially, in the – and I've met
actors and directors and people and personal acquaintance
of people I don't want to mention.
They are pretty stupid.
And I mean that in a neutral sense,
not as a put-down, not as a
pejorative.
They're not smart people, none of them.
That's such a strange world.
And when you talk about them generally, so
what do you do?
I mean, what are you doing?
This stuff is kind of – well, we're
just telling stories.
That's what they all – there's a spirit,
by the way.
There's a spirit behind it.
If you get to know like a –
let's not mention a movie studio like Paramount
Pictures.
If you get to know the CEO and
you basically have a sort of not even
a Greek-speak conversation with him but something
bordering on it, they'll just kind of roll
their eyes and like, yeah, we're just telling
stories.
So if you run into an actor like
someone who's in a major movie like The
Matrix, we're not going to mention anybody.
They'll say, oh, yeah, it's just a story.
I say, this is really dumb.
Well, that's just a story.
Or if you run into another, let's say,
an actress and say, well, this is –
why is it so superficial?
Oh, we're just telling stories.
It's like these people who don't know of
each other say the same thing.
We're just telling a story.
So this is like the Christians.
Yeah, it's a hive mentality.
That's their line.
Like the Christians, if you ask them, is
Christianity biblical?
Oh, yeah.
And they say, what about this, this and
that?
Well, we don't really do that.
Well, what about this, this and that?
Well, you see, it's based on tradition.
And then if you say, what about this,
this and that in the scripture?
Then they'll say, well, who wrote that anyway?
I don't need that to believe.
So then they end up discrediting it if
you push for more than 30 seconds.
So they have a hive mentality.
The Muslims have a hive mentality.
If you push them, they say, well, that
can't be true because the Koran was written
to be simple, and what you're saying is
not simple, so it can't be true.
That's their hive.
So they all have their hive mentality, right?
Yeah.
Usually politicians and high-end attorneys, which are
low-end, usually say, are you trying to
say we don't have a right to exist?
I've heard that from several political people and
legal people.
Yeah.
I'll tell you, the doctors, their famous line
that they all say is, well, that's what
they tell us to do.
They all say that.
You know, when you start criticizing blood pressure
and everything, they say, well, that's what they
tell us.
Like, what do you mean they?
You're the teacher.
You're the doctor educating doctors.
Oh, well, that's what's in the manual.
Okay, but you wrote the manual.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
So you notice these, when I talk about
the cosmic censorship and your mind, your thoughts
are not your own, that is one of
the quote-unquote statistical things that I put
together to come up with such a claim.
Right.
So when I make a claim like there's
cosmic censorship and your thoughts are not happening
in your head, I had seen repetitive repeating
statements from people unbeknownst to each other in
different times, in different settings, and they all
seem to say the same thing.
There has to be something behind that, etheric,
you know, spiritual, right, the guidance.
And, yeah, so once you're aware of it
and you have to guard, one thing you
find in scripture is you constantly have to
guard yourself.
And people say, well, I can't do that.
I don't want to be, you know, that'll
make me worry or whatever.
What's the old saying?
Worry is the interest you pay when you
borrow trouble, right?
Right.
That's an old saying.
So, you know, the thing is most people
are like, oh, I don't want to constantly
be a thing.
Well, you are anyway.
About dumb shit.
Right.
If you've ever been around people who have
specialized training like, you know, let's talk about
the weaponized morons like military people.
Someone who is, let's say, trained for that
as a special ops type person, they're always
on guard and they're relaxed about it.
Actually, if they weren't on guard, they wouldn't
be relaxed.
Right.
Because they need that.
In other words, these people are trained to
have a higher sense of greater input.
Another example would be musicians.
How many times have, well, let's just say
you walk into a room and you hear
someone playing.
You're like, oh, that instrument's out of tune.
And they're like, really?
I'm like, yeah, it's out of tune.
You better stop playing and tune that.
Right?
Right.
If it's a wind instrument, you know, the
reed needs to be tightened or replaced.
The string instrument, obviously, the tensions need to
be adjusted.
You know, I remember, not recently, but fairly
recently, I walked into a place, a piano
man was playing.
I said, that soundboard sounds cracked.
This piano is out of tune.
No, we just tuned it.
See, there's a crack in the soundboard.
You know, the soundboard is where all the,
right?
Right.
You open the top, right?
Okay.
Right.
And then later on, I discovered, I said,
let me look in there.
And I said, there's a crack in the
soundboard.
Well, how can I hear that?
You know, I mean, most people don't hear
that.
Right.
Because I know what, I had heard a
piano with a cracked soundboard, and I knew
it.
And you remember.
And it's not, okay, some people say, well,
that's too much detail.
I'm not interested in that.
Well, that's fine.
You're just a, you know, whatever.
I know the feeling about when you walk
into a room and something's out of tune,
you know, immediately.
Yeah.
And years ago in the mining, working with
mines and stuff, there was a couple of
people that were around.
There were ex, high level, I should say,
intelligence people that were, got kind of, they
stole enough money or whatever from, and they
left, and they were semi-retired, and they
hung around the mines and stuff.
And, you know, we're in the car one
day, and a guy says, you know, we're
being followed.
And I said, what do you mean?
He says, well, I don't, well, no, not
the car behind us, and not the car
behind that, but two cars behind that.
You know, you see that yellow pickup?
That's been following us for the past few
hours.
You know, and I'm like, wow, I didn't
notice that.
You know, you don't follow someone like the
movies, you know.
Right.
Directly behind them, you follow from a distance.
In other words, if they're in your sight,
you're being, well, you're following someone, they're in
your sight, whether it's a mile or half
a mile, you know, whatever.
It could be a couple of miles.
As long as you know where they are,
that's following them.
Right?
So, and we put that to a test.
You know, we pulled off a highway, went
into shops or whatever, and that car, again,
came off.
Yep.
It didn't go where we were going, but
we were in line of sight.
And I was like, holy shit, this guy
is right.
How the hell did he pick up on
that?
In other words, our field of view was
the immediate car or the immediate surroundings.
This guy's field of view, he was trained
to be as far as the eye can
see.
Right.
You know, in perspective, right?
Yeah.
And recognize.
So, I learned right there.
I said, wow, this is a good idea
or a good mindset to have.
You know, when you're going to take in
a field of view or a field of
perception, use it.
Don't say, well, that's further away than this,
so I don't need to pay attention to
it.
No, you actually should look at everything.
But, again.
You have to exercise it.
You have to.
Yeah.
Keep it aligned.
Yeah, just like the gym.
If you go into the gym the first
couple of days, you won't be able to
use everything there.
You'll be really sore.
If you keep going to the gym like
everyone else, after a year or two, you'll
benefit.
So, again, these are things not for most
people.
But I think anyone with an earshot can
use it.
So, there we go.
If there's nothing going on, let's see.
The New Greek Speak chat, I see nine
people.
Any questions?
Nothing, really?
Inbox?
Nothing?
Yeah, we can make it a short one,
unless someone wants to call in or say
something.
Right.
Or do something.
You have many ways to call in, folks.
The contact information, of course, is Greek's email
address, theuncommonsenseradio1 at gmail.com.
Or you can call into live, colon, question
everything, colon.
Okay, cool.
We'll let that mosey on down the stream.
Takes a little bit to get to everybody.
So, you can get a telephone number by
using the browser of Google or Skype or
whatever.
I think through a fee.
Yeah, you don't have to call the telephone
company anymore, right?
No, no.
Okay, good.
There's many, many ways.
Right, and there are apps, I know, for
cell phones.
Okay.
So, that entire convention has happened to stay
within the realm.
Really, really break along and got away from
Mobile in a lot of ways.
Right, but it doesn't work the same way,
right?
No, no.
So, do you hear the background music?
I'm going to turn this down.
Yes, I do.
It's a lovely music.
Yeah, okay.
I'm going to turn that down.
So, I'm pretty much wired for sound here.
Okay, I guess if there isn't much, is
there anything else on your mind, Bruce?
Let's see.
What else?
You know, I was thinking about trusses, the
things that people tie them.
You know, I notice more and more.
Trusses as in what, structural?
Belts, things that people tighten themselves down with
in order to keep their garments on and
everything.
So many people just walk around with these
things so bloody tight on themselves.
It's like, how in the hell?
And then you notice how they always have
these different irritabilities with themselves and abdominal problems.
Well, girding oneself is good if you do
it evenly.
Right.
Yeah, but not as a point source like
a strap.
Yeah.
That would be annoying.
If you go to the ghetto, it's the
opposite.
They don't have belts.
Right.
It's a matter of letting everything fall.
Yeah, there's plenty of that around.
Well, yeah.
I was telling someone the New World Order
is not what you think.
It's about getting everyone to wear sneakers with
no shoelaces, their pants hanging down, their baseball
hat tilted to the side.
Improper use of language.
You know, this ghetto, the black American ghetto.
Ebonics.
Yeah, ebonics, being into the culture.
That's your New World Order, one of the
implements.
It's not this, yeah, dystopian.
Yeah, exactly.
It's working.
It's one of the tools.
And they don't even know.
That's one of the tools that's been used
for a while.
You know, you had me thinking ever since
you mentioned about the subtle effects and everything.
Boy, that's left me thinking for weeks on
that and looking around.
Oh, yeah.
There's an interesting, someone sent me a link
to a YouTube recently.
I think it's 54 Minutes Media and 9
-11, like hints in the media from 9
-11.
It's 54 Minutes.
Okay.
I don't think I bookmarked it.
It was something about clues to 9-11
in the media.
It's around 50 some odd minutes.
And it goes back to the 70s where
they showed jet airplanes going into the Twin
Towers, like a G.I. Joe cartoon.
Right, yeah.
And it's just, some of them you kind
of have to, it's kind of like pushing
it a little.
But most of them were just direct.
I mean, just really direct.
Oh, my.
You know, hundreds of examples of the Twin
Towers coming down, even like in wrestling with
Hulkmania.
It's like, look, those Twin Towers are going
to be knocked down.
You know, they keep saying that.
No matter how strong they are, they're going
to be.
So, I mean, at that time, from the
70s.
Well, how did you say it?
They're telling a story.
Yeah.
And even when they did come down, they
told you a story.
That's not how they came down at all.
Right.
If they were on fire on September 11,
2001, still burning, they would still be burning
and be just fine.
You know, they would still be standing if
the fires were burning that long.
This is how things really are.
But in a sense, what are you being
shown right now that you don't see?
Well, here's a personal, I mean, direct, firsthand
experience.
What I was doing, July, August of 2001,
I was telling people, watch this Osama bin
Laden guy.
Kind of like later on, I heard a
Bill Cooper say that.
Bill Cooper, a few months before, and I
was just, they're going to blame it on
Osama bin Laden.
And I didn't know about Bill Cooper.
I think it was Seth who turned me
on to Bill Cooper by talking about him.
I was telling people, I remember I was
with a mining engineer in 2001.
I was doing some mural work and saying,
this Osama bin Laden guy is in the
news a lot lately.
They're going to do something with this guy.
Just watch it.
Ah, no, no, that will never happen.
No, no, our security forces got everything under
control.
I said, I don't know.
And I saw him after 9-11.
I said, I told you that they were
going to do something with Osama bin Laden.
He was just quiet.
And someone else I knew, it was the
beginning of what they call September.
He says, this is an interesting month to
watch.
Remember 9-11?
This is the 9-11 month.
I was like, really?
And before that, someone approached me.
He was in insurance.
He was like, how's your credit score?
I'm like, well.
He says, well, you better have a good
credit score because the world is going to
go into a security business.
And it's going to be people with good
credit scores are going to get good positions
in the security business.
So if you want to get it.
I'm like, what do you mean security business?
He says, well, your security business is going
to boom.
Watch.
And it's good to get your stuff in
order now before it comes out.
I was like, what did this guy know?
So there you go.
Very subtle.
But you just go through with it.
Right now, all the subtleties are how quiet
it is.
You might say that a lot of the
things were put in place prior past few
years in the situation, whether it's American politics
or international geopolitics.
Many of the things that you still see
transpiring were put in place weeks, months, years
before.
But the thing is that you're not getting
new little jabs of attention seeking stories like
they call them stories.
So that means that they're trying to figure
out how they're going to do it.
And I think these things are going to
stick.
Because, see, for example, I keep bringing this
up, the next biological, what do you call
them when they have flu epidemics and things
like that?
The epidemics.
It's not going to be like the past
ones.
If you've ever seen videos of the WHO,
the World Health Organization, they laugh about it.
Yeah, we told people it was an epidemic
and they all cried for vaccines.
We told them they all wanted it and
they were laughing.
Well, when you're going to start getting the
next epidemic, it's going to stick.
In other words, it's not going to go
away.
In other words, whether it is an epidemic
or not, it's going to be made more
so you have to comply to some bizarre
demand.
I don't call them laws.
They're demands.
And that's why I was telling someone who
was going to court recently, I said, well,
I said I broke this law.
No, that's a demand because that law is
not being used right because by definition, it
doesn't apply to you.
So if you go in there, don't say
the word law.
Say demand.
You get it?
Anyway, when they tell you you can't smoke
pot on the public bus, no, that's not
a law.
That's a demand.
They demand that you don't smoke pot on
the local bus.
How do they demand it?
Well, there's a guy going to come in
a uniform, a Leo, and he's going to
hit you over the head.
That's how they enforce it.
They're not laws.
They're demands.
Even though Charlie brought up this public policy,
not public policy, they're demands.
I don't get so stern about it because
once a topic is brought up and I'm
enthusiastic about it, an hour will shoot by.
So what you'll see is things that are,
they'll be reintroduced into the mindset and they're
going to stick a little bit more, stick
around, I should say.
But it is rather quiet, but I don't
see it as being quiet.
One of the things that I see is
the further reaching of what they call Iranian
politics or Persia.
They're trying to reach out further, and they
are, because they're a superpower.
They've always been, I should say, well, since
the French and the English got out of
there.
Well, I say definitely from the late 70s,
80s until now, they are a superpower in
the Middle East just as Israel is.
And I wouldn't say they're competing because wherever
you see the Israeli Mossad, you see the
Persian mob.
If that makes any sense.
I'm not going to get into that detail
because if I start getting into details of
that, it's going to sound like I know
more than I should be talking about.
But let's just put it this way.
There are central places where there are Israeli
Mossad.
And believe it or not, Tokyo is one
of the largest populations and places in Asia
where you have Mossad.
And who works with them side by side
is the Persian mob.
And the Persian mob are involved in things
that are pretty unusual in itself, mostly financial,
by the way.
Not as nefarious as most people would say,
like, you know, the drugs, human trafficking and
assassinations and these types of things.
Not as much as that as actually just
purely financial stuff.
And they do manage to get in a
lot of different areas that you're not a
common to see in them.
The Persian mob, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
They have several factions.
So either way, watch Iran as a superpower,
not going away as a superpower.
As a matter of fact, in the future,
what you call Iran, well, they're going to
rework politically because they're, again, puppets like the
rest of most governments.
But they're going to be reworked and reunified
in a way where they will actually be
allies with Israel in a sense like financial
and supportive allies versus the public opposition and
adversarialness that you see now.
So, yeah.
I noticed Russia is fading away finally.
Not as much.
In terms of American politics.
Right.
They are Russia, China, Malaysia, Indonesia.
You know, like what about Malaysia, Indonesia?
Those places have huge populations, by the way,
workforces.
And if you go anywhere, like from Malta
all the way to Saudi Arabia, all the
way, you know, the island of Malta, all
the way across that whole rim down even
to India.
Most of the workers come from Malaysia, Indonesia.
The people do the labor.
So, because they work.
You think Mexicans work for cheap?
They really work for cheap, you know.
And I would say that that whole region
is going to start harmonizing and working together.
You know, they're going to be the satellite
forces around the Middle East.
I mean, it is right now.
If you go to places like Kuwait, everyone
in the service industry is, they're not Kuwaiti.
They are from that Pacific Rim, usually in
India.
So, yeah.
But again, this is a condition, like, you
know, bring back what Dimitri, I think he
put it together really well in those short
videos.
The concept of a sovereign state is what
you see running on the world right now.
That is the new world order.
And this was assembled during the Victorian times.
You know, and America, of course, is used
as an example of the sovereign state.
Right.
You know, because it has a little bit
of everything.
Yeah, yeah.
And the real world leaders, the ones you
hear about them spiritually, are the sons of
gods and the people behind, you know, behind
the sovereign state.
We don't know who they are.
They have a very good apparatus or apparati,
is that the plural, to maintaining secrecy.
It doesn't mean that they have disclosed who
they are, but not as the owners of
the states known as the world countries.
You know, the hundred and whatever, 80 countries
on the UN, those are all sovereign states.
So anybody on the UN, those are all
the same thing.
So the rhetoric that you hear there is
just that, you know.
So you're pretty much finished.
But you don't know that you are, so
that's the best part about it, you know,
in terms of being under global and viewed
as property.
In other words, you are in the worst
possible political, lawful, legal state you can be.
Everyone on the planet is right now.
But it's not as bad as it's going
to be in the future.
But you are in the worst possible.
In other words, if it got overtly, if
people knew really what was going on, there
would be less order than there is now.
That's why it's the worst possible.
And it would be for the wrong reasons.
If you ask them why they're rioting, they
don't know.
It's like the cartoon boondocks.
You just throw a chair, a folding chair,
and a riot starts, and no one knows
why they're rioting.
Just someone threw a chair.
Gustav would get in there, and somebody would
take hold, and everybody would be following.
It's rather organized and predictive.
All right, if there isn't anything else, let's
just call it.
I don't see anything in there either.
No calls or nothing.
Yeah, okay, that's fine.
All right, we'll do it again next week.
Okay, well, you take care, Greg, and thank
you very much.
You're welcome.
I'll see you again.
Yes, you have a good night now.
Bye.