And greetings everyone we're live with the Greek
and how are you doing tonight Greek?
Greetings.
Yeah, it looks like this might be a
another short sonic.
Maybe we'll see everything seems to be going
along as expected so Yeah, it's cold by
Where were you say about central continent of
America slightly to the north?
I'm often Wisconsin mid mid, Wisconsin Hmm yeah,
I noticed the idiots are complaining about how
somebody's jamming up the jet stream And it's
not moving Well, I happen to just I
left a small device in a tree Pointing
West it's actually very well isolated It's actually
not really in a tree, but it appears
to be very well isolated and very small
and it took about eight nine days, and
it's just Translating quite well Yeah But anyway,
anybody could play with this kind of stuff.
I rotated everything I rotated pointing north now,
so it's gonna make the block a little
more severe Then it'll just break it in
about two days.
I know everything will reverse you'll get warm
weather I'm looking forward to it Mm-hmm
Yeah, like I said earlier are there any
questions or any comments or anything and not
much I mean This kind of talk is
not for this society or the people on
this planet But you know it happens to
exist You know and it happens to be
done so so you're mentioning something.
There was a comment.
I'm going on the chat right now Let's
yeah I Got I looked into that Olaf
Alex Anderson what a fascinating gent Yeah, the
the guy who the Swiss architect who wrote
about Schauberger's work.
I know this was one that was playing
with the beetle in levitating bow up right
that's a perendikov I thought that was Olaf
and Alex and Olaf Alex Anderson is the
Swiss architect that Or from Sweden you're right.
You're all right.
That's right.
He for different Articles and I might have
got that back for perendikov is the other
guy with the insect chitin Yeah, and he
made he made some shutters on a little
platform he's a little brown and Also, he
noticed that you know tubular Paper tubes painted
black you could bunch them up and Make
certain Let's say phenomenon right yeah the insects
were able to notice immediately right right Fascinating
guy Yeah, he talked about Schauberger a little
bit, but mm-hmm.
It's all it's all a mixed bag.
This is this is a broken Divided kingdom
you know it's a slave Kingdom you know
that the earth was given up to Especially
after the flood more than prior to the
various deities You know you know them as
patron deities right and They're not very they're
they're hostile, and they're in different hostile and
different Proactive and getting people to do the
wrong thing and make them allow them think
it's the right thing And this has been
going on for thousands of years That's why
if you just discuss a myopic version of
existence Which is you know what happened in
the past few hours or the last two
weeks?
Everyone's into it because that's part of the
censorship.
That's part of the The you know what
the effect of that you know so interesting
how that comes about and the many different
facets that are used to do it and
Quite quite interesting yeah to be a lot.
You know don't be rebellious.
Don't be stubborn, so if you had slaves
the which is expensive just like you know
people for example in the American especially Vernacular
or parlance discuss slavery as being a bad
thing because they're only taught about let's say
the American you know the the African Americans
or the blacks that were brought over here
Mistreated that's not true.
They were not mistreated Yes, they did you
know once they became more educated and so
it was going on popularly They didn't couldn't
have that kind of life, but slaves are
mistreated in the same way a Farmer today
would mistreat a quarter of a million dollar
Columbine harvester yeah, right If a farmer goes
out if you know any farmers, and he
goes out and spends 50 grand on a
brand new tractor He doesn't mistreat it no
right That's equipment You know just like people
in the military don't mistreat their equipment or
any you know a shoemaker doesn't mistreat his
tools They're the slaves are human tools.
You don't mistreat them right what the the
concept of mistreatment comes in on?
A subjective level depending on the actual concurrent
master because you have concurrent mouth you have
you know this plantation here as a master
Then they you know the next geographic area.
You know because slavery also has geographic Attributes
to it right if you're a slave in
South Carolina in in Massachusetts let's say you're
going to probably have different tasks than someone
down in you know in Louisiana right, Louisiana,
you'll be You know probably wet You know
and and working in a different industry Then
in the cold dry of Boston and don't
think that the north didn't have slaves So
they're not being mistreated other than what each
master decides for them right So again back
to the slave when you have slaves What
is what do you have to have for
them other than you know tasks right is
you have food clothing shelter?
Right so let's not this is a slave
existence, so don't be Dreaming about anything so
if you focus on food clothing and shelter
if you don't think you're a slave you're
an idiot Right because you're on a plantation
even the politicians say this politicians running the
country like a plantation This is you know
you could look this up.
I think Hillary Clinton said that that Bush
Yeah, so So food clothing shelter and minimize
oppression and the way you minimize oppression is
by minimal interaction By just it by by
choice if you have it some people don't
have a choice if you're a barista at
a cafe well Overtly you will not have
minimum interaction obviously because you'll probably be interacting
with no less than Several hundred people you
know and half part of your day at
least if it's a busy place not a
thousand But you don't have to interact with
them on the level that they're used to
interacting emotionally personally socially And it's difficult You
know it's difficult So but it still can
be done so Until it's over and later
on you're gonna notice the 50 70 80
90 hundred years whatever was nothing It was
a blink of an eye in in relevant.
You know time you know in terms of
Suffering something with people say oh, they're suffering
someone recently said oh, I'm suffering old suffering
what?
suffering means to voluntarily or Cognitively endure it
You know that's why if you ever know
you've been around any of these real smart
judges You know when someone sues a police
officer right and and the the attorney that's
defending the guy suing the state let's say
quote-unquote state and the quote-unquote police
officer they set up the The his client
sets up his client as a victim right
all right by the way there are no
good attorneys right there Semi-competent and incompetent,
but there are no good at you know
so anyway He'll put that he suffered You
know all these injuries and all this other
stuff well, that means it's voluntary And the
judge always s he sticks on that point
he'll ask the plaintiff.
He says did you suffer those injuries?
From the police officer allegedly says yes, I
did okay dismissed case dismissed right that means
you you know you were okay with it
All right yeah the word suffer means The
that you know it's what's cut it's like
the Greek tragedy They tell you what's going
to happen at the beginning of the story
right right they go, and then they go
through with it so Anyway, so when someone
says they're suffering.
I always ask what what are you suffering?
I know is what are you?
Deciding that you need to endure Yeah Anyway,
we could go look at etymology Oh Let's
see what etymology says it's obviously an origin
of some sort So if you're a slavery
is voluntary by the way, and this is
something that people don't understand because they're too
stupid of course But you know you could
look it up There's plenty of some what
they call the founding fathers America one of
them got famous He was an attorney because
he defended someone who claimed to be an
African King, and he never volunteered So they
quit they queried him on all the various
things that he did and he didn't volunteer
So they send him back with full fare.
You know mm-hmm Here suffer verb allow
to occur or continue permit tolerate fail to
prevent or suppress Pretty much sums that one
right up Yeah, another one that I asked
someone to look up Which I had read
somewhere was the word federal people think it
has something to do with the government it
doesn't It's a term that's used to just
like justice has nothing to do with law,
but it's used to Okay, federal adjective.
It's a theological term and reference to covenants
between God and man guess what God they
What do you ever heard of something called
the apotheosis of?
George Washington where they got that moron up
in the Capitol Dome They have him sitting
in a throne looking down at you with
angels around him You know right feels is
when you raise a man to a godlike
level to be worried on a level of
worship Yeah, so anyway, it's a planet full
of morons.
What are you gonna?
Do you know like they say?
Stay the hell out of the way Yeah,
food clothing shelter.
You'll learn a lot.
I remember once we did a sonic with
Sam Sam is young You know and he
says well, and I said food clothing shelter,
and he's well.
That's really Based you know or that's really
what I said no because if you pursue
those things you're gonna learn about everything else
yeah Quick it's the wax on wax off
and karate kid you know right Why am
I doing this you'll see later yeah, oh,
yeah And here's the thing The thing about
what's coming.
I noticed here to scroll up in the
chat this guy I see Nathan put in
what is it didn't choose RSS feed.
What is he doing there?
I haven't was having troubles with their With
his podcast he posted yeah, I see yeah
podcasting Those things are not meant to be
listened to by anyone by the way Those
Greek speak things are not meant to be
listened to by anyone if you think you're
someone maybe you can handle it Not many
come back, but the any ones but the
any ones can't handle it so Um Yeah,
here's the thing if you heard me talk
about and time stuff or speaking on it
It's going to happen really fast once it
starts.
You know mm-hmm Everything is in place
if you know what to look for that's
why I always give all the details in
a way that I don't give details on
this on the actual events once they start
happening Just a you just need a generality,
but I give a lot of details on
what to look for now For it to
be put in place right So Sputnik news
is that the one you're talking about yeah,
that's what I was talking about yeah Chat
oh no There's a I got the guy
nailed to a cross wearing a diaper Yeah,
or a loin cloth or a girdle in
this case with the in that's the Eastern
Orthodox version of it Also, they're a bunch
of morons Are we gonna predict it as
Jews call for third temple to be built
yeah, it doesn't work that way well Armageddon
har Megiddo har Is they translate to arm?
And then Megiddo is the odd Megiddon, which
would be the Greek very way to say
it Megiddon Don't Megiddon or Armageddon Is a
place it's before the final battle.
It's a gathering place the battle is not
at Armageddon I mean obviously you know when
a battle starts it starts right, but it's
right.
It's it's the launching point for the battle
against Anyway Yeah these things that you know
there are articles like this in the 60s
Biblical conspiracy theorists Where's the conspiracy in the
Bible?
I mean this is really still who's the
author and who is Middle East written doesn't
say no You should we should email them
tell me you're a f-ing moron The
person I mean just shows you they're a
product of the university system Yeah, they don't
even know how to write, and they're probably
interviewing idiots or you know right Yeah It's
not even worth reading yeah, I'm gonna look
at it, okay But no that that stuff
has been going on for a actually You
want to really get down and dirty on
stupid predictions?
Mid 19th century there was forever the Millerites
the Millers You know he said you know
there would be you got everyone to sell
possessions and all that and took advantage of
prostitutes Right because you may get some free
a lot free tail He was a all
these people are horrible people that are public
figures.
I mean which Which one of these evangelists
is not a pedophile a satanist or whatever
which one is isn't now which one is
Right you get it right you know It
was oh this this is this guy came
out to be a pedophile and a satanist
this of a Christian evangelist Really which one
is not That's the one that should be
in the news not the one that is
because they're all they all are There's a
general rule this because they're they're part of
the system It's a state.
You know there's no form of evangelism that
will take place unless the state or the
legal society the Justice Society and the Owners
of the country put their seal of approval
on directly or indirectly acquiesce to it so
Yeah Make a long story short The Millerites
back.
I guess I'm the term was Miller.
He came up with the rupture.
I call it.
You know the rapture Okay, well at the
end wasn't it because the rapture has to
come first of the rupture.
There is no that words not even in
Scripture mm-hmm, so You're talking about you
know anyway There's not there's there's no relief
food clothing shelter.
Yeah, you're not gonna get any cognizant Food
out there anything that it's for the mind
Which by the way I was having a
conversation recently with someone who's censored about many
of the things that I say And I
was trying to explain them like all right
go do research this way You know like
even today the quote-unquote most advanced Scientists
cutting-edge and all that are looking for
the mind Right in the but they understand
the brain They Believe I mean they're constantly
researching it and evolving their you know mapping
out the biology and the chemistry and the
physicality And what it does allegedly But they
don't know where the mind is they don't
see the you know what animates you in
the brain They see certain motor function connections,
but you have motor function connections to everything
yeah, you know not just the limbs But
let's say if you damage the kidneys your
motor functions are damaged Right as a matter
of fact if you increase motor functions you
affect the kidneys from the adrenal gland right
mm-hmm, so anyway Yeah, they need to
listen to some girl they don't need to
cuz though you know, but anyway Yeah, there's
not much just not much going on This
is what's cool about it though is we
started another seven year period that the middle
of it.
Let's see will be Around 2020 2020 will
be about the middle of it, and you're
gonna see a resurgence Not necessarily as public
as it could be even though.
It will be like the idiot who wrote
that article about The biblical conspiracy theory I
mean what a poor choice of words like
someone says I'm suffering.
I was suffering what anyway There's gonna be
a resurgence in what I've spoken of they've
been speaking of for years and years people
are gonna go back to Basics enough.
I'm gonna say wait a second.
What is this supposed to be based on
and Obviously this is the time for the
gods, and it's going to be obviously discussion
on you know how come we're not even
Acknowledging the biblical text you know forget about
religion surrounded You know in the academia is
worthless academia is a prank You know you're
stupid enough to go beyond the eighth grade
now.
We got a really good prank for you.
You know And yeah, so there's gonna be
there's gonna be like a research this you
know the good thing about it You know
sometimes.
I'll go online do reference work and the
the AI or whatever you know the algorithms
be on YouTube We're trying to recommend things
they can't figure me out right.
I'm looking at stuff regarding audio You know
sometimes news items sometimes this Sometimes you know
electrical stuff or reference material They can't figure
me out and just to screw them up
sometimes.
I'll put in their Barbie doll molds.
You know or whatever and Pokemon I'll put
that just to screw them up sure you
know so because doesn't make any sense Oh,
maybe they'll think it's two people you know
using so anyway They send me stuff about
like some kind of secret space program or
whatever and most of it was kind I
looked into a little bit.
I was like all right secret space program
What was that these morons are talking about
they don't even know they can't tell the
difference between their ass and a paper bag
We're gonna talk about secret space programs, which
do exist by the way just like everything
is everything is a secret and space is
not what you think it is, but It's
a fluid, but a fluid medium like gas.
You know gas is a fluid man.
I'd say liquid.
I said fluid right Like think of the
ocean, but less dense.
I've been I said this for publicly a
long time ago I want to know what
outer space is like.
Do you know what do you know about
the ocean except?
It's not water Saline water, it's a gas
various gases and liquids there are liquids out
there by the way Yeah, and what do
you know about the the solar system?
You know they tell you there's nine planets
or eight planets or ten pilots or whatever
But do you know there's at least 20
dwarf planets that if you were aware of
that some of those planets would you know
be?
Pretty sizable.
I mean yeah people don't talk about this
about 30 or 40 planets out there Including
the major ones they're called planet toys or
dwarf planets, but they're sizable I mean they
approach the size of the moon if you
know half Half to half the size of
the moon, but you know it's sizable around
large enough Yeah, so yeah, of course.
There's a space program, but anyway look at
so just as predicted I don't focus on
these idiots, but they're they're at war with
each other I noticed Though some of these
videos were on YouTube were about them bad
-mouthing each other and fighting each other perfect
What a better way to get right rid
of a bunch of stupid people Than to
get them to just kill each other off,
and I'm not I don't mean that literally
They're going to be killing each other.
They will later, but right now.
They're just Destroying each other from internally you
know so a little catfish is a man
Yeah, a catfight between women or whatever yes,
I noticed so be aware of these Like
environmental groups, I'll be fighting each other.
You know these alternative media people.
I think they're already gone through several fights
Right the political fight that you see going
on between Democratic and Republicans in America was
when the country was sold and you know
Bought went under privately and that's happened in
the 1800s, right?
So you just get them to fight amongst
themselves.
It's very efficient that way But look for
that because all this bullshit that people are
involved in not some of it all of
it is Got to go because they're going
to have to acknowledge a certain level of
lawfulness Before they're taken out as a society
you know like I've mentioned before the gods
will not execute judgment, or they will not
execute Let's say what they call apocalyptic mayhem
until people acknowledge why it's being done or
they from the Either the seat of their
pants or their their mouth or in writing
or thought they have to acknowledge that What
is lawful?
and whether they what it whether they Pose
it as a contrast to what they're doing
for repentance You know which is to reverse
what you're doing whatever is irrelevant he says
they just have to acknowledge it and then
the mop-up clues got the mop-up
crew has got the Yeah, do you have
a mop-up clue?
Yeah the mop-up crew?
has the green light Hmm and there's no
fix.
There's no one said Greek.
Would you stop them?
Hell no stop them up if I knew
the mop-up crew was coming later in
an hour.
I'd say hold on guys Come over.
I'm gonna make you some really good coffee
and some sandwiches, so you got your energy
You know You see because there's no other
way to fix this you either want to
fix it or not It's like a dental
problem or whatever you do you want to
fix it or not right you're going to
have to quote-unquote suffer Yeah, if you
want to fix the the man's condition you're
gonna have to suffer the destruction Sorry Get
over it.
It's like it's like The pain that you
feel when you jump into a cool or
not and say cold, but cool pool of
water it is painful You know like the
first day at the beach.
Yeah, you know early summer first day at
the beach.
Yeah, yeah, it's pain Yeah, and then it's
okay, so So you learn either way real
quick yeah Someone mentioned the tablets of thought
worth discussing never heard of this net really
well The worth of it is you know
one man's Treasure is another man's junk right
yeah Go on the internet to me and
most of its junk except for reference material
Even current events you're gonna have to figure
out the rationale Behind it like California's burning.
I'm like well depends on who you ask.
It's a bad thing Yeah, you know there's
you know certain powers want it to burn
You know from a general perspective.
Well most of the planets going to be
burning Later anyway, but from the general perspective
the owners do want it to burn.
Why the fuck not?
The people on the ground are scratching their
head because they believe all the propaganda Through
some minimal correspondence with someone that recent fire
that burned really fast It was supposedly a
campfire, and then there it wasn't a camp
no one says there was no campfire.
You know who started It's like I've gotten
witnesses from Australia when they had those bad
fires.
It was started and people had witnessed it
being started You know what it took like
six hours for the fire crews to come
in there.
You know so it's just bullshit Let him
burn you know Tough, you know tough shit
isn't it so by the way if you're
if you're smart There are ways.
Let's say you live in in California or
near not in because you can't live in
California But what they call a forested area
that that's dry there are ways to quote
-unquote fireproof Your dwelling and you'll be like
the one that didn't burn down, right?
So I'm not going to get into they're
very simple ways, and it doesn't involve water,
and it doesn't involve clearing You know yeah,
but you're going to need you know even
a messy vineyard or a messy You know
any of this messy landscape area or place
where you have growth is easy to burn
So you don't want it to be messy
and you can clear a large area and
that won't really help either because the wind
can fly the ashes over and if Once
the fire starts to have something called convection.
You know like air convection and you can
have 50 mile an hour winds blowing Fist
-sized chunks of hot you know coals right
on your house, so how are you gonna?
How are you gonna fireproof that right?
but anyway You could there's things you can
do, but you know what I'm going to
say about that why bother Because here's the
thing the way the quote-unquote attorneys set
everything up for the owners You know what
they call the state the fake state, or
it is really the state You know the
way they set it up same way like
when you build a house without a building
permit they know you're doing it and they
They know you're fireproofing.
They know you're building a house up or
they wait Until you succeed and then they
come take it away from you because it's
worth more Yeah, you see it all the
time if someone's building a house without a
permit They'll wait for you to finish and
when you got the curtains up and the
you know Everything Yep, then they come and
take it because they can get more for
it than if they stop you in between
right yeah So when you prevent the house
from burning down the state will come and
take it away And say we're condemning it
anyway because it's unsafe to live in this
area That's the way the attorneys work.
You know yeah It's illegal it's demonic.
It's it's the typical and the people are
so Censored they can't see it.
That's why you can't fix it.
You can't help them Separate yourself, and then
just hope that they it gets cleaned up.
You know when you look at turds in
a toilet Do you hope they just turn
into sunflowers and strawberries and cinnamon sticks?
Is that what you do when you look
at turds in the toilet you say oh?
I when is this turd gonna turn into?
strawberry shortcake That's ridiculous.
It's never gonna happen you flush it When
you look at the current people in this
society that you can't fix them they have
to be flushed Sorry not my opinion not
my desire not my whatever.
I it's just the logical You know but
it is a rational desire by the way
It's not my desire, but anyone is rational
and knows the truth.
We'll see that as it is a level
way to do it Okay, do you hear
the music in the background should I turn
that down by the way just a smidge?
But you know actually I'd like it so
Okay Let's see as a concept here Okay
Yeah, that's Egyptian if I reckon the Egyptians
were Quite interesting, and if you want to
talk about the space programs and all that
if you anyone that studies Egyptology, you know
there's different types of Egypt also There is
the the original original which we have very
little about then there's the divided kingdom right
mm-hmm Then you have the old dynasty
which united them Right and then you have
the newer dynasties which incorporated the Greeks and
Whatever, but if you if you look at
across the board, you know later on you
know they became very secular Let's say, but
they're very cosmic in other words.
They're really looking into the the neaters you
know the gods and Space out there and
inner space also you know meaning the the
the levels of science that they got into
was The Symbology is is not about just
symbology.
It's about representing things that are intangible You
know something is intangible you have a symbol
for it and their accuracy was was astounding
to Their what their their accuracy on their
star stars and things and geometry yeah Sure
sure sure most cold, but I would say
the best were the Sumerians and Also the
known to be in other words Well there's
it's hard to be in if you're doing
star work or astronomical work It's hard to
be inaccurate Because you do use it's like
if you're looking at a clock.
Well.
You know the mechanical clock.
What time is it 557?
Well is it 557 or is it 556?
Oh, sorry.
It's 556 right, but there's not Why you
read in other words the accuracy comes from
are you reading it or not?
There's not there's not much Yeah, anyone who
studies Anything that is a highly refined.
You know reference system will always be accurate
but the ones that I Bring up on
the Sumerians is because perhaps we have more
records overt records of what was up there
From them rain and the methodologies they try
to pen certain Movements that were repeat repeatable
repeatable and rep repetitive and They also had
a higher thinking they use a lot of
math, but not solely math right so Yeah,
right now.
They just got a bunch of asshole mathematicians.
It doesn't matter if it's medical Philosophical philosophical
Scientific physics, whatever they're all just math.
You know based on math and mathematics You
know that's why they tell you about photons
or some of the photon.
You know how you spell photon fa ux
to n, right?
All right, there's not much going on I
see there's I've got a bunch of emails
believe it or not again stuff that I've
gone over Mm-hmm and a couple of
them are like if you don't feel like
discussed You don't think it should be discussed
and don't discuss it.
I'm not You know Again, I've gone over
most of the stuff You know one question
here is like birds and trees and scripture.
Well, what about it?
You know when you're communicating it Here's the
thing I've always said scripture says what it
means and means what it says But you
have to take it in context because there
are metaphors there So when you give a
metaphor or an analogy and it's taken as
such and illustrated as such does the analogy
mean what it's saying?
Say what it mean?
Yes You know and you know if it's
figurative literal and I mean an analogy and
a metaphor is literal because it's it's Presented
as such to be taken So the thing
is are you getting the communication or not?
And the answer to that is no most
people can't really Get the communication that's held
in the scripture and it's fine It's better
to be familiar with it though Then not
be familiar with it familiar means, you know,
you've read it once or you know It's
like when you download a program on the
internet, you know, you haven't used it yet.
But are you familiar with it?
Yeah, I downloaded it because I need it
for let's say Video editing or whatever you
graphics or number credit.
Yeah, I know I'm familiar with that, but
I know I have not used it I'm
not aware of what you know the ins
and outs of it Right.
Mm-hmm.
So it's better at least, you know, say
you've downloaded it to a certain degree So
And generally again most the messages I get
are just you know, I'm not gonna say
stupid but they are I'm not gonna brand
them as stupid to disencourage anyone from sending
emails But if you think you're writing something,
that's not Whatever don't write it.
Just don't bother sending it.
I'm not, you know, trying to discourage anyone
but again, it's just typical human stuff, you
know, I Mean if I if I get
emails and messages, it's usually gonna be from
humans from planet Earth, right?
Right, so you expect don't expect much And
I don't want anything from Alpha fucking Centauri
either So, you know, I'm not saying that,
you know, I Don't know I don't see
much every Yeah, not much going on.
There's always something going on if you if
you've got mobility In very and you take
that term how you like it, you know
There means getting up off your chair walking
across the room or wherewithal, you know access
to things use it And just to pass
the time, you know that a certain degree
you want time to pass by fast Personally,
I'll tell you like the past 10 years
passed like a few months for me.
Yeah, I'm glad for it I hope the
next 10 years passes like a few days
and I'm out of here This is not
it.
It's kind of like when you're in the
waiting room Do you want it to go
by real slow or do you want the
waiting room to go by fast?
You say great, right?
This is a waiting room So Yeah, and
I'm and yeah, it's not entertaining it so
so you're gonna have to find ways in
general The the waiting room is very cruel
and and whatever you could figure it out
So you and it's not entertaining and the
magazines on the coffee table aren't cutting it.
So you're gonna have to Entertain you have
to create forms of entertainment for yourself.
Mm-hmm Whether you're stupid enough to think
that what academia or the religious leaders or
whatever is going on out there is enough
to Take your attention and be entertained then
fine Go for it but if you're wise
enough to see that it's it's really low
-level crap, then you're gonna have to invent
your own entertainment and Invent meaning, you know
Put it together in the way that suits
a certain task You know, how much to
entertainment are you looking for?
Great, right?
Back, but basically I found out the the
more suitable the entertainment for the individual the
faster time goes by it does That's a
good thing.
Yeah.
Yeah Whether it's what quote-unquote a job
or a job that you like or whether
it's you know Whatever you do during the
day or waking hours and sleeping hours, by
the way It is possible to have a
night go by like it took a long
time You want your nights to go by
quick also, which is you know, comfortable sleep
and good sleeping manners, right?
Right, don't eat before you go to sleep,
right?
Don't eat chocolate Don't drink too much.
It's gonna knock you out like a sedative,
but you'll pick up the brunt of that
in the morning So it depends if you
know how to if you're masterful You know,
you know in what you do, you'll you'll
reap, you know some reward out of it
or some pleasure But I was telling someone
today if you want to be successful in
this society you have to master mediocrity By
the way, all these things that people that
look at as being successful organizations corporations or
individuals It's because they've mastered mediocrity like take
the for example the rich people, you know
You that are put in front of you
which are not rich at all But for
slaves they are like the Bezos guy who
does Amazon, you know is richest guy, whatever
and for you know, it's bullshit but Okay,
this this idiot He's so great because he
started Amazon.
That's like Mediocrity man.
I mean he mastered mediocrity people want crap.
That's a bit That's a that's known to
them through the marketplace and he organizes it
So you get it all in one place
and offers other tangible services along with it
I mean how freaking mediocre is that you
want to talk about mastering mediocrity?
Look at Microsoft?
Yeah, it's a mediocre crap and they mastered
it and they're huge Apple talk about mediocrity,
yeah right Braun who's the designer for Braun?
the famous designer the famous German designer in
the 50s that has that Modern look that
you see in Braun's logo and bronze.
He did a lot of products, right?
He was You know Right.
That's what Apple use is using by the
way.
Don't think Apple is so cool with their
designs They're just a bunch of freaking morons
You think some Lebanese guy?
Immigrant son or whatever came over here and
they figured out the guys mediocre Steve Jobs
I'm not knocking them, but you know, it's
just garbage That they've recycled for you to
absorb and you like it.
I mean look at General Motors Toyota Dieter
Rams Dieter Rams is a designer Okay, Dieter
Rams is a German industrial designer retired academic
closely associated with consumer products company Brought Brown
or BRAUN and the functionalist school of industrial
design.
That's what study the functionalist school of industrial
design That's Apple.
It's a mediocre shit Which is you know,
whatever you want to talk about all cars
automotive They're so mediocre in the cars you
pop the hood and they have to have
a fake plastic cover over the engine Mercedes
Bavarian Motor Works, you know, they all do
it because they're freaking mediocre.
Don't talk about your medical system band-aids
drugs mediocre look at all of your What
you call your the champions of instant industry
and they're all meet mastered mediocrity mastered it
means they make it available to you the
moron and And they give you access to
it in a way that if you if
you didn't have wherewithal They also the other
credit system provide that's all they're just pumping
you with mediocrity Right, yeah name any any
industry or anything that people aspire to and
you'll see that the only reason they've aspired
to it because It's a mastership of mediocrity
Cars Computers planes.
I mean they got like this new airplane
This shit looks exactly like the the the
747s.
They came up with in the 60s.
Yeah, but it's got the wing It's got
slightly more aquiline shaped wing with little the
vortex, you know, a little tip flared up
in the end.
Get out of here Kind of stupid crap
is that?
They're masters of mediocrity You want to be
successful?
Master mediocrity So all that crap that's put
in front of humans, it's just look at
your religions totally freaking media The Vatican is
the mastership of mediocrity.
Come on You know, yeah Mine is bigger
than yours.
That's the Vatican, you know a bunch of
which yeah Good riddance to all of it,
so That's a positive.
No, you don't want to think the negative.
You don't want to hear me say talk
negatively about stuff That's that's my positive Remember
well Yeah, so there's your there's your word
of the week the term of the week
master mediocrity and you'll be successful with these
it's Hmm, I mean I pick anything food
Right, you know that there's a documentaries and
the best restaurants in the world I tell
people I wouldn't take do take out from
there.
Look at that shit.
It's mediocre But they've mastered it so they're
successful, right?
Be successful by mastering mediocrity and they'll all
you know, they'll shower you with their credit
and they'll praise you The why because if
you do anything, that's authentic and let's say
evolved, you know Completely opening the the field
and what's possibilities.
They're not gonna understand it Since it's not
gonna go anywhere so Master mediocrity and you'll
do well look at people in their job
positions Stick to your job description and you'll
be successful.
Don't try to innovate and whatever rate, right?
You'll be successful, right?
And then those that say they left because
they couldn't Eve would do whatever they just
adopted another they just met see at the
point when they left whatever they were doing
to do something That they got praised for
is because they just we're still mediocre.
They just weren't masters of the mediocrity, right?
So that open so there you go to
something new, you know, yeah, that's something new
it's just as mediocre as before But now
they've mastered the mediocrity, right?
Yeah, that's that's your industry human industry human
religion human society is mastership of mediocrity Just
junk, I mean I look at stuff, you
know, they they do promote, you know on
the internet and other places, you know The
new thing I'm like, that's garbage It's embarrassing
to say that this is where you are
right now state-of-the-art anything Embarrassing
but deep down they know why bother So,
mm-hmm, come on mop-up crew A
Good one for a t-shirt Yeah, they're
good The thing is that people will get
used to but the thing is they're not
at the state right now where the green
light can be given obviously and And we
were given an outline of how the things
will transpire.
In other words.
These are the events.
They're going to allow the green light You
know not specifically but yeah, you're gonna have
you're all going to be organized together You
know under a certain system and that system
will put will portray like a transparent outline
of what's lawful So, you know, you're aware
of it.
It'll be used improperly and Because of its
improper use Will cause destruction and to trump
that destruction and end the whole cycle the
mop-up crew comes because you've already acknowledged
the lawful Concept you see because you know
the the the not the new world order
But the one world order was going to
be a revival of ancient ways all the
way down to you know What people do
in there, you know every day?
All right, right or Bible of all that,
you know, not just the powers that that
means of the behind institutions So 13 years
left, you know give give or take I
mean a little bit but here's the thing
Let me just say, you know, if some
people say we've got 13 years.
I've gotten some messages back yeah, but what
people don't remember is the the the contours
and the contrasts That will be in those
13 years Let me just rephrase this when
I say 13 13 and a half years
now, it's about 13 or so Or, you
know, you can even say 12 and a
half, but but I would say around 13
still, you know, roughly but pretty close The
contours and contrasts are such you If you're
really thinking and you've got just one and
a half But let's say two pencils in
your pocket and one of them needs sharpening.
You should have noticed by now That you've
got less than seven years of the pleasantries
that you considered as things being pleasant Right,
you get it because the last seven-year
put your peers gonna be extremely unpleasant at
progressively You know, let's say today started the
the beginning of the last seven-year period
it may not be so unpleasant today But
tomorrow is going to be a little less
pleasant than today in the day after and
then it's just gonna Eventually be pretty obvious
to those that know So if you got
one and a half sharpened pencils in your
pocket, you know you've got less than seven
years of Reasonable modicum of what you might
consider to be pleasant Does that help yeah,
I think I've stated the obvious there so
much yeah When I say 13 years people
think oh, yeah, I just mark off 13
scratches on the bathroom wall.
No Because the last three and a half
year is going to be absolute nightmare on
earth Proceeded by another three and a half
years of just Rat the worst shit you
can imagine not new but and in and
done in old stuff done in a new
way Like imagine Use as a metaphor, you
know, they put in what kind of ancient
military stuff They put in front of the
Roman Army.
Everyone's familiar with that With the breastplates and
the skirt, you know the way they dress
and all that.
Okay.
Well imagine that technologically advanced They'd still have
the you know, the eagle they'd still wear,
you know Maybe some kind of head helmet
the headdress, but it won't be made of
feathers.
You know, it'll be it won't be bronze
It'll be carbon fiber You get it.
Mm-hmm So new and improved but all
right Yeah DK
justice was worshiped area show.
Yeah, and by the way, you know Biblical
studies a good thing, but I think the
way I think I'll take credit for many
people out there many 10 20, maybe a
hundred or so Revisiting scripture because they listen
to Greek speak.
So you got to give some time, but
there's still no Inquisitive enough inquisitiveness in scripture
to start discussing things More because people I
think if they already get it Even if
you you have no intention to read scripture
and never read it If you listen to
enough Greek speak you can confront any biblical
academic and blow them away You know, of
course, you won't be able to do the
two whole beef patty special sauce sesame seed
bun thing Like they do they'd like to
throw verses but you'll get the idea and
Actually, you got the idea you got it
But there's a lot to talk about, you
know, like what's why the New Testament?
What is that?
You know who who really is show?
You know or Apostle Paul who really is
he you know, and it's there it's all
there You know what what's going on?
you know, so Yeah The reason why and
I haven't stressed this enough and I haven't
brought it up enough the first century, especially
the the first Third I would say that
between 20 ad what you call 20 ad
and 60 ad is an important period Because
there was certain things that were happening on
the earth and at that time if you
try to research that by the way on
The Internet what you're going to get is
strictly religious Christian garbage, right?
There's no give on for early first century
Information they have to attach it to that
Christian Christian rubbish But if you understand let's
say even the century prior to that But
there was a peak of things happening between
the spiritually between the 20 ad and 60
ad Which you could say unleashed a level
of?
demonic Presence on the earth that was unprecedented
Malevolent The same is going to have started
already, by the way It started 20 some
odd years ago, you know the end of
what you call 1998.
I haven't really gone into much.
I Had a discussion recently, you know numbers
are important in Scripture with someone and you
know, why two thousand years of nothing?
Well because you don't know the feast days.
You don't know the ordinance You don't know
the laws of the Creator then you'll see
why everything is so neat and tidy Is
how I started and I went over them
why?
2,000 years of nothing happening but that
nothing if you were to consider the beginning
and end of that 2,000 years the
beginning being like 20 ad to 60 ad
and Then from let's say the end of
the 90s or beginning 2000 till now Though
the two time periods you have an unprecedented
amount of demonic like influx like imagine a
Gate or a door where they start coming
into this Reality in form of in for
in form of attention You see because they're
non-material so whether if they're what they
say a million light-years away or right
in your room It doesn't matter because they're
immaterial right they they connect it differently What
I mean is focusing on on this society,
right?
so, you know agenda a Influence and focus
they're poised, you know, would you rather be
watched by no demons or a million demons
watching you?
I think you should get a little nervous
if a million demons are watching you and
you could probably sleep better if no demons
are Watching you you see but you don't
know either way.
You can't perceive it Unless you're you know
Coupled in or you know to it so,
mm-hmm But the 2,000 years is
very simple at basically just a short of
an hour and a half conversation a General
generation because a generation could be 70 years,
right?
Right.
Some even say generation could be over a
hundred years, but Especially if you're speaking on
an Adamic level That would it be more
of a hundred because Adam in the year
hundred and all that but General generations are
40 years.
When does a when does a cycle if
you know the law a General cycle where
things are reset the general social reset The
term is known as a Jubilee.
So at the end of the 49th year
is the 50th year Which is when the
Jubilee starts, right, right?
The 50th year, you know the day after
the 49th year you're into your 50th year
So that is a quote-unquote Jubilee year,
right?
So what's 40 times 50?
mm-hmm Yeah There you go 2,000
years again So you see and why were
the you know, there were 40 years there
in the desert in the wilderness, right?
When you're in the wilderness What's going when
you say well, you know, I was camping
I was in the wilderness or I was
homeless is nothing It's the same synonymous really,
right?
Wandering of indigent Well, all those terms are
synonymous.
So if you said the Israelites were indigent
for 40 years That's pretty synonymous with being
in the wilderness, isn't it?
Yeah Right.
So 40 years now When you look at
that last 40 years because it was the
first 40 years that they were injured and
also the last if you Only have one
episode of a given amount Quantity if you
can call it the first and the last
and one right, you know it's only gonna
happen one time if I say Bruce I'm
gonna hit you on the on the Big
toe with a 20 pound a 20 ounce
lump hammer only once.
Well, that's the first time I've ever done
it It's also the last time I've ever
done it, right, right Right, so what do
you know about the 40 year in terms
of social change?
Not not just you know, when you read
the book of Numbers, I mean Which is
pretty good gives you direction They these idiots
are still doing documentaries and we don't know
where the Israelites were they talking about You
know Mm-hmm.
There's a corresponding each each time.
They were They settled in 42 different places,
that's why there are 42 generations in the
book of Matthew.
Mm-hmm You know, anyway, I wouldn't say
that's why it doesn't say that's why but
it's an interesting coincidence, right?
So if you if you look at the
happenings Generationally because the generations are types of
people generations are mentioned.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you have to understand the application of
geography To be a marker, you know, we
watch Israel Jerusalem for certain things as a
clock, right?
All right.
So what changed what changed in in let's
say What what that generation that first and
last generation that was in the wilderness?
As they are as humans because they're going
to be back in the wilderness, by the
way, I don't know.
That's another discussion You know, they're gonna be
sent back.
Yeah.
Yeah after the return 40 years maybe not
As it was the first time but yeah
sequestered for teaching, you know, those are those
those are the ones that are not resurrected
But anyway just to cut to the point
because I feel like I'm I'm not even
getting to the point The they were not
able to go into the land which is
symbolic Also go when you're going into the
land It's like you're achieving you're achieving a
certain precedent or you're achieving something, right?
Right, you know like even Martin Luther King,
you know was saying a promised land.
Well, what promised when you're ready here dummy
The thing was was civil, you know to
have rights to do things right in other
words a certain freedom or whatever So until
certain freedoms are granted which would be called
privileges or whatever Which would be going into
the land and settling and no longer being
indigent what what had to take place?
Well, the the fighting men all had to
die Right in the book of Numbers.
Remember there was no one left of the
fighting men, right?
You know, well who were the fighting men?
Well, there were six hundred thousand of them.
How do we know?
Well, it says it says so there's six
hundred thousand fighting men that have left of
fighting age or fighting types that left Egypt
Not six hundred thousand people but fighting okay,
so those six hundred thousand had to perish
before the only there was only a Small
exception of who didn't which was Joshua and
Caleb, right?
Right.
They saw the land right?
They were actually ruling so if so Okay,
so in modern parlance and in modern convention
and in modern knowledge and what we know
What do we know about fighting people?
fighting men regarding modern wars regarding Israel right,
so we have the ones that were in
1947 48 49 and Then we have the
ones and the several day wars and the
wars in Jerusalem, right, right?
So just to cut to the point When
you read about like the six-day war
or whatever it was five days six days
seven day war What you know of several
countries attacked?
Jerusalem in Israel and was it 67 or
something 68.
Yeah.
Okay, the people who fought in that war
Need to die before the next level goes
Before we get to the next level on
a spiritual plane, it doesn't mean that there's
gonna be other actions You know that you
know, like people desiring the temple to be
built the Israelis bombing the shit out of
Gaza Strip and you know The newest Syria
the Assyrians running around because you know, the
Assyrians are not known as Assyrians, by the
way They're known as Mideastern Christians, right?
You know, they're the they're the predominant group,
you know, there's this quote-unquote people stupid
enough to follow that in every country there's
quote-unquote Christians in everywhere except Saudi Arabia,
I mean even there there are but however,
they are but make a point here is
The Group known as the fighting men of
that war in 60 in the late 60s
for Jerusalem when you start reading or understand
eventually in the near future, there'll be some
articles about All of these people that fought
in the Jerusalem war in the 60s Whatever
are dying and we have none left or
there's one or two veterans like a Joshua
type, right?
Because remember that Joshua and Caleb, but they
did they did they were the exempt from
that statement.
Mm-hmm you see so there are going
to be some exceptions and exemptions made but
in the near future one thing to look
for in what's called the media is That
all the veterans of this Jerusalem war thing
that happened in the 60s are dying and
they're almost all gone.
I Know Yeah, I think I've discussed this
before but I'm just saying it again because
as we get closer I think it's more
important to give more specifics So Old age
would be taking its toll pretty pretty close
now, right?
Cuz that was over 50 years ago and
let's say there were 20 and even then
they recruited people that were as young as
14 and 15 right Right, so they would
be in their late in the majority of
them are in the 70s and 80s that
are notable right now Majority of them.
Mm-hmm.
They're probably some in there.
I'd say it's very rare to find any
less than 70 Years old because but then
again there was something that were in the
teens early teens I mean many times have
you heard years ago people lied about their
age to get into the military and they
were let in Yeah But in many cases,
you know wouldn't be if you necessity is
necessity, you know If you if a 12
year old looks like he's 16, you know,
bring him in, you know so Yeah, watch
out for that.
You're gonna in the near future look for
Stuff in the media regarding veterans of those
late late 60s wars in Israel Being rarefied
their numbers being rarefied That's an important piece,
but not minor, but it's a gateway principle
to understand those when you see that You
know in the forefront as being talked about,
you know, the time is really, you know
being Communicated spiritually to society like hey, you
need to do some study to see how
everything is repeating, right?
So watch that's something to something to watch
for there mean there's lots of things to
watch for of course, you know Many people
know me as the guy who says watch
for the new Assyria there's going to be
You know the revived Assyria, yeah, and you
know, and I'll just say this and we'll
end the sonic, okay Not only is the
new Assyria Geographic, right, you know, I gave
a lot of details through the years about
that, you know, it's northern Iraq Actually, you
know, right.
It's going to take land from Turkey and
Syria and all these other things, right?
Yeah.
Yep Yeah, the idea.
Yeah, anyone can research that maps and all
the details that I've given in the past
What people also need to understand is the
mindset of the Assyrians will take place in
the Middle East which is the mindset of
what?
conquest brutality Right pride.
The Assyrians are very proud And you know
how many times you read in like book
of Isaiah Syrian King goes your gods mean
nothing to me All right.
All right.
So who's ever which one of?
So which society have we attacked whose gods
have helped them?
Right stuff like that you see about these
things so look for that.
That's what so that's part of You know,
not only the formation of a new Assyria,
but a revival of that mindset that is
quote-unquote an Assyrian mindset Right, right Okay,
so with that said thanks Bruce.
Okay.
Let's see anything else going And we'll see
you guys next week.
Maybe okay You have a good night.
No, sir.
Okay.
It's you.
Thanks again.
See ya