Greetings folks, we're live with the Greek and
good evening to you Greek.
Good evening.
All right.
I'm going to be in and out.
Hopefully the connection will hold up.
OK.
So.
All right.
Let's just get right down to it.
We're going to say today it's.
Wow.
Am I losing track here?
It's about the second.
Well, we're into the third week, aren't we?
Or past the second week of the of
the ninth month.
It's just in other words, we've just completed
two weeks whole weeks.
And it's the third beginning of the third
week of the ninth month as a Nova,
meaning nine.
Yes, I believe the 14th.
No.
Fifth, 16th, I'm reckoning.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The 15th.
It's the Sabbath.
Yeah.
So that's why I want it.
Well, when the weekends I kind of it's
still really an interim.
Is it part of that week?
Yes, it still is.
Because the seventh day of the week, you
know, but I consider it the end of
the week.
The week is complete, but it's not really
right.
The end of the right.
OK.
You know, it's I think we've gone over
the counting enough ad nauseum.
I think one day we'll probably do a
fifty nine minute, fifty nine second sonic event
strictly on introductory Greek speak.
What did they used to call it in
the old educational circus?
Condensed version and abridged version, right?
Yes.
The abridged.
Yeah, it would be an abridged and slightly
condensed.
Yes.
Just before we get into anything, I got
an email regarding water.
People are still trying to get in touch.
They say they go to the Web site.
Just a colorful black background in an email.
I haven't linked anything, the sonic events or
or anything, not because I'm not proud of
them or anything.
It's just something to be proud about.
But about anything on this planet.
But it's just I don't I just think
that if you've come across Greek speak and
you've figured out that the only place to
get live stuff is on a chat, an
obscure chat on the obscure side of the.
It's not the very last page of the
Internet.
Do you remember that right back in the
day, the very last page of the Internet?
They had like some strange technological stuff.
I haven't really done anything.
Rumor has it someone wants to start an
official podcast on a pod stream on what
they call January.
The same person is doing the just Greek
speak Web site.
Oh, OK.
And yeah, I mean, OK, fine.
They think it's going to go real big.
And I never said it wouldn't.
It could, but not right now.
Right.
People are still too censored and getting worse.
But remember, the censorship has to be opened
for enough lawfulness to be admitted, not remembered,
not acted on.
Right.
In order for the mop up crew to
come, because they will not.
But you did say that it increases the
censorship also increases, but then it opens at
a certain point.
Well, only increases because how can how can
a society on an entire planet be so
morally devoid and so full of depravity that
they don't notice it?
Right.
The only way that could happen is with
censorship.
I mean, no, there's talk about like, you
know, how did the headhunters do it or
certain cultures that were full of depravity.
But were they really depravity?
You know, no.
I mean, look at the depravity.
You know, it's a sense, you know, I
say stupid people are dangerous, not because it's
just, you know, like even a most lethal
snake or tiger or lion or rabbit dog
is dangerous, but not always.
There's their methodologies to get around that danger.
The reason why stupid people are dangerous is
because they're stubborn, they're dimwitted.
In other words, they react on that impulse,
you know.
And anything they believe is the truth.
Which is why they're stupid.
So essentially, I've been getting a bunch of
emails still, like someone just sent an email,
would you talk about Enki and Enlil and
all that?
And I'm like, well, would you stop watching
so many alternative YouTube videos?
Because it's really minor.
Put it in perspective, you know, why should
that stand out?
That was like the time of Abraham.
That's like what they called, they dubbed the
Bronze Age, which there's no such thing as
a Bronze Age, Iron Age or Stone Age,
by the way.
It's a Bronze Society, Stone Society, Iron Society,
because there still are stone societies.
There still are iron societies.
You know, this is a plastic society, let's
say.
There's no such thing as an age of
such.
Yeah, the only reason they call it a
Bronze Age is because they discovered the easiest
way to get, yeah, the easiest way to
get copper and zinc was to go on
the opposite ends of the earth or globe.
Most of the majority, this is something that's
being hidden from the people.
If you do isotopic analysis of all the
copper that's been found from the quote unquote
Bronze Age, I'd say about 10 to 20
% is from the Cyprus region, like the
southern, the Aegean.
And the other 80% is from here,
the states, the American states.
And to make bronze, you need zinc and
copper, basically, and then there's a slew of
other impurities or alloys that are in there.
Actually, I have a formula for a secret
copper alloy that has to, not only do
you have to combine the metals, certain metals,
but the way you do it also that
is as strong as carbide steel.
So now you understand how it's easy to
make stone cutting tools, copper.
Yeah.
So it's sort of alchemic.
Alchemists still exist, but not in the way
they told the public, right?
But if you look at where most of
the zinc and other alloys came from, it
came from the area of Afghanistan back in
these ancient times.
And this is not discussed.
This is just like when the Baghdad batteries
were dubbed Baghdad batteries were discovered in the
30s, well, they were acknowledged in the 30s
publicly.
All the museum curators ran and tested all
the supposed solid gold artifacts, and they never
printed the findings.
They made public.
Because most of that stuff that they told
you was solid gold was not solid gold,
like Tutankhamen's mask and all these other solid
gold things are not solid gold that they
have in museums.
They're not.
They're plated.
So this is just how it shows, again,
is it censorship?
Yes.
Is it stupidity?
Is it stubbornness?
Yes.
Is it the sign of the times?
Is it because you're being ruled by a
series of patron and matron deities?
Yes.
Is there pranking going on?
It's very simple.
Last week, there were no questions or anything,
just like there isn't much, so we could
probably make this a very short one.
There are just a few questions and emails
that I've answered.
I usually get emails about people struggling with
certain things in a good way, and they
ask me to expand on it.
I said, well, your questions I've already expanded
on.
I already answered your question, so I would
invite anyone and everyone to consider.
I know it's not neat and tidy and
compact, but put it this way.
You've heard certain things, certain euphemisms or colloquial
things, like if you think you're the first
one who thought of it, you haven't.
Someone else has came up with it before,
or you're not the only one asking the
question.
If you're going to send me an email
about something specific like that, 99% of
the time, I have a pretty good memory,
it's been answered already.
It's just a matter of rehashing.
Years ago, I was a little more, quote
-unquote, forgiving, and people would ask me questions,
which I knew I'd gone over in great
depth, either in smatterings or in one sitting,
and I would answer it back.
Now I don't.
If you get an email back that says,
well, I've answered this before, I'm not being
sarcastic or lazy or anything.
It's because I didn't just do it in
passing.
I actually went into it in great detail.
Unfortunately, there isn't one single place.
There is no card catalog or appendix that
will lead anyone to any specific topic.
I didn't think doing it formally...
You know how a lot of events, whether
they're written literary events or sonic events, are
cataloged and given titles and topics?
I think the time for that is over.
You either develop a mindset that is perceptive
and objective and lawful, so you can pick
up on everything that I've discussed, or you
don't.
In other words, if you're a type of
individual or human or man or woman or
child that needs to have their hand held
on each and every different topic or theme
or whatever, you're not going to get Greek
-speak.
That's not for you.
Yes, there might be some information that's given
here that you could check up as being
true that you don't get anywhere else, but
how did I figure it out?
How does anyone figure it out?
That's the point of Greek-speak.
The early Greek-speak talks from years ago,
if you remember being on interviews, always started
out by, no one's paying any attention.
No one's being objective.
No one's looking at stuff just five feet
in front of them.
The biggest hypocrites are these researchers that are
trying to find out what's on the bottom
of the ocean or out in space or
across the world, because they don't even notice
what's five feet in front of them.
So the whole thing is about mindset, mindset,
and one more thing, it's mindset.
So when people ask about certain subjects, it's
irrelevant.
Some people think of me as a science
guy.
Other people think of me as just a
pain in the ass.
Other people think of me as a scripture
guy.
I'm none of that.
All of it, none of it.
Other people think of me as a health
guru.
No, I'm not that.
Other people think of me as an alternative
shrink.
Other people think of me as a mechanical
genius.
I'm none of that.
None of that.
It's all mindset.
Are you paying attention?
No, you're not.
Are you being objective?
Are you being lawful?
No, you're not.
Lawful just means what is it based on?
For example, if you said Stan Lee invented
Mickey Mouse, that's not lawful, because Stan Lee
is Marvel Comics.
It's Walt Disney, Walter Disney, that did Mickey
Mouse.
That's lawful.
But they're both fictions.
They're all into fiction.
But you see, are you connecting the sources?
So even though something is a fiction, are
you attributing it to the source?
As simple as that.
So when you look at all the religions
of the world, Christianity, what's the source of
it?
Well, they'll tell you history and the Bible.
Well, nope, sorry, you failed on that.
So what's it based on?
It's not lawful.
It doesn't matter what you believe.
See, what they do, this is all about
human livestock management, or livestock management, because I'm
using that term human loosely anymore.
I really don't think they're human as such.
I think they're just really upright pigs, goats,
and dogs, and whatever else you want to,
spiritually that way.
Now, what you would say on that, for
example, is if you look at something like
Christianity, or Judaism, or Islam, or whatever, any
religion, or even though science is in it,
if you say something that's not scientific, the
people that do control the other people, because
it is a free world, by the way,
and I'll explain what I mean by that.
Instead of, get the people who believe in
certain things to separate, and also we use
it as a marker to see how stupid
they are, because if they say they believe
in, we don't have to ask them if
they're stupid, we know they're stupid.
And then what you do is you put
out a credo that says, how dare you
insult someone's belief, or you shouldn't speak out
against someone's belief, or freedom of religion.
You're being set up, that's a prank.
From the get-go.
Now, at least in the past there was
more honesty in it, where you either did
our God or not.
Now there's no God, just saying God is
not good enough, it never was.
So, if you look at any of the
major religions or scientific stuff and you ask
them what they're based on, because science, knowledge
is based on these beliefs also, you'll find
that it's all unlawful, all of it.
Now, Christianity, I haven't found anything that's Biblical
in it, at all.
Sounds like a ridiculous thing.
Judaism, a little bit, where they'll pull up
some strange, esoteric, rabbinic arguments, that do adhere
to narrow points in what they call the
Torah or the teachings.
Even something as ridiculous as fundamentalists or orthodox
Jews saying you shouldn't eat milk and meat
together, which is not scriptural, by the way,
at least that points to the specific doctrine
of the last commandment, or an analysis, an
interpretation of it, which is kind of swayed.
Christians don't know any of the Ten Commandments
written in stone, none.
Actually, by coincidence, one or two, by coincidence.
But they're not aware of anything.
By the way, the last commandment is do
not see the kid in its mother's milk,
or it could be taken as do not
eat a goat or kid that is still
nursing.
Right, right.
Which I would say is closer, because it
also talks about when you take eggs from
a nest, don't take the mother and the
eggs, just take the mother or the eggs,
right?
One or the other, but not both.
So you'll always see a connection.
Eventually, when you start reading what people loosely
call God's law, in the beginning it's kind
of strange, but as you study it, you'll
say, oh, here's one that I'm beginning to
read now.
Oh, that makes total sense, because if you've
studied the others, you'll see there's a pattern
that emerges, right?
So there's a pattern there.
So Islam, again, there's no law in that.
The Koran refers you back to Moses, by
the way.
No one has ever come back to me
and said, no, no, Muslims are not supposed
to do Moses' law.
No, you know why?
Because they can't.
Because the Koran explicitly says they should.
Right.
And I love, years ago, I shouldn't say
I love it, I hated it, but I
love how simple a point to hang on,
you know how a cheap sweater, you just
pull on a thread and the whole thing
comes apart?
Whenever I speak to one of these Muslim
idiots, I just hang on that thread.
Law.
That's it.
It doesn't matter what they say.
I keep pulling on that until the whole
thing falls apart.
Not to pick on them, even though they
deserve it, basically.
And the whole thing just falls apart, because
obviously these are what's called state religions.
Let me go back to what I was
saying about freedom.
Okay, you know, like America is a free
country.
All countries are free countries.
The world is a free world.
How do I know that?
Let me run through this, because this is
going to be explicit, in a sense, in
your face, that you've never really realized.
I know you haven't realized this, and no
one really has.
And I'm going to just spell it out
again.
Okay.
Except that it's in private.
The Creator put the various patron and matron
deities over the countries, right?
You could read about that.
You know, and also the hybrids, you know,
that had more power.
Which, the person who asked about the email
about the Enki and Enlil, all that Akkadian
stuff, you know, the Anunnaki.
What about, there's another group.
The Anunnaki just means the royalty.
But there's the Apkali, or the Apkalu.
No one talks about them.
They're the hybrids.
They're like the Nephilim.
They're the hybrids, right?
Okay.
No one talks about the Apkali, right?
They're like Anunnaki.
You know, like who's that idiot, a bunch
of UFO idiots, the Project Camel moron.
Yeah, yeah, right.
They get so stuck in the New Age.
They don't know that they're being pranked.
Why not study anything, right?
So, like, you know, so when you look
back and you see how the setup is,
those people of power did not go away.
And the Creator set this up.
And if you ever read anything in scripture
or old, it's always free will.
In other words, if you remember reading Old
Testament stuff, what kind of an offering is
it?
It's a free will offering, right?
Right.
And if you don't bring the offering by
free will, then you have to wait a
certain amount of time, whether it could be
immediate or really lengthy, multi-generational, to suffer
the repercussions of that, right?
Because you can do something and it might
just not hit you even in your lifetime.
So these are large scope in terms of
man's perspective of livelihood, you know, how long
your life is.
But if you go back, the Creator, everything
was free will.
Well, he's put free will in there as
more than an option.
It is set up as a free will
setup.
Right?
Anything that's a free will option always has
stringent requirements and constraints.
Like, I always give the concept of free
will as a ship with thousands of passengers
going from London to New York.
Okay?
Well, the ship is going from London to
New York because it says it on the
ticket.
It's planned to go that way.
No matter what, it might deviate on the
path a little because of weather or what
have you or frequent stopping, but it's going
to go to New York.
Okay, that's the set thing.
Now, your free will as a passenger is
on the ship, what you're going to do
on that ship, right?
Right.
But you're all going – so the free
will is what you're going to do.
And also based on your rank and class,
if you're on the ship's crew, you don't
have it because you're on a different schedule
than the passengers, right?
So you have to look at it that
way as well.
So the whole world, we know how it's
going and nobody can change it, but there's
free will even there, you see, within one's
life to a certain degree because the large
overall outcome is still based on actions of
people and groups of people known as nations
and minor gods and things like that affecting
both ways.
Right.
So this free aspect of free will –
now, when you're chosen to do something, you're
also chosen freely, you should do it freely
if you are part of that covenant, part
of that group.
You could be born into it.
Like, for example, Yonah or Jonah is an
example where he was asked to go to
Nineveh to tell them to straighten up or
the destruction will fall and he didn't want
to go, right?
Well, somebody might say, well, there's no free
will.
Well, you don't understand that this man already
had a covenant with Yahweh.
So once you make a covenant, by definition
of what constraints or freedoms are listed in
that covenant is what you live by, you
see.
And you can be chosen.
Right.
A covenant would be like a marriage.
If you are married, now your free will
to go and fornicate is over, right?
Right.
You can only be with that woman unless
it's by consent that you marry again.
Right.
Because it is lawful to marry again, right?
Mm-hmm.
For a man.
And a woman, it's not lawful.
So for that woman, it would be this
is the only man I have until the
day I die unless he dies or we
divorce, which would be through adultery anyway.
Right.
So certain covenants will show you the path
that you're on.
Just like if you're going cross-country, there's
only a certain amount of highways you can
take.
And if there's one that clearly takes you
direct, you know you're only going to be
on that road.
So, again, when I say free will, it
really is free will.
Jonah did have free will overall, but a
certain amount of free will to deny going
to Nineveh to prophesy to the leaders of
Nineveh was not in the free will equation
because of previous allegiances he had to that
god.
And that's implied and inferred.
It doesn't have to be restated because we're
not that stupid.
You see?
Mm-hmm.
So when you look at how much freedom
man is given, and you've heard, for example,
in America, this is a free country, and
there's a lot of quote-unquote freedom here.
All nations were like that.
Even when they were under the division of
each related patron or matron deity.
This is the difference.
What your national gods do, you know, each
nation has a god or group of people,
is essentially they just demand human sacrifice.
If you really want to boil down to
it.
They don't give any laws, really.
They send demons and things like that to
communicate with various oracles of the people or
what they call psychics or give dreams and
various things based on the culture.
But they basically, the bottom line is they
just want human sacrifice.
They just want you to sacrifice.
That's why it was so normal for Abraham
to accept bringing his son.
It was normal for Abraham.
Abraham said, that's a terrible thing to do.
Why would you ask me to do that?
Because it was normal back then.
And it still is.
We just convert.
So it's freedom, freedom, freedom, freedom.
And again, to go back to America, people
are free here.
But let's just say we comprehend.
We're not stupid, right?
I know it's kind of hard for most
people to do, to think that way.
In other words, not in a stupid way.
In other words, let's not be ignorant.
When I say because we're not stupid, I
use that in a facetious way.
Especially when I describe the biblical Christ.
He was not nailed to a cross wearing
a diaper.
How do we know that?
Because we're not stupid.
When we're reading the New Testament, we know
it's PhD level.
You have to go back and see how
it would be done, right?
What I mean by that is, are you
paying attention?
So, if you're not stupid, and you know
it's a free country, and you have wherewithal
to knowledge, you have wherewithal to what's called
money, funds, power, influence.
And again, remember, you're not stupid.
You're aware of human society.
If you have two people on an island,
and they get along, what are the chances
of you leaving that island and coming back
in 500 years?
Let's say a man and a woman.
Coming back in 500 years, and there's still
just two people there.
You're probably going to come back, and there'll
be thousands of people, or hundreds of people,
right?
Most likely thousands.
This happens all the time.
When you had a colony, in any condition,
any situation, you had Australia, the US, Canada,
places where you had indigenous people.
You had colonials coming over by the hundreds.
Dozens, scores, hundreds.
And then, less than 50 years later, there's
a million of them.
Yes, there's a lot of interbreeding with the
natives and all that, but they are considered
the people that came over from, right?
I have people in acquaintance that are here
in the southwest, and they're like, oh yeah,
what do you do?
I come from a family from back east.
We started the Costa Naga wagons, one of
those big, famous large wheels wagons.
Sure.
They mass produced those, so people would go
on long journeys.
Basically, it was the first RV, the Costa
Naga wagon.
It had kitchen area storage, even a gun
hole, so if someone was inside, they could
lay down and shoot through it.
Yeah, it was the first RV.
That's where they come from.
They came from England and Scotland.
Well, that was like 300 years ago, dude.
Right.
There's a lot.
But he still attributes it to that.
You see?
Lineage.
Okay, so I'm going slow here, but there's
free will.
If you're smart, again, let me go back.
You have access to knowledge.
Notice I didn't say education, but let's consider
it education.
To funds, you have access to history.
You understand how people operate.
When you put a few people in an
area that has a lot of cheap energy,
back then it would be easy access to
water and wood and animal products, surface products,
right?
That's why people mostly came over here.
Like they didn't mind the church in Europe,
even though they just stayed out of their
way, but they minded that they had to
pay for firewood, right?
Or there was no firewood.
When you came here, there was wood everywhere,
right?
Cheap energy.
It still is cheap energy.
America is still the capital of cheap energy,
except for places like Kuwait where basically they'll
give you gasoline.
Basically gasoline there is like 15 cents a
gallon, five liters, and Venezuela also.
But either way, let me just get to
the point here.
When you're smart or less stupid than others,
you understand how people operate when they move
and how they expand.
You're all free, but you have an advantage.
You have access.
You might want to purchase or control land
and waterways before they do.
There's actually a race.
Like when a new area starts to develop,
there's a race to who's going to control
it.
Right.
And when you're early on the game and
you start controlling early in the game, and
eventually your influence of control over the environment,
land, water, people, and all that, hopefully we'll
be slightly ahead of the population expansion.
Why?
Because as the population is expanding, you will
be the first one to put schools in
place.
You will put media in place.
You will put religion in place, right?
And if you don't believe that, usually when
a colonial or a small town you can
even look at, it's the rich person's religion.
He's the one that builds the church or
the synagogue or the mosque.
You could read about this in history.
All through America, I know a family from
Ohio, a little town in Ohio, my dad
was a painting contractor, the largest painting contractor
in the area, and he built the first
church.
Well, guess what?
That church would be the denomination of the
guy who funded it.
You see how it works?
Oh, yeah.
So when you're ahead of the game and
you start to see the people, you could
steer the people and say, well, we'll keep
telling them that they're free because this is
how the world started out, but we're going
to control them.
We're going to give them bullshit because, look
at them, they believe they like it anyway.
When we tell them bullshit and give them
garbage, quality mental stuff, they smile and laugh
and enjoy and go back to their jobs.
But when we give them serious information, they
become contemplative and they don't work as well,
you see.
They're still free.
Everyone is still free.
So, like, even in the most despotic state,
you could pick, like, Stalin or, you know,
let's use modern terms, you know, Bopod, Hitler,
whatever.
The people there were still free.
Why?
Because none of those atrocities that you've heard
about in history, whether they're true or not
is irrelevant.
I'm giving it as an example.
We could use another planet.
That could not happen without the support of
the people.
Just like the video I put up recently
about somebody coming forward.
They call it TIs or gang stalking or
whatever.
All kinds of techniques.
Well, there's a million people that are doing
that.
I mean, it's like – how many times
have you heard me say that even your
best intellectual professors can't go beyond third or
fourth grade mentality?
I remember growing up in the public school
system and private school system, in both, it
doesn't matter how – if you go to
an expensive school, private or public, there's always
going to be a, quote, unquote, kid that's
being picked on.
Or no one wants to touch him, right?
Okay, so that mentality stays in.
And then it's applied now.
So it's very simple.
It's not part of human society or human
culture only because it's – it is now
because you don't think about it.
It's tradition and culture, you see.
Okay, so you're still free.
So even the most despotic dictators and atrocious,
quote, unquote, governments or controllers that were put
in place could not do it without the
help of a percentage of their people, a
good percentage, right?
Now because of technology, and I put it
in that YouTube, because you only need less
than 1% of the people to really
dominate the other 99 because they've already agreed
to electronic dog leashes and electronic devices to
capture their attention and their mobility, right?
Yeah.
So you still are – you're always going
to be free, right?
It's just that you don't know what it
means.
Like Dimitri, on one of his videos, said,
Calasso says, people don't have the ideology of
freedom.
Like in America, in the Western world especially,
if you said, well, let's get rid of
these systems, no more electronic money, we've got
real money, people would freak out.
No, no, no, we want the convenience of
it, right?
Right, right.
See?
I mean, how easy would it be, for
example, for – I know that when I
was at AFR and I was asking for
donations for AFR, which you could just go
to the home website or whatever, and raised
about $1,500 in three weeks from people
electronically because it's so easy.
Oh, I like what he's saying.
I'm going to go PayPal right now, click,
click, click, click, $20 or $100 or $50.
Or for Ocelli, it could raise like $500
for Ocelli in two days electronically.
But when I tell people, if you want
to send something in the mail, oh, no,
I don't want to do that.
I still get some people sending stuff in
the mail.
You know, more and more people don't even
know how to fill out an envelope.
Yeah, yeah.
And I don't think they even teach it
anymore.
No, I don't think anything is really being
taught outside of what needs to be taught.
Correct, right.
So you're always free.
The only thing is you have to factor
in that the pranksters, like they always tell
you in the media you're free.
By the way, I'm looking on the Internet,
it says election day in America.
Oh, yeah.
You don't need to go.
If you think that has anything to do
with anything, you need to go get some
pills for your brain.
You need to get some, what do they
call it?
Vacation.
Oswald, that's like the old Bill Hicks thing.
He went to the memorial at the book
depository where Kennedy, his assassin supposedly, shot Kennedy.
And he says it was very accurate because
they had the rifle there, the window was
there, and the rope, but Oswald wasn't there.
That's why it was very accurate, right, when
he saw the memorial, right?
Sure.
So anyway, it's just so stupid to vote.
And they even tell you, if you understand,
do you know why they promote voting commercially?
I've gone over this before.
I'm not putting you on the spot.
Right.
Because you have to fill out a form
to register, and that form is monetized 50
,000 bucks front end in most places.
How do I know this?
I poked around where I shouldn't have been.
It got me in trouble back when I
was in New Mexico for a little while,
about a dozen and a half years ago,
or a dozen years ago, I should say.
I knew a guy who was driving around
in a brand new BMW.
His wife had a brand new Mercedes and
had a big house, a young guy in
his 20s, and he was like the Republican
registrant voter.
He was in charge of collecting registrations and
getting people to register to vote.
He got a commission on those forms, which
was a tiny amount of commission, but still.
When you figure out that, I'm like, whoa,
that must be at least 50 grand.
I started poking around and started seeing numbers
in code, and it was way up in
the tens of thousands for every time someone
signs up.
Where do they get it from?
They get it from the social, the credit
that you have.
By the way, I want to talk about
that.
You have a credit line.
You can't use it.
I remember a case where someone had used
it and bought a whole bunch of stuff,
and then a year later, the attorney general
crashed on him because they were supposed to
punish him for figuring out the truth.
In the court case, it said that he
was using public funds because he was taking
the Social Security number and sending it to
the Treasury on a check.
So guess what?
Where do you get the Social Security number
from?
Health and Human Services, the Treasury Department of
Commerce, it's all public funds, and they're telling
you it's private.
Yeah.
Hold on to it.
It's public funds, man.
In other words, the credit line that you're
given to operate in this country is considered
public funds.
All right.
Anyway, too much.
Too much TMI, they call it, right?
Right.
Oh, my.
Thankfully, I didn't have any of the pranksters
reminding me that I needed to go vote,
which is very good.
Of course, I'm in the back.
I don't have to do it.
It's on the Internet.
Yeah.
Oh, God, yes.
Let me just complete the point more about
the freedom.
Sure.
Even in the most dystopian society, you still
are free.
Well, you're free to leave.
Actually, scripturally, it is valid to do that.
But the problems that inhibit the freedom, and
even in a dystopian society, is the people
that are making other people's lives difficult, let's
say, are unlawful, which is kind of hard
to say unlawful because pretty much there is
no law anywhere.
But let's just say use it anyway.
Use the term anyway.
They're pranksters.
They don't care about law.
I don't know if you – they tell
you you're free in America, but if you've
ever walked into an attorney general's office or
a state attorney of any capacity and had
a discussion with them, a free discussion, he
says, no, you're not allowed to do this.
You're supposed to do what everybody else does.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I don't know if you've ever spoken to
any sheriffs in private or sheriff chief of
police or sergeants or captains.
No, you can't do that.
You have to do what everybody else does.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
You see what they tell you individually?
You ever walked into speaking to people, prank
managers?
No, no, you can't do – you have
to do what everybody else does.
It's like they're in a hive.
Yeah.
Or the lawfully – well, I don't care
about the law.
Just do what everybody else does.
So do you see the problem?
Well, here's the essence.
How many times have I – you heard
me say we have to make the world
better to save the people?
Never.
You know why?
Not one.
Because it's the people that are screwed up.
Why?
Because their leaders are saying, we don't care
about the law because we're ruling over a
bunch of vulgar animals.
And we like it that way because it
makes it easy for us.
So the pranksters now are ruling over the
– you see?
How many times have you heard me say
you can't fix it, it just has to
be mopped up?
Right.
Right?
The worst thing with a toilet being clogged
is when the toilet's full of shit and
it's clogged.
Yeah.
Ain't gonna happen.
See, people think that the toilet is just
clogged.
No, I'm telling you that it's full of
shit to the brim and it's clogged.
What are you going to do now?
See?
So, it's the people's ignorance.
Now, the thing is, you can't say the
people are ignorant and vile due to lack
of access.
Access to information.
Right?
You can't say that.
No?
Ever.
Ever, because how many times have I said
pretty much everything you need to learn is
five feet in front of you and then
you go ten feet and then out from
there?
There's a book somewhere, Everything You Need to
Learn in Life You Learned in Kindergarten, you
know, which is a stupid social thing, but
that's kind of like the sentiment.
So, everyone is free.
You've always been free.
Right?
In general.
But if you read in the book of
Judges, for example, or other places in Scripture,
they became enslaved or oppressed by other people.
The Israelites did.
Why?
Why did they lose their freedoms?
Because of previous agreements that they did not
uphold.
Right?
Yeah.
It's not because they worshipped idols.
Because there were plenty of cultures that worshipped
idols that were not oppressed.
It's because they promised not to worship idols
and they worshipped idols.
Do you see the difference?
Mm-hmm.
Big difference.
So, you're always free.
You've always been free.
But when you get subject, when you drift
away from objectivity and lawfulness so far, and
the pranksters discover, because people are always going
to discover that pranking is the easiest way
to get what you want or need.
Stealing.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
Whatever.
Is always easier, unlawfully.
You know, it's easier in their minds because
it's allowed culturally.
Yeah.
Do what everybody else does.
It's not the leadership.
I'm telling you, it is not the leadership.
It is the people themselves.
And I prove this on a daily basis,
especially when I'm speaking to people and I'm
out, and there's families around with children.
You know, well, children that can speak, not
just children that are like in a stroller
that are, you know, newborn or something.
Right.
And I said, watch these, you know, you
see these, just let's stop speaking for about
two minutes and look at how these parents
are relating to their children back and forth.
And you tell me you have a future.
They're like, oh shit, this is terrible.
And I'm talking about any social economic group.
Any social economic group.
I have a golden ghetto up here north.
We go up there, there's Prada and Apple
stores.
And, you know, Prada is the, I think
it's Italian designer, Gucci store.
Okay.
You know, there's a hundred million in credit
worth of cars in a small parking lot,
you know, because they're all, you know, Rolls
Royce, Ferrari, Bentley, Maserati, whatever.
Sure.
The golden ghetto.
Right.
You know, retired people.
And you look at how, you know, in
their case, because it's a retirement community, let's
say it's grandchildren and parents.
And it's like, whoa.
No different than the white trash in the
middle of town.
Or the Mexicans or the blacks or the
Italians.
Anywhere.
All the group.
Wherever you go, it's just trash.
Whether they're wealthy or not, poor or not.
It's just humans are just trash at this
point.
Right?
Yeah.
Because they've agreed.
They've allowed.
And you don't have to get to know
them.
You just listen to how they interact.
So they're complaining about, like, even the video
I put in, oh, how are we going
to make this country better?
And the guy catches himself.
There's no way.
You're finished.
Because you're lazy and stubborn.
And, you know, I'm not going to blame
the cosmic censorship, even though it is the
major fault.
Not at fault, but a fault.
You know, like when you have a fault
in a circuit and you find the wire
or the solder joint is broken or something.
Right?
Or a short, you know, where it kills
the whole thing.
Or sends it to a path that doesn't
allow the signal to work.
That's all a short is, right?
Right.
It's not working for you.
It's like a leak in the pipe.
You turn on the faucet.
Why am I not getting water?
Well, because there's a big-ass leak down
the street.
So it's just not doing what you want
it to do.
It's not the leader.
The people, if they're looking at the leaders,
they're looking at the wrong place.
Because the leaders are there because they're lazy.
And also, the people in this age are
not going to find out who leads them,
really.
Because, obviously, they have no concept of the
spiritual world.
And they have no concept of the secular
world.
You see?
Right.
There's not a lot of biblical history on
the past 2,000 years.
Because it all ended 2,000 years ago.
And if you really want to know who
is behind the scenes, you have to go
back and see who was behind the scenes.
Or who was running overtly 2,000 plus
years ago.
Who was running the world.
And I've broken that down several ways.
And my research on the Magi, because there's
three levels to that.
It's not over.
I haven't been as diligent as I like
to be on it.
And I'm not doing it online, by the
way.
Some of it.
But it's not.
You put on stuff that you're not going
to get a Magi.
You have to go at it indirectly online
if you could find it.
But, nonetheless, there are powerful groups of people
that have been endowed by deities.
Like the Apkallu, for example.
They're still around.
Or the Nephilim.
The sons of gods are still around.
The Hybrids.
I'm not sure of how much of the
early Genesis man is around.
But descendants of Adam are around.
In other words, I'm not sure of how
many men that are descendants of the people
that Cain said he was afraid of.
Because when Cain said he was afraid of
going out into the world, basically, he didn't
mention he was afraid of his brothers and
sisters, did he?
No.
He was afraid.
He was just afraid of them.
Who's them?
You know, when you're speaking, directly or indirectly,
you never give people that are kin the
term them.
No.
No, you don't.
Notice that?
Always.
When you use the terminology them or they,
it's strangers, foreigners.
Right?
Yeah.
So how could they, if Adam and Eve
and Cain...
The High One knew who they were.
Oh, yeah, because he told you.
He gives it to you.
In etymologically form, if you look in the
Hebrew etymology and in the Hebrew concordance and
or interlinear, you'll see that they're not given
names, but they're given descriptions.
Yeah.
You had the man of remembrance and you
had the female.
Mm-hmm.
Where Adam was never called the man of
remembrance and Eve was never called a female.
No.
Yep, and they had 2,000 years to
muck about.
To do a lot.
Yeah.
That's a lot of time.
And there's a lot of other stuff in
Genesis that needs to be discussed.
That's right in front of you, right there,
and I haven't brought it up yet, and
I'm waiting.
And last week I said the reason why
there hasn't been much commentary on it is
because you can't yet, is what I should
have finished off saying.
You can't yet.
So hurry up and do it.
Somebody.
But not because of my sake or your
sake, just for the sake of it.
Because we can't be that piss poor of
a human race, are we?
Yes, we are, actually.
It's that pathetic.
What else is there in Genesis prior to
the creation of man, even after, all the
way to chapter 5 that needs to be,
it's just like in neon lights, if you're
reading an interlinear, and no one's saying anything.
It's like, man, I'm not going to say
it.
You know what?
I better get quote-unquote paid for it.
I'm not saying it in public, and I'm
not going to do it for free.
Sorry.
Too much work went behind to figure it
out.
So, in other words, paid for it doesn't
mean, well, you send me money and I'll
tell you.
No, that doesn't mean that either.
It means that it's a position of empowerment
that shouldn't be granted freely, based on the
subject.
You know what I mean?
No.
Like, for example, let's talk about the medical
industry.
You could talk to these medical morons that
have licenses in state training and all that.
How many of them actually tell you how
to treat a simple cut or a wound
effectively, that goes beyond anything that they can
do?
None.
Not a one.
They don't know it.
And it's instinctive to do it.
If you hit your nose by accident or
your elbow, or you get a bump on
the head, instinctively, don't you want to squeeze
it?
And don't you go, ow, my nose.
Ow, my elbow.
Ow.
Right?
Don't you do that?
So how many of these medical morons can
actually explain to you, how much is that
worth?
A lot, believe it or not.
By the way, it works really well on,
not a lot in terms of, you know,
I'll give me money and I'll tell him,
Greek.
No.
Empowering.
It's worth a lot.
It's very empowering.
Yesterday I used, I have an oven that's
modified.
By the way, just jump around here to
cooking.
Sure.
I have like a Roper brand.
It's a restaurant style oven.
But it's not stainless steel.
It's baked enamel.
But it has the restaurant type grid on
top, you know.
Sure.
It's not the, you know, it's very wide.
Anyway, when you open up the oven, it's
gas burner on the bottom, broiler section, oven
section.
What I did is I put a solid
partition so when I turn on the oven,
it gets really, really hot beyond the 500
or 600 degrees really, really fast because it's
a small volume.
Well, I was doing something stovetop like I
like to, but I wanted it crispy and
I knew this oven will go to 500
degrees in 30 seconds flat with that compartment.
So I threw it in there.
It's a Lincoln pan.
Sure.
It's a restaurant, very thick, heavy stainless steel
pan, copper bottom, you know, with a handle.
So I put it on the stovetop and
about five or six minutes later I forgot
that I had been there and I grabbed
it and I actually hear the searing sound
when I touched it.
You know, the searing sound?
Yeah.
I'm like, oh, that's not going to be
good.
So I wrapped three of the fingers and
it was quite painful for about an hour.
Really tight, to the point where I did
let it go for about half an hour.
It got a little numb.
Replaced it and went over this.
Today it looks like nothing happened.
And where the blisters would have formed, there
was no fluid in the blister.
You just see that the skin is partitioned
white in that area, like a pale chalky
white color.
But there's no fluid in the blister.
You see?
Yeah.
You get it?
Right.
Because the vacuum was not broken.
So it does also work for that.
So there are so many things that can
be discussed that are very high value, empowering
and all that.
Let me just go back to Genesis.
Again, if you're going to be conservative, there's
the rabbis, the ancient sages, says, if you
know, be happy.
If you know what it is, don't say
it.
And for the commoners that don't know, be
happy with what you know, because these things
should be kept secret.
I don't really agree with that.
I'm not saying what they're saying is wrong.
There's purpose to it, though.
There is.
Yeah.
Right?
Because, see, the wicked people always mock.
And they don't know how to act.
I mean, there's plenty of people that I've
been around for years doing Greek speaking and
other things like that.
And then I pull back and I'm going
to look at this person.
They're just, you can't polish a turd, really.
You have to just walk away.
They don't improve themselves.
They can't explain anything.
So you've just got to walk away.
You've just got to be like, okay, that's
next.
Well, I think one of the bigger reasons
would be when the pranksters get a hold
of the info.
Oh, well, the pranksters won't understand it because
it's in conflict with their mindset.
But if they do, they have a huge
opportunity.
Well, look at Simon Megas.
Oh, in that case.
Yeah, well, the thing is, humans are very
easy to prank.
So, I mean, you should be able to
see through it if you have the mindset.
So they don't need much to do it.
See, what the pranksters, like all the politicians,
the heads of your scientists, your heads of
entertainment, your medical people, your religious people, they're
figureheads by the secret people that have been
in power for thousands of years.
We don't know who they are.
Actually, you can figure out who they are.
I'm not going to get into that.
You could figure out who they are.
But if you put their names in Google,
they won't show up, by the way.
And if you got real specific with their
names, you're going to have a problem with
Google, by the way.
Yeah.
Because they control Google as their company.
And they know that.
So these are all just your basic morons.
The reason why, you know, all your religious
leaders, your political leaders, your medical leaders, your
legal leaders, lawful, they have to put a
moron in that position because if he wasn't
a moron, the people would see them and
say there's something wrong with this guy because
he's not a moron like us.
Right.
They won't be able to relate.
You get it?
Right.
And that's why they're called figureheads, you know,
all of your religious leaders.
I mean, you know, give me an example.
Years ago, back in the 80s, I was
hanging out with some people that did, quote,
unquote, real estate rentals, high-end rentals in
New York.
We rented some people from Tibet.
And I thought I was being cool by
talking about the Dalai Lama, and they all
put a frown on their face.
They were like upper-class Tibetans, you know.
Sure.
And they were like, and one of the
younger said, well, you guys don't like the
Dalai Lama.
And he said, nope, we do not.
He's a CIA drug dealer pedophile.
He deals, he steals children.
He deals in drugs.
He works for the CIA.
He covers up for all the crimes of
the Western intelligence agencies and Western business people,
essentially.
And I was like, ooh.
And I thought, like, the Dalai Lama was,
like, the shit, right?
Because that's what they want you to think.
Right.
Right?
Wow.
So if the Dalai Lama is imagining what
the Pope is doing, right?
Well, you know.
Right.
Whoa.
You know?
Wow.
Talk about fried foreskins in a bag for
snacks.
So, you know, and all these guys, you
know, all these guys are put in front
of you.
They have to be this way because that's
what people resonate with, you see.
The people that are in power that are
behind the scenes are completely, you know what
their number one thing is?
Secrecy.
That's their number one thing.
They still get out.
They get out and about.
They're not, like, underground and they're not hiding.
They're in your face.
You can run into them if you know
what to look for.
Right?
And I've explained this to people.
I did a long Skype about ten years
ago or less.
Maybe it was Skype.
I was a year into Skype or whatever.
I was talking about the Bilderbergs, right?
So I said, look, okay, we got all
these Alex Jones photos and all these other
people.
Try to get as many photos as possible
of people going to the Bilderbergs.
You see, like, Henry Kissinger and this other
guy in the back of the limousine, right?
Window down.
You see Prince Charles.
You see all these other guys.
I said, well, look, you're not noticing.
You see these guys that you're looking at
the wrong person.
These people in the back seat that you
know about, look at their faces.
They're in terror.
And who are they in terror of?
The driver.
Because the driver is the guy who's really
in power.
The janitor.
When you control the world and you want
to go to a Bilderberg, you dress up
as housekeeping.
You drive there as the chauffeur.
Take the chauffeur's photo, not Kissinger's photo, and
run him through a database.
You won't find him.
Because he owns the database.
Wake up.
Think about it.
It's 007 time, people.
Or, you know, who was it?
Ben Franklin was number 72.
You know, they like to number their agents.
You know, Ben Franklin was a spy.
He probably instigated the Revolution, but it only
goes so far, so the English always still
had the upper hand to put their institutions,
banking, religion, academia.
Because if the American Revolution went so far,
it would have prohibited anything English other than
commercial, and it would have been filtered as
such.
But anyway, so he was number 72, allegedly.
There's a mysterious number 72 during the war,
and although the correspondence fits only with one
man, it was also with France, because the
enemy was not England.
It was France, and it was France versus
England during those times, because France was the
most advanced country in the world for at
least 100 years already.
But anyway, so no one is paying any
attention.
No one's being objective.
Let's say no one.
Yeah, there are out there.
I don't know where they are or who
they are, but it doesn't matter at this
point.
No one's being lawful, because lawful just means,
you know, what are you basing it on,
right?
So, for example, if you know that mankind,
I'm not saying believe in, know that you
are a created being, and there are gods
put over each nation, but there is one
creator, who actually humbled himself to come down
and be a god over a group of
people.
That's why they're called chosen people.
People don't know why.
They're so stupid.
You still hear, oh, what makes them chosen?
That's embarrassing to ask that question.
It means you're a total oaf.
How many times do you hear, like the
anti-Semitic, anti-Zionist types, what makes them
chosen?
You hear that all the time.
Even Ocelli used to add people on and
laugh about that.
That shows you're just like a common oaf.
That means you have no education at all
about anything.
None of them do.
People that are educated and don't have an
agenda and do not do YouTubes, people, they
don't do shows.
That's why I don't do shows.
I do sonic events.
Here it comes.
I heard it or not, or was I
listening?
Did you hear that?
Yeah, I heard that.
Yeah, but were you listening?
Right.
So, you can't polish a turd.
There's seven billion, you could presume seven billion
turds on this planet.
Which one can be polished?
Don't bother.
You don't want to find, you want to
find people.
Who was the Greek philosopher?
I keep forgetting his name.
I look him up and I forget him.
He lived in a clay vase, a large
terracotta vase in the forest.
And he would come out into the marketplace
in ancient Greece with a lantern at noontime,
a lit gas lamp, an oil lamp.
Right.
And he put it in people's faces.
And he says, what are you doing that
for?
He says, I'm looking for an anthropos, which
is, you know, mankind.
Because none of you fit.
None of you fit the bill.
Anyway.
All your secret societies started with the ancient
Greeks, by the way.
Your attorneys, the Bar Association, all that shit
in the western world.
And there was always a very deep connection
between the eastern and the western.
Don't ever think that there's xenophobia.
Xenophobia came later with what they call the
early dynasties.
But no one ever wants to tell you
what was going on when you had a
new world order on the earth, you know,
after the flood.
You know, around the time before the flood
and just after the flood, the whole world
was connected.
It became disjointed later.
Because the nations were set up in populace
and in priority over each, you know, each
god decided, you know, let's make it interchangeable
here and xenophobic here.
Xenophobic means no strangers.
So xenophobia came later.
But anyway, yeah, I don't know what, you
know, every time I do a sonic event,
it's like, why bother?
You know, why bother?
But I know that there is a very,
very, very, very small, minute group of people
out there, not as a group or as
followers or whatever.
It's like someone was saying, you know, I'm
not looking for students.
I'm looking for teachers.
I'm not interested in students.
Right?
Because then you have to set up a
form of exchange and tuition.
You have to set up a school and
all that.
And then you have to check them and
make sure they learn it.
Nah, fuck that.
I'm looking for teachers, people that, people who
want to teach.
I'm not looking for students.
I don't care about students.
It's too way down the ladder.
Not that I'm way like a high.
It's just that it's too far.
It's too late.
I mean, there's not enough.
In other words, there's 7 billion people on
the earth.
You know, you go, you find 5, 10,
20 or 100 that can, that can be
objective, that can be lawful, that could be,
have a good mindset and let them go
teach it.
A student is irrelevant at this point.
So anyway, the whole thing, again, just where
we started off, I did put a YouTube
in there.
It's worth looking at in the chat.
I don't know what the title is.
I should go look on the computer.
Look it up.
It's about a guy who used to do
gang stalking and he's speaking about like Seattle,
Washington is a hub for using tech.
What is it?
What do you call radio?
Tesla called it when you use technology to
mind control people and harm them.
What's the term?
Tesla coined it a while back, Bruce.
Anyway, it's where you use radio waves and
microwaves to beam at people to inflict pain
or mind control or voices.
Anyway, so he says Amazon Corporation and some
company called SIS in California and all that.
So anybody in Seattle, Washington got any firsthand
knowledge or even secondhand knowledge of that?
It'd be interesting to start a little conversation
about it.
I'm not against it.
I'm not for it.
It's just I just want to know if
I run across something like that.
It'd be good to have it confirmed.
And if it's not confirmed, it doesn't matter.
Are you still there, Bruce, or are you
muted?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was looking at a video up for
you and also checking on the Greek guys
in the clay pot.
Oh, OK.
Muted in between there.
Sorry about that.
No, he's a Greek philosopher.
Yeah.
He was just tired.
He was just, you know.
So we're here on this planet with this
sick society, depraved, sick, and waiting for the
mop-up crew 12 and a half years
or less.
So what do you want to do?
Do what you've always been doing.
Food, water, clothing.
Good company.
All right.
Looking at some e-mails.
I think I mentioned them.
They were mostly sent before I started.
So I don't see any questions here.
Molecular weight of water.
Someone was sending an e-mail about it.
He doesn't understand it.
I get it wrong.
He had it wrong.
Water is 18.01528 grams per mole, right?
Right.
And air is 28.97 grams per mole.
So if we do a quick division.
So it still is.
So I just sent them that information.
So if you take roughly a rough estimate,
18 divided by 29, air is 40%.
It's not even 5 or 10%.
It's 40% air than water.
You could almost say double.
Because 18 is pretty close.
Yeah, 29 is pretty close to 36, but
it's not quite still off.
I put it like guardians to the galaxy.
They're going to put us a quarter of
a mil.
A quarter of a mil is a third.
No, it's not.
A quarter, you can't even get a pair
of boots for a quarter.
Right?
Right.
Yeah, anyway.
Yeah.
That's just really shitty.
But, so, is it diogenes?
It could be, but I'm not sure.
I think it could possibly just put it
in.
So, again, learn to cook good meals.
Take care of yourself.
Good hygiene.
Use soap.
My favorite soap is any kind of a
liquid soap is good, by the way.
It doesn't have like vegetable tallow where you
have to scrub your shower down every so
often.
You know, more often than not.
But I like the Chandrika soap from India.
I do, too.
It's about a dollar fifty apart.
I've shared that with quite a few different
folks, and all had a very favorable response.
Oh, good.
There's a green one, and there's a yellow
or an orange colored one.
I like the green.
You like the green?
It's a little more potent, yeah.
Yeah, it's really good.
It's just basic.
It's basically olive, and there's no animal in
it is why I like it.
Because the last thing you want to be
washing with is animal tallow.
Soap is basically alkaline fat.
Soap, by the way, is alchemy.
How can you start off with fat and
turn it into something that actually dissolves fat?
There's so much alchemy going on that catalysts,
like a catalytic converter, like a hydrogenated vegetable
shortening is water and oil, and it's passed
over nickel and some other material, beads.
Water and oil don't mix, but if you
pass it over the nickel material, you don't
deplete the nickel unless you go high velocity,
a lot of friction, and you end up
with this vegetable shortening.
It defies science to explain because it's not
real science.
Or the catalytic converter.
How does the platinum get the fuel to
reignite and burn off the sulfur?
It's just passive.
So when you understand how, to a scientist,
a tree, an oak growing from a seed
is considered passive, by the way.
It's in their paperwork that way.
It's not dynamic.
They don't consider natural growth to be dynamic.
They can't.
Definition.
Yeah, they don't.
That's why back in the 30s there was
a movement called dynamic farming, with Steiner and
all these other guys using dynamic farming methods,
because they basically, even in science, what they
consider organic, they still use terms as if
it's not dynamic.
It's still dead to them because they only
know the chemistry of it.
They can't touch the physics of it because
it goes against their god.
And that's where you came in with the
copper tubes and all that, or the copper
plowing and different implements.
Right, or soil inoculation.
You can take a very potent compost and
you stuff it in a cow's horn, literally,
for a certain time of year, and you
bury that in the ground.
And then you take that stuff you stuffed
in the cow's horn and you empty it
into a tank of water and you mix
it a certain way.
And you take the water out of that
tank and just add it to your irrigation.
It could be like parts per thousand.
You could put just like a quart of
this water into a large irrigation channel and
it will make everything bloom like mad.
Now, chemically, it doesn't make any sense, because
the quantities are so small.
Right.
The way certain composting should be done, geometry
is very important.
You can't just bury it in the ground.
It's how you bury it in the ground.
How deep and what the shape of the
hole looks like and what you cover it
with.
So, yeah, there's a lot of discussion on
progress and edification to be done, but I
don't see any need for it.
I think that when I want to get
on certain subjects, whether they're general or in
depth or just as simple as cooking methods
or whatever, I don't think there's a need
for it.
I think there's just people find to get
kicks out of it.
And even when they come back and say,
well, it's much better now, I didn't ever
really think there's a need for it in
this society.
In the next society, it'll be the only
way it's going to be done.
So it won't even be considered a need
because it'll be known.
You see, this society is too entrenched in
their ways.
And that doesn't mean why bother.
Yes, it actually does mean why bother.
But in a sense, if you're going to
speak, a fool has to say something, but
a wise man has something to say.
I'm not saying that I'm wise, but I'm
saying there's a lot to be said, a
lot that could be said, that can be
said, that's very edifying and all that.
And, yeah, I'm not inspired to do that.
I seemed like I was in the past,
and I did, but I never expanded on
anything because the feedback was never in a
point where it graduated to the point of,
you see.
Even when people send me an email, most
of the time it's not to expand on
stuff, but most of the time it's just
to restate something that they missed.
And if you missed it, it's not my
problem.
You need to stop saying, did you hear
that?
And start saying, maybe I should listen again.
Instead of, did you hear what he said?
No, I don't care about hearing, I care
about listening.
And if you tie in, let's say, the
biggest feedback I've gotten from a positive outset,
which is, of course, what you expect from
a materialistic society, is based on water and
food.
Some on scripture, but it just dies on
the vine.
I mean, there's really no one really interested
in scripture.
They say they are, but it doesn't matter
what they say, I watch and see what
they do, which is, nothing's going on.
And that's not a complaint, by the way,
that's just an observation.
You don't want to hear my complaints.
I don't complain because, why bother?
Complaining doesn't help.
And it's not a disapproval, because I don't
want to give approval or disapproval.
The thing is, are you pursuing a mindset
that is objective, that is lawful, that is
clear?
So, again, make sure you prepare some good
water and food for yourselves, and whatever.
And if you're white people, you have to
try extra hard, because you have a handicap.
If you have a culture that comes from
Europe or Asia, that handicap is not there
as much as Western culture.
Just remember where you came from and that
place, they did a pretty banging job.
As long as you could hybridize the methodologies
of European, let's say, Mediterranean and Asian cooking
with lawfulness, you'll be alright.
So, I don't see any questions or anything,
any other comments or anything, otherwise we'll just
do it right here.
You don't have to be long.
Just to reiterate, you're always free, and everyone
has always been free, as Free Will would
have it.
That's why they want you to pledge allegiances.
Have you ever heard of that?
Oh, yes.
Pretty harsh if you don't.
Well, that's okay, because they don't know.
Well, you should remember that when you were
growing up, you had that.
And the reason that they're harsh is because
their lives will be harsh if you don't.
If you don't, right.
You see, right now it's hard to call
the attorneys, the doctors, the priests, the rabbis,
the politicians, the scientists pranksters, because their followers
are so deeply entrenched, which is the majority,
that they're also pranksters.
So there's no reason to state the obvious
that it's a pranking society.
Again, when you see parents pranking their own
children, you know it's a...
Forget about what the politicians, the scientists, the
attorneys, the priests, the rabbis are saying.
The parents are pranking their own children in
their homes, in private.
They don't stand a chance.
Forget it.
When they go out into the world, they're
going to be accommodated and whittled down, especially
with a credit-based economy, when there is
no money, when your actions are being monetized.
There are people I know in alternative media
through the years, and I've always asked them
when they talked about YouTube being monetized, where
does YouTube get the money from?
I don't know.
I don't care.
All I know is I get a couple
hundred bucks every month.
These are the people that are bringing you
alternative media that talk about making the world
a better place.
I don't have to mention names.
You know who they are.
They don't know anything.
They don't want to know.
There's nothing going on, people.
Nothing.
Sorry to give you the news if you
haven't gotten it yet.
So, if you really want to find out
what's going on, learn to look beyond five
feet in front of you, beside you, behind
you, all around you, and you'll see what's...
rectify that, and you'll see what's beyond that,
what you see on the stupid rectangle, all
the morons on there, all of them, and
wherever else, whether it might be in your
own home, or at work, or out in
the street, or whatever, you'll see that the
best thing to do is food, clothing, and
shelter.
And up the quality of that.
And on that trip, you will discover the
things that matter.
You know?
Take time to enlighten yourself, too.
So, a little bit over a decade left
is not a long time.
No.
But it depends on how intense it is.
You know, like, if you're in a car
accident, the moment you acknowledge you're going to
be in a car accident, even though by
the stopwatch it's .8 seconds, it seems like
a really long time.
Like, you ever fall off of a bicycle,
or fall off of a ladder?
The moment you realize that you're not going
to recover, and you're going to go through
a control, you know, fall?
That's why I used to, in cycling, I
used to tell people, practice dismounting.
Many, many different ways, and rapid dismounts in
many different ways.
Why?
Is it because a crash is just an
indeliberate dismount, isn't it?
It is.
You fall off of a ladder, it's just
an indeliberate dismount, isn't it?
Indeliberate.
What's the difference coming off of a ladder,
as you would normally, and falling off of
a ladder?
There's no difference.
In both cases, in one instance you're on
the ladder, in the next instance you're not.
What's the difference?
One is deliberate, the other one is indeliberate.
Right?
You could ram a car into a tree
any time of the day.
What's the difference when you have an accident?
Well, the result is the same.
One is deliberate.
You deliberately ran a car into a tree,
or you had an accident.
What's the difference?
Or running someone over, you deliberately ran them
over, or you hit them by accident.
What's the difference?
The result is the same.
One is deliberate, one is not.
You see?
In other words, the more you practice, and
the more ways you are aware of, and
not only aware of the ways, but aware
of going through that way, you can see...
For example, if you ever hung out with
upper-middle class teenagers, usually if they jumped
out their wallet, or they said, here's my
wallet, and you went through it, you saw
there was a bail bondsman's card in there,
prepaid for $500 or $1000.
Because the parents knew, well, my son likes
to drink, he's 16, 17, he's probably going
to get arrested or whatever, at least he
has a prepaid bail bondsman's card, he can
just walk out of jail if he takes
it.
So the parents had already considered that and
prepared.
Well, no one says, well, my child's going
to go to jail.
Most people don't think that way, and when
it happens, it's just a surprise.
But upper-middle class and wealthy people prepare
themselves.
They say, well, they've got a teenage son,
or even a daughter, and they're kind of
rowdy.
I think we should go to the bail
bondsman and get a prepaid card, just in
case.
What's the difference between the two?
One is considered what might happen, and prepared
for it, right?
What is it?
One out of 1,200 times of driving,
you're going to get a flat.
So one out of 1,200 chance, or
one out of 2,000 sometimes now, with
better tires.
Back in the early days, it was one
out of 50.
I remember back in the late 60s and
70s, flats were still fairly popular.
When they were experimenting with the extra-heavy
steel-belted radials that actually blew through the
thing.
And back then, there were still some tires
that had tubes in them.
But anyway, why do you have a spare
tire in your car if it's a one
out of 200, or one out of 1
,200 chance?
Indeliberate.
You can deliberately go out and put a
hole in your tire.
People don't do that, because it's inconveniencing.
But if you went out and put a
hole in your tire, deliberately, you said, I'm
going to go put a hole in the
tire.
Well, before you do that, don't you say,
well, what if I want to go somewhere
and I can't?
Before I put this hole in the tire,
shouldn't I get a spare tire first and
then do it?
Because it seems kind of wasteful, I know.
It does.
Same thing when you get a flat, you
prepare for it.
So that's why I say this was a
long way around the block, a slow walk
around the block, to why bother?
The mop-up crew is coming, like it
or not, or know it or not, believe
it or not.
So why bother?
So, in terms of, the reason, again, I'm
saying that is back deep in the mind
or in the spirit of most people is,
well, I shouldn't say some people, not most,
is they do want harmony and peace for
everyone.
Even the psychopaths, the real, when I think
of stupid people, it gives me the chills,
it's really creepy.
But the stupid people, even they want harmony,
but they can't admit it because they just
don't know, they're just going to do what
everybody else does, right?
This is the great majority, the seven billion
plus, or eight billion now, whatever it is.
Inherently, most people that do have a proper
mindset, in the back of their spirit or
their mind, they do consider, wow, what about
a day of harmony?
What about being free from all this bullshit?
Because most stupid people think, oh, there's a
threat of war, there's a threat of economic
collapse, former people have spoken to you, what
a ridiculous, how can you crash a credit
-based society?
All they do is cut off your credit,
just like your parents cut off your allowance,
they're not broke.
You're allowed to access, because it's not even
theirs.
But anyway, all of these things that people
are thinking of go away, because they're all
fictional.
They're there for several reasons.
Most of them are not fiction once they
take effect socially.
Like, for example, rioting is a good example.
Most riots are caused by some plausibly misgiving
event, like Rodney King, remember in L.A.,
there was blatant evidence that all the cops
were acquitted and people rioted because they're not
getting justice.
There are so many levels to all of
this.
Or opportunists, these things are in the mind.
So in the mind of a rational mindset
that is a proper mindset, you want to
think of a future that is clear and
prosperous and all this, and you're going to
get it, but it's not going to be
based on the systems that are in place,
that have been in place since time immemorial.
It's going to be a new system.
But here's the thing, all of the corruption
that you see that your average human is
involved in, willingly, is still based on something
lawful.
You see, that's why it's so difficult for
them.
See, they're putting the chips in cards right
now, I know it's bank cards, right?
They know that if they outwardly come in,
one of their other problems is how they're
going to chip everyone for money.
Because they know that as long as you
have something you could hold or use, like
money, a credit card or an object, as
long as it could be objectified away from
you, they'll accept it.
But very few people will accept the chip
in their body for it.
So that's another problem that they're having.
The transhumanism, they want to start integrating it.
They already got everyone pumped up through the
food.
There are elements and compounds you could put
in food that you will ingest that will
stick to your intestines, right?
You know there's magnetic drinks you have to
take before you do a CAT scan, right?
And some of those have been recalled because
it actually killed people, those magnetic drinks.
Actually I told a lady, don't do a
CAT scan, it doesn't matter, just do a
FAST if you think you have a tumor
in your head.
She did the CAT scan anyway and then
she had to have her thyroid removed or
something a year later.
Anyway, drink.
Human livestock though.
There's so much to discuss, but you see,
most people still think money is lawful, and
it's not, but once they go to a
chip in your hand, then it's obvious, right?
But it's too late.
Years ago there was a military base in
Hawaii and a woman that lived there says,
oh yeah, a friend of mine's brother is
part of a protest on the base, they
don't want to get chipped.
So what they did in the military, whoever
protested, they threw them in the brig and
then they just chipped them in the brig.
Anyway, right?
You get it?
Is that the point?
So.
Yeah, you get it one way or another.
So, alright, we were going to cut it
short, let's I guess cut it, I don't
think there's anything else.
Okay.
And we'll do it again next week maybe.
You'll notice we're doing, usually I've been kind
of temperamental, if there are any questions or
any reason to do a sonic event, we
won't do it, but we'll just come on
every week maybe and if there's just nothing
we'll just keep it short.
Okay.
Thanks for doing all the work behind the
scenes to keep it on the servers.
And I don't know how well organized it
is, I haven't really been there in a
long time, but if we can, I'm thinking
of maybe putting some stuff on the site,
by the way, I'm not upkeeping the Uncommon
Radio site, or I'm not doing anything on
it, but I might start putting some stuff
on it, right now it's in free mode,
I don't even want to give them the
80 bucks or whatever a year, I'd rather
buy smokes and coffee, which I have a
$300 or $400 a month of smokes and
coffee anyway.
but I'm thinking of, that's what I mentioned
earlier, maybe next week or the week after,
or the week after that, sometime do the
essential Greek speak abridged, mixed notes maybe, and
so I could put something like that on
the site, so when people look it could
be something.
If I can help in any way Greek,
just let me know.
Well if anyone's listening, here's the thing, if
they do want to help, if anyone is
listening, because everyone will hear, notice I said
hear and listen, hear things and listen to
things differently, if you folks are out there,
I know it's been done in the past
not well, and I never really told the
person it wasn't done well, there's no reason
for it, because I've discovered, not to complain
about people's writing abilities, because I think I've
discussed that for over 100 years now, the
dumbing up, there's hardly anyone that could really
write or read anymore, but if you want
to go beyond that, and are not bashful,
if you want to send me each one
who's listening, if so cares to, a personal
outline of what they got out of Greek
speak, it could be bullet points, it doesn't
have to be written, just bullet points, and
I'll look at all those, and I'll put
all the common ones together, and do an
essential Greek speak thing, and put it up
on the site as an introductory thing.
Because of course, there's lawful timekeeping, body cooking,
pranking, cosmic censorship, whatever you guys think, do
an outline for me, and just email it
over, and I'll take a look at it,
just out of curiosity, to see how things
go around.
With that said, thanks again Bruce.
Okay, you take care.
See you next week.
You too.
Thanks everyone.