Greetings folks, and we got Greek on the
line here tonight.
How are you doing sir?
Oh okay, I was thinking we would do
a short sonic just specifically to answer some
emails.
I've been getting questions.
Believe it or not, I even have one
fellow who sends YouTube video messages.
So yeah, so I guess yeah.
So I might play some of that.
Basically it's a question about lawyers.
The questions that I want to address I
think will work well with things that I've
been speaking on for a long time, and
there's two sides to it.
One is, well, you know, if I'll read
actually maybe one or two of the emails.
Other ones get really personal, let's say, and
I'd rather just I'll just bring up the
subject matter.
But my answer is always I have discussed
that in the past here and there, but
maybe I'll do a sonic on it as
a specific segment on this question again.
Yeah, one thing I've noticed your streaming.
I put a link on Common Radio for
the stream.
You said there's about 200 hours roughly so
available that's playing on the archives that you
have, Bruce.
So are you still there?
Are we still on?
Oh yep, there I am.
Sorry.
Okay, that's fine.
So with that said, I mean I think
there's a lot of stuff there and actually
it's a very small percentage of what can
be said, what I've discovered.
But at the same time it's 200 hours,
so the ability for people to go through
all that and pick out what they need
specifically and have it be very usable is
the way I try to always speak.
I try not to leave a point hanging
unless I say I am, right?
Right.
And yeah, if I say I'm gonna leave
it hanging till later, that's fine.
Most of these questions again were covered before
and I just figured in my reply I'll
just do a specific segment on a sonic
because there are things that anyone and everyone
listening, you know the three or four people,
can benefit from.
Right.
So yeah, the first one was regarding nightmares.
Okay.
And the person that heard what I discussed
the source, you know, of its external input
and essentially, just to recap here, you're being
messed with, right, by spiritual beings and they're,
you know, there's such a mass plethora of
variety of gods and demons and imps and
angels that I wouldn't be surprised and I'm
highly inclined to say as a fact that
there are specific demons or imps or angels
that their job in a lot in life,
let's say, is to give people dreams, right?
Right.
So keep that in mind, you know, just
like you have a painter who paints and
a carpenter who works with wood, you have
angels, spiritual beings that just give dreams.
So what I want to suggest here is,
without giving too much information about the recent
one, because I know there are a few
people that have tackled successfully or reduced the
dreams, in this case it did not go
so well and my answer, they gave me
a pretty good synopsis on what they did
and my answer was reflecting why it didn't
go so well.
They were a little aggressive against the entities,
almost in a threatening way, and you don't
want to do that unless you have the
firepower to back it up and it's kind
of like one of those movies where you
shoot at a hologram and it doesn't matter,
right?
So my suggestion there to terminate the cycle
that was happening, because essentially if you threaten
or too aggressive with the, let's say, the
demonic world, all they're going to do is
say, oh, we got a tough one here,
let's get the colonel down here, you know?
They're going to have your artillery.
Yeah, yeah.
So now you've attracted a worse demon.
So what I would suggest, just like recently
I kind of discussed a professional way to
unhaunt a house, is essentially not address anything
that they're doing, just address that you know
what they're doing versus being, you know, steeped
in the ignorance that the rest of the
society is, right?
You do it in a humble way.
Situation.
Yep.
That's all you have to do.
So we'll see how that works out.
Yeah, so right.
So essentially, you know, like even on with
Seth and, you know, because he mentioned it
at Benefit People that he knows personally that
had nightmares and we discussed it.
So but one of the things, you know,
is a gesture to even just close the
door, slam the door, tell them to get
out and slam the door.
Yeah.
Right.
You know, but that's not even necessary.
All you have to do is acknowledge verbally
or in writing or both that you know
who they are in terms of their position
to affect man and you'd prefer not to
have it.
That's all.
You know, just it's the simplest and that's
the that's how hard on a personal note.
I only had one probably all within the
last six months, seven, maybe even.
And it scared the bejeebies out of me.
It literally caught my attention.
And I got up and I'll do that.
I got up the next morning and said,
well, that was a pretty good one.
Oh, yeah.
They have real high.
They have some super highly specialized ones that
work with, let's say, the notion of getting
you to the point in your dream that
you don't know it's a dream.
You think it's real life and you could
actually be killed in your dream.
You see.
So it is pretty dangerous.
Yeah.
If it scares you.
But the ninety nine, nine, nine, nine percent
of the people on the planet don't know
what what's going on.
Right.
You know, so the there's a free for
all on the other side to just they
look at, you know, they look at people
as I call it nickname demon, demon food.
And someone says, what do you mean by
demon food?
Greek?
It's as well.
You know, if you're raising snakes, you also
raise mice or rats because they're snake food.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So people are being raised as demon food
for these demons to play with.
And they've gotten to the point where they
don't have to go hunt anymore or deal
with any adverse responses because people don't know
what's going on, though.
You know, that's basically a pagan or atheistic
or science, you know, bad science, BS mindset.
They wake up and they said, I had
a dream and all everyone runs or what
was it?
I want to know, you know, they don't
know that it's a prank on them.
Right.
The majority of the time.
So especially when it comes to children, the
reality with children is there should be you
should have worked out everything with that, you
know, with children before you had them.
It's not about having a good time and
oops, you know, now you're pregnant.
You know, that's that's the way society goes.
No one really discusses what happens to a
woman's genitalia after she has a baby.
Yeah.
Right.
You know, no one ever discusses, you know,
it takes a woman weeks and months sometimes
to recover.
It's quite disgusting what happens to a woman's
body internally.
You know, some women die from it.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
I think what children know, they're unprepared for
most everything in life because they're, of course,
being acclimated to it.
And they're going to be hit with a
dream, you know, straight off the get go.
And they're not hip to it or, you
know, that's got to be a horrible thing.
It's up to the parents to create the
environment where that is mitigated or doesn't happen.
That's the point.
Because let's just put the children are pathetic.
If you don't change their diapers, they will
die from having feces on their diaper, you
know, pathetic in a sense that they're completely
helpless and they're pain in the ass until
they learn how to speak and behave themselves
and do basic chores.
Right.
You know, they basically pick up after themselves
and not run in front of a car
and get run over or.
Yeah.
So it's not a joy.
I think the idea that people say they're
such a joy is an absolute lie because
the majority of the parents that I've seen
raising children are always in some form of
tension or stress.
And then, of course, I've seen the ones.
And the children are as well.
Yeah.
Are we breaking up or is it just
you that's breaking up?
That might have been just me.
OK.
I'll keep an eye on.
Yeah.
So.
So I'm making a rant on children.
It's part of the the existence that we're
in.
If you haven't had any, get your tubes
tied, get a vasectomy or use a hat
or, you know, I don't recommend making children.
That's if I were to just say maybe
just one thing tonight, don't have any children.
Right.
All right.
You get that.
I'm not saying don't have fun.
You know, friction is good, but children are
not.
Yeah.
So.
OK.
So from that perspective.
Yeah, it's very plain and simple.
But what I wanted to say earlier, people
raising children, just a thought there before we
broke up is there are I know people
as well who don't raise their children.
They have nannies and maids and babysitters full
time, you know, and the stress goes off
of them.
But it still is a stress to them
mentally to know that they because if they
didn't have children, they wouldn't need a nanny.
Right.
Or a full time maid and all this
other stuff.
So either way.
Now, the again, just to finish off on
the topic with the dreams.
From from looking at it from both sides,
from the spiritual side, looking in and then
from being in and in the material world
and looking out, there is ignorance on humans
part regarding what's going on.
So, again, just to close in conclusion, I
would suggest that just acknowledgment that your dreams
are not your own and they're actually you're
being planted with them should suffice.
OK.
And this is going to tie into the
next one.
I don't know if there's anybody in chat.
Let me I think I go back in
there.
So regarding dreams, because dreams are pretty I
mean, they could mess up your day if
you're susceptible to them and they have a
negative impact on your psyche, on your spirit.
So, OK, nothing on that.
The next thing was a fellow sent me
the video message regarding lawyers.
He says, I've heard he's heard me speak
poorly about them.
Well, if you know, if you don't, he
was raised, you know, in a certain Christian
backing, which it's funny that you would bring
that up because it's actually a negative, but
that, you know, the lawyers review poorly also.
That doesn't mean that he was raised right,
but that that aspect is right.
And the other aspect of it is, you
know, if you don't have an attorney in
many cases, you're you're going to be shafted.
So he's in kind of like in an
immature way, he said, what do you I
want to know what you think about that.
So, well, that means that question is overall
very typical, human, unstudied, meaning that, you know
how we discuss any subject, you have to
go look at where it started, right?
You know, I think I've mentioned back to
the children, I do some fraternal twins, a
boy and a girl that were brilliant.
And I was I noticed they're watching TV
all the time, one of these nannies that
were raising them.
And they felt that they had no history
on the television.
They thought the TV was around for thousands
of years, since the time of Noah or
something, right?
Because they had already seen the Walt Disney.
So I had to explain to them, you
know, about Charles Farnsworth and the 20th century,
you know, the because there was a mechanical
television before the electric one.
Yes, like half the size of like a
size of a shed, right?
So yeah, or half the size of a
house.
Yeah.
So once they got that, so what do
we know about lawyers?
Well, first of all, we could just throw
a couple of points down.
There are no more lawyers, which are people
learned in the law, there are just attorneys.
The first thing you have to remember when
you see the title lawyer or attorney, now
they interchange them, but they're attorneys is they
only represent corporations or legal fictions or people
who are wards of the incompetent.
Like if you're a ward, which, you know,
which is an interesting thing years ago, people
didn't want to live in the city because
they were divided in wards.
A ward just means an incompetent, right?
The second thing is you will not find
any legislative act anywhere in any state or
any country that created or allowed the Bar
Association to operate the way that it does
today.
You could look up what the Bar Association
is.
There's a lot of patriotic conspiracies back and
forth.
That's not what I'm discussing.
It's a private organization.
There is no such thing as a license
to practice law.
They only have a bar membership card and
that supposedly is their license, right?
Which it's not a license, right?
Okay.
The other thing is what the legislature later
did do is they created the courts, right?
You could read it in the constitution and
the constitution actually tells you they have no
power in law or equity, right?
So what do they have power in?
So what they did is they created the
court building and then if you start looking
at the early definitions of who was to
operate in the law, it was someone learned
in the law.
So the Bar Association in America was created
around the 1870s.
Didn't really start taking effect until turn of
the century and now it's spread like a
major disease.
Now you have more regarding the legal society
there.
Imagine a dog with more tics than dog,
right?
It's a really bad situation.
The other thing is you have to understand
that it's a mild theocracy, okay?
Because it's justice, right?
It has nothing to do with law.
There are no attorneys that know any law
in context or by definition.
That's a fact.
And there might be some that do but
they don't last.
They usually get disbarred and they become car
salesmen, right?
And I'm saying this right in a way
because it's pretty sad.
This is just the same with priests and
doctors and all that, right?
So essentially if you have a situation where
you're going to need an attorney, it depends
on what it's going to, you know, is
it a hill you want to die on,
right?
Recently I've had discussions about a parking ticket
or a traffic, just pay it, because it's
getting worse and worse and worse, right?
You remember the medical is getting worse, the
religious is getting worse, and this is religious
by the way.
Essentially if you spend an hour a day,
the thing is I've spoken to people studying
what's called law, which an hour a day,
in three months you'll know more than any
attorney on the planet, right?
I'm not talking about case law and all
that.
And by the way, you know, this can
be an eight hour conversation about what attorneys
are doing wrong and in five minutes I
can tell you what they're doing right, which
is basically what they're doing correctly is they're
part of a mild theocracy, unacknowledged, unspoken, but
in your face, right?
It's kind of like, you know, people look
at, let's say, the Dodge logo now, the
Ram, and they say that's a Dodge logo.
They don't really stop and think it's a
Ram, an actual effigy or image of an
animal, right?
They don't talk about that, right?
Or whatever.
So what you're dealing with here is a
society that is a mild theocrat, it's theocratic,
but the problem with it is they're sort
of on autopilot where you go in an
airplane or and the airplane's flying was full
of passengers and there's no pilot.
No one, you know, there's no one there
piloting it, right?
So that's what's going on in a sense.
It's a free-for-all.
It goes the same with, basically, it's lawless.
What you have is social control, which is
necessary.
I'm not saying there should be no attorneys
because, you know, if you lived in a
society of headhunters, you need certain control because
if they're running low on shrunken heads, they
might start trying to get it off of
each other versus the ones they conquer, you
know.
So like, for example, in Western society, if
you just announce on the telly or the
news that there is no more emergency services,
if you dial 9-1-1, no one
shows up.
They'll be just random wanton rioting for no
reason.
If you ask people why you're rioting, it's
because they can.
So this is a savage society.
What do you expect?
People that administer your law to be in
like kind.
So you're not dealing with a civilized group
in the legal society.
You know, the oxymoron is police or law
enforcement.
They don't know how can they enforce something
they know nothing about, you know.
So it's like going to a shoemaker and
saying, I want a strawberry milkshake.
You know, he doesn't know anything.
He's not set up for that.
So yeah, it's basically a sick, crazy society.
And you have, you know, the like, controlling
it or keeping it in check.
But I do enjoy watching sometimes a sci
-fi movie when they show like the Klingons
or the Romulans, and they're really brutal, you
know, to each other.
Yeah.
And I don't like watching brutality.
But this is what's going on now.
And you love it.
I mean, people, no one's complaining.
It's the way it is.
You know, I'm like, yeah, it is.
But, you know, the other thing, anything in
the legal society, by the way, just to
leave off maybe something you could research on
your own, anyone can is all by presumption.
So simply denying everything, anything they say categorically
or specifically piece by piece or countering it
is the is how they operate.
Right?
And the evidence doesn't matter.
It's what it's, you know, the posture that's
taken.
So it's all presumptive.
Everything is by presumption.
You know, even people that are discussed on
the television show, they call the news, they're
still suspects, right?
They, you know, they read the guy was
wanted for robbery, and they beat him up
through him in jail.
He's a suspect.
Well, why do they have, you know, why?
Why do they do all that to him
if he's just a suspect?
And if he spends five years in prison,
he's still a suspect.
It's all presumption.
I've seen attorneys in many cases, they're state
attorneys, they railroad someone in a prison, and
someone approaches that all this stuff is false
as well.
Yeah, but he agreed to it.
You see what I mean?
Right.
So this is the, the, you know, let's
go from that.
They, they work very much hand in hand
with what's called psychiatrists or psychiatry.
Which is really screwed up.
The psychiatrists are there to adjust you to
a, to a fucked up society, like Jack
Fresco says, basically, they're there to adjust you
to that.
They don't know anything about anything.
They don't even know what the, the word
psychiatry means.
It's at a malad, you know, it means
spiritual, you know, spirituality or spiritualist or psychiatrist,
they can't even define anything.
They're just pawns of that system, just like
the police are and the attorneys and all
that.
Right.
So and they're put there, usually when psychology,
psychiatry is brought up, it's usually a threatening
remark.
Usually, when you threaten someone in this cannibalistic
society, whatever you want to call it, savage,
uncivilized, not just America, but the whole world.
Generally, you know, if you have like a
traffic light, and some asphalt on the ground,
I'm talking about you, your society, right?
You know what I mean?
Right?
Just one traffic light will make you qualify
for this bullshit, right?
Right.
Basically, people in these societies are threatened with
legal action and psychiatric action, and then medical
action, and then imprisonment.
That's those are the threats put on people
in the society generally, and on a nationalistic
level, it's war, which is again, the same
thing.
And by the way, one of these days,
I might have briefly, I think with Ocelli,
which it's like talking to the straw man
from the Wizard of Oz, but you can't,
most people can't grasp what I want to
say.
I have no one really to discuss it
with, but I have insight on how war
is actually done in modern times.
And no one's speaking on it.
I don't know if I want to be
the first.
But let's just try a little bit.
The presumption.
Before these wars happen, this a lot a
little bit of this broke out, by the
way, when Israel went into Lebanon in 06
or 05.
Okay, what the Americans, let's say the Americans
want to attack Iran.
Now, what they do is they send them
a bill for whatever.
That's why they're doing those court cases with
Saudi Arabia and Iran that, you know, they
have to pay for billions for the violent
victims, put it out.
People say it's absurd.
No, it's not.
What they do, like Israel back in 06
sent Lebanon a bill for like 5 billion
and Lebanon says, screw you.
Well, they have three days to pay it
or we're going to attack.
And then once you attack, you send them
another bill for the bombs that you dropped.
Right.
That's all it is.
That's how war is done.
Yeah, the legal people in the military know
this.
It's not spoken about in any history book,
but this is how it functions.
They're always in communication.
They did that with Iraq and Saddam Hussein,
you know, and most of those governments, you
know, are puppet governments, by the way, you
know, in the Middle East, except for the
Saudis.
Right.
I would say.
So, yeah, it's basically a pretty sick world.
Like I mentioned lately, I've been getting into
watching old Star Treks on TV because I
don't like doing drugs.
And it's good to just zone out other
than sleeping or studying or, you know, whatever
else I like to do.
It brings me pleasure.
And it really is a potent drug when
you turn on TV between the flicker rate
or whatever.
And it's hard to imagine that the majority
of the people find that to be, you
know, there's, you know, it's normal for them.
They don't think about it.
You see.
So in essence, studies done back in the
day on the flicker rate and all that
and putting people into kind of like a
state.
And it makes you wonder now with the
new and improved TVs on the newer refresh
rates, how much better, faster.
Yeah, they can do a carrier.
They could do like several frequencies, you know,
easily.
And I sense it.
Yeah, I sense it.
So basically, you know, the majority of the
people are basically what I call demon food.
You know, if you're raising a bunch of
snakes, you have to also raise rats and
mice.
So when you go through the turmoil, the
spiritual turmoil that's going on in the universe,
you're going to have to raise a lot
of humans to keep those demons busy.
I know it's kind of a harsh statement
to make, but I assure you it's true.
So how do I know it's true?
Well, look around you.
You know, basically, you know, the snake metaphor
would be the spiritual world and the rat
or mouse metaphor would be the human at
this point.
And I'm not just mean on a physical,
I'm purely on a spiritual because they're feeding
off of your mind and your actions and
you're quite deplorable as a species and have
been and it's just meant to be that
way for now.
So yeah, so the dream thing, just to
make, make, let it be aware that you
know what's going on.
And you don't need the dreams.
No, thank you.
And with the attorneys and the lawyers, sorry,
it's just like anything else.
The question regarding the lawyers is the same
question as well.
Why shouldn't I go to church?
They talk about God.
You see, it's almost a question like that.
Well, you know, if you don't want to
study anything, you don't want to learn anything
and you want to do it, you know,
what's fed in front of you, then you
do that, right?
But of course, the church isn't going to
stick it to you as much as they
used to back in the days, right?
By the way, a lot of state attorneys
do admit that they're like the Spanish Inquisition,
by the way, which was part of the
church system.
By the way, they do admit it privately.
Yeah, and I'm not making this up.
So if I search several people negotiated this,
well, I didn't you know, they're like, well,
this is basically the Inquisition.
They're like, yeah, basically, they're not shy in
private.
Yeah.
So tying all that together.
The next thing I wanted to bring up
was more of a general email, several questions
about being lawful.
And of course, if I've spent any time
discussing anything in the past, or even now,
it's about being lawful.
Right.
So let me just bring that up.
This is a fairly long one.
And this I left this for last because
it says I'd appreciate if you could discuss
finance lawful, lawful jobs in the modern world
raising your children properly.
Stuff a man could use to get his
house in order without sacrificing the safety of
his children.
Excuse me.
Practical strategies of finding ways of living lawfully
in a world seems to be against it.
So it was finance work, I guess, job
or you're a J.O.B. not Y
.O.B. So but you know, the Y
.O.B. is also spelled with a J.
Yob.
Right.
Yeah.
Like like Juan is spelled with a J.
Anyway.
What do you call two Puerto Ricans playing
basketball?
Juan on Juan.
But anyway.
Anyway, let's see.
So, okay.
In terms of lawful finance, anyone could look
up.
Let's just go down the line here, because
this is really simple, but it's as simple
as you as as simple as it can
be.
It's not easy.
Right.
The easiest part of this is going to
be the money part, believe it or not.
Not in an altruistic way that it's going
to make the world better.
Are you really better off?
But at least you'll be as lawful as
you can be, according to the law.
Again, like I mentioned earlier, this is not
a joke when I say attorneys don't know
any law.
It's I'm not joking about that.
It's kind of I want to go back
to this again.
Two things.
Just like doctors don't know anything about the
human body.
So how can they not know anything about
the human body?
They have neurosurgeons and be able to do
transplants and limbs.
I said, yeah, but the way they've learned
to do those things is really slow with
a lot of trial and error.
You know, if you can go to one
of these special ed schools, you know, where
they have people that are really functionally because
their brains are damaged at birth or whatever
from learning, you can turn those people into
surgeons given enough time.
They're not that smart.
You see what I mean?
Because their brains are physically, the brain can
be physically impeded, you know, with drugs, with
lobotomies and or born, you know, you know,
like sometimes I joke around with people, you
know, your mom is lying, you know, lied
to you about what when when you were
born, you fell on the floor and you
landed on your head first and the doctor
picked you up real quick as if nothing
happened.
But now I can tell, you know, I
could be talking to you.
But anyway, I tell people, so is it
obvious that you were dropped on your head
when you were born?
But anyway, so you ever hear about with
doctors?
Oh, there you know, we had a long
procedure and there were some complications.
And the complications could have been, you know,
with medication, prior treatment, blah, blah, blah, blah,
you hear all that stupid stuff they say
right in their language or legalese medical term.
Okay, but how about this?
That's the way to cover up their ignorance
when they say they have complications, right?
That's it sounds plausible.
It sounds okay.
Right?
Because they don't understand that the body is
under a vacuum.
You're going to get complications, duh.
Right?
If they understood how to work with the
vacuum in the body, the biological vacuum, they
wouldn't be using a word like complications.
It would be specific.
You see?
Yes.
It's like going the doctors are no different
than going to a mechanic and you leave
the car and you tell him you want
this stuff done.
And he's by the way, is this the
steering wheel?
How confident do you feel?
Yeah.
You know, this is what's going on with
the entire medical industry, right?
Now, I've had discussions with people that work
in the medical field in the past, I
bring up the biological vacuum in various modalities.
And they tell me, I don't fully understand
what you're saying.
But I know you're not wrong.
And they weren't placating me, because I had
given the examples, right?
Right.
So they're fairly honest.
I've had other medical people say, well, yeah,
they don't acknowledge that never, not, I don't
acknowledge it, or I don't, or I want
to learn more about it.
Some do some actually have had some that
do say, people have been practicing medicine for
30 years as surgeons and all this other
stuff.
I want to learn more about it.
And I'm like, but you're there, you'll get
fired, you have to, you'll kick you out.
Yeah.
I've had others fancy toilet paper certificate.
Right.
Jack in the box.
What do they call it the cereal box
diplomas, I call them.
The only thing they really they work on
cadavers, they have very little opportunity to comprehend
what a what a healthful or healthy body
is like, for example, I remember athletes saying,
should I go to a doctor?
I'm like, no, you better be.
No, you should go to a sports doctor.
Because the regular doctor is used to looking
at sick people, you'll walk in and you'll
look totally fine to him.
He won't be able to diagnose your you
know, your your tendon or, you know, like
a professional cyclist or swimmer or something that
has a knee pain, they that doesn't look
apparently damaged, they can't tell because they're looking
at old sick Americans, right, which is not
much to look at.
You know, barely resemble a human figure anymore.
You know, so yeah, so it's really so
when you see words like, you know, this,
that and the other, like I mentioned, like
complications in medical terms is to cover up
their ignorance and they're blatantly ignorant.
You know, one way to do it is
watch.
There's plenty of stuff on the Internet.
And by the way, people have asked me,
where do I go online or whatever to
find out on the rectangle more about biological
vacuum?
I said, I haven't found it.
The only place that I found it a
little discussed slightly is with Victor Schauberger, but
he uses his own language again, and people
can't see the crossover.
So this is where I speak because there
is no support in this direction.
And I have, excuse me, I have in
the past gone and not directly solicited, but
I'd say as directly as one could without
making it his life endeavor, indirectly soliciting support
to further on this research, and there is
no interest, right?
Whether it's from the common man or the
upper.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's why very often when, you
know, I get into the rent, like Sam
would say, and I, you know, everyone's an
idiot or a moron.
It's don't don't do anything.
Why bother?
That's that's because I'm slightly further ahead than
most people that are listening to this down
this road, right?
And that's not because I'm jilted.
And not because I'm pessimistic.
I'm actually very optimistic, just like you've heard.
The optimist said, this is the best the
world can be.
And the pessimist says, Yes, I'm afraid you're
right.
Right?
So, yeah, like, today is worse than yesterday
by a little bit, but tomorrow is going
to be a little worse.
It's not as bad as it's going to
be tomorrow.
And after tomorrow, it's going to get a
little worse, you know, and you know, it's
the frog in the pot, right?
Yeah.
So until you get the break, I've discussed
in the 2020s, where you're going to be
led very dynamically by a group of young
people from the Middle East and everyone else
is going to follow.
And you will all proclaim that you've made
it, you know, peace for the next 1000
years and all that.
And once that settles in, you've got less
than three years left.
So as a society, you know, and after
that, it'll be like, you know, post Dresden
bombings for 40 years, you know, you see
the world, the old war movies, people come
out of the survivors, I guess, come out
of the bomb shelters, and they're walking around.
And there's, you know, the middle of the
city in Europe, and see elephants and tigers
in the sheet, because the zoo was blown
up.
Also, you know what I mean?
Sure.
Yeah.
Actually, I'd gotten a woman firsthand during World
War Two, a while back in the 80s.
She was in her 80s in the 80s,
when they bombed, the allies were really the
axis of evil, by the way, if you
really study the history, it's backwards, bombing Europe,
and they came out of a bomb shelter
in Austrian Hungary area, outside of Budapest.
And there were elephants and lions in the
streets.
I said, Wow, what a visual, you know,
imagine hearing that from someone who stood firsthand,
you know, with a heavy Hungarian, you know,
Magyar accent, Magyar is how you say Hungarian
in Hungarian.
And yeah, it makes it gives you chills,
you know, so yeah, but yeah, so got
this is what you guys are going back
to the children, by the way, it's those
places in the scriptures should regret the day
you were born into this mess.
But this is not this is these talks
and gaining knowledge, of course, you know, gaining
knowledge is its own reward.
And these sonic events, I should say, are
there to help navigate how well you navigate.
You know, there's an old metaphor about being
up some kind of creek with a paddle
or without a paddle, that's up to you,
right?
Yes.
And the creek, the creek is that what
they say in the metaphor, right?
So, yeah, you're gonna have to figure out
the paddle and the navigation on your own.
But I would suggest the to go back,
I guess, to recap, none of the entitled
classes know anything.
They know what you know, through the media.
Okay.
Including the medical and the legal and the
religious, especially.
And of course, we've gotten through the political,
they know absolutely nothing.
No politicians or government people.
They're just fulfilling.
I'm going to just this ties in again,
with much of the other stuff about being
lawful or what the contrast of being lawful
is.
They talk about it being a democracy where
you participate, right?
And like Fresco says, Did you participate on
deciding the way the highway is going to
go?
No.
Did you participate on the color of the
flag?
No.
Did you participate on the what the Capitol
building looks like?
No.
Did you participate on who's on the dollar
bill?
No, you're not participating at all.
And most people say, Well, that's for them
to do the experts.
And here's the thing.
It's crazy.
But it would be even worse if it
truly was participatory, because have you met your
average citizen in any country?
Yeah, yeah, it would be even worse.
But what makes it bad saying it's a
democracy and precipice participatory is that it's an
outward lie.
It's a demonstrated outward lie.
And no one sees it.
They all agree with it.
But I'm telling you that it shouldn't be
because the average idiot or moron couldn't, you
know, poor, you know, the piss out of
the boot with instructions on the heel.
So it's kind of good that it isn't,
at least the chaos is limited.
You see, so I wanted to throw that
in because it ties into being lawful and
asking for the attorney and I brought up
what the doctors are and all that.
The first thing was the finance that's really
simple.
In America, and perhaps it needs to be
tried in other countries because of reciprocity.
In America, there's a law under US Code
Title 12, section 411 basically tells you you're
not authorized to use the money.
And instead, if you do have this Federal
Reserve note, you're to go and get lawful
money.
You'd make a demand for it.
It doesn't say they have to give it
to you.
That's why you still don't you don't get
any lawful money.
But you have to show that you made
a demand.
So the way you interact, like, for example,
with the money, right now, the majority of
it is very little cash.
It's either checks or electronic transfer with signatures,
and, and you're bonding instruments with your signature,
right?
Those are bonds that you're issuing.
That's why when you go down the street
and the county or whatever jurisdiction you live
on doesn't say thanks for all the taxes
you guys paid to pay for the bridge
or the roads, does it?
No, it says bonds.
You get it?
Birth certificates, prison records, those kinds of things
are the bonds, right?
So essentially, when you have a financial instrument,
you are bonding whatever they want to do
without any attachments.
And it basically the old uniform commercial code
laws stated that if you unilaterally sign the
name, your full signature on something without any
conditions, that means you're never looking to redeem
anything, to get anything for it.
Think about that for let it sink in
for a minute.
And you were never taught to understand how
to put conditions on things growing up because
why should you?
You're just demon food.
But anyway, you're here to be fed, you're
being raised to be fed spiritually to another
entity, which you know, not you will never
know anything about, by the way.
Years ago, I used to tell people, you're
being controlled by forces you will never understand.
Now, I still say the same thing.
You're being controlled by forces you will never
understand in the ever that you have left,
right?
Because you're getting really close.
Essentially, so whenever you sign anything, you would
write demand for lawful money or per U
.S. Title 12 Section 411 and sign it.
Now, you've created a condition that you're operating
lawfully.
And one of these days, if I can
get other people perhaps to come together, we
could discuss, you know, how you get from
underpaying the use fee from the IRS, you
know, and if they do do that, you
have records that you've been always endorsing the
checks, even if it's electronic check, you know,
they like to do no more paper.
If it's an electronic check and the boss
says, well, I can't give you a paper
check.
Well, what you do then is you just
close the account.
And then when he tries to transfer it,
it bounces back to him.
And he's going to come to you and
say, well, the check, your funds are bouncing
back to me.
What should, you know, you got to do
something.
He says, no, you got to do something,
asshole.
Get your, how's your check writing hand?
Write me a check.
And then you can endorse it, right?
And then you keep a copy of all
that and send it to the IRS.
You get all the, not a return.
They shouldn't have taken anything out.
See the, the accountants, again, they don't know
anything.
I've met plenty of accountants.
I've had corporate accountants for that company that
makes the hamburgers with the clown.
They don't know anything.
They don't even know anything about this.
They, just like I said, attorneys in the
Supreme, like if you ever listened, for example,
a Supreme court judges, what's their purpose is
to, is to work with people in the
bar association.
It's on YouTube.
Don't even, don't believe me.
They don't know any law, you know?
So, I mean, just look at the characters
that are up there.
I mean, it's, it's, you know, you couldn't
make up how, how ridiculous it is.
So the way to do that is non
-conditional.
And the other thing that you remember how
I mentioned when you do a signature, just
a signature with no condition in the old
law, it means that you don't want anything
in return for it.
And you're never going to, you're never, you're
not intending to ever redeem it.
Right.
You get it?
Okay.
Why do you think they switched over to
electronic pads?
You ever, you ever returned something?
What they're doing is harvesting your signature and
putting it on blank contracts that you know
nothing about.
You don't believe that, do you?
Oh, well here, I'm not going to say
I'm indicting them for it, but do you
remember about a year or two ago, Wells
Fargo had opened about 2 million or 3
million credit, credit card accounts.
How did they do that with signature?
They already have it on electronic files.
Can you cut and paste or move over
a signature, you know, to another contract flawlessly?
Yeah.
Has it been done?
It's being done all the time.
So, you know, that's all I'm going to
say on that.
The rest are like, you know, more and
more and more.
I don't think I felt if I think
the people that are listening, these Sonics were
more receptive.
I could get into more detail, but I'm
going to just stop right there.
Okay.
In essence, the rest of it was how
to a lawful job or a job.
Well, why are you doing a job?
Why are you doing a job to get
that right?
To get what we just discussed, some kind
of credit or something that at least you
show you're not endorsing fully that you can
pay, you know, attempt to settle all of
the other requirements that are put on you.
But, you know, because all you know, the
thing is, the more you learn about how
the society functions, the more disgusting it really
is on every level.
I'm not just talking about the American society,
talking about the Canadians, the Iraqis, the Colombians,
the Guatemalans, the Mexicans, the Brazilians, the Russians,
you know, the Koreans, you get you get
my point, Malaysians, the whole, you know, whole
200 and whatever countries there are, they're all
operating in some level of vulgarity and criminality,
all of them.
Okay.
Is it something you can change?
No, because it's been operating for so long
this way that it cannot be changed.
It has to be eliminated completely on a
global level, on a complete social and cultural
level, because it's part of the culture.
What I mean by that is, let's say
America was taken over by the Chinese.
You know, through military loss and the Chinese
won.
No matter what, how much of occupation the
Chinese do in America, the Americans are still
going to retain a certain amount of American
culture.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
So that also has to go.
So there is no possibility of change under
the current conditions.
And I don't mean one condition or two
conditions or three.
I mean, all of the conditions do not
allow a lawful, smooth transition.
Even Jack Fresco said it has to collapse.
Right.
He says, how do we transition from this
to the Venus Project?
You can't.
Right.
So and you know what?
The ancient Ritz say you can't either, do
they?
Don't they?
You see?
Dug in like ticks.
You cannot transition.
There is no transition.
It's like the old miners said, you fix
it or blow it up.
And it can't be fixed.
So this is humankind.
I mean, this has been preset, pre-willed
and functioning and manifesting every day for the
past few thousand years, mostly the way we
know it now.
So in other words, a lawful job or
a job would be what the end result
would be for getting what people call some
kind of payment or satisfaction for their time
compensation.
You see?
Now, there's an interesting slippery slope with that,
which is and it isn't about doing the
right thing with a job.
Right.
So would you want to be an attorney,
accountant, a doctor or a priest or a
lawyer?
Well, none of those are attorney or doctor.
None of those are lawful or being done
lawfully.
But if you it depends on how what
level you view humanity.
If you view them as a bunch of
lab rats, well, then who cares?
So what?
You throw your railroad a guy, throw him
in prison.
So what?
Just a lab rat.
But if you value the man or the
woman or the human being, then you can't
be any of those things lawfully, because you're
going to be part of a machine that
is there to destroy people, not help them.
You see?
Right.
So and what I mean by destroy people,
the Greek, the doctors help a lot of
people.
Attorneys help a lot of people.
Oh, really?
This is the analogy on that.
The military, the military helped me out a
lot.
I get paid for my college and I
get a pension.
And you see, I remember going through that
same subject with my daughter when she turned
about 18.
The purpose of the military is to kill
people.
Yeah, I told her that was the first
thing to watch people being shot.
And picture you doing it.
If you can most of them will be
right and most of them will be your
own done by your own, especially if you're
in the American arm.
40% of the Americans that are injured
or killed by them are done by their
own kind.
By the way, this is a majorly hidden
thing.
So that's not good.
Right.
So they you know, the member patriotism is
a disease regarding regarding any country during any
time.
Right.
There's so much psychological disease.
Yes.
And some spiritual.
So these entitled classes are just like that,
you know, and there's still people that aspire.
You know, I once I once said years
ago when I was younger and dumber, I
went around interviewed people in the entitled religious
classes.
And one of the priests was proud.
He was an orthodox priest.
He says, I used to be an attorney.
Now I'm a priest.
I was like, everyone's like, wow.
And I'm like, wow, that is really bad.
Shit, man.
That's like really bad combination.
I mean, but it's perfect.
It's perfect transition.
You know, you learn to live from one,
you know, then you learn to lie again,
you know, it's perfect, you know.
So that is the job part is is
anything I think I think the easiest way
to be lawful is it's not time for
humans to change.
So in the meantime, no matter what the
trends are, whether you're in the industrial age,
the space age, information age, you know, when
the pipe breaks, all that other shit goes
away and you need a plumber.
When the electricity doesn't, the electricity doesn't work,
all that other shit in your life goes
away and you need an electrician, right?
When the car breaks down, all that shit
in your life goes away.
You need a car mechanic, right?
Right.
So yeah, regardless of who you are, where
you are, how much money you have or
little money you have or what type of
house or where you live, whether you're renting
or, you know, your own house or whatever,
right?
Pipe breaks need a plumber.
Everything else stops.
Movie stops.
Stop contemplating everything.
Right.
So you see, your hair is always going
to grow.
Hair cutters.
Right.
So dry cleaning isn't a profession that used
to be as much because of the clothing
styles of changes like haberdashers.
Right.
So, you know, so and there is there
is.
Yeah.
So, you know, food, people got to eat.
Right.
But the thing is, the restaurant business is
a very piss poor business.
One thing in the restaurant business is if
you need 10 people to do the job
to run the restaurant and you hire 10
people, you're overhired.
You get it?
Everybody has to do like the work of
two people in order for a restaurant to
be the way the economic model is.
If you need 10 people to run the
restaurant, you hire five.
What does that mean for the five people?
A lot of work and not a lot
of pay.
And they're used to high rotation because they
usually specialize the job.
And when they need to replace you or
make a replacement, they have, you know, a
narrow field compartmentalized, you see.
Right.
And then, you know, they're constantly training.
And that's the brilliance of the fast food
that Ray Kroc did with McDonald's about how
to automate and all that.
It's totally for that.
But the food is, you know, very low
quality.
I remember eating, for example, McDonald's back in
the 60s and 70s was delicious because it
was mostly organic back then.
OK, so the lawful job or job either
way is, I guess, it's what sense of
morality you have.
Remember, the gods don't think much of people.
That's why I put that in the personal
sense.
If you think people are crap or whatever
and you don't mind putting them in jail
or injecting them with vaccines or poisons or
flying a plane that sprays them, that's fine.
That's up to you because the gods don't
care much about them.
I wouldn't do it, though.
You know, personally, I couldn't be an attorney
or a priest or a doctor.
If you're going anywhere in life, if you've
got better knowledge of what's going on, is
it going to matter at the job anyway?
You're there to work.
You're not there to make friends and convey.
Sure.
I find that once if your mindset is
advanced and you know what's going on on
this planet and you're acting like you've been
here for more than 15 minutes, because most
people on this planet are acting like they
haven't even been here for 15 minutes.
They're completely shut down.
Completely.
You know what I mean?
That's why I use the pun.
You know, now I shifted it to about
an hour to give a little more leeway.
Have you been on this planet for more
than an hour?
OK, that means you see how screwed up
it is, right?
Well, no, I don't see you.
Well, you're not looking hard enough.
Yeah.
If you've been here, all it takes is
an hour to figure that out.
Right.
On this planet.
I know I'm being a little harsh, but
this is the reality of it.
That's how screwed up it is.
Right.
But, you know, to the headhunter, he's not
going to realize the headhunters are bad, whether
he's there for 15 minutes, an hour, all
of his life.
You see what I mean?
The point there also.
Yeah.
So the thing with the job is very
simple.
When you you're advanced in your ability to
see what's really going on, the best job
or occupation is when you don't have to
deal with people like, you know, where you
work by yourself, you know, whether it's packing
envelopes in a room by yourself all day,
listening to Greek, speak 24 seven or whatever
or whatever.
I'm just joking.
Or, you know, a chef or a cook,
you don't have to deal with people like
the worst thing would be like a waitress
or a cop or an attorney, you know,
again, not in title class, but where you
have to deal with people.
If you know what's going on now, if
you know a little bit about what's going
on and you still want to work with
people, fine, work with them.
But there's no way you could know a
lot of what's going on on this planet
and work with people.
That I have never seen anyone be able
to do.
So that would be one way to alleviate
the occupations.
It does touch the spirit when you, well,
I think privately you and I, I mentioned
where I'm at and I see a lot,
but I tone that down with my own
spirit.
I mean, it's not my concern.
My concern is me, my knowledge, my way.
I'm going to run my life.
I'm not there to evaluate and that's somebody
else's.
Well, or the way I do if I
have to be around people, like sometimes I
have to be around them and not in
mass anymore if I can choose not to,
but you know, a three, four, five, I
know they're vulgar and offensive and what they
think and do is criminal, even the best
of them.
And it's temporal, meaning there's not a lot
of time left where in the future, the
society will be structured to what their, the
way they think, act and behave now will
be in the future considered outwardly vulgar, offensive
and criminal and be able to be enforced
as such.
Right now they're just, you know, like I
said, don't take offense, just get, understand the
cross between an insane asylum and a pig
farm.
If you know you're in an insane asylum
and a pig farm, you know, how can
you take, you know, you know, you're, you
know where you are, you know what's going
on, it stinks, it's crazy, get over it
until you're not there anymore.
Sure, sure.
So yeah, don't, you know, the thing is
that when you get to the point where
you start to see more and more, without
a doubt, the people around you are vile,
offensive and criminal from a, you know, a
lawful perspective, all of them, not some of
them, you know, majority.
So, but you, you, you negotiate with your
own self on that as it not being,
you know, terminal in, in the big picture.
Yeah, it's terminal for them and this, they're
not going to, you know, make that kind
of stuff isn't going to make it over
to the next society, but it's just right
now, you see, it's just small.
But the other, the main suggestion there would
be just avoid them, you know, stuffing all,
what are jobs you, you know, you can
do in, you know, solitude, you know, working
a machine, stuffing all envelopes, janitor late at
night, without a crew, let's say, I wouldn't
say menial.
For me, I work in receiving, so I'm
constantly drivers by myself.
Yeah.
And you interact with momentarily with people that
are exactly you're receiving from, right?
Yeah.
And the machines will probably be involved.
They'll look at you.
This is what you got.
Let me see the paper and then machines
or take effect.
You take effect.
Yep.
So very, very little interaction.
And when I do have to, you know,
of course, I'm a polite, courteous person, and
I'll share with it in that respect, it
doesn't mean I have to be harsh to
anybody.
As a matter of fact, I have a
compassion enough to say I truly do feel
sorry, in my heart.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's, that's fine.
It's adequate.
One, one way to to think about that
also, like what I do is I, I
provide really good water, really good food for
people, right?
You know, like, I think I've given my,
a lot of the food sonics was when
I was out at the mines, I was,
everyone's running down to the 24 hour store
to get microwave pizzas, and I'm cooking rice
and beans and things on the back of
the truck.
And they're like, you can make rice?
They were fascinated that I could even just
make rice, you know, it was like, you're
joking, you know, so.
How did your, your new test on rice
go?
Hmm, still haven't tried it.
I still haven't even purchased it.
Okay.
Where I, what was interesting, I was going
to purchase it yesterday.
And not only was the road tore up,
road closed, you know, with all the, the,
and there was actually a police action with
a bad car accident on the other side
of where I was trying to go on
a detour.
So I was like, Oh, it's not meant
for me to get any rice today.
But, but I've been trying to be a
local vor, you know, what's growing route, right?
And what's easily to reach, you know, in
the garden, flatbreads, just simple fast food, food
that I make at home, which rice is
actually, you know, I call it quick rice.
Instead of letting it sit for 10 minutes,
you just rinse it in hot water, and
then go ahead and cook it with a
lot of weights.
And it'll get, you'll have rice ready in
less than 15 minutes.
You know, real rice, you know, I mean,
white rice, not converted rice and stuff for
white people are told to get or whatever.
I don't think it's converted rice still on
the market.
I don't even know.
I've I remember that came out in the
70s.
I've had it once.
I'm not sure on that one.
I'll have to take a peek next time
and go to the shops.
Yeah.
I know they have I've seen pre cooked
rice and in vacuum sealed plastic bags, either
frozen or on the shelf, which is scary.
Yeah.
I think you'd have to put a gun
to my head to eat that.
So yeah.
And even then I would feign eating it.
But yeah, so these things are easy.
I mean, simple, but not easy.
The other thing is regarding children.
Well, children are a pain in the butt.
I mean, they're just it's very difficult.
It's a very difficult thing.
One of the most understated things either with
Greek speak or in the world, I haven't
spent a lot of time talking about it
is how difficult it is to raise children.
Forget about raising them properly, just raising them.
And if you're going to do anything, you
should do it properly.
So that word shouldn't be in there, you
know, raising children properly.
How about just consider raising them?
Forget about, you know, focusing on the properly
because you've got everything working against you and
that even if you were in a proper
society.
Well, I shouldn't say that because in a
proper society, you would have small things for
small people.
Right?
Small chairs for small tables, small bathrooms, small
sink, small clothes, small shoes.
And most of the things I just mouthed
off there listed off do exist.
You know, when I found out when I
was raising mine, time slows down.
And you got a lot more of it.
And you got a lot more of it
with a young child.
And that's a whole, whole different world.
Yes, yes, it is.
Yes, it's we've been also as humans in
culture, through conditioning have been trained that it
that it's pleasant to go through the maladies
that you go through right with raising children.
It's not pleasant in any way.
And but people in discussion with their lip
service say that it is.
But what I see going on, I don't
see it as being pleasant at all, either
objectively or subjectively.
What I mean, subjectively, especially when a parent
says, I want to throw that baby out
the window, I haven't slept in three months.
Right?
And not just one parent, but most parents,
I haven't slept in three months, you know,
we try to take turns, but we can't,
you know, we both get up, right?
Let's say mother and father, right?
So there are there are better ways that
will be in the future on how to
do that.
I think that the biggest detriment is the
subculture, I call it the kids subculture, the
goat, the baby goat subculture.
Right?
Well, they have, you know, stupid, like Jack
fresco says, you know, there's the cow and
the lamb, the cow went moo moo, the
lamb went baa baa.
Children don't want any of that Mickey Mouse,
Disney, Sesame Street, all that stuff is rubbish.
It's actually satanic if you really were to
use a lawful yardstick.
And one easy way to shed that, again,
with children is say that's for babies, you
know, once they start communicating, just tell them
that's for babies.
And they don't want to be a way
to shed them, but make them familiar with
it.
It's the same with the King James, you
know, people say, I don't want to read
the King James.
You know what, you have to, because you
have to know it, because that's what people
know.
So the child still should know all that
crap, but present it in a way that
it's crap, but not in a way that
the child feels bad if he likes it.
Well, inspire them with knowledge, you know, to
their own liking.
Yeah, the child is going to ask, why
does the airplane fly?
Why does the car go?
What's a horse?
You know, that stuff.
Yeah, how the TV got there, and believe
it or not, back with how the TV
got there, the parents didn't know.
Right, right.
Well, the parents didn't know.
Yeah.
You see, so many times I've said, well,
if daddy has a plane, I don't know,
like politicians.
I don't know.
That's why there is no future in this
society.
There can't be, you know, the way that
it is.
But so in that sense, again, just to
recap this person about discuss finance lawful jobs
in a modern world and raising modern just
means the end of the world, by the
way.
And raising children properly, and keeping a house
in order without sacrificing safety of the children,
that's an interesting thing.
Because you're basically going to you've heard of
the spies in the land, you're going to
have to be very much aware of the
offensive vulgarity and criminality of all the people
around you, to the point where you don't
want to be so right that you seem
offensive, criminal and vulgar to them.
You see what I mean?
Right?
Yes.
Yeah.
So that's the interesting part.
But the other interesting part of this is
I have yet to see a household survive,
you know, like a normal, you know, which
means fucked up household.
When one of the either the man or
the woman discover they want to be lawful
from Greek speak or anywhere else.
I mean, this is even before there was
Greek speak.
I've heard of this.
It always divides the family.
Yeah, very, very, very, very rarely harshly do
they stay together.
So if you want to be lawful, you're
going to have a divorce or worse or
whatever.
Okay, unless you're truly fortunate to have a
mate.
That's right, because we're going to be interested.
Yes, that is so rare that it's not
even worth mentioning that.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it does happen.
It does occur.
It does exist.
But it's so rare that to bring it
up is disservice.
Because 99 999% if you told 100
couples, a 99 and a half of them
are going to get a divorce.
Well, Greek had a half of them get
a divorce, you'll see about all of them
divorce.
Well, this goes back to the time when
you and Sam were talking about going out
and talking to different people.
You know, and it's the same thing with
couples, you have to talk to each other.
And it's how you bring the information about
how you can articulate it to each other.
And their perceptivity is receptive or not.
You're a lucky man if that happens.
Or woman, yeah, or woman.
Yeah, yeah, either because sometimes a woman can
bring it, which I would suggest is better
in some cases.
And you could use your imagination.
Why?
Because the power of a gentle, gentle touch
in their aspirations when when truly wanting to
bring another person in to the fold of
things.
And sure, well, the power of the woman
as the chief economist, economists mean echo, meaning
house and almost meaning law.
That's why if you want an educated society,
educate the women.
If you need to educate a society in
one generation very rapidly, focus on educating women.
That's your focus.
Yes, of course, you provide education easily accessible
to everyone, but you have to make a
focus on the women because that's where the
children are going to look forward.
You look at what society offers women just
for jobs.
They should have played dumb in the 60s.
Yeah, yeah.
Instead of instead of protesting, they should have
played dumb.
No, I don't know how to.
I don't know how to write.
I don't know how to go to the
bank.
I don't know how to use a phone.
They should just play dumb.
That would have been fine.
Everything would have been fine.
Yeah.
You still would have a sanitation worker or
a guy working at McDonald's support supporting the
whole family.
Mm hmm.
But but, you know, no, you know, so
anyway, go and burn my bra.
Yeah.
That was just a show.
Actually, there was more plans.
If you remember the new the New Order
of Barbarians, the day the Dr. Day speech
that was already set up.
I know once in a while I revisit
that just remind you.
Yeah, just to remind myself.
Yeah, it's true.
Yeah.
So that's the secular force.
So here's the thing.
You know how I say, never say make
the world a better place because you have
the malevolent against you because they never want
it.
But now you have the benevolent gods against
you also because it's time to knock it
knock it all out.
But on top of that, you even have
the entire the the ones that are ruling
the world behind the scenes also doing it,
you see.
Right.
So you have the the true, true power
on the earth, the true power in the
heavens on both sides.
You see, as above.
So that's right.
And it's all against anything getting better, it
will appear to get better, only to the
point and it will be manifest to a
degree.
So humans are without excuse later, you see.
So it's kind of like the last meal,
someone on death row.
So I think the children part on the
last part of this email is the most
difficult.
If you really want to be pragmatic about
it, what makes it more difficult, the more
you learn is, you know, I'm one of
the few people I know that could perhaps
do this when I see someone with a
newborn baby, I see that baby has no
future.
I said, What would you do if you
only live to 14?
Like, what do you mean?
Like, well, if you only live to 14?
What would you do?
You live your life differently?
Yeah, well, don't you don't have to make
the baby do that.
But make the baby aware of that.
I mean, would you go to school?
Hell no.
But you still want to know how to
read, don't you?
Right?
You want to know where televisions come from,
you want to know where babies come from.
So anyway, so that's, that's, that's one thing
when you see these young people, you just
add 14.
You know, that's their age, you know, and
of course, you know, it's going to be
nine out of 10 that won't be here.
But the chances, it's a lot, it's a
lot safer to say, well, they're not going
to make it, you know, if it's a
10% chance, they're going to make it,
I wouldn't, you know, I wouldn't focus on
the making it part, I would focus on
you're not going to make it to that
point.
So live your life better.
You see, right aspect, and if you do
make it, you'd wish you didn't, in a
sense, unless you're granted tremendous amount of protection,
which is something I don't discuss, I haven't
discussed much, but it is a spiritual thing.
There's nothing you can do, you can't dig
a hole in the ground, go join, you
know, the guys that have the underground cities,
that's not going to help storing foods, not
going to help.
Yes.
Do you consider all of that?
Of course, you know, it's just good common
sense, right?
It's to say it's the same common sense,
preparing for a future 14 years plus from
now is the same common sense that you
have when you have a spare tire in
a car.
You don't you know, the only difference is
you don't have a spare in a car
because you're planning on flatting.
It's just in case.
This is different.
This is going to happen.
You see, it's a little different.
So carrying a spare or backup, because of
the way things are going to change, and
when they're terminated is going to be so
dynamic, your backups don't mean shit.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So, but it doesn't mean don't have it
in the meantime, or whatever, and just see
what the gods do for you or with
you, you know.
This is an interesting thing, you know, and
very often, just to maybe finish this off
or wrap it up, the thought, you know,
even myself personally, a personal thought, I question
myself, so these are really 14 years, let's
go back and check this and all this,
and I, not self-doubt, but like just
check it again, you know, like when you
do a math test, for example, just check
it again, check your answers, check all the
answers again, and I'm sure.
And then on the other hand, I'm like,
well, how come no one else is giving
any specifics?
And I'm like, I got to, you know,
remember the old V8 commercial?
I got to slap myself on the head.
They don't even know what day it is.
They don't even know how the body works.
They don't even know what money is.
They don't even know this.
They don't even know that.
They don't know anything.
So relax about why no one else is
saying anything.
You know what I mean?
Relax.
It's fine.
It checks out.
So everything checks out really well.
And it can't go on for much more,
and you'll see later on, it'll be more
evident why.
You've heard of rapid changes, rapid progressions, but
this society is not going to end the
way that you've been shown.
It's going to end, like Seinfeld says, you
end on a high note, really good, like
good supper clubs.
I remember you set them up, you run
them for three years, they get really great,
and you shut them down right at their
peak.
So no one will ever say, I remember
when it used to be good, you know?
Because if it shuts down when it's at
its peak, there is no, I remember when
it used to be good.
Oh, it was great, and too bad they
closed, right?
But the thing with this society, it's not
going to be too bad it ended.
Well, it ended, now we better just shut
up and listen, because we had it all
and couldn't deal with it.
You see?
So from that point of view, another point
of view would be, if let's say there
was extraterrestrial intelligent life that came to Earth,
they would figure out everything you've heard in
Greek speak and more in less than an
hour.
And there are people that go from cradle
to grave on this planet, and even if
they do hear it, they still can't figure
it out.
You see?
So that's how off humanity is at this
point.
And it's not going to get any, in
other words, I was going to say not
going to get any better, but it is
going to get really good, because that's part
of the setup.
But in other words, you're not going to
get any of the things that you've ever
been made hopeful of in the past, which
you are not being made hopeful anymore.
An example of that would be, do you
remember Bruce growing up and hearing about World's
Fair, whether historically or presently, right?
They had the World's Fair, the world's of
tomorrow, and the world of tomorrow, you don't
get any of that now.
Anything you're shown of the future now might
be only in Hollywood, and it's despotic, it's
negative, it's violent, right?
And that's it.
I mean, isn't anyone paying attention?
What happened to the World's Fairs?
The Eiffel Tower was a function of the
World's Fair.
And it was temporary, by the way.
It was built for the World's Fair, and
it was supposed to be, they were saying,
well, the architects were like, this has really
disrupted the way the city looks, let's take
it down.
And obviously, they let it go, right?
It became an icon for using that word
loosely.
So you're not getting any more World's Fairs.
In any futuristic, there is no more discussion.
Yeah, well, for a reason.
Yeah.
But you will have...
Well, just like all the other fairs that
did, you know, the ones that came and
went.
That's why one of the things is the
setup.
That's why you're all going to fall for
the mid-2020s when you're told it's a
perfect world.
And they will start working on that.
You're going to fall for it because you
haven't had such endeavor or altruism or any
kind of hope like that in such a
long time.
And you're all going to fall for it.
Very simple.
There'll be world peace and you'll have, you
know, freedoms and liberties.
Liberties just means time off from what you
normally do or committed, pledged to do.
It makes you wonder what the technique would
be that they'd be using.
Spiritual.
Well, I realize that.
It's going to be mind.
Manifested on earth here.
How would that manifest?
Oh, yeah.
You know, it makes you just ponder on
that sometimes.
And I've meditated many times on what could
they have used that would be that profound?
Well, the hints that we get is it's
going to be of supernatural paranormal in nature
on a terror, atmospheric and terrorist terrorsphere, right?
Signs and wonders kind of thing.
But it's it's it's going to obviously it's
going to have to trump the effects you
get from the rectangles, you know, phones, iPads,
computers and movies.
It's going to be more than that.
But the but the technology that people focus
on are the screens.
You notice that if the resolution on the
screens went to pot, people would think the
technology is no good.
The only reason they think the technology is
good is because the resolution is getting up
high depth.
That's why, you know, not because the number
crunching.
Oh, it's faster to stupid to realize anything
that's past their sensory systems, you know, the
basic senses.
So they think the technology is so high
because of the resolution of the what they're
watching.
So this paranormal activity and supernatural stuff that's
going to take place is going to mesh
and dovetail very well with the media that
they're using.
You know, the media is not going to
go away.
You're still going to have the, you know,
it's going to get even more intrusive.
In other words, not intrusive, I should say,
because most people don't consider intrusive.
It's going to be more incorporated into your
daily lives and into what you consider to
be, you know, the go to thing.
Yeah, so it's whatever it is, like you
asked, I don't know specifically, but I know
it's going to have to integrate well with
the rectangle, right?
Yeah, clearly, clearly.
It doesn't integrate with, you know, like I
said, the this is just a beta test.
In the end, there are things that are
going to be happening parts of the world
that everyone will be able to see.
Even though they're anywhere else in the world
because of the the data transfer audio video.
I caught myself I was going to say
YouTube, but no, it doesn't have to be
YouTube.
It could be streaming from any platform that
allows it and will be advanced.
Well, something that would be uniquely available on
every device where a new function could be
displayed in real time.
The Jesus app.
Yeah, I don't even like this.
I don't even like to use that word.
The J-E-S-U-S app.
He's coming.
Yeah, you know.
For the, you know, just like I said,
if you if you lose some of the
morality, take advantage of these idiots, right?
You know, they're stupid, right?
They're really dumb.
You know, somebody wants to say, I don't
know what to do.
I could invest a little bit to start
a church, start a church, and I'll get
an earpiece and any question they answer you,
I'll just have it.
I'll just answer it.
Right.
You know, there's this I assure you, there's
no question these any of these Christians could
ask that could stump anyone that studied even
just a little bit.
And it's not like you're harming them because
they're suckers.
If you don't take their money, somebody else
will.
They're going to lose their money.
In other words, they're going to lose their
time, money and effort and where they're focusing
their energy anyway.
You see?
Right.
So might as well be you.
You're just saying, you know, you want to
you don't know what to do.
You want to invest in something that's lucrative.
Open a church.
You'll be the only one that could answer
all questions directly from any Christian, period, even
the pope, even if you had the pope
sitting there and all the cardinals and all
the more, you know, high clergy, you would
answer all their questions in a second.
Just give you an earpiece.
And as soon as the question is asked,
I'll give you the answer right away.
Not because I'm smart, because I'm just not
that stupid.
You see?
But you see, that's they're like the sucker.
You know, if you work, you know, been
around mob and they and they mug someone,
they're like, be glad as it was us.
You know, you were going to get mugged
anyway.
Right.
You know, you were going to get burglarized
anyway.
Right.
Look at you.
Pathetic.
So here I give you a story.
I know an old guy and he told
me that his mom did he didn't get
any inheritance whatsoever because she left it to
this little church in Texas.
And he felt bad about that.
Well, I was in his car one day.
He's like, I go to the mail and
guess what he was doing.
He was giving a donation to that same
church that got his whole inheritance.
Oh, my goodness.
This is how brainwashed.
This is how screwed up they are.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, you can't like at that point,
you're like, wow, there's no intelligent life and
there's no morality in these people at all
whatsoever, lawfulness or anything.
I mean, it's just too far gone.
And I had one more on one say,
well, we do charity.
I'm like, well, don't you think the Canaanites
who ate who ate their children, dogs and
pigs on a regular basis had charity?
Of course they did.
It's in their records.
You know what I mean?
You know, the Canaanites, you know, when in
the Levant, when they do archaeological digs, you
know how they say this was a Canaanite
or a Philistine city because they find dog
bones and pig bones and children's bones where,
you know, the food would be thrown away,
you know, the waste from the food.
Sure.
Yeah.
They said, well, this can't be an Israelite
one.
This was I mean, later on, Israel participated
in that kind of stuff.
Do you get my point?
Yeah, I do.
So so when you read of how ghastly
that is, I saw what this guy was
doing was just as ghastly to me from
a moral point of view, you know, and
it's not like he was giving to some
temple.
These guys in this little church in Texas
are all a bunch of liars.
I don't have to go.
I mean, I know they're because they're, you
know, lying.
So all of them are.
How do I know they're lying?
Because they're still in business.
If they stop lying, no one will go
there.
It's very simple.
Accommodations.
It's like saying when is two plus two,
not four.
You could say two plus two is one.
Like, you know, you take two pieces of
butter and two pieces of butter and mash
them together.
Now it's one big piece of butter.
Right.
But other than that.
Yeah, it's really, really I mean, the stuff
that I've seen, I mean, I don't even
very often I have thoughts like that pop
in the head when I'm doing a sonic.
I'm like, yeah, fuck it.
I'll just share it with everybody.
You know, so screwed up.
They're so screwed up anyway.
And from all sides, you know, it doesn't
matter.
Just throw it in the mix.
So soup salad, like they say in the
military, I'm a soup sandwich.
Yeah.
You know, you try to make right.
As I say, in the army years ago,
you just made a soup sandwich.
Right.
So that don't mean dunking your bread in
the soup either.
I'm pouring.
They'll give the illustration.
You're pouring a bowl of soup over two
slices of bread and expecting it to hold
together.
So, yeah.
Right.
OK, so.
So those were the emails.
Basically, the dreams be easy.
Just let them know that, you know, attorneys,
lawyers, why do you need them?
That's a that's like saying, why don't why
shouldn't I go to church?
They talk about God.
You know, I mean, there's so many levels
to all of that.
And then lawful finances just basically are you
unconditionally endorsing it?
You know, conditional endorsement always on everything.
And remember, whenever you sign anything electronic that's
being harvested and used, I'm not saying every
time, but you it's kind of like, you
know, going to a bike.
When you sign a electronic pad unconditionally, it's
like having a 18 year old blonde take
all her clothes off and walk into a
biker's bar and think she's going to be
OK.
I know it's kind of a stereotypical scene,
but I don't know what else.
I don't want to get into racist scenes
or too many of those.
Yeah, there is.
But you see, man, 18 year old blonde
girl voluptuous walking naked into a biker's bar
and she'll be fine.
That's what happens every time you sign the
name on either a government corporate hardware store
bank on a pad.
Right.
So this is planet Earth, you know, and
most people don't care.
I mean, there's only maybe a handful of
people on the planet that can even understand
what I'm saying here or comprehend or find
it, you know, cognitively acceptable.
Like I remember the last time I was
on with Ochoa, I was like, what is
he say?
Things I don't understand why it's the Greek.
He keeps saying things that I don't understand.
Right.
So, you know.
Mm hmm.
All right.
And again, with the job thing, it depends,
you know, how you view humanity.
Personally, I would say be compassionate, be helpful.
If you don't be an attorney, be a
doctor, be a priest.
Who cares?
But just, you know, you remember if you're
the worst one of those is a priest,
minister, pastor, you know, cardinal, imam, rabbi, any
religious guru, because now you're you're using the
gods, you're misrepresenting the gods.
And how do I know you're misrepresenting?
Yeah.
If you're misrepresenting the financial, that's the worst,
absolute worst.
And most people don't know that.
And they will later.
You know, someone said, well, you know, my
granddad passed away.
He was a pastor.
I'm like, oh, shit.
Oh, that's really bad.
That's really bad.
Yeah.
What was it?
Serial.
Serial killer is going to have it easier.
Mm hmm.
Charles Manson will have it better.
Anyway, because Charles Manson never, you know, unless
he did, knowing the way things are, Charles
Manson, I think, was part of the process
church anyway.
So process church of the final judgment, which
they run, they run a lot of stuff
with people in the Mormons, Coca-Cola, and
they used to, you know, all this stuff,
the Mormons, you know, all these Scientologists, you
know, subsects, these are all spiritual manipulations.
And here's the easiest part.
There's an old maxim that, you know, whose
law, whose will you do is your father
and you're their son or daughter spiritually.
The majority of humans, if you could say
safely, all humans are Satan's children because they're
doing the adversary's will.
Right.
So how do you reckon with that?
That's a very, if you had to say
a spiritually poignant thing about this planet, that
would be this is the planet where Satan's
children, you know, his daughters and his sons
live.
How do I know that?
It's very simple.
Just research it a little bit.
Yeah.
And they don't even know.
It doesn't matter if they know, don't know,
you run a red light, oh, you get
pulled over, let's say, well, officer, I don't
know, that wasn't red, it was amber, you
know, you gonna argue it?
You know, no, you did it.
So but the worst, absolute worst profession is
the is the is the working in the
religious fields, by far.
It's not because I say so, it's because
the gods say so.
And those are the ones you're gonna have
to contend with later, or the ones that
you see as being the most favored.
Now, on a descending order, you know, would
be the worst.
Yeah.
So again, very simple.
I think, like I say, if half the
people in the world, each helped one person
that would take care of everyone.
It's very simple.
You know, so I would be more into
helping out and leaving people better off than
you found them every time, whether it's a
short time, or a long time.
Yeah.
Even I remember traveling, doing things cross country,
when I have to stay someone's house that
a leaky faucet, I fixed it.
If the door wasn't closing, I rehung it,
you know, or if the car wasn't working,
I fixed it, you know, always didn't have
to, you know?
No.
So just the nature.
Yeah.
But either way, I would just the only
thing I would again advise against is, don't
call yourself a priest, a minister, pastor, imam,
guru, rabbi, any of those things.
I would avoid that, like the clap, if
you're old enough to remember what that is.
There are people that are proud of that,
and people feel that that's a good thing.
Yeah, that shows you how far gone they
are, how far removed they are from any
reality.
But they don't know anything, and generally, anything
about the money system, how the body works,
about history, time, any of the ancient writs,
any law, anything, nothing at all.
No one does.
And if you do meet someone who does,
it's very, it's so rare that it's like,
why don't you get a metal detector, go
out your front yard right now, you're gonna
find a big nugget of gold.
Nah, it's not gonna happen, unless you're living
near an alluvial flow, where there used to
be an ancient river somewhere near Georgia, or
Colorado, or Arizona.
Even then, you're not gonna, it's not gonna,
you know.
That's planet Earth, folks.
Sorry to break the news to you, if
you've never heard this kind of stuff before.
I'm sorry for myself more than for you
guys, really.
But yeah, there's nothing, and yeah, there's no
reason to be pitiful, and you know, whatever.
It's a battle, and I think how are
you going to have peace on Earth, when
there's no peace in Heaven?
They're telling you there's a war in Heaven,
so.
Yeah, yeah.
And we're caught in the middle of it.
There you go.
So, okay, those were just the emails.
If there's anything else, I mean, I think
we'll just wrap this one up.
It was just addressing certain things that have
come up, and keep coming up, and people
keep asking.
I think just focusing on one side of
each question, and addressing it, versus, you know,
including these answers over a vast plethora of
hundreds of hours.
Either way, they'll, you know, people will get
it.
Well, as always, thank you for sharing.
That was most insightful.
We had eight people listening out there, so
they got to participate, and listen to all
the thoughts.
Twice as many as normally get it.
Yeah, that's not bad, okay.
Usually three or four people get it.
And I'm not joking around, by the way,
with the three or four.
There's only three or four people that ever
heard Greek speak, that can do anything with
it, or comprehend it.
Maybe five.
I'd say maximum 10 for a few minutes,
probably, and then it kind of fades out.
You know, the amnesia and schizophrenia kicks in,
you know.
So, okay, it doesn't mean you shouldn't do
it, because years ago I said if it
helps one person, that's worth doing.
Exactly.
I think it has helped more than one,
like I said, two, three, or four.
Mm-hmm.
Great.
Thanks, Bruce, and we'll do it again soon.
Well, thank you, sir, and you have yourself
a great night now.
You too.
Take care.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye.