Good.
Got the rest in there.
Okay.
Yep.
Got the rest in there.
Let's see.
Okay.
So, anyway, anything that you've got brewing on your mind?
Interesting conversation on Tai Chi yesterday.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, that's an interesting thing.
I don't really get into a lot of public discussion on things that people can't access immediately.
Right.
That's why you notice most of the things I always come out ranting about is the calendar food.
Yeah.
No one's paying attention about things that they're already engaged in.
You see?
Yeah.
So, the other...
I'll give you a little background.
Years ago, people used to come to me about health issues, and I said, well, eventually I discovered through experimenting with them, believe it or not, you know, because no one really knows, most of the time the remedies did work, and I said, well, wait a second.
Wait a second.
The ultimate experiment is on their onus, meaning, hey, if your state of health depends on your behavior, right?
Right.
And your state of health goes down, that means that it's something in your behavior is doing it.
So...
Something's changed.
Right.
Or what you've been doing is catching up with you.
Finally.
Yeah.
So I just told people, make a list of your behavior, and then make a list of the things that you think you should be doing, or foods you don't like that you, you know, things that you should, you know, like that you prefer, don't prefer now, and take those two lists and switch them.
Do the ones that you, the things that you think you should be doing, which are better, and foods that you don't like, which are better, which you're not eating, and do those, and don't do the things you normally do.
Like change where you sleep in the house, you know, or wherever you sleep.
Change your bed position, in other words.
Change your...
The diet, yeah.
Seasonal.
Right?
Right.
Just start switching everything around, and you should get better.
And nine, nine out of ten times, they did.
And take note, each time you make those changes, give a little time in between to see that, you know, that you're manifesting the right things, or things are still kum-si, kum-sa.
Yeah.
There's a surgeon, to give you an example, there's a surgeon that was diagnosed with cancer up in the north, central north, midwest, like in the Chicago area, let's say.
I don't want to get too specific.
And because they're so brainwashed, they kind of, you know, freaked out about it.
And somehow they got, I got in touch with them, and I said, why don't you do that?
And about six months later, they were cancer free.
I'm not saying this is a cure for cancer.
I'm just saying I have that example, you know.
Yeah.
So, nonetheless, I wanted to maybe, because whenever I go out and interact with people, I was out at the shops a lot today, and I realized that people kind of freak out when you give them blanket statements.
And I think maybe more detail on that would be a good thing.
You know how I say there's no religion that does anything in their texts, and all that, right?
And you know, I make a lot of blanket statements.
Like attorneys don't know anything about law, doctors don't know anything about medicine.
So most people don't like to hear that kind of stuff, because they're so entrenched.
That's all they have.
And they're always told how insecure the world is, and all of a sudden you're showing them that the things that they have full faith and credit in, and full faith and confidence in is also no good.
Now what, you know, they have nothing to stand on.
So I wanted to give us a little bit more detail in that direction, what I mean by those blanket statements and clarify them.
Right.
Yeah.
So you think anyone's going to come in?
In the meantime...
I don't know.
It's early.
Or unless they're shy.
You know, I know there will be a couple of them for sure.
And like I say, I had that gentleman called just a little while before, and so I'm sure that he will find out.
And folks, you are welcome to call in, and we'll sit here and chew the fat, as they say.
Mm-hmm.
So, with the blanket statements, let's just, you could, I'll give a few examples.
We could either do, I'll let you pick, medicine, law, or religion, or money, or any one of those subjects.
Just pick one.
I'll go through how a blanket statement on that works.
I'll do money.
Okay.
Money.
Very simple.
There's hardly anyone, if not anyone really, anymore that works in the banking system that knows anything about money.
Now, the final, or how it works, how the credit system works, and the final thing is, that has any moral character.
Because I have met, by the way, certain people that work in retail banks, and they just downright don't care that it's, you know, a sham, right?
Amazing.
So, what I mean by that is very simple.
If you go to a bank teller with a check and say, I'd like Federal Reserve notes for this, they freak out, and they get up, and they walk away, and they get the manager.
They don't know what you're talking about, but they're counting them out all day, right?
The other thing is, they offer all these products.
You ever notice when banks offer mortgages and loans, they're called financial products in the fine print.
So, there is no money in that respect.
So the confusion on what they're doing is not even clear to them.
But essentially, a small percentage of the people that do work in that field, when they find out what's going on, quit.
So that one is an interesting one.
But there are, the thing about a blanket statement like that, there are all the people that remain in that for a long time.
It doesn't matter which one of these institutions that mankind deals with right now is, oh, ringers on high.
Well, I should have probably muted that Dona Smith.
I'll go ahead and take this call, and go ahead, Rick.
They're either, I've said before, they're evil or ignorant throughout their entire career in it.
And what I mean by evil, for example, I have run into bankers that know that there is no money, and they're actually using your credit line, and they know that the system will back them up.
And they do state that, say it doesn't matter.
You see, there is no, we don't need any just scales and measurements, and yeah, we'll just take all your stuff anyway.
Then you have the ones like the tellers that work at the banks that don't know what Federal Reserve notes are, and they're counting them out all day.
And then there's a third part where there's a group of people within that banking system that do find out what's going on, and then they want to leave, or they switch over and say, I'll just be evil.
I don't care about it.
Yeah, we know that we didn't lend you anything, but we're going to come take your stuff anyway and give it to someone else.
You see, now that small group of people are the ones that usually you find in certain fields or former professions.
Like someone says, oh, I used to be an attorney.
Well, what happened?
Well, I don't want to talk about it.
Or they'll say something.
They'll say something.
Usually, I've had several of them say, well, the Bar Association, that's a very evil group.
I've had a couple of attorneys that I've met say that, right?
One says, I don't want to talk.
Then I run into another one who retired, knew what it was about, and came out of retirement and started another practice because he just liked fleecing people.
Oh, God.
That's sad.
Oh, no, no, no.
This is the reality of it.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
And the same with the doctors.
When they work in medicine and they find out that what they're doing is not healthful, it's just emergency medicine gone wild.
It used to be in the Girls Gone Wild tapes.
OK, it doesn't matter if it's banking, religion, medicine, what they call law, the legal society, which includes police and all that also.
There's a small percentage of them that do find out what's going on, and then they're at a crossroads where it's, well, I either stay and go the evil route, throw everything out and just be predatory and manipulative and pranking because the system will back me up and the majority of people will never find out.
Or the other group says, well, I have to find an exit strategy.
I got all these years invested in this and I've got to get out.
What else am I going to do?
That's got to be a tough one.
That's very tough.
They usually stay in after they make that moral decision between six weeks and two years, typically six months to two years, and then they're out.
So when I make these blanket statements, there's always a small group of people consistently finding out what they're involved in is just downright evil, I should say, and misrepresented.
Evil meaning the opposite of good.
And they're looking for an exit strategy.
They're like, oh, man, I've got to go pay these student loans now even though I'm not going to be working anymore.
I've got children to feed.
I've got to have all this other stuff.
And I have met quite a few people in law enforcement, legal society, medicine, and religion that have left once they found out what was going on.
And I have met quite a few that are just – they know what they're doing is immoral and wrong, but they do it anyway because it's an easy way of life for them.
And I could say I've met many people that are ignorant about it, but I don't have to say that because just about everyone involved in those fields is ignorant, the great majority.
So we were basically – again, it goes back to the planet being inhabited by morons.
So these blanket statements are true, but I just wanted to give a little more detail, which I felt I have in the past as well.
I just wanted to give a little bit more depth.
And then, of course, you've got the adversary that's in control of the earth.
And then you've got the independent gods that are ruling over the countries.
Yes, that's pretty much the summation of it, yes.
Yeah.
You're just not going to win on that.
No, no, it's a matter of setting yourself apart.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's another subject unto itself.
Yeah, there's several ways.
There's a lot of people speaking in, especially in the Western – well, I should say Western even more than that – the American society about leaving the cities and living in the country or getting away from people's physics.
That'll set you apart, but you're still going to have some interaction.
Then you have the other way of setting yourself apart, being amongst them, but just not being like them, right?
Right.
And it's a mindset.
It's discipline, learning, and practice, lots of practice.
Well, ultimately, the spirit, meaning the mind, when your personality makes you – that's going to be reprocessed in a different body in the future, and you'll probably have most of the memory, and I hate to call them lessons.
I think it's more of a process than a lesson, because most people just go to the grave as dumb as shit, to use that medical term, right?
Yeah.
And most people – and then the other people are the evil and the set-apart ones.
That's basically a very simple way to break down the whole group of what's on humanity.
There's several ways with different clichés.
There's two types of people, those who want to be left alone and those who won't leave them alone.
Lots of different ways to look at it.
But essentially, for the ones that go to the grave that are just completely clueless, which is the great majority, what kind of lesson did they get?
None, really, because they didn't know anything that was going on.
The only lesson they got, really, is basically you get hungry, you eat.
You sleep.
You want a comfortable bed.
When it's cold, you want to get warm.
When it's hot, you want to cool down.
I like the color blue, right?
I mean, that's pretty much it.
That's the depth and breadth of the character.
So the reason I'm saying it in this context is not to be condescending, but to say, let's subjectify the great majority of people that have been born, lived, and died here as being utterly clueless about anything that's going on, or what things are supposed to be based on, or anything lawful.
That'd be a good way of looking at it, yeah.
Right.
People say, well, once your lessons are done here, then you can do...
What lessons did they get?
Right.
Nothing.
What lesson other than...
The only thing there would be the implementation of the Spirit in this incarnation.
And it wouldn't even be for their purpose.
Right.
Well, of course, they were serving...
It would have been for a higher purpose that we don't understand yet.
Right, right.
So here's an interesting thing to sum up.
I'm just kind of...
Dumb people are there for a higher purpose.
So anyway...
Yeah, yeah.
And I don't mean dumb, because a lot of these dumb people actually score very well on IQ tests, and are professors.
Well, ill-informed, still closed in the system.
And we had a question in chat about, could you speak more about the bar, which is always a fascinating subject.
Oh, boy, that's a mess.
Well, you want to look at it several ways.
First of all, it's a monopoly.
Second of all, it's a religious institution.
Third of all, it's an occult institution.
It's a schizophrenic institution.
It's an institution that misrepresents what they do in the field.
The bar members, and also those that support them, are boots on the ground representatives of the adversary.
It's even in the language.
So that's the easiest way.
There's someone that describes them as a closed union shop.
What they're doing, believe it or not, in the Bar Association, is completely illegal and unlawful.
But it's kind of like the organic food when you go to the market.
It's like, why do you have organic food in the market?
Well, so people can eat better.
But what kind of a society would allow a great portion of the food or a great amount of the food to be toxified and not fit to eat, or who knows if it's fit to eat or good for them?
And then because of that situation, we're going to bring one that is organic.
That's a pretty – organic food does not sit – I mean, I prefer it, but it doesn't speak well for society at large.
How can you allow that?
Right.
You see?
So people talk about all of these political issues and all that and whatever.
And when it comes to the Bar Association, the way you deal with them is you can't deal with them from the top down because if you interact with their members and you go to the Bar Association, it's like, well, we have nothing to do with that.
You have to get an attorney.
Ha, ha, ha.
Right?
Right.
Or we'll consider it.
So then you have to go from the bottom up, you see?
Yeah.
Like if you can't kick out the general, you take out the foot soldiers one at a time.
Right, right.
And the way you take them out is with you, you don't take them out physically.
You take them out spiritually with the mind and not by bringing them down, but by bringing yourself up, by finding out what the laws are.
And here's another blanket statement.
There are not any attorneys that know anything about law.
When I say anything, meaning when you just pick one law, it doesn't stand on its own because it's attached to definitions and it's part of another series of codes and things.
So when these attorneys understand the definitions and the series of codes that a law forms with, now they know the law, they will get disbarred because you can pick up, let's say very simply, someone crosses – I'll sort of change this a little bit.
Let's just say it's based on a true story.
Someone crosses the border from Canada into the U.S. with a duffel bag full of that green stuff that everyone smokes, right?
Or they're saying that they want it legalized, right?
So he gets busted by the Canadian side, but they decide to let him go to the American side anyways, and the Americans bust him, right?
I mean the Canadian side knew he had it, but they let the Americans deal with it.
So they run him through an arraignment, all this stuff.
They're going to get him 10 years in jail and all this stuff because it's like 35, 40 pounds, right?
And he gets an attorney who says basically according to public law 9-whatever-whatever, Title 21, which is possession, has been repealed.
And he goes in front of the judge with the attorney that says that, and the judge says, I never heard of that, and if you say that again, I'm going to put you up for review.
That's what the judge tells the attorney, right?
So what kind of a defense does he have then?
Yeah, he's guilty or not guilty for drug possession.
The whole thing has been repealed.
So now that attorney gets disbarred, he loses his ability to operate.
He's not a license, you see?
There's no attorney on the planet that's going to go in front of a judge and tell the judge to represent you according to the law.
What they all say is just do what the judge says.
And they always put in a non-guilty plea.
You know why?
Because in the justice courts, any plea entered is admitting that the charges are true.
Right.
Immediately.
Yeah, so I've heard also there was an attorney that brought up the U.S. bankruptcy, a place in Ohio, an attorney in Ohio, two of them, brought up the U.S. bankruptcy and its inability to pay on a foreclosure case, and they got disbarred for doing that.
Now a bar is not a license to practice law.
It's that you're a member.
But what happens is the state supreme court is not really a state supreme court.
It is a state supreme bar court.
They gave themselves permission or a license.
Yeah, and there's no record of that whatsoever.
No, there isn't.
So this is not on them.
Who cares what they do?
Essentially, it's like saying we have a locust swarm coming through here and it's going to just decimate everything, which would take one-tenth of everything, right?
Let's talk about locusts.
What are they?
At this point, you'd better focus on protecting yourself and your property from these things.
It's a little late.
Yeah.
Do you see what I mean?
It's like you fall overboard and there are sharks in the water.
Well, let's talk about what sharks are.
Well, I think get yourself out of the water first, and then we'll talk about sharks because you don't want to find out firsthand.
No, no.
Same thing with the medical society.
The same thing with the religious society.
I mean it just goes – accountants are also like that, really talk about.
So you find yourself on this planet, right?
And then you find yourself wanting to gather information.
And when you prioritize the level of importance or the priority of the quality of that information, you'll find that no one knows what's there.
Most people are on the secondary or tertiary, third step away from it.
See, most people would say you need law.
That's an attorney.
Oh, no, sorry.
That doesn't work.
Well, unless he's going to get disbarred tomorrow after he talks if you get him to.
So the same with a doctor.
Ask a doctor, any doctor, when you put your feet and your toes or your hands in water, why does the skin shrivel up?
Oh, boy.
You want to see like the rabbit in the hat look?
And you know if any of them speak out in the trade that they're in and admit in any way, shape, or form that goes contrary to what has normally been established, you're done.
You guys will find a different job.
They are, yeah.
Right, right.
Most likely they will meet a brutal either – yeah, they'll either be excommunicated because it's a religious thing, and then it will go downhill from there.
If they persist, they could get physical harm done to them as well.
That's basically any field.
The automotive industry is the same, by the way.
Amazing how that kind of turned around, huh?
I discussed an aircraft propulsion system that worked really well, and the faster you went, the less fuel you used, and it was totally silent.
And I had a retired aircraft structures engineer tell me, we'll never do that because it doesn't make any noise.
Right.
Yeah.
Oh, my.
Yeah, yeah.
And I've had a retired spark plug person tell me, we'll never use those spark plugs because you have to have some pollution.
In other words, when you improve the spark plug design, the emissions go down almost to nothing.
Right.
You can't have that.
So after a while, you have to relax about it and don't take it personally.
You have to say to yourself, okay, these people on this planet, it doesn't matter what country you're in or when you lived, right, this is really not a good place.
And you know what?
If you read the ancient holy writs, they tell you it's not a good place.
Yes.
That's why people don't understand it because they don't understand everything else around them.
And Vandy just pointed out construction is the same way.
Most of your fields, your biggies out there are getting that way.
Oh, yeah.
And that just also tells you that the gods are doing a really good job.
Yeah.
The ones that are not doing a good job are doing a good job.
In other words, they're doing what they're not supposed to be doing.
Right.
And the interesting thing is don't take it personally because it's not personal.
In other words, this was set this way, including you being here, before you even thought of it or thought of or heard anything like this.
Just to go back to the way people listen and to information, like when I go on The Rectangle, sometimes I have someone here and listen to it all, so we just crack up, and it's a serious subject matter.
They'll be like, quote-unquote, whistleblowers talking about something or a doctor.
Mainstream is even – I mean I'll just laugh and turn it off with the mainstream stuff, but the alternative stuff I'll just keep laughing and leave it on a little bit longer because you've got to give them a little bit of – a little more leeway.
And the reason why you give the alternative stuff, the YouTube videos and all the websites and all that stuff out there a little more time is because you know they're not bestowed or beholden to an institution.
Usually you don't have someone do a website regarding, let's say, GMO food in the mainstream.
They'll be positive for it, and then you've got to just laugh and turn it off.
The alternative, they'll be against it, but you still laugh because they don't know what the hell they're talking about.
But you've got to give them a little more time because you know they're not going to get fired for talking about it.
So in other words, here's a human or a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant who's unabated, free to speak, and this is all he's got.
And he hasn't even – doesn't even – yeah, you see?
And it's just stupid.
So – and also half the references the alternative guys make are the bullshit that the mainstream came up from, the bullshit science and the bullshit medicine, right?
Talking about viruses and this and that and DNA and all this other stuff, right?
Right.
I'm not going to get into this much because after a while you realize, ah, just harp on the important stuff, but all of it is really junk.
They say, oh, the DNA is so important.
RNA is so important.
There's a double helix, all this.
They try to make it sound so important.
So the efficacy of it and its importance in the organism, right?
Well, and if it wasn't them, if it wasn't them, then you'd have these other – the spiritualists out there who are, you know, it's the golden mean ratio and all this other good stuff.
Sure.
Yeah, it just goes.
But just back to the DNA, if anyone wants to look into it, you know, there's a little motor in the mitochondria that produces it, right, very rapidly.
And if you study that motor, it moves at, you know, the equivalent of 200 miles per hour if it was in our scale, right?
Yeah.
And everyone is talking about it.
You know, no one is talking about triple helix stuff that's in there also.
Isn't that funny?
You could probably research it.
I don't know how much is online.
What is the triple helix other than the – there's the double helix.
But no one is talking about the triple helix proteins.
What about those?
They get ignored.
Okay, so my point here is when you start bringing up a subject, you know, what is going to happen is, you know, you can't bring it up if you know it's not correct.
Speaking about it, if someone just listens to you for a moment, they think you're just another schmuck talking about, you know, whatever they're used to hearing, right?
So in some cases, some of the scientific stuff, what they call science, what is best left alone because ultimately that's not what allows you to stand up and walk across the room.
Again, ask any scientist or medic.
Like, for example, I was conveying in the engine-driven wagon today and NPR or something had science Friday, they call it.
Oh, I just had to roll down the windows because my own laughing was making my own ears ring, right?
Complete morons.
But, you know, obviously they're speaking to an audience that's even more moronic.
So obviously it's going to sound smart.
But the thing is you ask any of those idiots, well, what does it take for you to get up and walk across the room?
They don't know.
Or ultimately, you know, what keeps you alive?
You put 10 of them in the room, you'll get 10 different answers, you know, or some might be similar.
So they all can't be correct.
Either they're all wrong or only one is right.
In this case, they're all wrong.
You see?
It's like putting 10 attorneys in a room and ask them how should I handle this case.
I'll tell you right now, they're all wrong.
I don't have to know who they are.
That's obvious.
Put 10 priests, 10 pastors or whatever in a room or even the Pope himself and ask him a biblical question.
I don't need to know what the question is or what they say to tell you they're wrong.
Why?
Because this is how far gone down the line it is, you see?
It's too far down the line.
See, if, let's say, put the Pope and all these other pastors and ministers in a room and the priests, if you did that 500 years ago, they wouldn't even consider answering.
They would just threaten your life, you see, because it was critical for the political system back then.
Right.
Let's see.
We might have someone wanting to join.
I'll drag them in.
I think it's, let's see, it's Vandy, I think.
I'll drag them in and I'll just say he just messaged.
Might be having Eddie call in pretty soon, too.
Okay.
All right.
So, so these things are important.
And the thing is, you must maintain a light heart about it.
Some kind of perspective that doesn't allow you to allow it to get under your skin and make you feel angry or rough about the situation.
Because if there's anyone to be upset about, it's your parents.
And that's a common thing, too.
Yeah.
And there's the other higher level is, you know, the God that brought you here.
But just don't do it publicly.
You know, if you've got a beef with him, he's willing to hear it.
And later on we're going to find out why we didn't speak to the gods more.
They were always hanging around waiting and listening to us, right?
Yeah, and we don't talk.
Yeah, and they can listen to more than one conversation at the same time.
So get a frequent dialogue.
At least it's going to be a monologue.
You know, I like, for example, there was a Transformers movie a few years ago.
Not that I like the movie.
Everything that comes out of Hollywood is garbage right now.
Because why?
Not because they don't know how to make good movies.
Because where's the audience, right?
One of the Transformers, he spoke by what was on the radio.
If you ask him a question, he just tuned to the radio station that gave the answer, right, in little bits and pieces.
I don't know if you remember that.
I think it was the yellow one, the front one.
So you will get some kind of a response.
So we're joined also by, I think, Vandy in Demonsland, and he's muted, I think.
So that's fine.
So that's pretty much the hash on the broad brush strokes right now.
There's always an exception, but it doesn't take away from the statement not being true, in essence, because essentially when the people that find out what's going on in any of these institutions leave, you're left with the ignorant and the evil, right?
When I say evil, it's not the imitation Hollywood evil thing, you know, whatever.
Evil just means the opposite than good.
Oh, somebody's puppy.
Yeah.
An interesting example would be what they call the food markets.
You have a choice between good and evil, right?
Let's say organic versus non-organic, right?
It's interesting and ironic almost how this choice is being put in front of us.
Where years ago it wasn't.
It was all good.
All the apples were good.
Yeah.
There weren't as good this year.
There was no choice of evil and good, meaning evil potentially spread and GMO'd versus good, which is not.
Doesn't that bring back the story of good versus evil or the knowledge of good back into this society?
I think it never has been.
This might be the first time that what I know it is through recorded history that you have a choice between good apples and bad apples at the market.
You know, organic versus non-organic.
It's a precedent.
So society has allowed that to happen or the gods behind it, I should say.
Yeah.
Yeah, because it had to start somewhere and then trickle down.
And I think the human population in some ways is really just the effects of what the gods have given them.
Sure.
And within that, what they do is they give you a ship, what you do on the ship.
And then they have to, like if someone's doing something they shouldn't be doing on a ship or too much of something that spreads, then the gods step in backwards.
In other words, we do things here, then the gods have to come and change it a little bit.
Little tweak.
If necessary.
Or they'll either tweak it or boost it.
Yeah.
A lot of times it's boost.
And you get your butt handed to you sometimes.
Builds character, though.
Yeah, they have diminished much of the ability of humans to see.
Again, the cosmic censorship is still pretty thick.
And that's going to be a curious anomaly to watch that open up on certain subjects to allow for a more lawful perception of the gods.
Because right now, you know, most people's perception of the gods and even themselves is completely unlawful.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Completely unlawful.
Yeah.
So no one else yet.
We lost Vandy.
And let's see here how long we've been going.
Yeah, we're about half over.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I thought I was thinking of springing up a stream or a round, like what you call a round table.
Yeah.
To see if I'll come around.
Well, it's still early, yeah.
And we have a few people that are sitting on, definitely listening.
Let's just see.
Take a quick here.
We've got about seven or eight.
Okay.
Which is a good start.
And I'm popping in messages once in a while.
Let them know that we're.
Good.
So the pervasiveness of how the same, let's say the undercurrent of this evilness and just blocked censorship and pervade, you know, this is the falseness of any field, whether it's money, religion, science, medicine, law, anything, you know, food.
You find it in just about everything that's institutionalized.
And even that word institutional doesn't sound good because of that.
It's not by chance.
It's a setup, you know, and you're not going to change it.
It will change.
Actually, it will change.
They want it to change.
Sure.
And the people also.
See, when some of the censorship is lifted, certain things will change.
Great.
Trickle down.
A few other things, perhaps, to bring up with, you know, things that are coming, because this is, I keep saying this was a springtime.
Yes.
But also to consider, just to go back with the, when I bring up all these various institutions and the censorship, when the censorship is lifted, you're going to see more people, you know, their perception of these institutions changing and either going away from them or changing those institutions.
So, so it's not, you know, these things are not in stone.
I mean, it's still unbe able to table.
In other words, it's still not going to be fixed to the point where it'll be around and, you know, and then in the world to come at all.
But it'll be able to allow, you know, more of a lawful perception of of the gods.
And that's, that's one other thing that when you, when you discuss the coming Middle East Union, when you discuss, you know, the 15 years or 14 years we have left, you know, as a society as it is.
That has to do with the gods at this point.
You know, I heard someone recently said, oh, yeah, the, the, the people that, you know, made us love us enough.
They're not going to let asteroids hit.
They're not going to destroy everyone.
I said, no, they're not going to destroy everyone.
But they're sure going to open a big can of whoop ass.
And they're, they have very low regard for physical things, by the way, the gods.
They do know that's how.
And they're rather targeted about it too.
Yeah.
I mean, when you read about some of the things.
Well, you know, different people.
If I remember correctly, if I'm wrong, but you're the wrath will be something on the order of what you've what what you've put in what you reap what you sow.
I guess was what it really boiled down to.
Sure.
But the interesting thing about this is that it's going to be brought upon the entire environment.
So those that were selling well and reaping well are still going to get a whoop ass.
Yeah.
That's why I keep saying don't take it personally.
And I think it's going to affect, you know, how much of lawful timekeeping affects knowledge of the gods.
You know, that's something because there's a mention of the times changing, which means different things are actually.
I want to bring up another point since I just brought up the timekeeping thing.
I noticed there was always comments about timekeeping, and I realized someone is actually counting the days, and that's a good one.
I think 301 days for this year so far.
Yeah.
What's interesting is what you will hear with the pagan, the non-lawful timekeeping.
You hear this everywhere on the street, on the rectangle, people you know.
Usually when it approaches the end of the year, especially they'll say, oh, it's December and the year is over already.
Where did the year go?
You ever hear that?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Now that sounds like because everyone is saying it or it's a cliche and you're used to it.
It's been said for a long time, and you've always heard it.
It should be just discounted as just one of those fluffy sayings, but it's not.
Let's analyze that for a minute.
What's going on there is the psyche is trying to reach out in a pleasant way towards the subject, not in a negative way because they don't know any other way.
It's like when you think of law, you think of an attorney.
You have to think of them pleasantly because you know nothing about any other way.
Right.
If they don't know the law and they've got you believing that they're the ones you go to for the law, how the hell are you ever going to learn the law?
That's their profession.
Yeah.
Right?
You see?
That's very simple.
You just have to read.
So what happens when people are saying towards the end of the year, oh, look, the whole year is gone.
2017 is gone already.
It's already December.
They're trying to keep that pleasant because they don't know what's going on at all.
They're completely removed because, you know, you could say, hey, OK, idiot.
Decem means 10.
How many?
How many months are in a year?
You see?
That should raise a question.
Hey, moron.
Novum means nine.
Octo means eight.
Like Octopussy.
You've seen the movie, right?
Yeah.
OK, so what are you talking about?
Oh, well, I don't get it.
Yeah, that's right.
You don't get it.
And you never, ever will.
So what's happening is they know something is wrong.
How many times you hear this?
I know there's something really wrong.
I just don't know what it is or what's coming next.
Right?
You hear that all the time.
Yes.
That's not a that is.
And why does no one address?
They'll just.
Oh, yeah.
We'll just hold hands and agree.
I just when I do interviews and people say, I agree with you on that.
Oh, I'm like, wait a second.
Does that mean that if you disagreed, it was wrong?
Who cares if you agree with or don't agree with?
Most people are not used to hearing anything objective.
At all.
Yeah.
Ever.
They're going to go to their grave and back to the worms, and they will have never heard anything objective in their entire lives.
And not heard it, but processed or being able to work something through objectivity.
Felt it.
Yes.
And no.
It's pretty scary.
It is.
So I wanted the reason I brought I see this with every subject all the time.
I brought up the timekeeping thing because this it's within the the recent history here.
Oh, it's December 2017.
Look how fast the year went by.
You know, they're crying out.
Like help us, but we can't be helped at the same time.
Right.
Because because, you know, there are a lot that will just turn you off right away or change the subject.
Yeah.
And so the spirit is trying.
But the mind is just pooched.
Yeah.
And the only reason the spirit is trying is because it comes from the same source.
And that source is a true source.
Yes.
It's just like you can take, you know, a wheel off of any Chrysler vehicle pretty much of the same body chassis, even though, you know, or a Dodge and a Chrysler, they're interchangeable because they come from the same thing.
Same with Toyota parts.
You know, you can take from the same class, you know, or size.
Yeah.
Most of them are interchangeable because you see, because so it just shows that they have a common source, but it also shows the effect on them.
Right.
So I just want to bring that up because it's with everything.
Today I spoke to a woman.
She goes, I have Crohn's disease in my doctors.
I said, Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
Let's start all over.
Is that okay?
She goes.
She goes, Yeah, it's okay.
I said, Okay, you were diagnosed with Crohn's disease by a doctor.
Are you sure he's your doctor?
Like, where can I get one on my own?
Or does he see you the only one that he sees?
She goes, Yeah, that's right.
You see, that's just the start of it.
Yeah.
I have diabetes.
They say.
Right.
And I said, No, no.
Hold on.
Can we start all over?
Yeah.
You were diagnosed with diabetes.
You get it?
Big difference.
I have high blood pressure.
Now, hold on.
I won't even say you were diagnosed with high blood pressure on that one.
Yeah.
That's the magic cuff syndrome right there.
You got had big time.
The sticky on her.
Yeah.
You got 10% of the people in this country just, you know, ready.
You know, they're goners.
How do I know?
High blood pressure.
And I think one time you and I touched on the fact of how lonely people are that they'll just accept this stuff.
Yep.
You know, just because they're in contact with something.
Well, they're lonely also on many levels.
They think that human contact is the only thing there is.
They're not aware of lawfulness of the gods.
They're not aware of.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
So, in essence, it's a crazy game, but there's no prize.
You know, as the old saying, when you play stupid games, win stupid prizes.
Yeah.
That's exactly what's going on.
Very simple.
Now, there was something else we were going to bring up, I guess, so no one else has come on.
But you mentioned about the Tai Chi and all that.
And I diverted in saying that I always like to discuss things that are.
Yes.
Regarding what people can contact.
When you start discussing an element of, let's say, movement or, you know, like Tai Chi, people, you know, are always looking to find, well, I have to learn it.
Well, yeah, you do, again, like the diagnosis, yes, Tai Chi.
But you're doing – everyone is doing it anyway because how do I know you're alive, right?
Right.
You're alive and you're moving.
It's that same energy that is moving you around.
It's the same energy if you understand how to put it in a can.
You could use it to change weather or shake the ground or move meteorites in space and all that stuff, right?
So, it's that same force.
It's just that your body picks it up differently.
And if you understand how your body is picking it up and manipulating it or using it or it's going through you, now you're conscious of it, now what are you going to do?
You know, it's the difference between being asleep behind the wheel or being conscious when you're going down the road.
Big difference.
What I mean by – you could still go down the road if you fall asleep.
I've actually done it.
I've actually fallen asleep on the highway and woke up and I was fine.
I wouldn't recommend doing that.
I would say anywhere from one second to 15, 20 seconds, let's say, right?
Who knows?
You'll be cleaning the wrong 25 out of your shorts on that one.
Yeah, right.
So, but spending your whole life asleep, I don't know about that.
And the old masters, especially the ones that we were tossing about in chat, those masters took the time, the discipline, the practice.
They started understanding what was out there.
But the time is a matter of who you are and it's up to you.
Some people could learn it in six weeks.
Some people could learn it in six years.
Now, what it is, that's also – the Tai Chi Chuang, that's as that school is, let's say, identified, was around 1000 A.D. from a master in that part of the world.
What I like to discuss is the manipulation of this energy was around before, all the way since the beginning of mankind.
And I would even say that pre-flood people and not even pre-flood people but just people in the past walked differently, stood differently, spoke differently, meaning the way regardless of language.
Their posture was different.
The way they handled things in the physical realm with their bodies was different.
One simple way to look at that is look at how the geometry of the tools were made.
Very different, right?
Have you ever noticed that in the past, even if you couldn't afford exquisite or fine things, there was some embellishment always done on stuff.
It always had a little bit of a curve.
It always had some kind of a marking.
It had some kind of an artistic visual, something to smooth it out into the environment, right, if you look at how things were made in the past.
And that had to do with they understood this energy flow, right?
So, I would suggest that there is, if you want to call it movement of the body for just getting out of bed, working in the field, or even self-defense or fighting, it was always done slightly, well, let's say different than it is today.
Right.
So how were they doing it back then?
I also put in a video with Lars Anderson, the archer, who redefined archery by looking at ancient artwork and what's been memorialized about the posture and how the arrows were held of archers, right?
Yeah.
And also, of course, what does the establishment do?
That's trick archery, like trick shooting.
Well, I definitely want a trick shooter to be a bodyguard.
Yeah, oh yeah.
Or whatever.
Or like Bruce Lee was a trick martial artist or something.
Right.
So these people, I mean, the comments, I think the merit should be obvious when you see it.
Yes, yes.
In terms of the body movements and all of that, if you look at ancient statuary, even how vases were painted, how people were depicted in artwork, how, and again, statuary would be probably the easiest, you know, ancient statuary.
One thing that stands out is they were very proud of who and what.
They were always upright, very structurally sound, I should say.
Yes, sort of.
But I would say if you look at, if you understand how energy flows, it has to do with how the joints are managed.
Yes.
You always see the joints were always bent.
And they were centered and they were not, the only time you see the very vertical postures is against the Egyptian temples.
Yeah.
Or the Oracle temple, where they had the back against the stone.
But the actual, I would suggest, what's been memorialized about the movements of people, again, on certain statuary vases and drawings next to inscriptions, you will see there was a fluid movement unlike what you see or consider to be a posture today.
Yes.
For everyday movements.
Remember when you brought that up about the Master who was borrowing the Chi from another person in order to manipulate?
Yes, that's how it's done.
Yeah.
And there are no videos on YouTube that discuss that.
No, no.
And there's a reason for that.
I'm not going to be, put it this way, I'm not going to be the first one in public to do it either.
Gotcha.
Well, I've done that in private.
Let's just say that.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, think of it this way.
I also put the question in chat.
From whatever partly, see, you know, partly some, meaning a little bit of what you can glean off of the rectangle or even reading books about this, what they do is they tell you, give you technique in what's going on, but they don't give the specifics on how you actually do it.
Right.
Like give you, for example, Trevor James Constable, Will M.
Wright would talk about whether work, but they don't tell you exactly how to do it.
And so there's a bunch of stuff on the internet, but that's not, you try that.
It might maybe work a little bit, but you'll, it'll just be a passing hobby or whatever.
Or you'll turn on the TV and it's like, why did I just drown 100,000 people?
You know, or something like that.
Yeah.
It's not, it's not something that the fine points on why these things work, and how they work are happening discussed on the rectangle, period.
But it's one of the comments I put on there is that when you do listen to all of these guys anyway they tell you it's all external isn't it.
No, every one of them.
Right.
Well, yeah.
So, because it's all external, what are you doing thinking about what you're going to do?
Why don't you start thinking about what you're going to do with these external forces.
But, it's hard not to take it personally in this case because that's what's keeping you alive when you get down to the chi, right?
Right, right.
So, and also the other thing you have to remember is if anyone listening has ever done anything that they were considering themselves good at, you know, like a discipline, let's say playing an instrument, a sport, what have you.
If you don't do it for a few days, what happens?
You regress slightly, don't you?
Right?
Bodybuilding or sports are excellent example.
Sometimes it's good to take a few days off or a week off, but if you don't do it every day as a discipline, you'll notice that it regresses.
But what happens though, I'll give you an example with professional cycling.
It takes years to get there unless you're a natural.
I've met some people that are complete naturals.
They never really trained, but they did get into a training regimen because once they were recruited, of course, they're going to train.
But what I'm saying is they achieved that high level without a lot of grooming and a lot of investment.
And the same with music like Yo-Yo Ma, right?
Played the cello at Fork or played concerts at 10 and all that sort of stuff.
Maybe I got the same guy right.
But anyway, what will happen is once you learn a discipline and you get at the top of the field, you have what's called a memory.
So even though you haven't done it in weeks, months or years, even many years, if you decide to get back into it, it will take you much less time to get up to that level.
You may never attain that peak because let's say you're much older now.
You don't recover as fast as when you were younger, but you will have imprinted in you the techniques, things that you almost can't explain, but you know how to do.
And you will achieve a very high level again in a short period of time.
Let's say I've noticed this with cyclists and bodybuilders and people in the sports, usually 30 to 60 days.
They can get the best they could ever be at that point where a novice getting into that field would take a year or two.
Oh, easily.
Easily.
So another example would be you can take a professional musician who hasn't played the instrument in a few years.
In 30 days of practice, he will be where a novice wouldn't be in 2 or 3 or 4 years because you have an imprint in you already.
Yes.
So when we go back to the Tai Chi and all that, and Tai Chi just means the energy around you.
I mean I don't like using the Star Wars reference, but if there's anything in Hollywood that ever exhibited that more than any other, let's say, thing that people – you can mention and people understand what you're referring to, it would be Star Wars, the Force, right?
Yeah.
Good visual.
That's exactly what the Chi is.
But they don't see – because they didn't know what it was also to the extent – or they're holding back how anyone and everyone can access it.
And also you see the Jedi were trained to be such unless you had a natural inkling, which they're using occulted demonic terms from Hindu references, by the way.
Jedi is a demon, right?
Right.
If you study the Hindi culture.
And within the Hindu culture, they have hundreds of religions and millions of gods through the ages.
But the essence here is that these are core understandings that anyone can grasp, but very few can use, right, because of the discipline aspect.
Because there is a technical, mechanical aspect to it.
And then there's getting to know the why, why you're doing it.
Well, simply because it's there.
Well, I think the spirit and the energy have a lot – Well, the spirit is your personality, what makes you you, like a fingerprint, but better.
I mean fingerprints, they're good for, what, 140,000 or 200,000 and then they fall apart, right?
Mm-hmm.
Your spirit is unique to you and no other.
Right.
And I guess what I was alluding to was the, I mean, if you're, let's just be frank here, if you're a jerk, your chances of really learning the discipline well is not going to be so easy or good a path for you.
No, it might be a good path for you, but really bad for others, like Darth Vader.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Let's say, or the Emperor, in Star Wars again, but they had pretty good access to the, and they weren't reserved about using it when they felt they had to either.
Exactly, yes, yes.
It could be used either way.
Mm-hmm.
It's the, I call it the Ether.
Right.
The ancient Greeks called it Zoe, that's where you get the Z-O prefix for zoology or zoo or, you know.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Right.
Prana in India.
Right, right.
Let's see, it would be nefesh in Hebrew, really, the breath, or nef, Arabic.
Okay.
Right?
The breath is really the aspect, because though, see, you have to understand, see, one of the videos they stated that's what makes the blood flow.
Well, yes, but it really, the blood flow is part of your metabolism, because if you stop breathing, okay, let's say you stop breathing, and let's say indefinitely, you just stop someone from ever breathing again, their blood flow will stop also within what?
Right.
Three minutes, five, 10 minutes, 15, 20.
I'd say three is a good number, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd say really 15.
Oh, okay.
The heart beat will get down to two beats per minute.
It could be resuscitated.
The breath is very important in all of that.
Yes.
Now, if you stop the blood flow, you're going to lose the limb, right?
But it's very difficult to stop the blood, so it's really the breath is the trigger.
Right.
So when you're inhaling, I think I've discussed how you get nutrition from the air.
Yeah.
You know, yeah, so your body is not porous.
There's no pores in your lungs at all.
They're completely sealed like a rubber raft or an air mattress, or even tighter than that.
It's biological.
It's always adjusting, right, where you know how tires are porous, you know.
So, yeah, how you access it is just that, right?
I could give an example with weather work.
If you want to put a rain over a city, you have to understand that whether you're on the northern hemisphere or the southern hemisphere, the flow is from west to east, right?
So you look at where the city is relative to where you're set up, and you look at it and you say, well, if I speed up the flow, what will happen?
Or if I slow down the flow, what will happen?
Or if the flow is blocked, what will happen?
Right.
You see, so the only three things you can do, and the combinations of those three things give you nine possibilities, I think, right?
Yeah.
It's the same thing for breathing in a human.
So the same thing happens when you direct energy.
You have nine possibilities, let's say.
Yeah.
You can slow it down.
You can block it or you could speed it up.
And now here's the other interesting thing.
What are the chances of you getting an active chi or ether from something like a chair or a door or a computer versus getting it from a cat or a plant or a human?
The cat, the plant, the human offer a lot more than a chair.
Mm-hmm.
Get it?
Yeah.
So now, the cat out of the human out of the plant, which one has more flowing through it?
Simply by size alone, the human.
Because even a small human is bigger than a cat, let's say, right?
Mm-hmm.
Or a plant.
So when you understand how the energy flows through people, what am I doing?
I'm explaining what I said I wasn't, right?
When you understand how the energy is flowing around people, let me just say it this way.
You ever notice when you're in a crowd and there's a speaker, let's say a political thing, and the people get all roused up?
And what happens to the speaker?
Well, let's say someone's making a political speech and the crowd is agreeing and they all thrust their hands up to clap and shout in agreement.
What happens to the guy at the podium?
Doesn't he feel a rush?
Oh, yeah.
Big time.
You could see it, even if you've never experienced anything like someone.
How about even let's get back on a personal level.
Have you ever been complimented?
Someone patted you on the back and just with a real smile looked at you and said, you did great.
And they meant it all earnest, not just one of these casual things you say that's polite, right?
You can feel it.
You feel that rush.
Why?
Okay, yes.
Now, we've been taught that it feels good, yes, and all that.
But right there, when you're being complimented, that person is sharing through words and through their spirit.
Because if they complimented you and meant it, you only feel that rush.
If they complimented you and didn't mean it, which means they didn't focus that energy on it, you don't feel it either.
You notice?
You're like, well, that guy complimented me, but it was hollow.
He didn't mean it, right?
And you know it.
Okay.
All right.
So when you understand what people mean, they have different flavors of emanating this energy.
And you can direct it and capture it and put it in a bag, right?
And it doesn't – you can't hold it.
You can slow it down or speed it up past you, right?
And that's what you redirect.
And that's why when you were watching these videos – I'm not going to say right now more on that.
But when you're watching the videos, especially the masters, they were able to throw people without touching them.
Yep.
Right?
Every one of them.
So – and they had learned through their own experience, and they knew what they were looking for.
And not only did they know what they were looking for, they knew when they had it.
Yes.
So there's a lot of people that know what they're looking for, but they don't know when they have it.
You see?
Because they don't know that much about it in the first place.
That's what you saw, the various macinations and movements that certain people will do different than others.
Right.
Right?
Because that's them – that's how they interact with it.
The best thing is to not have to externally exhibit all of that and then refocus it.
And you notice I haven't brought up fighting.
I haven't brought up conflict or anything because this is how you – this is what people do all the time.
Also, you can charge – there are things that are done – like let's say when you're excited to do something.
All right?
Whatever it might be.
It could be cooking or whatever, even anything menial.
When you're not – you don't feel like doing something and you try to do it anyway.
You feel like this dullness, like you're moving through peanut butter, or you're not really there.
You don't perceive what's going on around you.
But when you want to do something, you start perceiving more of what's going on.
What you're actually perceiving is this life force.
So this is just a little primer to get people.
I have never really brought this up in presentations because, number one, it goes a little – well, the thing is it's not an immediate thing.
It can be with more discussion.
But it's better to discuss things that people can see immediately, right, that they're always engaging in anyway through interest.
Like how can you not be interested that you're being pranked over the calendar?
How can you not be interested that you're being pranked by the medical system telling you that in the winter when it's cold outside you're going to catch a bacteria that's going to make you sick?
Well, then why don't we just throw out all the refrigerators then because I thought the cold renders bacteria inert.
You see?
So anyway, this is just ridiculous.
So these things, like just right away, the magic cuff, all these things, the blood pressure and the magic cuff, the prank.
All of these things can be addressed immediately.
When you start getting into discussions about something that is a core reality really and how to really function without even having a handle on any of these other things, I think just sonically in a general Western audience is not that important, even though it is one of the most important things.
I'll give you an example.
One of my former mentors, Trevor James Constable, he had gone to India and he spoke to a group of weather people and scientists and university types.
And he lifted up a tube and he says, this is a device that channels prana.
And none of them batted an eye.
They were like, they all nodded.
Yes, we understand what you're talking about.
Where if you held up with something that looked like a hollow tube slightly modified to a Western audience, professors, when I say this channels energy or ether, they'd be like, oh, yeah, sure.
I'm listening.
I don't know.
He'd be laughed off the stage.
Or he might just say, I don't know.
He's going to have to prove it.
Or whatever, you know.
But in that culture, they're like, yes, we understand exactly what you're saying.
Do you see the cultural difference?
I am presuming that the majority of the audience that listened to these sonic events are of that Western mindset.
But I think it's a fairly reasonable assumption to presume that.
So I don't get into a lot of these other things.
In other words, I am, I wouldn't say custom tailoring, but I am, you know how I said you accommodate the audience, right?
Most of the things I discuss are to accommodate a Western mindset.
And it's a shame.
That's why when I get into, let's say, discussions of food, it's like how to make the most basic flatbread, how to make basic rice, how to make basic.
If I did that in another culture, I'd be laughed at.
They're like, what's wrong with you, Greek?
We know that.
Right.
You get it?
Commonplace.
Right.
I went to a Middle Eastern audience and said, this is how you make rice.
This is how you make flatbread.
This is how you cook meat.
They'd laugh at me.
Yeah, we know.
That's how you do it.
But if I have a Western audience of Americans or, you know, white European or whatever, they're going to be like, wow.
Yeah, it works.
I make perfect.
Right.
Because I know they don't know how to cook.
So, you know, you have to, again, speak.
You have to know to who you're speaking with.
Right.
And I don't know everyone that listens, but I'm, again, saying this because I'm presuming it's predominantly Western.
And I think I'm correct in that.
Yeah, I would say so.
Okay.
No one's calling in.
Anything in chat?
No.
No call-ins and no Skypes.
And let's see.
Let me just check chat real quick here.
And pretty quiet.
Yeah.
Okay, that's fine.
The Japanese adapted it from the Greek.
Say again?
There was one comment in there.
Heard a jujitsu master say the Japanese adapted it from the Greek M.A. It's possible.
This is one thing.
Okay, this condition, what we call international condition that we're all aware of, is not the first time.
This has happened prior in history.
It's just not discussed.
You know, like I was having a discussion recently with someone regarding the Renaissance.
I'm like, what Renaissance?
That is a complete propaganda thing.
What Renaissance?
If you look at how they define it, that's just like saying, you know, some street in Iowa got some street lamps.
Right.
So what?
That doesn't mean.
You know what?
It's getting everyone to focus on, you know, the Roman, you know, the Pope really.
Right.
Telling everyone what to do.
But it was really, there was an emperor also that doesn't get a lot of play because Europe had an emperor and the Pope.
It was the emperor and the Pope that ran, you know, the world at the time.
Right.
And then the subsequent, I wouldn't say they were in suzerain to the, but you could almost say they were suzerain to the Pope.
All the kings and monarchs were, you know, subject.
In other words, they ruled their own area, but ultimately, you know, they were subjects of the Pope and the emperor.
So regarding that, but this sense of internationalism that is sensed today about, you know, easy communication and all this and knowing of other cultures has happened before several times.
And when the further back you go and the more evidence of this is found, the faster it's sequestered or censored because, you know, it's not popular.
It doesn't agree with the history that has been told.
That's why very often when people tell lies, they spend so much energy covering up, you know, what they've said.
Right.
And we also got to bring in that the fact that the gods in the censorship also had their hand in that, too.
They just wanted us to not know.
Well, because it's very here's the other interesting thing with so many people on the planet today and there's a level of stupidity with almost everyone is that it's so easy to create a panic event where most people just kill each other off for no reason.
You see, so they have to stage the numbers up for them to do it, for the gods to do it.
But even though men will have a pretty good chance at it.
It is all about them.
Yes, well, it is.
And like, for example, if you're building a small theater of 10 people, the chances of an injury happening, or even if 100 people, if someone cried fire is not that great.
If you built a theater with 50,000 people and someone cried fire, the chances of injury is much higher.
You know, you could easily say, you know, 100 people were trampled to death.
Right.
So, as the numbers get bigger, and more of these morons communicate, you want to obviously censor them.
That's an obvious statistical fact.
It's too bad to say it that way.
It's just, I'm not, don't take it personally.
They have to be censored.
That's why you'll never hear me say, well, there has to be less censorship so people can learn.
I would never say something as stupid as that.
What I'm coming out and telling you is, there's another society called the gods, and you guys are being set up.
And you don't know it.
And it's not just that one thing.
You'd better find out about how the body works, how to keep time, what all these institutions are really doing, subtly.
And check the anomalies.
Yep, and all these other things.
And there were a few of them, as you pointed out.
And I think we noticed one just a little while back on the third Sabbath, which was way out of alignment with the...
By a day.
Yeah, yeah.
And it was weird when it caught up.
Oh yeah, it'll do that.
It's been doing it since 2005.
There was like a big shift of time there.
I'm still trying to wrap my head around that one.
Around 2000, what they call 2005, it's hard when you use the number because they end it in December.
You miss out on the progression of that when you use the Pope's work schedule, but that's when it stops.
And this year was rather well-behaved.
A few years ago it was really, really off.
And yeah, we'll see if it behaves this year after the first month.
And that's just a sign that in the latter days it will start to err in its ways.
It doesn't mean you can't tell the month, it just means that you can't tell the Sabbaths with the moon strictly on point.
And that, by the way, is in the Book of Lamentations also.
It's in Isaiah.
But most people read that and don't know what that means, how critical that is.
What do you mean, I'm going to break your Sabbaths and all this other stuff?
I do a Sabbath every Saturday, what do you mean?
They don't understand.
You know what I'm talking about?
Of course you do.
Let's see, we had one from Vandyman.
Can you ask a question about Zechariah?
And then he also has, trying to find the meaning of the word hekel and having difficulty getting anything.
Interesting picture search.
The word hekel in reference to the Scripture Institute translation.
There's a translation that's put out by some scripture people out of South Africa, those guys, right?
Yeah, they're just making stuff up.
They're applying a different word that's, I think, not there.
But, hekel, that's the word that they're using for temple or house.
Okay.
Yeah, there's some strange things going on in that one too.
Which, by the way, it's hard to recommend any biblical...
People ask me, like, what's a good translation to read or what version, what do you...
So you've got to read all of them?
Mm-hmm.
None of them are any good, but you've got to know them all.
Why?
Because you're on this planet.
If you try to bring up a conversation regarding biblical stuff, you better know what they've read.
You see?
And knowing the law.
And you'll get to see the anomalies.
Well, yeah, what I mean, the point that he's bringing up, I'm assuming, is from the translation.
You have to know the King James and all that, because that's what's being used for common parlance.
If you go to a party and people are discussing the Bible, well, guess where they got their information from?
Most 99% of the time, King James, or NIV or one of these others, which are King James also, you know what I mean?
So you have to know it.
You can't say, well, I don't know the King James, I know the real scripture.
What happens to the conversation?
Well, there is none.
Yeah.
Well, should we take a little pause here, if you want?
And we can come back to this in a little bit and give us a chance to maybe stretch legs and grab a coffee and all that kind of good stuff.
And we can return to this in, say, maybe five, ten minutes or so.
Sure, let's do that.
And just real quick, I want to say, when you're reading a biblical version, you can read many of them at the same time.
You can literally, if you have them in paperback, just turn to the first page of Genesis, all three or four, how many you're reading, and just read them all at the same time.
Right?
Right.
So you get familiar with all of them or whatever.
But that's what crazy people do, though, right?
Anyway.
Okay, so we'll see you back here in a few minutes, okay?
Okay, we'll see you in about five or ten then.
Okay, see you.
Okay.