Good evening folks, we got here the Greek
and hope everybody out there is fine.
Greek, how are you doing tonight?
Greetings, doing okay.
Yeah, I guess they could call this the
the most rational misanthropic talk on the internet.
If anyone wants to look up what the
word misanthropy means, anthropo meaning man and misos
meaning hatred.
That's why I would consider, it's funny like
soul and spirit, how they run around definitions.
It's forbidden, like the Germans say forbidden to
define certain things, you know what I mean?
Yeah, it's funny when you when you speak
with either academics or, heaven forbid you make
a comment on the internet defining anything.
It's like, you know, then you see where
the moron magnets are, which is everywhere.
But, you know, the word mis, M-I
-S, I'm pronouncing it in a Greek, misos
means hatred.
So, when you hear misspelled, it's hatred for
spelling.
Misunderstanding is hatred for understanding, right?
You've heard of the word mis as a
prefix.
Now, they try to excuse it away saying
that, well actually it's not the Greek prefix
meaning misos, it's the Latin mis means mistake.
So, there's a there's a little bit more
of an underlying feeling to looking at etymology
than meets the eye initially.
But, I can tell people objectively, this is,
you're not going to get this kind of
speak anywhere, and neither has there been this
kind of speak anywhere from several kinds of
perspectives, by the way.
Whether temporal meaning, well of course I wasn't
around before, but this kind of talk has
never happened in this capacity, publicly at least,
ever.
So, if you've, yeah, and if people found
us on the internet, they've probably found a
lot of other stuff, and I'll tell you
right now, it's all crap.
It's all dummy load, and if you feel
like there's anything edible or good, you're actually
eating corn, edible corn out of someone else's
poop.
Now, if you guys want to guess, you
get three guesses on what we're going to
speak on tonight, and the first two guesses
don't count, right?
We're talking about food, and it's going to
be rather short, because I have done on
that, was it AFR, I think you have
some, where there are archives about speaking on
food, I think I did it with Seth
Michael.
As a matter of fact, that one was
just explained tonight on a re-broadcast, and
brilliantly done.
Well, that was a time like, I've been
chided a lot by Sam behind the scenes,
like, you're always talking about how people are
so bad, they're all morons.
I'm like, yeah, you want me to lie
to people?
And, you know, he says, well, I had
a different demeanor back then.
Well, yeah, because you want to be neutral,
and you want to see if you're going
to become a moron magnet, and if you
become a moron magnet, you want to start
repelling, you know what I mean?
So you want people coming, not for the
character or the personality of what they're used
to hearing, but the content and quality of
the content, right?
I mean, I speak to people and captains
of industry, even in the past political figures,
or I can, I can rub, I mean,
in other words, I can go to the
best restaurants in the world, and it would
look like I fit in, right?
Well, most of you wouldn't, you'd be kicked
out.
So anyway, I wouldn't, I wouldn't say that
if it wasn't true.
Right?
But anyway, I know how to speak on
various levels.
But essentially, if you study the term misanthropy,
you know, there, which it's a trait, it's
not discussed that it's been adopted as a
trait, which is basically the definition is kind
of skewed, but it says the hatred of
people or humans and their society and human
nature.
Not really, that's, you know, it has to
be packaged in a sense, where, okay, is
there a virile hatred for just people because
they're people, you know, like, if, you ever
see these squeamish women that are afraid of
snakes and spiders, and you ask them why
they can't respond, they just been taught that
way.
Yeah.
It's funny, like I bring up, you know,
there's a miso technic, which is the hatred
for technical things.
There's a someone that I got in touch
with recently, and she has a secretary actually,
about six months ago, and I started bringing
up some points.
And she says, Well, I'm not technical.
And she works in a medical, you know,
industry.
She's a secretary, I said, Well, can I
give you a little personal, a commentary?
Because, you know, when people say they're not
technical, and I don't know if it helped
or screwed her up, psychotic, did irreparable damage
to her mind.
But either way, when someone says they're not
technical, if you translate that into proper rational
speaking, what they're actually saying is, at a
young age, I there was someone in the
family or friend that was respected and either
accomplished or accepted by others.
And they would always say, or had heard
I had heard them say that they are
not technically inclined, and everyone still found that
trait or that characteristic to be agreeable.
So that person at a young age, decided,
Well, if this older person is still respected
and liked, and they say they're not technical,
often enough, well, I can get away in
life saying that, too.
So I'm just going to shut myself down
and just use that excuse, you see, just
the same, the same goes, we're going to
be speaking about cooking tonight.
Well, I don't cook, I don't like to
cook.
That's because they were around somebody in their,
in their formative years that not necessarily in
their family, it could have been a favorite
aunt that was having an affair with their
dad.
Oops, sorry, did I just say that?
No.
Because you know how pagans are.
But anyway, yeah, so and she says, Well,
I don't cook.
And she was still liked.
So the child grows up saying, you know,
I'm going to try that.
I don't cook bullshit, right?
You know, so this is it's, in other
words, when I speak of misanthropy, and the
dislike of people and their condition, it's a
rational one, right?
In other words, if you give someone 100
choices, and two of them are really bad,
and you keep repeating this experiment, and they
always go for the two really bad choices,
and they negate the others, consistently, that being
is to be avoided, right?
This is the nature and of humanity.
So again, I brought that up, tying it
back in with cooking, there's a lot of
people that still have not done any self
examination.
Right.
And by the way, what's called the theoretical,
it's alternative media and informational in the internet,
it's theoretical, right?
In other words, in theory, if they ever
put it alternative media, or the information on
the internet in practice, maybe you'll get some
improvements, but it's not being practiced.
So.
So the reason I bring that up is
because you can go on what's called the
stupid rectangle.
And it's a device of your choice.
That tends to be a rectangle, and it
is quite stupid, even though they're called smart
devices.
But in reality, if they're stupid, and the
devices are called smart, but you're never called
smart, could you imagine how stupid people are
considered to be?
Right?
So anyway, in other words, if stupid things
are considered to be smart, and people are
never even told to be that they're smart,
could you imagine how stupid people really are?
But anyway, it's really off the chart.
I mean, there's, so if you go on
the stupid rectangle and look for foodstuffs and
recipes, human sharpening knives, it's just a wasteland.
No wonder nothing gets improved or done with
information alone.
You know, there's, you're not going to learn
it by osmosis.
And if you don't know something, and you're
average human, which lacks discernment and objectivity, you're
probably going to run into some poorly done
presentations or instruction, you're not going to get
it anyway.
And if you did, you're still going to
be doing it poorly.
So and this is this is the rule
that I'm giving, I'm not giving the exceptions,
there's always an exception, right?
What I mean by that is, there's a
lady that I know, she was actually a
client, and then she wrote a book on
ghost towns in America, she'd go around and
take photographs.
And it's quite interesting.
And the first thing this is quite commonly
known, maybe listeners don't know, when you find
a ghost town, not only do you want
to look for, you know, where the treasure
is buried, or, you know, whatever might help
you sell your book, but you want to
find out where the outhouses were.
Why?
Because that's where people sat down and all
kinds of interesting stuff fell out of their
pockets, like even a revolver would fall out.
And if it falls into the outhouse into
the pit, you're not going to necessarily go
down there diving for it if it's you
know, the outhouse or basically the public toilet
for you know, a place, right?
Right.
So after about 100 years or so, all
that stuff is kind of decomposed and mineralized.
And it's kind of safe to dig down
and find all kinds of gold coins and
silver coins and gold guns and anyway.
So the exceptions are quite interesting, but the
rule is that it's all crap.
So speaking of crap, you don't want to
eat crap, which is coprophagia, right?
I think that's C-O-P-R-O,
phagia, P-H-A-G-I-A.
But unfortunately, if you are living in a
quote unquote, white people society, which would include
Northern Europe and the United States of America,
Canada, let's see where else we go, should
you find a prolific white people be like
Northern Germany, Scandinavia, Netherlands, England.
I think if you go south from there,
their Mediterranean rim, you go further south, it's
Africa.
And if you go east, it's Asia.
So basically Northern Europe and if you come
over to America would be Canada.
If you live in those societies, you're kind
of like at a disadvantage because you're not
going to get good food on the go.
In other words, the type of foods that
these cultures and food methodologies that they've have
allowed to become culture and tradition is crap.
And that's just a quick little encompassing word.
And that is the rule, not the exception.
There might be an exception, they don't last
very long.
But let me give an example.
If you go anywhere in the world, you
know how you have various style restaurants, right?
Well, go show me any city that has
an English restaurant, you'll see Chinese, Indian, Greek,
Italian, you'll never see English or Irish restaurant
food chain, will you?
Right?
Because the food is crap.
And they don't know how to cook.
American is the same thing.
The only reason American food, you'll see like
KFC and McDonald's all over the world is
because guess what, not because it's good, it's
because it's what?
Mostly what?
Deep fried.
If you deep fry a shoe, it tastes
good.
Anything fried tastes good.
Why?
Because it's fat.
Umami.
Umami is a term, Japanese term, which is
one of the fifth or sixth flavors, which
is just deliciousness, like a real delicious cold
beer, you know, something that's really delicious, like
MSG tries to create that umami, right?
It's a fake umami.
And don't believe these clinical scientists, by the
way, that tell you MSG is in cheese,
it's in tomatoes.
No, no, no, it's not.
There is no MSG in tomato.
There is no MSG in cheese or mother's
milk.
It does not naturally occur the way that
they add it as an ingredient.
You cannot show me the MSG in any
natural food.
The only way you could show MSG in
any natural food is if you crush it,
blend it, dehydrate it, and burn it in
a gas spectrometer, right?
And now you changed it.
Right.
So back again.
So most people I believe that I'm addressing
here because we're speaking English are eating or
have eaten or in what's called a white
people food.
This is not racist, by the way.
Because the whole world, by people that are
into food culture, and even a few people
know the food culture, the chef culture, meatloaf,
mashed potatoes, right?
Macaroni, cheese, tuna, casserole.
That stuff's called white people food by white
people also.
It's not good for you.
It doesn't taste good.
It's a part of the culture and tradition.
I believe you called it the SAD diet,
Standard American Diet.
Right.
That also envelops, it's Canada.
Canadians also don't know and neither do the
Northern Europeans.
Okay.
So how do we move forward from that?
We move forward from that by several, several
directions that could be taken.
And the first direction, by the way, if
you have interest in this conversation, that's fine.
Because I've noticed in life through many years,
not, not constantly uniform, but people are not
interested in food or upping the food quality,
usually a poor character anyway.
That doesn't mean that if you're listening or
you know someone that is not a poor,
not interested in food talk is a poor
character.
Definitely.
I said mostly they are.
And I've been noticing this in my life
where people say, well, I don't really care
about food.
I wish I didn't have to eat.
I just take a tablet, a pill, which
scientists come up with a pill.
And if you look at what else this
person is doing in their lives and how
they focus, you're like, Oh yeah, this is
not someone I, you know, that I see
any quality in any way.
And you'll notice that.
And it's actually for me to say that
is not an opinion.
Think about it.
No food, no air, no water, no shelter.
You're done.
So one of, you know, it's one of
the most important things, actually, you know, food,
clothing, shelter.
You could live the longest without shelter and
then clothing and then food.
You know, depending on temperature and things like
that, you might want to reorganize the priorities.
But essentially that's it.
So most people, again, I'll say it again,
are probably used to being surrounded or exposed
to white people food.
Another example of that, you'll see, why is
he harping on white people food?
I'm not harping on white people, just their
food.
Because if all the white people started eating
healthy, creative, delicious foods, then I wouldn't say
white people food is a pejorative, right?
Well, there's a history behind that too, and
how much it's degraded over many, many generations.
And it's getting worse.
We're probably at our worst.
And it's going to, well, it'll be a
little worse tomorrow.
You'll see.
And the next day, it'll be a little
worse.
So essentially, one thing you'll see is if
you go to a European market, Asian market,
it kind of smells foodie.
Even if the fermented stuff, you know, the
dried fish, cheese, or whatever, veg, you know,
you go to a white people market, it
smells like powder detergent.
Right?
You ever notice that?
Even when you walk into the kitchen area,
it's clean, and it has no, it doesn't
have an appetizing feel to it.
Yeah, no, no.
Even when you go to the section where
they're cooking food, it doesn't smell good.
You see?
Yeah, that's the other thing.
If you live in a white neighborhood, and
in the spring, fall, and summer, when people
are cooking, shut your windows and your doors.
It stinks.
It's interesting, when I do cooking, I had
a neighbor once, he came and knocked on
the window, and I said, what's up, man?
He says, I gotta come around and talk
to you, you're killing me.
He had a real serious, I said, why?
He says, that food that you're cooking, it's
killing me and my wife.
I said, what do you mean it's killing
you?
It smells so good.
What is it?
And he's, you know, we're talking about 100
feet away, right?
Right.
And what's interesting, there's a family, an Afghani
family that moved in the middle of the
block, and the wife and I will joke
around, we'll say, if it stinks, oh, that's
the white people cooking.
Or if you smell something delicious, oh, it's
probably the Afghanis cooking.
And someone said to me once, how do
you know?
I said, come on, let's walk over and
I'll show you.
You see.
So this is like one of those real
obvious things, you know.
And the reason I spent the first 15
minutes or 10 minutes discussing it is because
be aware of what I'm speaking on, in
other words.
Immediately, you know, if you see something that
ain't good, it's white people food mostly.
I'm not talking about 100-year-old egg
and some real nasty stuff that certain cultures
do.
I'm talking about the general thing.
Okay, so, have you gotten the hint that
maybe you should explore and expand your horizons?
Maybe some Latin cooking, some Asian cooking, Mediterranean
cooking, you ever get that concept, hint, hint?
Right?
So, right there, there's nothing wrong with saying
that's white people food, because I've been around
chefs, and when they have their big pagan
holidays, they even, you know, even white chefs
will say, oh, we got to go cook
white people food, you know, Thanksgiving, Turkey or
Christmas, whatever, right?
That's the white people food thing.
So they're like, shit, you know, at least
we don't have to do it once or
twice a year, you know, because it's very,
you know, unappealing.
To make a long story short regarding the
white people food thing, that is a big
disadvantage if you are in Northern Europe, England,
Ireland, Scotland, America, what they call the United
States and Canada.
Big, big disadvantage.
Not because, well, because, you know, you still
have the freedom to cook what you want,
but because the markets are piss poor.
So you're going to have to run and
find yourself a European market or an Asian
market or something that doesn't have, you know,
really old stuff vacuum sealed in plastic.
You know what I mean?
So that is the predominant rise to any
occasion for better food.
Before we get into the food discussion, let's
say you live in the middle of Kansas
or Wisconsin or Tennessee.
You want to eat better?
Move.
Sorry.
Move to the East Coast or the West
Coast.
That's where you're going to have more international.
The same with England.
You know, move.
But in England they do have a lot
of formula.
Like in England they'd say, oh, I think
I'm going to have an Indian.
Oh, I'm going to have a Mexican.
You know, that means like a food, right?
Right.
I could murder one.
Right?
It means you really want it, right?
I'm feeling a bit peckish.
I think I'm going to have an Italian.
Right?
So they have, you know, a bit in
Scots and Irish.
I don't know.
That's, you know, that they've always been put
down through history anyway.
So they're used to it.
We don't need to get into it with
them any much, any much more.
Same with the black people.
They've been put down for so long.
You don't need to do it anymore.
You know, just stop beating a dead horse
about it.
There's the ups and downs of every culture
and every race and creed and color.
But there are certain races, creeds, and colors
and cultures that have been for centuries just
under the foot of the elitist class, the
middle class, so to speak, and all that.
And this has nothing to do with it
in terms of, you know, how you see
politically.
Oh, you know, the white people, it's a
white man's fault.
No, it's not.
You know, I'm not talking about that, right?
You know, like turning it around.
It's like if you go study anthropology or
sociology in college, all those courses, if you
distill them down, you know what they're really
about?
Just how to blame the white man for
everything.
That's all.
They don't really get into anything.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about the inherent objective aspect of
it, right?
So there we go.
White people, food, avoid it if you want
better diet.
If you don't think you want to cook,
move to the east or west coast of
the states.
That's where you're going to, or an international
city, right?
And that's pretty much it.
Now, the rest of the crux of this
sonic event is what do we do now,
right?
I've got fire, I've got water, I've got
some cutlery, pots and pans, right?
What do we do, right?
Let's start that part of the conversation in
terms of food preparation.
What people are mystified, I've noticed through time
when it comes to cooking and food preparation
are two things other than the ingredients of
the food is pots and pans and knives,
utensils in the kitchen.
We're not talking about serving now, right?
So which one do you want to do
first, Bruce, the pots and pans or the
knives?
Okay, the knives.
Thanks, Bruce.
You're welcome.
So let's go with knives first.
I've yet to see, again, I'm going to
be referencing a lot about white people, so
don't, whatever, and this is still true for
many, but I've never been to a white
person's house that had a knife that worked
in the kitchen.
I've never used a serrated, you know what
a serrated edge is?
It's used on a cutting board, you know,
for cutting.
That's only for bread.
You ever go to a white person's house
and you see a cutting board and it's
fuzzy?
It looks like it's a shag carpet.
That's a serrated knife.
And the reason they like serrated knives is
because they don't dull quickly, right?
And all white people have fuzzy cutting boards.
I don't say, I mean all, but, you
know, there's maybe a few dozen in the
world that don't, that are not chefs.
Never use a serrated knife.
You're going to use a serrated knife, get
a glass or do it openly.
You know, don't cut all the way down.
If you have a serrated knife and that's
all you have, a serrated knife means it's
rough, it's not smooth.
When you have a cutting board, cut three
quarters or seven eighths or 90% down
and then turn the item vertically and then
continue cutting.
You see?
So the blade just barely ever touches the
base of the knife or the cutting board.
So what I just did there was save
you from, well, I have to go, I
don't ever want to tell people they have
to buy anything, right?
So, I mean, otherwise I would have done
a podcast that you had to be a
member for it.
I knew that would become a moron magnet
so I don't want to do that.
By the way, just to interject this in
the middle here, I want to thank someone
from Ohio.
I got your anonymous package.
Thank you very much.
So anyway, just going to go back.
Serrated knife, instead of making the fuzzy board,
let's say you're cutting bread or meat or
whatever, cut across however you do, turn the
item or curl it or if it's a
soft item, roll it so it cuts up
into the blade instead of the blade cutting
down.
Please don't know fuzzy cutting boards, okay?
So serrated knives are only for cutting bread
on a bread board and even then most
people don't know how to use them.
I've seen people try to use serrated knives
that keep cutting all the way down to
the base.
What you're supposed to do is cut most
of the way down and then turn, rotate
90 degrees the item you're cutting and then
finish your cut that way.
So you're always cutting in the air.
Do you picture that, Bruce?
Did I get a visual from that?
Okay.
Even if it's a piece of salami or
a piece of tofu, cut most of the
way through, rotate the tofu or the salami
90 degrees and then continue cutting and you'll
notice you're cutting in the air but you're
using the food or whatever you're cutting as
a guide for your knife, right?
So you're basically just touching the board slightly.
Now, if we get to the real talk
about knives, there's something called a santoku knife,
there's something called a chef's knife, there's carving
knives that are very narrow and very long.
Basically, what's called a short chef's knife or
a chef's knife or a santoku which means
three ways in Japanese.
San means three.
They're easy to get.
You can even go to a closeout place
like TJ Maxx or Ross or Marshall Holmes
or whatever.
They have them prepackaged.
They're pretty good.
Santoku, it's a three-way knife.
Usually they have dimples on the side.
They're pretty tall, the knife.
So not quite like a butcher knife but
anyway, look it up.
Or a chef's knife but don't get a
chef's knife that's so like freaking long that
it looks like you could skin a crocodile
with it.
You don't really need that.
Or carving knives are totally useless.
They're really narrow and very long, right?
So get yourself a medium, an 8 or
9-inch, what would that be, 20-centimeter
chef's knife or so or a 7 or
8-inch, 20 or so centimeter santoku knife.
Now, here's the deal about knives.
I've got knives of every variety.
Lately, I've been preferring the closeout ones that
are made for, you buy them for $5
or $10.
I have a Rockwell hardness 64 Japanese sushi
knife that costs about $300, $400.
I have one here, a Mac knife that's
about $250 and all that.
And the ones that I use are just
the ones that I find that are easy,
the most workable and the thinnest blade.
What you want to find also, like Mac
knife, M-A-C, there's a lot of
companies that are copying their technique.
You don't want a forged knife.
You want a stamped knife.
In other words, you want the blade to
be stamped.
So when you're looking at the back of
the blade, not the edge, the opposite, you
want that to be very thin and narrow.
Unlike years ago where even though it was
a sharp knife at the top or the
back of the blade, it was very thick.
You notice that, Bruce?
Those are for, yeah, you don't need that
because what that'll do is it puts too
much of an angle on the edge.
So as you're cutting, it's going to create
more friction on the blade.
What you want is a thin knife.
Mac, for example, part of their claim to
fame is that their knives are stamped and
forged that way.
So the other thing is sharpening a knife.
There are the pull sharpeners.
There are stone sharpeners.
Get a pull sharpener and a very thin,
low abrasive sharpener to practice on.
Have a practice blade or something.
Learn how to practice on a popsicle stick
or a piece of wood because believe it
or not, it won't cut much.
But if you can create a fine edge
on a piece of wood, you can move
up to metal.
You won't really ruin the knife if you
don't know what you're doing because you could
always take it to be sharpened.
But even with a knife that costs several
hundred, even a thousand in credits, it doesn't
come with a really good edge on it.
I know it sounds kind of crazy.
You have to learn how to do that,
which is called knife sharpening.
If you're going to enjoy it.
That was a knife that used to be
handed down from one generation to the next.
Yes.
That's gone.
You don't see much of it.
I consider myself to be a master sharpener,
but it took me over a year, well
actually 10 years of doing it or more.
Actually, I've been sharpening knives for 30 years.
I don't want to talk about the first
20.
It was hit or miss.
I couldn't explain what I was doing.
Once I discovered the way it should be
done or could be done, that's only been
the past few years.
I can cut anything.
As a matter of fact, once I had
an orthotic, that is an insert that you
have made in the shoe.
I was doing coaching and cycling and I
measured the leg length discrepancy.
I said, this one needs to be a
little thinner because that leg is a little
longer than the other leg.
How are you going to trim it?
It's a $300 orthotic.
How do you do that?
You don't want to ruin it.
I just took the sushi knife that I
have and I sliced off a half a
millimeter across and then I went again another
half a millimeter until we got the right
size across.
It looked like the entire orthotic.
See, nothing disturbed.
Like a laser would cut it.
No resistance, no deformation.
Super, super sharp.
Someone would say, well that will dull the
knife.
It would, but so what?
Because now we sharpen it again.
Right, which you should do all the time.
The practice that I do is before I
use a knife, I sharpen it.
Let's say I'm going to prepare a meal.
I'm going to use this particular knife.
Sometimes I'll use more than one type of
knife depending on what I'm cutting.
I'll take the knife out and I'll sharpen
it.
I'll wet it down with a cloth, clean
After I'm done using it, I clean the
knife and sharpen it again and then put
it away.
The reason why they do that is because
when I've sharpened it after I've used it,
I know it's as good as new now
and if I just have to pull the
knife in a hurry, it's ready to go.
I don't have to be mid-cut saying,
oh, it needs sharpening.
You see?
Right.
And also if I sharpen it, if I
have the time and sharpen it before I
start cutting, then I know that I'm at
the performance.
Now I know to expect the performance that
I would want to expect from a sharp
knife.
Never put knives in a drawer.
Never put knives in a dishwasher.
The drawer is obvious.
It gets knocked around every time or anything
touching the blade is going to skew the
edge.
So what do we do about sharpening knives?
Well, there's these things called tungsten carbide knife
pulls.
You could see there are two pieces of
metal if you look very closely.
They crisscross each other at an angle.
It looks like a V and you pull
the knife across that.
The ceramic ones are good, but they wear
out.
So they're not worth getting as much anymore.
Use a tungsten sharpener.
And then you have to learn how to
hone.
Now in the Western world, they go with
a 15 degree angle.
I prefer a 10 to 12, which is
a little steeper, more of the Asian.
It's a little sharper.
It doesn't hold its edge as long.
They found 15 to 20 degrees is when
a knife keeps its edge the longest.
So most sharpeners you're going to get are
going to be in the 15 or 20
degree on the market.
Now I've had a lot of success with
going to closeout stores and there's a blister
pack hanging $5.99 for a Japanese knife.
I just get it just to try it
out and I give it away if it
doesn't work out.
But I do sharpen and check out the
quality.
So between five and ten bucks at a
retail outlet type place, you could get a
pretty decent knife, but you're going to have
to sharpen it.
And it'll still come sharp out of the
package.
It's at that 20 degree angle.
In other words, it's going to rock left
and right.
It won't cut like a razor blade.
So that's pretty much the story of knives.
No, there's no YouTube video I could recommend
for knife sharpening.
I've looked it up and I'm like, huh,
what?
That's not what it's about.
So you're going to have to learn how
to sharpen either from, yes, doing internet research
and also trial and error and understanding the
concept behind it so you have the tools.
You see, when people go to research how
to do certain procedures, it's monkey see, monkey
do.
Most information on the internet, whether it's video
format or not, doesn't give the background, doesn't
really give you the fundamental tools on why
you're doing it.
You see, you get my drift on that,
right?
So you're going to have to learn the
fundamental drift on what shear pressure is, right?
You know, the narrower the edge, the more
it penetrates, you know, the object, right?
You remember years ago, if you saw one
in someone's house or a hotel and it
had a wood floor and you see all
these dots in the floor, that was from
the stiletto heels in the fifties and sixties.
You know, so a 90 pound woman and
a little tiny heel put 1200 pounds of
pressure on the wood floor and deformed it,
made a hole in the floor, right?
You see, so the smaller the surface for
the same amount of weight, the higher the
pressure, that's what cuts.
So the finer the edge, the better.
Because even the sharpest knife in the world
looked under a powerful microscope will look as
blunt as, you know, a dunghill or something,
right?
So that's pretty much on the attitude I
have on knives.
Most of everything you'll see is stainless, but
when you get into the more demanding reaches
of knives, it's going to be carbon steel
because carbon steel has a higher Rockwell hardness.
I think the hardest stainless is in the
mid-fifties, so carbon goes much higher than
that.
And what does a harder knife mean?
It means that you can maintain a sharper
edge longer, right?
The reason why knives dull out is because
the material is soft and deforms, essentially.
Notwithstanding impact or other things, right?
Talking about normal use.
So I don't think most people listening to
this are going to aspire to getting a
carbon knife which does rust and oxidize, right?
Should be oiled if you don't use it
daily.
Even if you do use it daily, oil
it because it creates a seasoning, you know,
like cast iron pans do.
But that coating won't survive when you're sharpening.
And when you're sharpening, it should always be
wet, maybe a dab of soap.
I use Falspar, which is called, Falspar is
a white powder, it's in Bonami, B-O
-N-A-M-I, never scratches yet.
It's a gold foil thing, has a little
chick on it, never scratched yet, been around
for a hundred something years.
Are you familiar with Bonami cleaner?
No, I'm not.
Oh, okay.
You could brush your teeth with it.
I'm going to look that up.
Yeah, because I smoke sometimes I'll get stains
on the lower teeth.
I'm like, Wes, are you going to go
to the dentist and get, no, I'm going
to get some Bonami.
She goes, are you going to brush your
teeth with Bonami?
I say, yeah, I'll burn your lip because
it's alkaline, but yeah, it turns teeth really
white, so.
Anyway, yeah, yeah, it's pretty neat.
It doesn't scratch like, you know, many powdered
cleaners that will scratch.
Right.
The ones that, especially the ones that are
chlorinated.
Bonami, Falspar is a white abrasive.
It's used like in Crocus or what do
they call those honing, years ago with the
old cars.
When you had a new engine before you
turned it on, you threw some Falspar powder
while you first turned it on to go
inside the valves and it polished everything up,
you know, but it doesn't scratch.
It would be in the 3, 4,000
grit, you know, or higher.
Oh, wow.
You see?
Yeah, but it doesn't scratch.
It's Falspar.
It's like chalk.
It's not like granite or ruby or garnet
that scratches.
I use that for a knife.
I use it as a compound because, you
know, I have wet on the, I have
a diamond plate and I have various stones.
So, now we got into a little more
detail on how to maintain knives, which most
people probably won't get into, so I'll switch
over to pots and pans.
The reason I'm saying that, I might be
saying it sarcastically because when I discuss this
for 10 years with people, I'm not as
social as I used to be.
Only like one out of a hundred will
ever do anything about it.
So, we'll keep moving.
At least you know.
Pots and pans, this is something where people
can do something more about it because it
doesn't require any skill that you're going to
have to go out of your way and
acquire that could take a long time to
determine how are you going to use pots
and pans.
Essentially, pots and pans, I'm not going to
talk about Teflon and coatings.
If you're stupid enough to have one of
those, it doesn't mean you have to throw
it away if it's your only pot or
pan.
Just don't make it, just don't ever put
it on heat with anything, nothing in it
and it gets really hot, right?
Because I think Teflon starts to evaporate at
what, 400 or 500 degrees?
Oh, 500.
So, anyway, and it's a fluoro, and it's
really messed you up.
That's why they like using that ceramic coating
because it'll, and you're already too messed up
anyway to reverse it.
So, you keep using it, you'll get a
little worse, but if you don't use it,
it's even better.
So, the biggest thing I find, especially with
white people, is unless they have like an
old cast iron pot that they inherited or
didn't know what to do with, all their
pots and pans are too thin bottomed, right?
You pick up, you tap it, you tap
the side, you tap the bottom, it's the
same thickness real cheap, right?
A decent sauce pot, one like that, costs
in the hundreds, you know, if you're going
to get like an oil clad or a
Lincoln or anything like that, most people have
never invested in that.
If you happen to have inherited a thick
bottomed pot, it's the bottom of the pot
if the whole thing is thick like a
Le Creuset, which is a baked enamel cast
iron.
Are you familiar with any of this stuff,
Bruce, by the way, I'm bringing up?
No, I'm not.
That's why I'm taking notes.
Okay, Le Creuset would be French, it's L
-E and then C-R-U-S-E
-T, okay.
Now, there's no shame, there's no fault and
there's no flaw to having cheap pots and
things like that.
What you do to fix that is you
go out and you, for two bucks or
whatever you are, you get what's called a
heat diffuser.
Look up a heat diffuser.
It just looks like two pieces of thin
metal with lots of holes in it.
And what that does is you put it
over your burner and it doesn't create a
super hot spot and it does just like
the name says, it diffuses the heat.
So now, you take a real cheap ass
pot with a thin bottom that usually would
burn the food on the bottom and the
food would still be cold on top because
it doesn't transfer heat very well in terms
of evenly.
You get a heat diffuser and you save
yourself the trouble of getting pots and pans,
okay.
The rules for humans, by the way, and
the gods for all these utensils is if
you have meat, cooked meat or touch animal,
any kind of animal flesh in these pots
and pans, they're considered unclean so they have
to be scrubbed, right?
That's how you scour pots and pans and
forks and knives to make them clean, right,
to declare them clean.
But then again, we'll talk, okay, so pots
and pans, there we go.
Then we're going to jump over to the
fridges.
By the way, do you know if you
put a piece of meat in a fridge
or animal flesh, that whole fridge is declared
unclean, right?
You're familiar with that concept, right?
I would think that would be the way
to go, yeah.
Yeah, so the only way to really go
to maintain a divinely clean fridge is to
have two.
One for animal flesh and one without.
Actually, there's some people that I've told this
to and they've actually done that.
They actually kept the meat fridge outside and
the one in the house only has veg
and dairy products because dairy is not dead.
It's not animal flesh.
Okay, so by the way, if anyone has
any restaurant experience, you can look this up
in the health codes.
If you have a fridge in the restaurant,
the meat always goes on the bottom and
the veggies on top.
So if the meat storage starts to drip
and leak, it's already on the bottom.
See, if you put the meat on top
and it drips and leaks, then it's going
to drip and leak on all your veg.
Now, all the home fridges have this thing,
it's a white people thing, vegetable crispers where?
On the bottom.
Right, now when you get a roast beef
or a turkey and you put it in
the fridge, where are you going to put
it?
On top of that, aren't you?
All your fridges are built to be unclean
and dirty.
In other words, if you had a restaurant
business, this is a universal code by the
way, and you, the inspector from the state
or whatever health board came over and saw
that you had meat over vegetable, they would
fine you.
But in your homes, it's okay.
Think about that for a moment.
Actually, don't think about it.
It might get you in heaps of trouble.
All right, so now we've covered how unfortunate
it is to live in a white people
food society, getting proper knives or at least
addressing proper knives.
And if most of you have serrated knives,
which you do, don't say you don't because
you do, don't be aggressive on the cutting
board.
Make sure it never makes it down to
the board directly by rotating and get yourself
a heat diffuser because I know you all
got cheap ass pots and pans.
That's the rule, not the exception.
Yes, someone listening might have some proper cutlery
or cookware, but that's not the rule.
So there you go.
Very simple.
Now we're ready to cook, aren't we?
Well, do you think we should add more
to this?
Because there is that discussion I did with
Seth.
And you know, Seth's demeanor is very good
in that sense because he's very like, he
sounds like he just woke up and he's
kind of tired of everything.
So it keeps me going slow and it
keeps me going.
And he'll ask a question that's redundant.
I'll have to repeat myself like he wasn't
listening, which is fine.
Because it's good for the audience, right?
A lot of people do like, say, why
don't you do something with Seth?
And I'm like, no, I don't want to
do anything with anyone.
Because I don't want to be a moron
magnet.
In other words, we're at a time in
history now that if you know this, you
know it, shut up.
And if you don't know it, just that's
too bad.
And it's like this is if you're listening
to Greek speak, it's an anomaly.
It shouldn't be happening.
So I think there's a lot of stuff
we covered there, which is how to make
the perfect rice, which I'm still playing around
with, which essentially is.
Oh, hey, I know what I was going
to ask you.
Did you ever get to figure out about
what was going on with that rice?
Hit or miss.
Yeah.
Other rices have gotten better.
Really?
This was a variety of an organic variety
that was just uncookable.
And I tossed the package.
It wasn't returnable.
But this is prophetic, by the way.
You know, why?
You know, here's the thing people don't understand.
And you're going to get, you know, when
everything in society is told and shown to
be perfect, that's when the shit's going to
hit the fan to the point where the
blades break off.
Right?
Yeah.
One of the things that happens that there's
nothing to eat, not because of Monsanto or
whatever.
Yeah, they're going to adding it to it,
too.
But because of certain events, you know, regarding
irrigation, water, solar heat, weather.
Right.
So one thing you'll notice prophetically, is things
are very rarely do things just hit happen
all of a sudden, there are things that
hit too suddenly.
But usually you're given fair enough warning in
advance, and it takes generations to take to
happen.
And it happens.
On occasion, prophecy happens on occasion, so gradually
that the people don't see it coming, even
when it's upon them.
You see, so, like, for example, the invasion
of the Babylonians, their Jerusalem was under siege
for over a decade and a half by
Assyrians and such, and they thought it was
going to be the Assyrians.
But last minute, there's a switch into the
Babylonian sack them, right?
Talking about 5600 BC.
So they were used to it.
They're used to siege.
Look at Hezekiah's tunnel, you know, Hezekiah was
all about siege, you know, and others, you
know, and then, you know, so anyway.
Yeah.
Why don't you put on some music?
I want to take a five minute break.
I've got to run and do something.
I'll be right back.
So we get into some food preparation.
I'll see you in about five minutes.
Sounds good.
Greek.
There we go.
And we're back.
We're back.
Cool beans.
Yeah.
All right.
So regarding of what to cook, I've gone
over on the archives there regarding making a
perfect rice, which is feared by most white
people and most cultures too.
But, you know, the Asians and Middle Eastern
cultures, you know, they are quite well, even
there, then there's room for improvement, but they're
well skilled in that.
Basically, just a quick thing, follow the instructions
on the rice, but rinse the rice and
let it stand in water or in a
strainer for at least five or 10 minutes
before you put it in the pot.
Right.
And make sure that your lid is long
grain.
With the brown rice, I believe you mentioned
that it should be for significantly longer.
Overnight is best.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Whole grain.
Now here's the thing about whole foods and
whole.
I would suggest that when you hear the
term whole food, it mostly applies to grain,
I would say.
OK.
Right.
Because when you have a steak, is it
a whole steak, a whole, you know, or
anything else.
So it's usually grain.
So when you hear the term whole food,
it's not processed, which would be grain.
By the way, there's no such thing as
gluten allergy.
That is just an allergy to a very
bad quality grain.
If there was such a thing as a
gluten allergy, there would be no one alive
today because most societies relied on wheat to
stay alive.
Yeah.
So again, that goes back to the degradation
of the product.
Yeah.
So all that gluten-free stuff is really
stupid.
But, you know, it's planet Earth, so it
has to fit.
Right.
Essentially, when you're dealing with a whole food,
I'll give you a story from several people.
If you've heard of macrobiotics, which is about
eating seasonally, eating locally, I don't recommend it
because it's very Sinocentric, Japanese centric, and they're
very dogmatic people.
I mean, it's almost they've turned it into
a I call it macro neurotics because it's
almost like a disease.
But it does work.
The spirit behind it, of course, is not
a good one.
But evidently eating the way that they suggest
is good.
You see what I mean?
It's been hijacked from the beginning, especially when
it was brought over to America by Michio
Kushi, who I knew, and Shizuko Yamamoto, who
I knew, and also George Asawa, who was
their teacher, I didn't know.
He died before I was born, I think.
Then there were other bunch of white people
that tried to take it over and run
it.
But one of the stories about macrobiotics is
when they first brought it to eat whole,
basically grains, proportions of grain to bean, and
how to eat a balanced diet, and also
how to heal things by changing the attributes
of the food.
Changing the food, because each food has an
attribute to the body.
Get my drift.
Eventually, you can get into the medicine of
it.
Each type of food corresponds to a certain
organ of the body.
Mostly the ones that are neutral, like the
cabbage looks like the brain, or the lotus
root cross-section looks like the lung.
No, a banana doesn't look like you know
what, right?
That's tropical, right?
You see more of the mid-temperate stuff
grown.
When they started having seminars in Northern California
and Central California, a lot of people were
interested in it, from all sorts of life
came over.
I think I've said this story before.
They had a seminar every week or every
two weeks.
They noticed that, this is in the late
60s, early 70s, they noticed after about a
series of seminars, the only people that were
showing up were the hippie types, the stoners
and all that.
One day they just stopped and said, well
why do you guys keep coming back?
Because no one else is.
He said, well because we don't have to
get high anymore.
We've noticed that if we eat what you
say, we feel high all the time.
There you go.
If you get yourself a good quality whole
grain brown rice and you have some other
grains that you can mix it with, like
some barley or whole oat, millet is really
good to add to it in small amounts.
If you have a high quality organic brown
rice and you cook it properly and have
it in low proportions of protein with it,
you will start to feel high.
In other words, you will feel this constant
feeling of euphoria.
Nothing wrong with that.
I just wanted to bring up when you
hear whole foods, it's grains and what eating
whole grains cooked properly can do for the
individual.
What else?
We spoke about hearty tubers, what would be
a potato.
Learn how to do stovetop.
Even if everyone likes a baked potato, don't
bake it.
Put it in water and lots of salt,
15-20 minutes.
Poke some holes in it with a fork.
Go at least to the middle of it
or a third way through.
Put it in a stovetop in a pot
with a tight lid with a weight on
it.
Make sure it doesn't overboil or overspill.
Then take the water out of the pot
and just leave the potato sitting on a
low heat for five minutes.
Rotate it.
Turn off the heat for five minutes.
You'll open the lid again.
You'll see the potato released a lot of
steam.
Rotate the potato for another five minutes.
Turn it off for five or ten.
Come back another five minutes on low.
This is all stovetop.
You've got a stovetop baked potato.
Go figure.
You know, one of my favorites, by the
way.
Have you done it?
Oh, yeah.
Many, many, many times.
It works well.
It works well and it's safe.
And you know when you talk about that
aroma towards the end.
It does have that.
Oh, yeah.
If you're going to do mashed potatoes, do
it the same way now people chop up
to make mash or potato salad.
When the potato is barely fork tender, take
it out of the water and put it
back in the pot.
If you're making potato salad or mashed potatoes,
imagine opening the pot lid and you have
that baked potato flavor in your potato salad
or mash.
You know, like the most delicious mash is
baked potato mash, not the kind that you
boil.
So now you can achieve, when I do
mashed potatoes, people freak out like I never
had mashed potatoes in my life.
Basically because they do a stovetop bake to
make mash.
Actually, as a matter of fact, let's just
be dogmatic and say this.
If you cook potatoes, do it all stovetop
baked and whatever potato dish you have, it
will be really potato-y and delicious if
there is such a thing as potato-y.
Now, you can do the same with beets
and turnips or any other tuber, any root
vegetable, carrots.
A simple carrot recipe is to steam it
or just put the carrots in a saucepan
or a pot with a tight lid, barely
cut.
I never got into how to do cuts.
Various cuts change the flavor of food.
You know, if you grate a carrot, slice
a carrot or chop a carrot, it tastes
like three different things, even though it's the
same carrot.
The cut changes the flavor.
Like a steak will taste different than a
hamburger, even if it was the same cut.
What was it, a turquoise?
Oh, roasting it.
That's what it was.
You mentioned that.
With carrots, you could do stovetop roasting.
The key to a roast is the browning,
the caramelization.
You cheat with it by adding just a
little bit of honey or sugar or some
sweetener, even some kind of a fruit juice,
a dash of apple juice or grape juice.
In other words, if you're making carrots, just
go ahead and slice them the long way.
Actually, I would hate to see a white
person with a serrated knife trying to cut
a carrot the long way.
But anyway, you got to go, yeah, no
way it's going to happen.
So anyway, I don't get into a lot
of the techniques because I know the rule
is that people have crap equipment.
And you don't need gizmos and gadgets.
Back to the carrots.
Just get some heat into them, steamed where
they're just barely fork tender, meaning they're still
crunchy.
Drain the water out.
And with carrots, I don't because they're going
to leave a glaze.
I just put a couple of tablespoons of
water and when the water evaporates, it's about
time to add some kind of sweetener and
a little bit of fat.
When I say fat, it would be butter
or oil.
Avoid using too much olive oil if you're
going to use a long duration of heat
because it doesn't taste good.
It goes to a high level of rancidity.
Use peanut oil, sunflower oil, and even a
quality canola oil.
They call it rapeseed.
For a while, they're saying, oh, it's really
bad.
Well, that's how you make siren gas with
canola oil, right, rapeseeds, that real toxic gas,
if you know what you're doing.
So anyway, there are many movements of latching
onto something that's bad for you and pushing
it.
But either way, olive oil should be a
finishing.
You could use a non-toasted sesame oil
also for cooking.
That's also good for oil pulling.
If we've ever discussed oil pulling when you
wake up.
Anyway, you take a teaspoon of oil and
gargle with it and then spit it out.
Does the body good?
Okay, but back to the carrots.
When you get your sweetener and they're low
heat, go from low to medium until you
get a char.
If you don't stir it, move them around
or a glaze and it makes it really
delicious.
I have prepared personally roasted meals, baked meals,
all stovetop and served them and people thought
they were roasted or baked in the oven.
It was all stovetop.
Now, what does that mean?
When you do everything stovetop, you conserve a
lot of heat because an oven is basically
a big box you have to get really
hot and they're very inefficient.
They're only about 10% efficient or 50
% efficient, the best.
And the burners in the stoves and ovens
are always in the wrong spot.
And electric's a little better because the burner
goes around the edge.
But most ovens, they put the burner in
the center, which is a hot spot.
It should have double burner left and right.
We never got into master roasting or master
baking techniques.
But if you understand that there's been a
culinary movement in Spain that actually have surpassed
the French culinary movement in modern times, most
of the hot cuisine or high-end cooking
places in Spain or restaurants, they have to
still design and build their own equipment.
If I were to do a restaurant, I
wouldn't go out and buy the equipment that
they sell.
It's crap.
It's whoever put it together is stupid or
is not into making good food.
I would have to build and design my
own grills and ovens and all that to
put the heat where I want it.
I know it sounds kind of crazy, but
I just finished mentioning that look at the
refrigerators that they sell you for your homes.
They're backwards.
Pretty much sums it up, doesn't it?
Yep.
So again, you can get a good glaze
or caramelization on the stovetop by, I call
it cheating, by adding a sweetener.
Anything that has a little sweetness to it,
starchiness will caramelize and it'll just dark brown.
That's where that umami flavor comes from.
So pasta is another thing.
There's noodles pasta.
Make the water saltier than you normally do.
There's an old saying in Italian where the
water for the pasta should be as salty
as the sea.
That's a little too salty.
It actually really isn't.
But when you do that, it gives the
noodle more flavor.
Very often I see or have had, I
don't eat that much, but a noodle dish
or whatever, and I could tell that the
water was not salted enough.
The noodle is kind of bland, right?
Also good salts.
Find out what they are.
Not all salts are created equal.
The best salts are the ones that are
assured that were harvested without metal.
You're going to say, what do they use
in Greek?
What are they, plastic spoons and wooden shovels?
Yeah.
Expect to pay 20 pound or 35 credits
in US credits per pound for a quality
salt, right?
So we're looking at $2 an ounce roughly
for a quality salt.
I've landed on lately some Thai.
I've been investigating salt source from Thailand.
Seem to be a very high quality.
They don't cost that much.
They're actually pennies on the ounce and I've
been enjoying them.
A really good salt should be salty initially.
You just dab some on your finger.
Don't wet your finger and dab it in
the salt.
Just do it dry.
It should be enough.
It should be salt initially and then have
a sweet, earthy finish.
If you have like white people salt or
table salt, it's salty and then it gets
really salty and metallic.
That's poison.
Right?
Have you ever had a good quality salt,
Bruce, where you taste it and it's salty
and it finishes off as being sweet and
earthy?
Yeah.
And we do get a caller, by the
way.
Oh, we do?
All right.
Let's bring him on in.
And his first name is Joe, I believe.
Go ahead, Joe.
Greetings.
Hey.
Greetings, you guys.
Okay.
Can you hear me?
Can you hear Greek?
I do not hear nothing.
Okay, just a second.
Oh, you don't hear us?
Okay, try it now.
How about that?
No, I got to put it in like
this.
Okay, go ahead.
How about now?
You hear us?
Yes.
Loud and clear.
All right.
Okay.
Joe, go ahead.
What's on your mind?
You know what?
I really wasn't sure.
I just saw that there was some folks
calling in and I thought maybe we were
just having a conversation casually, but I didn't
know the call was still going on.
I thought it was over or maybe that
the Greek was just having more entertaining conversations
in a private capacity.
I didn't know we were live right now.
We're live, but let's just say that it's
a private conversation that happens to be streamed.
So you are our first stream monkey of
the night.
I'll shut up so you can say what
you got to say.
Go for it.
Man, I really don't know what to say
at this point.
I was expecting just to be having a
conversation with some gentlemen on just kind of
casually talking, but I don't have the wherewithal
like Sam or somebody like that to be
going live with you, man.
That's all right.
I got casual shoes.
I got casual shoes, casual pants, casual shirts,
and now we got casual conversation.
No, we were talking about food tonight, aspects
of food, the pitfalls of white people, food,
the pitfalls of how people let everything go
where they don't even have sharp knives in
their house.
They got thin pots and pans where they
can't cook even if they wanted to.
Teflon, we talked about basically how to pursue
various ways to remedy those things without abandoning
those things.
Would you say that sums it up, Bruce?
Yeah, that pretty much sums it right up
and a lot of good info.
We'll have this, of course, up in the
archives.
Did you have anything else, Joe?
I got a question for you.
I read a book called, I think it
was called The Electric Body, but somebody stole
it from me and I cannot remember the
name of the author.
I had looked into it before, but it
was a good reference of information.
He was talking about piezoelectricity in the body.
That just made me think of all sorts
of things with regards to converting energy in
the body, the relations of that and how
it is, I guess, I don't want to
say replicated or displayed in other forms because
it seems like that's a major function with
regards to magnetism.
Let me just interrupt because without the vacuum
of time, even when we show Frankenstein, which
is a parody of Ben Franklin used to,
when he was a big proponent of electricity,
he used to get slaves and chop them
up in pieces and put them back together
and try to revive them with electricity.
Mary Shelley found that out and freaked out.
So she wrote, yeah, these are your founding
fathers in America, a bunch of scumbags.
I was going to ask you, Greg, do
you think this also harkens in now when
he mentioned about the piezoelectricity in the body?
I think it goes much farther than that.
It doesn't work.
It's irrelevant.
Hold on, it's irrelevant without the vacuum.
Right, exactly.
I was going to say, this explains a
lot of things in the lawful, in Leviticus
as far as being lawful, food, clothing, shelter,
as far as what was laid down for
what man should be doing.
You look at some of that, how that
might play an effect to stay lawfully and
why it was put there.
Of course, the gods don't really say why,
they just give it to you and that's
that.
Well, here's the other thing, even back then,
the people were too stupid to comprehend why.
Correct.
If you don't believe me, go read about
the comments of what the people were doing
while they even were in their presence.
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, the biblical text is a
misanthropic text, right?
You understand?
You get what I mean?
It's misanthropic.
You read the Bible, you're like, these people
suck.
So anyway, without the biological vacuum, electricity doesn't
mean anything.
I think the vacuum, take care of the
vacuum and the electrical part will take care
of itself.
As a matter of fact, there's a guy,
John Bedini, did a bunch of DVDs called
Energy from the Vacuum.
You remember that?
Energy from the Vacuum is a short movie
about that.
Oh man, that's a name I haven't heard
of.
His brother died within four hours apart, and
they were in their mid-60s.
Yeah, talk about, just like the, talking about
talk, Anthony Bourdain allegedly was committed suicide.
Yeah, right.
He was mixed up with CNN, which is
mixed up political.
By the way, just to bounce around a
little bit, are you guys familiar with the
treachery and the crap that was going on
in the Roman Empire?
If they didn't like you, you're a political
official or famous person.
They said, well, the emperor doesn't like you
anymore.
You have a choice.
Either take your own life or we'll kill
you.
And if you take your own life, it'll
be more honorable, you know?
Right.
I guess when they killed you...
When you're talking about the vacuum, the way
I understand it is that matter or the
fields that encompass matter have the ability to
compress or go, I guess you could call,
go in phase to smaller levels of space.
Is that what you mean by vacuum?
I'm just trying to be clear.
Yeah, well, it's really hard to be clear
because it's out of this, this type of
thinking is not in the world right now,
but you have to comprehend counter space also.
Counter space is the opposite of space, but
it's not the opposite of space.
You see, it's not like hot and cold.
You could but it's not the, it's not
like in science fiction, they got matter, anti
-matter.
Counter space, everything comes out.
Like, for example, if you draw it, if
you have a, imagine a dot in the
center of a circle and that represents the
locus point of a circle, the center.
And from that dot to the, that's how
you create a circle.
You make a radius and you spin it
around 360, actually 361 degrees and you make
a circle, right?
So now we're talking all two dimensional, right?
And with the dot, you think is one
dimension, but there's actually a counter spatial element.
When you're drawing that dot or you're imagining
that dot, it's not just a point in
space, but imagine that it's the end, you're
looking at the end of a line that
goes to infinity.
That's what a dot really is.
And when you bring in counter space into
the picture, you could imagine, you know, taking
a pole, it looks like a rod, let's
say 10 feet long, and you hold it
and you just look at the end, it
just looks like a dot on the end,
right?
So now you're starting to, that's how you
deal with counter space.
And some people ask me, can you explain
counter space?
And I do, I spend hours on Skype
or have spent explaining counter space and it
takes usually a week or two to come
back and they're like, oh, okay, I either
don't get it or I want to hear
more.
So once you understand counter space, like if
you think space, you define it as pressure,
counter space would be the opposite of that,
would be a negative pressure, but it's not
sucking like a vacuum cleaner.
You know, sometimes I'd make public discussions or
whatever, and oh, the Greek says we're like
vacuum cleaners, you know, no, I do not.
It's not that type of vacuum, it's a
counter spatially induced vacuum.
And when you talk about fields, you know,
there's no branch of science that can define
a field, still.
They tell you it's waves and waves is
not what something is.
Waves is what something does.
So they can't define that something.
And I will probably never do public discussions,
I've said this about other things, as I
see about counter space and these other things
in great detail.
So would you, would it be safe to
say, and I sometimes refer to that as
a complimentary domain, sort of like if you
could think of what is manifested in space,
the polar opposite of that would be what's
not manifested or whatever would be the
Well, all right, let me just fill it
in for you, so it's more continuous.
What you see as space is a manifestation
of a pattern that comes from counter space.
Like remember that dot that we constructed, the
circle using a radius?
Now everyone says that dot is one point,
one dimension, I'm telling you that's the end
of a line.
You can visualize that, right?
You're not looking at the length of the
line, just the end of the line.
Whether it's the beginning or the end is
not important at this point, it's just the
end of a line.
Okay, so what you see, it manifests everything
in the universe, physical and energetic, is the
end of the line of counter space.
Can I ask you a question, Greg?
Do you dream a lot or have you
had
Never.
I don't dream.
I don't know how old you are.
I'll tell you, I'm half a century plus
three.
Did you experience anything during that psychedelic era
in life?
I'm not sure, I'm making an assumption, but
I'm just throwing that out there, because that
kind of language, I usually only find people
who have experienced altered states of consciousness who
really understand that kind of language, and I
can kind of like
I'm not a relativist, but I would suggest
that the psychedelic stuff was a dummy load.
You don't need it, you're already equipped with,
you already got everything you got.
To me, what's psychedelic is what's considered to
be normal.
For me, psychedelic is like going to look
at what Harvard is teaching, or MIT, or
some underground government lab.
That's some bullshit.
Actually, BS, bad science.
To me, psychedelic is seeing what's going on
around me.
Counter space is interesting.
Why don't you go check out a little
bit of J.J. Thompson and Charles Proteus
Steinmetz.
A little bit of Eric Dollard, maybe, if
you could stomach it.
He seems pretty normal on YouTube.
I would get his older ones, when he
was talking about when he was in electronics.
Who was that first person you've seen?
J.J. Thompson.
Recent Studies in Electrical Experiments.
It's a 900-page
Charles Proteus Steinmetz.
Don't try to read Steinmetz.
There's very few people alive that can still
comprehend what even his point of view was.
I would just go read about what he
wrote about counter space.
Believe it or not, on the rectangle, anywhere
you go, there's very little about counter space
discussion.
It does exist.
I use it all the time when I
do weather work.
The weather is a function of counter space.
Flowers, dandelions are a function of counter space.
Animals, plants, planets, everything is a function of
counter space.
Let me ask you a question.
I know you are familiar with Wilhelm Reich's
work.
His terminology is screwed up, though.
Go ahead.
I've experimented for years with Tantra and preserving
my discharge, if you will.
No, no, no.
Hold on, hold on.
Those are a bunch of degenerates.
All that information that comes out of the
East is the same degenerate crap that you
get from the Catholic Church, I mean, on
that level.
In other words, an average Catholic thinks that
everything they're doing is right, but if you
go look, everything they're doing is wrong.
Everything that you hear in the Western world,
and I mean everything, about Eastern sciences, you've
been pranked.
And the degenerates that they send over here
that are gurus, they call gurus a bunch
of assholes.
So does that mean that you're never going
to find out about Kundalini and all this
other stuff?
No.
You're going to have to find out for
yourself, because there ain't no real information about
it on the rectangle or has been taught
ever in the West, ever.
Just like Tai Chi, you're going to see
some slow movement and all that stuff that
works well, but the real Tai Chi is
so fast you can't even see it happening.
In other words, if you're a real Eastern
master coming over here trying to teach Kundalini
and all that stuff, you would be dead.
Once they found out you were teaching it,
they'd come over here and assassinate your ass.
I think now they'd be suiciding you.
That's hardcore truth right there.
There is no mastership on the rectangle.
I believe you.
I'm just saying from my own experience.
I'm not asking you to believe me.
I'm making a claim and a statement that
holds true to anybody that researches what I
just said.
I don't doubt that, man, because I believe
that.
So I'm not going to address that, believe
it or not.
Now, William Wright, just to address the William
Wright part, he thinks that, which I would
be in agreement with him, it is an
expression of discharging excessive life force.
We're not talking about the fluids now.
We're not talking about the fluids.
We're talking about the actual nervous and metabolic
reactions.
I figured that at that point the fluid
would be just the residue of the leftovers
of something smaller that would be electrical.
I just thought that that was something that
was just...
The electrical still can't be defined because electrical
is really dielectric and magnetic.
What you call electromagnetism, dielectric has been completely
negated.
And rightfully so.
Waste product of ether.
That's right.
It's a manifestation.
I wouldn't say a waste product.
It's just a manifestation.
Is a bullet a waste product of a
gun or a manifestation of what the gun
was designed to do?
Charles Steinmetz or something like that.
How do you pronounce it?
What was his name again?
Steinmetz.
Charles Steinmetz.
Years ago, recently they say you eat no
Einstein, meaning you're not smart.
Einstein was an asshole.
Einstein, by the way, means stupid in German.
Stein is stone and ein means one.
It means you only got one stone, one
rock.
It's like one brain cell.
Someone's got two brain cells, they rub them
together.
You don't even have that.
You got one brain cell in a mirror.
So that's Einstein.
But just years ago, they say you ain't
no Steinmetz.
They stopped that in the 50s because they
had propagated everybody.
Just like today, you know, there's still people,
you know, stupid people talking about, oh, I
was Osama bin Laden.
Ain't no such thing as Osama bin Laden,
you know.
So I would say Steinmetz would be a
way to grease yourself about it.
I mean, like, you know, take the friction
out of the thought by looking at what
other people have established.
That's the thing about why I do a
lot of this speaking is because there's so
much that can be accessed and so little
is being accessed that you just got to
throw your hands up in the air and
say, OK, this is the wrong time, the
wrong people, the wrong planet.
You know what I mean?
Well, you have to start going back and
looking at old books, you know, old teachings.
You want a really new idea, read an
old book.
The older the book, the newer the idea.
OK, did we lose you, Joe?
No, maybe we lost him.
OK, well, that's OK.
OK, I don't want to talk too much.
I just want to be able to absorb
what you're saying and not, you know what
I mean, just kind of reflect.
OK, well, you have to induce it.
Well, we were good.
Let's go back to the food discussion.
Yes.
Let me turn on this chat.
Anybody?
Let me see anybody going on.
I don't see.
We got some.
Who's this?
We got a new 42.
Leon and my band from coming in at
the Greek coming in.
Where?
Go ahead.
Call in if nobody.
That was me.
Call it.
Forty two.
United.
Yep.
That's you.
That was Joe.
Oh, yeah.
OK, that's not a problem.
Go ahead.
And the food thing is important.
But, you know, when you when you look
at the rules that are out there, you
know, people are very poorly equipped with equipment
and skill.
Now, let me just give an example with
equipment.
You don't need any of those gadgets, gizmos
and whatever.
That's one thing I wanted to get into,
Bruce, which I didn't.
Yes.
You need basically you need small, medium and
large.
It's like the rule of hammers.
I got toolbox.
Fix everything.
Open it is three hammers, a small one,
medium and large.
Right.
In other words, OK, so if you're going
to buy anything, what do you need?
You need in cooking.
You need to cut, stir and cook.
Right.
Or cut, stir and strain.
So if you're going to buy anything for
the kitchen, I see people try to compensate
for their lack of skill with gizmos.
How many times you've been in like, you
know, what's called like a high net worth
person.
You know, they got the million dollar, two
million dollar house in the Golden Ghetto.
You go into their kitchen.
It's all canned food.
But you open the doors.
They got every gizmo, every shaker, cutter thing
you can imagine.
They can't, you know, do anything right.
That stuff was not designed for it was
to compensate for people's willingness to be in
the kitchen.
So, for example, what you're going to need.
That's why I suggested one knife.
You might want a small knife.
Right.
They're very helpful if you're working with certain
types of fruit.
Right.
Or if you want to make a small
cut, a short blade, a medium and a
long one, you probably won't need too often.
So, you know, a 20 centimeter, eight, nine
inch was fine.
OK, same with pots and pans.
Let's say pans, a small skillet, six inch,
right.
14 centimeter or so for if you're going
to make yourself like some sunny side up
eggs.
Right.
You don't want a big ass pan where
they're going to spread out.
How about a little pan?
So when they do spread out, they take
the shape of the pan.
You get the picture.
Right.
Exactly.
You're going to you're going to grill a
piece of toast or make grilled cheese.
Right.
If you make grilled cheese, by the way,
don't use butter, use mayonnaise on the outside
and grill it with mayonnaise.
And look how that's going to be umami.
I thought like for a while I was
the only person in the world doing it.
Every time I do food talk privately, I
say make grilled cheeses, you use mayonnaise and
I never heard of that.
So you use mayonnaise and they come back
like, man, that was the most delicious.
Right.
OK.
All right.
And, you know, I was blessed with getting
me a small cast iron one like that
pan.
There you go.
I like the Lincoln.
You bet.
The Lincoln.
Yeah.
The heavy duty stainless steel with the aluminum
bottom insert, you know, so it's real thick
on the bottom.
Cast iron is good, too.
Just don't use soap.
No.
Cast iron.
You really have to.
Yeah.
You just water.
You could use some if you've got a
food flavor, you know, sometimes the seasoning in
cast iron will hold the flavor.
Like if you sauteed garlic and you want
to do a pancake, you might get some
garlic flavor in your pancake later.
Put some baking soda on the pan.
That'll draw the flavors out mostly.
All right.
So you're going to it's basically it's obvious
you're going to need a bigger skillet, but
get the small skillet, get the medium skillet,
you know, the same with a pot.
You might want to reheat something in a
one quart pot and then you're going to
want to jump to a four or six
quart.
And that's it.
Unless you've got a family and you're going
to be producing volume, then the sky's the
limit.
Right.
How big you know.
So don't get too much stuff cutting boards.
It's good to have a meat and a
vegetable cutting board if you do meat.
I wanted to get into in the future,
perhaps it gets real sensitive to just talk
about just vegetarian eating.
I've got a lot of stuff, you know,
where someone who's not used to it will
not miss eating meat.
You know, that that type of structure is
not necessarily vegan.
By the way, vegans are serious misanthropists, people
haters, by the way.
If you ever notice that, I'm not saying
that that's the rule, but it could be
the rule that there are exceptions that are
not people haters.
But essentially, when someone is vegan, they let
you know they are.
You know what I mean?
Right.
I think that's a Gustav LeBlanc kind of
thing going.
Yeah, it is.
They don't even know why they're usually I've
told you about vegan.
Usually when it's white people that don't know
how to cook, want to cook and don't
want to learn how to cook.
So when they cook and you say the
food's terrible, they say is vegan.
It's vegan.
Where in reality, vegan is delicious.
It's even more delicious than other any other
style, if you comprehend it.
Right.
So that's all you need, basically.
The other thing is, if you're going to
have a lid, whether it's for a pot
or a pan, make sure it's tight because
there's something called pressure cooking.
You understand as the pressure increases, the boiling
point goes down.
But if you have enough heat to drive
the boiling point up, you can actually boil
water at 270 degrees in a pressure cooker.
Right.
You see, or in other words, you would
have the effect, sorry, at lower, you could
have the effect of, I've got a pressure
cooker up to 270, it gets dangerous.
But what I'm saying is you could boil
at lower than boiling point with a pressure
cooker.
So you save energy and also you cook
faster.
So anyway, you two guys talk amongst yourselves.
I'll be back in about three minutes.
Okay.
You there, Bruce?
I'll be right back.
Yes.
Yep.
Go ahead.
I'm just listening, man.
I do enough talking in the chat, so
I'm just trying to listen.
That's fine.
All are welcome.
That's why he kind of caught me by
surprise in the chat.
And I was like, well, I couldn't think
of any reason why you would have trouble.
Yes.
If anything, we're all, we're all pretty lighthearted
here and very seldom do we, there are
the occasional touchy times, but oh, well, life
goes on.
That's when I just stay quiet.
I don't really hold a grudge.
That's not really who I am.
I mean, I have a moment and I'm
just like, yeah, I would.
So, you know what I mean?
It's nothing.
I just, uh, there's bigger things, you know,
certainly, certainly.
And, uh, we got something in your, uh,
chana masala or sauce for chickpeas.
Hmm.
Actually sounds good.
All this talk about food is making me
hungry.
Okay.
The vacuum and foods, well, there's, there's two
aspects.
When the food is alive, like when you
have a veg up until the point that
you eat it, it's alive.
As a matter of fact, if you eat
a raw salad, you're eating live food and
that energy, that energy that maintains it alive
is now in the body.
You see, most carnivores are called predators.
It's not the, this is what the scientists
will never understand.
And the zookeepers and all that.
It's not that they need meat and protein
is they need that immediate release of life
force.
You see what keeps a whole different spin.
Yeah.
What keeps a predator healthy.
He's not feeding off the meat as much
as he's feeding off of the release of
the life force when the animal is killed.
But the same thing with what you said
with, uh, with vegetables and things and that,
that takes it to a whole different level.
Yeah.
The other thing is when you, if you've
been around predators, they don't eat the meat,
the muscle, uh, for the eat the, the,
the face, the brains and the internal organs
first.
Right.
You can still watch a mutual of Omaha
national geographic when the heinous and the lions
eat an elephant or a gazelle, they, they
got it first.
It's all gutted.
Of course, when there's a frenzy in a
pack, they'll pull a limb off, but you
notice they got the animal first and then
they, because the muscles, uh, if pure muscle
of them is toxic, cause that's where all
the adrenaline goes.
Uh, that would make sense.
Yeah.
If you send adrenaline to the organs, whether
it kills the Oregon, but it goes to
the muscle to provide the, uh, fight or
flight fighter Yeah.
Yeah.
So if you go to certain countries, uh,
if you go to a very ethnic restaurant,
let's say Chinese or so, and the menu
is in that language and they have just
a, a quick English translation.
If it says beef, it'll say muscle, organ,
liver, stomach.
You see most Americans, when you say I'm
going to have beef, they think they don't
think about eating brains or tongue or stomach
or intestine or tripe.
Yeah.
Uh, um, they, they think, they think beef
is just, they don't even know what they're
eating.
It's muscle.
Right.
When you get a steak, that's muscle you
see.
So, uh, here's an interesting eating, eating organ
meat, you know, liver, brain, all that, whatever
would be far more beneficial.
Uh, then, um, that's why in the Hollywood
they want the brains of the zombies, you
know, right.
Go ahead.
What's the question, Joel?
Shoot.
Um, I, I, I noticed the geometry of
plants has, um, more symmetry than would be
say, um, meat, but I noticed that the,
um, carrying mechanism for blood veins, um, oxygen
in, uh, what they call it, uh, trachea
or something like that in the, in the
lungs, there's, um, this geometry that looks like
lightning bolts.
Yeah.
Lichtenberg geometry.
The fluids.
I noticed that that geometry, um, seems to
be more, um, affluent in vegetation with regard
to, I don't know, you look at flowers,
you talk about flowers earlier, we talking about,
um, say like, um, lightning bolts.
It has more of a, yes, it, it,
but it has more of a, um, a
geometry that seems more symmetrical as opposed to
meat that seems to be more asymmetrical.
Wasn't it Dollar, wasn't it Dollar that came
up with that about the golden mean with
different, uh, uh, ancient Greeks did.
Yeah.
All the ancients of wisdom of any ancient
society had known that, uh, plants, animals, and
minerals are different manifestations of the same thing
specifically, just like you can send, uh, you
know, through a wire, you could send data,
you could send voice and electricity, you know,
have you seen the, the data connections where
you just plug it into the wall and
it, and it's a different frequency on top
of the, uh, the AC power lines in
the house, right?
So basically, yeah, you have this incoming field
and it, and field basically, it is, it
is, uh, uh, a two-way street, like,
just like you have a two, uh, uh,
two lane car, you know, one, uh, on
a highway, one car going one way, one
car going the other, as long as they
keep their lane, they're okay, but in, in
fields, they work one overlapping the other, so
one doesn't recognize the other as they pass
right through each other, is basically how fields
work and it's communication or transport from counter
space back and forth.
Let me give you an example.
Um, there are physical things that reflect and
change the nature of these fields, like there's
a book called The Planetary Effects on Plants,
right?
And, uh, if you check that out, like
the dandelion plant is attached to the Mars.
Now, if you guys are familiar with, I
think Mars is in retrograde, if anybody wants
to go outside past 12 a.m. by
the wind-up toy, wherever you are, just
look up slightly to the south, um, in
the sky coming from the east to the
west, you're going to see a red, looks
like a red-orange LED in the sky.
That's how bright it is.
That's Mars.
It's the closest it's been in a long
time.
I think it's the closest it's ever really
been for a long, long time.
Yes, I believe you're right on that one.
Yeah, I saw it the other night.
Yeah, that's, and if you look at it
through a telescope, it's like, it's like a
three-quarter moon is what it looks like,
right?
Yep.
So, uh, yeah, so, um, okay, I knew
this was coming before they announced it because
I noticed the dandelion plants are about shoulder
high right now, if you don't trim the
weeds, let's say, in certain parts.
Well, since when do dandelions get that high
or way above waist height?
They usually don't get more about knee high.
Right, yeah.
You know what I'm talking about?
Okay, so that means, you know, and we
know that, but, well, we know we, it's
been referenced that they're attached to, okay, you
see the connection?
Wasn't there something with, uh, metals too, wasn't
it?
Uh, certain metals?
Crystallization of metals and salts, just the crystallization
process on a micro level, or on a
macro level, because crystallization, like plating, electroplating in
the form of crystallization.
Right.
Uh, and all that, uh, because, you know,
you use salt solutions, um, is retarded during
the dark moon.
It almost, it comes to a stop, by
the way, during an eclipse, which is the
worst.
Oh, very interesting.
Yeah.
Oh, that makes sense.
It's funny that you say eclipse because I
was bored and I started watching, uh, the
heroes, uh, show that, it was a show
that came out of, I think, 2006.
And I heard of it, yeah.
There was this theme of a change in
the DNA of people, certain people during an
eclipse, and I just thought that was interesting.
So?
Because I.
Yeah, but hold on, you know, you could
take the DNA out of your body, you
wouldn't even notice.
That's overrated.
Everything, everything, everything in the, everything is spiral
form in the body.
That's a adenorhinonucleic whatever acid.
That's, that's a byproduct of phosphenes and phosphates
in the cells and the mitochondria.
It, yeah, that's a dummy load.
DNA is a dummy load.
The only people talking about are using DNA
as a legal society.
And not to mention the triple DNA.
Let me try to rephrase.
Yeah, that's the one that's more important.
I'm using DNA just as a reference because
that's what is commonly referred to as the
storage unit for the, um, data for the
algorithms that make up the geometric expressions of
biological life, if that makes sense.
And I'm using this just as a lack
of.
No, it doesn't.
That, that's what they're telling everyone.
They don't even know what they're doing with
it.
Everything is a spiral.
You know, just like you mentioned the patterns
of the vessels and the blood, they look
like this, the lightning bolts.
They really, they do on a, on a
planar, on a planar view.
But if you view them three dimensionally, they're
twisting and spiraling.
You see what I'm saying?
So everything is, uh, that's why Newton's law
first laws are bullshit because he says, if
something moves in a straight line, it'll move
forever unless another force affects it.
I'm like, you know, asshole, when was the
last time you saw anything in the universe
move in a straight line?
It's all bullshit.
So nothing moves.
I want to, I want to just jump
back.
I notice here, uh, odds and dive and
chat would Greek impart a method for preparing
a perfect cup of coffee.
Okay.
And then the other one was about sauce
for chickpeas.
All right.
Which one should we do first?
The coffee or the chickpeas?
All right.
Chick.
We'll do the coffee first.
Okay.
Now coffee is technical because you know, you've
heard of green coffee, which isn't roasted.
And then you've got dark roast and you
got everything in between.
So the first way the coffee is ruined
is by the roast or the first way
coffee becomes really good is by the roast.
Okay.
Now here's the thing.
Have you remember on previous Sonics I talked
about when you cook use inconsistent heat, don't
use this thermostat timer bullshit because it's not
organic.
You see for thousands of years, when you
cooked, you see you let up your coals
or your fire.
And then naturally what happens?
It comes down.
Oh, we got to load it up.
What happens to the contents in the pot?
It cools down and then the heat goes.
And then what happens?
Does the heat come up gradually or does
it really hit it hard?
It hits it hard.
Right?
That's why like in restaurants, by the way,
the best sauces and soups are the ones
they make the day before they fridge it,
then they reheat it the next day.
Right?
That's how you even notice how some leftovers
taste really good, but better than they did
originally.
It's not because they're leftovers.
Let's see what's really going on is because
inconsistent heating.
So why not give your food that leftover
taste?
I know it doesn't sound good, right?
It'd be like a new Swanson's ad right
away when you're cooking it first time around
on the pot by doing inconsistent heat.
So the best coffee roast, which you're not
going to, they don't advertise or talk about
it is inconsistent heat.
And you're going to get that with, you
know, when it's hand done, artisan roasts and
stuff like that.
Right?
Most of the commercial roasted beans are done
by machine automated.
And do you think they have variable heat?
Nope.
Right?
Because the scientist said, this is the best
temperature to get the roast.
So once you establish, you have a good
source, the good source of coffee is the
quality of the ingredients, right?
So once you have a good coffee, if
you're trying to pursue the perfect cup of
coffee, you must grind the beans yourself.
Do not buy pre-ground unless you're going
to buy what's called Illy coffee.
I-L-L-Y is real pricey.
If anybody, are you familiar with Illy coffee?
I-L-L-Y?
No, no.
I've never, never experienced that one.
Yeah.
It's the opposite of vacuum seal.
They do pressure seal because when you vacuum,
you suck the, you suck the flavor out
into the air, the container, right?
When you pressure seal, you're pushing all the
flavor in, but Illy is pretty pricey.
You're looking at, you know, 30 bucks a
pound or more.
Okay.
But unless it's of that quality, it's always
in a metal container.
You're not going to get a good coffee.
We have a couple of good coffees here.
One was just brought to me.
I'm not going to be promoting them too
much.
Did we get this coffee for free?
No.
All right.
Screw them.
I ain't promoting them.
But there's a couple of small, there's a
small, a couple of, if you could discover
a good roast.
Okay.
So that's how you start off with a
good cup of coffee.
The best way to ruin a cup of
coffee is an electric coffee maker.
You know, like a Mr. Coffee or whatever,
Sunbeam or whatever.
That's how you ruin.
Why?
Because the water goes through an aluminum coil.
It's too hot.
It takes too long.
All right.
There's two types of ways to do a
really good coffee.
One is you brew the coffee with just
water and an inert, like a glass.
There's a couple of gravity filters.
I'm not suggesting anything esoteric.
Microfiltration, not using paper.
You know, if you brew a coffee, you
got to brew it as fast as possible.
Try to avoid bringing water more than 220
degrees Fahrenheit or 100 degrees Celsius.
And you want to brew it as fast
as possible.
What I do, I'll tell you what I
do to make a perfect cup of coffee.
Two ways.
I could do a cowboy coffee where I
put, I grind the beans myself.
And when you grind and pulse it, don't
do a consistent grind because the temperature goes
up on the blades.
Right.
You ever notice when you blend or grind
something for too long and the temperature of
the contents, too much friction.
So you pulse it for a few seconds,
you stop.
Right.
That's why like certain good blenders have a
pulse function.
Right.
So what I do if I want a
cowboy coffee, I put the grinds, turn up
the heat.
I also make tea this way, certain teas.
And then I add the water, hot water
to it.
And then I put it into a cone
filter.
Now, I've been using the bleach cone filters.
I used to use the brown, but the
filters add too much flavor.
And if you want to take the flavor
out of a if you have to absolutely
positively make a perfect cone filter coffee with
a paper filter, open up the cone filter
paper in the cone.
Right.
You have a carafe below it.
You spray it, put some hydrogen peroxide in
a spray bottle and spray it, the paper,
and then run it under some water because
the hydrogen peroxide acts like an oxidizer and
it will oxidize any flavor out of the
cone.
So another way to get the flavor out
of the cone paper is to put the
paper in the cone itself and run some
water into through it first, because that initial
run of water will get rid of that
paper flavor.
You see what I'm saying?
Interesting.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
And if you have to use a coffee
machine, go ahead and do the same.
Put the paper.
I shouldn't say if you have to use
a coffee machine, no one should have to.
When you load the paper, you see the
people's load that they load the paper and
then they put the dry coffee beans in
the dry paper and they let the machine
do the rest.
Uh-uh.
Put water in the coffee filter first without
the coffee and that initial water that drains
out takes the paper flavor with it.
Then put your dry ground roast coffee grinds
in there.
You see what I'm saying?
You follow me?
Right.
Okay.
Now you're on your way.
Now that's for the cowboy coffee.
The only difference between that and another way
to make a perfect coffee is put your
grounds in of the paper cone filter that's
been pre-treated with water.
If you really want to go crazy, do
a little hydrogen peroxide and then rinse it.
Uh, what I do is when the water
on the kettle before the kettle whistle blows,
which is I've measured with a thermometer is
just below boiling.
Um, cause the bottom of the kettle of
water is real hot and the top of
the water is not that hot.
Right.
You see what I'm saying?
Okay.
So what I do there is I add
a little bit of lukewarm water while I'm
waiting for the water to come up to
temp into the coffee grinds to pre-temper
them a little bit.
So they don't have dry grounds being hit
with hot water.
You add a little bit of water.
So you have the hot water hitting wet
grind grinds.
You see what I'm saying?
So as I put the hot water in
there, I have a small spoon and I
stir the grinds with the water because what
you'll look up and find out about coffee,
I think 20 or 30% of coffee
is water soluble once it's been roasted.
You see what I'm saying?
Okay.
The stirring gap, the stirring would make sense.
So the stirring, the stirring, when it gets
the most out of the flavor, the motion,
also it allows for a faster pour through
the cone because you don't have the grains
of coffee sticking on the sides, clogging the
filter.
And also you're dissolving the coffee faster.
Now you have to do this with some
finesse because if you grab the paper while
you're stirring or make a hole in it,
you're going to have grinds coming through.
And that's how I make coffee.
I don't like a French press because it
doesn't press out the very fine stuff.
And also what happens, what do you have
sitting on the bottom?
The grinds the whole time, right?
Right.
You want them out of there because there's
each different, just like anything, each different stage
of the brewing process releases different things from
the coffee.
Also, the hotter the temperature of the water,
the shorter the brew.
Just that's why espresso, that's really hot, high
pressure steam.
And that's not designed to have any dwell
time in the coffee.
It's designed to go right through, isn't it?
Very quickly.
Yeah.
Now where something like a cowboy coffee, which
is the grinds in the water in a
pot or percolator, or let's leave the coffee
machines out, or a French press that has
a very high dwell time with the beans,
you see, different flavor.
So the least amount of dwell time would
be an espresso.
I don't suggest that.
And if anyone's had an espresso, you'll understand
that's an acquired taste for most.
But just the cup of coffee, paper filter
that's been pre-rinsed by just running water
through it, especially the warmer the water, the
better the paper flavor.
I hope you guys understand what I mean.
Maybe they don't, maybe they do.
That there's an initial paper flavor, you know?
Yep.
And don't be squeamish.
If you want to know what paper filters
are going to do to your coffee flavor,
put a coffee bean in your mouth, spit
it out, and then take a little piece
of the cone filter, tear a piece off,
put it in your mouth.
Don't say yuck and spit it out because
guess what?
You're going to get that flavor in your
coffee anyway, you see?
So if you put a piece of paper
filter or filter mechanism on your tongue before
you brew, that will let you know what
is going to be imparted to your coffee.
Makes sense.
And I just gave basically the account on
how I do it because I played around
with different gadgets and different things.
And I found that just doing it this
way with a direct filter where it allows
direct cone filter, allows you to make coffee
at any time, anywhere with very little, very
few devices.
As long as you get hot water.
Of course there's other ways, but as long
as you get hot water and a filtering
mechanism, you've got coffee.
Then there's the cold brew where they leave
the coffee overnight or two days in the
fridge or out and then fridge it, then
whatever.
That's fine.
I've never really tried that, experimenting with that.
I tried it once, I wasn't really impressed.
No, no.
It's just something about cold coffee.
It doesn't register right.
Well, also you have an extremely long dwell
time in the coffee bean with the water,
even though it's at low temperature, dwell time
is not negated.
So, now the chickpeas.
Yeah, they are delicious.
They have umami.
What I do, make hummus, also when you
make the hummus with the tahini and the
lemon juice, use a little cumin or powder
in with it, right?
The other thing I do, also if you're
going to pre-soak or even if you
get canned, which pre-soaked dry beans always
taste better, chickpeas have a pretty thick peel
on them.
It's a translucent, almost transparent peel.
Get rid of that, right?
Because that adds a grainy, it has no
nutrition other than fiber.
It adds some character to the chickpea that
I don't find pleasant, let's say.
Whether it's nutritious or not, it's there.
You could have it, let's just say, but
I would suggest getting rid of it.
The way you do that is just move
things around in a bowl and just skim
it off the top, where the peels usually
come to the top.
So, if you're going to do a dry
soak on a chickpea, make sure you run
your hands, keep agitating until the peels start
coming off, and you'll see there's quite a
bit, right?
All right, so once I've peeled the chickpeas,
what I do is I cook them twice.
They soak up a lot of water.
Twice meaning like I'll pre-cook them and
then hours later or let the temperature come
down and then I use them as a
raw ingredient.
What I do is I add potato and
carrot and some onion, some garlic, maybe some
celery.
Learn how to use celery if you want
that umami deliciousness to your food and then
take it out.
And I use a curry that I either
make or pre-buy, which is, you know,
turmeric, cumin, a little bit of cinnamon.
You know, many of the pre-made curry
mixtures are pretty good.
They're mostly turmeric.
There are red and brown curries as well.
So, I make a curry chickpea, potato, carrot,
onion dish.
I put that over long grain rice like
a basmati.
And I want to go back to the
celery.
If you're going to use, if you want
to add a lot of flavor to your
food, no matter what it is, if it's
savory, stock up on celery and just take
a celery stick.
Don't cut it with a knife.
Just break it in half by hand.
Make sure it's clean and put it in
the pot because you're going to remove that.
You're not going to be serving that.
That's just there to add flavor.
Okay, so no matter what you're doing in
the kitchen, if you want to make even
pasta, if you don't have a water bath
for the pasta, throw in a couple of
stalks of celery and remove them.
You're going to see how delicious everything gets.
Celery has a very good function, just like
onions do, to add umami or a lot
of depth of flavor.
You know, very often when we have a
very good crop of green or spring onions,
I would just leave, put the onions whole
in a dish and not serve them.
I remove them.
And the dish is so delicious and whoever
has it doesn't know why because they don't
see the presence of the celery stalk or
the onion.
It's removed, you see.
So it's like an infusion.
So there's another thing with the chickpeas.
Another thing you can do is don't be
afraid to mash the chickpeas and make a
paste by themselves, plain, without making a hummus.
And then you can use a dressing over
the chickpeas as if you would, you know,
make a dressing for anything.
You know, like a quote-unquote salad dressing,
a creamy dairy recipe, you know, what they
call blue cheese or, you know, ranch for
white people, whatever.
You can make a yogurt with cucumber and
garlic dressing for it.
Or you can make, you can just do
a simple vinaigrette.
Just make a chickpea paste, just salt it
a little bit and you can get creative
with that.
But when you make a chickpea paste by
mashing it or ricing it, if you know
what a ricer is, it's basically a press
that has a durable screen with small holes,
right?
That's the best way to make mashed potatoes
and other things.
Potato ricer.
You make yourself a chickpea paste and it
makes a good filling for various things, right?
If you know what I mean, a filling
for whatever.
You can stuff vegetables with it and cook
them again or you can have it cold,
you can have it warm.
You could use it as, for example, if
you go to, I'm not saying in this
directly, but in many Asian countries when they
talk about sweets, it's usually a red bean
filling that's very sweet.
So you could use the chickpea as, you
know, a filling.
Well, what other ways you can do chickpeas?
I guess you can consider it a meat
substitute.
There's something called falafel where you do a
coarse chop or a coarse mash and you
mix it with various, especially high amounts of
cumin and parsley and deep fry it or
bake it.
They look like basically meatballs.
I once, when I was not eating meat
at all, I had a barbecue and it
was all vegetarian stuff.
Skewers, things that look like patties and meatballs,
whatever.
And I had some ghetto types come over
and I knew that they would balk at
it because it's kind of like a culture
there.
And they asked me what kind of meat
that was and I said it was the
boneless kind because if I told them it
was vegetarian they would spit it out, right?
So they all said, oh yeah.
I said, what kind of meat?
What kind of meat did he say it
was?
I said, he said it was boneless.
Oh yeah, it's good.
I was like, okay.
You know what I mean?
I was like, all right.
No, that's fine.
Yeah, because, you know, it's, there's a, you
know, you have to understand the culture.
I think that Jacque Fresco talks about that,
you know, there's a cultural, you know, you
go down to the ghetto, if you don't
have deep-fried chicken wings with hot sauce
and ketchup, you ain't right.
So, and I know that's not the whole
ghetto, but yeah, if you tell them I
got vegetarian, you know, whatever, like, no, I
can't be good.
I don't want to taste it.
So, you know, I went vegetarian for some
time and I did get the looks, the
talks, et cetera.
Right, something wrong with you.
I still eat pork or beef.
I try to keep, even if I do
eat meat, it's turkey, regardless of what the,
anybody else says, it's very little.
But yeah, I feel that folks that eat
a lot of meat tend to be more
animalistic in regards to their approach to things.
It's the culture, not the folks.
Like, for example, Count Dracula, they don't show
him as being animalistic.
He seems very well, very well refined culturally,
socially, you know what I mean?
But he's a blood drinker, you know what
I mean?
I'm just saying from a sci-fi, you
know, metaphor here.
I think it's the culture, the traditions that
they have, right?
And for example, you have traditions in neighborhoods,
even, not even the, it's not even proper
to say culture because that has racial air
to it.
I'm talking about even a neighborhood can have
a culture.
I mean, I'm from back east and someone's,
I'm Brooklyn or I'm Bronx.
I'm like, and that's not even good enough.
You got to say Bushwick, we're part of
Brooklyn.
Now we do things this way here.
And if you don't do it this way,
you ain't no good, you know?
So I'm like, Whoa, you know, so when
I say culture and tradition, it can be
very local.
I got a question.
Anyway, what do you think about honey?
I know I've been told that honey has
some really good health benefits.
I mean, I've, well, it depends on the
individual.
See, the thing is, that's another mistake.
There's no such thing as health benefits because
what's good for one person might harm another
person.
Like, you know, the concept of yin and
yang, right?
Okay.
There is no, there's no such thing as
yin and yang as two separate things.
It's the aspects of a thing.
Is it more yin or is that thing
more yang, you know, or is it imbalance?
That goes with people too.
Yeah.
So you can have someone that has too
much yin, they should not have honey.
Someone who's too yang should have some honey.
You see what I'm saying?
There's a first aid aspect to it in
ancient cultures where they used to call certain
armies immortal because they left them on the
battlefield dead.
And then a year later, they came back
still fighting, right?
Well, because they had certain first aid techniques,
they'd stuff a wound like a guy got
stabbed or had half his gut cut out.
They'd stuff him with silk dipped in honey
until the body started to heal.
And they would push, they would push that
thing out, right?
Because why?
Because you got a big hole in your
side, you don't got to live too long,
but if you stuff it and wrap it
tight, it's like a tire that's leaking or
a garden hose is leaking.
You wrap it with electrical tape, right?
The body will start to close and start
pushing it out, you see?
So, but I'm not, I'm not going to
get into too much of that right now.
We're talking about food, but that was used.
Honey was used.
You know, honey is perfect.
You know, if you drop something inside of
a big jar of honey, that's basically keeping
it encapsulated.
You know, nothing goes in and out of
that.
So, but yeah, there's no such thing as
a health benefit or a health detriment or
whatever, unless it's a known toxin, like, like,
you know, what kills, what I think is
cyanide kills you is not because cyanide is
deadly, but it's deadly to you because once
it gets into the cell, it stops the
phosphate production in the cell, in the mitochondria
immediately.
And once that stops, then all the cells
start dying very quickly.
You see, that's what a poison is.
It's not really a poison.
It just stops a certain critical body function.
It's like cutting the wire.
You ever see when you just want to,
before they break into somebody's house, they just
cut the power lines.
They don't care.
They don't go, there's a, which breaker, which
breaker do we drop to turn off the
lights so they don't see us coming?
No, I just cut the whole power line.
Right.
You see?
So, uh, what, what, what was indiscreet?
So the same thing, is there anything that's,
that's going to be, that you're going to
take that's going to bring you to health?
No, that's why I, all that stuff you
hear through the years, oh, the cannabis.
Oh yeah.
This oil does every, no, that's bullshit.
No, it doesn't for certain people in certain
times and certain things.
Yes.
Done a certain way.
Vitamin C.
Remember a few years ago was the vitamin
C dummy load, right?
Yeah.
And before that it was something else.
Colloidal silver.
No, there's none of that.
And it's all of it for what you
see.
So, I mean, I guess you could say
that every person is vibrating at a particular
rate and that is individualistic and it doesn't,
it's not the standard for everything.
So just because something is good for one
person, that doesn't mean it's going to be
quote, unquote good for the next person just
because.
Well, there are things that are generally good
for everyone, but it's not good for that
person's condition at the time.
Like, like I just cut the finger, the
pinky finger pretty deep.
And, uh, what's good for my condition right
now is some paper towel with some tight
electrical tape.
Feeling me?
Now, if I tell you, put some tight
electrical tape on paper towel on your finger,
you say, what for?
You don't need it.
Well, I, you know what I did?
Um, find interesting that the material, the electrical
tape is, um, I saw that vinyl was
one of the, um, I don't want to
say ingredients, but one of the things that
it was, yeah.
But I thought interesting because, um, that type
of material holds data really well.
But I'm talking about the vacuum.
Let's keep it, let's keep it practical.
Uh, uh, it doesn't have to be electrical
tape.
The reason I keep it around is because
you got it in the car and the
hose starts leaking.
You wrap it real tight.
I'll get you where you're going.
Uh, you know, uh, you know, it's flexible,
it's cheap, easily available.
Vinyl is a fatality plastic, which is an
estrogen mimicker.
Um, you know, it's using PVC pipes.
If you want to destroy any kind of
fluid, you run it through vinyl.
I don't care what it is.
So any kind of fluid you run through
vinyl pipes or whatever, you ruin the quality
of it.
There's a known, known, very well documented.
Um, you know, if I didn't have that,
I do cowboy style.
When somebody was hurt, you saw they use
their teeth to cut off a piece of
their shirt and wrap it real tight.
Remember that person, the old movies, right?
So, yeah, I'm not going to suggest, you
know, the thing is, you know, people spend
at least 20 or 30 bucks a month
on paper towels and paper goods, right?
Um, last thing, you know, how much, how
much do they spend every month on cotton
and shirts?
And so not, not that much, but if
you told them to go and tear up
a cotton shirt or whatever, let's just say
for this as a, no, I'm not going
to do that.
Right.
So the vinyl tape is real cheap, 50
cents a roll or less.
And, uh, you can see, and it's not
only for, it's meant multi-purpose.
Yeah.
So the compromise of if it's flexibility and
ease of application for many, many things, as
well as wrapping electrical wires, by the way,
um, that's like the last thing you do.
I mean, how many times you need to
wrap electrical wires, but you, you should have
electrical tape around for that purpose.
Yep.
Now the band-aid concept is good, but
that's really wimpy.
You look at a band-aid, like you
can't make that tight and it's too local.
And also who's to say that the wound
that you need to dress is the shape
of the tape anyway.
But if you slap a paper towel on
it, that's a full-on bond breaker.
When you pull it off, you have no
stickiness on the skin to open the wound
again.
You see a band-aid as you're pulling
the band-aid off or the, the, those
pre-made bandages, they, they pull on the
skin and you could actually pull the wound
open.
You see, so you want to put a
bond breaker and wrap it tight with a
band-aid.
Yeah.
So, but if you have a full-on
wrap with a bond breaker, like a rag
or paper, and then the electrical tape, when
you remove it, you, you're not disturbing the,
uh, the break in the skin.
Yeah.
Okay.
Very, very good point.
And it works, it works for all kinds
of injuries.
So, uh, what else have we got?
Other, I see, see red, red pepper spread.
Also, you dropped in a chat.
Okay.
Oh, back to the chickpea here.
Um, what, when you make hummus, by the
way, uh, you can make it by hand.
It's a lot of work, or you could
use a food processor.
Blenders are too high speed, but if you
know, know what you're doing, you could use
a blender, but doing it by hand is
good.
But if you, you could put roasted vegetable,
you know, hummus.
Have you ever had hummus?
Either one of you?
I have, yes.
Question.
Okay.
If you have roasted red peppers and you
mash it in there towards the end, you're
going to get this red toned hummus, right?
So it tastes a little bit like red,
but it's a beautiful color.
You know, if you put a dark olives
now, all of those are really hard to
get.
Not the ones in the can or know
that are black, you know, the pitted, those
are not real.
Um, I mean, they are, but they're junk.
I mean, like all of us still have
the pits in them.
If you take the pits out and you
mash up olives, you're going to get this
dark puree purple.
If you put part, a lot of parsley
or something green, like sage or parsley in
what you're going to get a green hummus.
So now you could have, you could create
like the flags, the colors of a flag
of a country on a hummus plate is
basically what I'm saying.
So also changes the flavor, but also remember,
that health comes from variety.
Like there's nothing wrong with a diet of
bread and water.
If it's really good bread and really good
water, what makes it seem like a punishment
is that you have it every day.
You see what I'm saying?
So, so part of health comes with variety
and where, where are you going to get
that with food?
Absolutely positively with seasonal change, right?
That's the other thing about white people.
They try to eat everything all year round
the same, irrespectively.
That's why they're so screwed up physically and
all that.
So you ever notice how their governments don't,
don't tell them how they should eat better.
They, they tell them they should have healthcare.
You got to go to a doc to
get the information.
Yeah, it's crazy.
It's just like, I was telling something about
the military was say he knew somebody who
tried to convince him to get out of
the military.
I say, if, if it takes that much
convincing, let him go.
That's like natural selection, you know?
Tell them that the military, their own leaders
hate their own soldiers.
That's why they're in the business.
That's why they want you not to kill
the enemy to kill you.
They're, they're basically again, misanthropists, all the generals,
they won't say this if you, but if
you get to know people in the military,
that's how the leaders, that's how they are.
They hate their own people.
Now here's the thing, and this is the
proof.
They, they know their own people and they
hate their own people.
That's why they have a military, because if
they knew the enemy, they wouldn't be fighting.
Sun Tzu.
In other words, they win the battle, they'd
win the war and then fight the battle
just for the hell of it, right?
No, no, no rational human being fights battles
to win a war.
That's a stupid ass right there.
You got to win the war before you
start fighting, and if you got to want
to throw down and create some pain and
suffering, then you do the battle.
You see, I tell you, the western world
military leadership, your generals and president, whatever, whatever,
they don't know the enemy at all.
They know you.
That's why they want you in the military.
They want your ass done.
Again, because if they knew the enemy, they
wouldn't have to fight.
So simple.
I mean, this is, this is the state.
So someone wants to get in the military,
I'm like, screw it, let them go.
Natural selection.
Maybe you'll catch a bullet and be better
for everybody else.
Get rid of them.
You shouldn't sterilize them.
Cut their nuts, take their eggs out so
they don't have children.
You know, whatever.
I mean, you want to get real harsh,
and this is the kind of talk you
read if you study the gods, you know.
So anyway, yeah, there's, there's, it's really a
piss-poor situation.
By the way, there's, I think I put
up a while back in a video of
some guy that goes and finds military meals
from 40, 50 years ago and opens them
up, and some of them are still viable.
Yeah.
Classic.
So either way, we didn't get into too
many recipes other than discussion of the, the,
the sadness of white people, food, and living
in a white culture when it comes to
food.
The thing about...
But you did leave things better by, by
bringing in all sorts of different, there's a
couple of them I'm definitely trying out.
Yeah, points of view.
Yeah, not, not getting into too many...
Here's the thing, if you're going to really
learn about cooking, it changes so much based
on season that not necessarily learning about what
to make or how to make it, but
when to make it, you see.
Yes.
So one way to inspire good cooking habits
is say, well, okay, winter's coming, so what
kind of food should be eaten in the
winter?
What kind of food is sourced from cold
latitudes?
Start adjusting.
So examine, what are you eating now?
Are you eating foods that are from warm
latitudes?
Well, you should probably depart from that when
the cold weather comes, because if you don't,
you will, right, actually suffer the cold.
I'd be starting in the fall, myself, early
fall.
Get that, get that transit, because the body
does take time in order to transition in.
Right, three weeks, really three days.
Easily.
It goes on like three days, seven days,
and then three weeks you're in.
I mean, even people that go from the
lower, lower 48, they call it up to
Alaska, they call it the lower 48 when
you're up there, down here.
Before they go work for the oil companies,
they give you like a little cut sheet,
like a bunch of xerox-copied photocopies or
emails about how to prepare weeks before you
go up there.
They, you know, they start increasing your fat
intake, you know.
I actually saw one, it was kind of
ridiculous.
They told them go to get a tub
of Cool Whip and add a quarter cup
of corn oil to it, stir it up,
and eat that every day.
Whoa.
Yeah, I mean, that's like white people food
again.
Cool Whip's not even, it's not very, you
know, sad, you know.
They don't say anything about eat some high
quality arctic fish.
They don't say that because, again, because they
hate you, you know.
They're the real haters, you know.
It's just, he was asking about psychedelics, man.
It's amazing what you see going on.
It's completely satanic and demonic, straight up.
And after a while, you can't even feel
sorry for their children.
But I do feel sorry for the children
because it's like, damn, these parents are totally
incapable of doing anything good for their children
other than providing the most basic needs.
But they're really, but then what I, the
reason why I said what I did, you
can't even feel sorry for the children after
a while because they're going to grow up
to be scumbags just like the parents.
So they're just mini scumbags right now because
there's no way they're not going to be
like that because who's going to take them
away and rear them, you see?
Put the plug in for idiocracy.
Yeah, if you're an idiocracy, you look at
the children and feel bad for you.
How can you feel bad?
In 10 years, they're going to be just
like these other ones, you know.
So it's like, oh, the whole thing is
screwed.
All right, what else we got?
Yeah, rice pudding is a poor man's dessert.
Yeah, a rice pudding, make sure that you
get yourself some cardamom pods.
Put some, you don't need a lot.
You could get a couple ounces of cardamom
pods or cardamom powder.
Have you ever played around or cooked with
cardamom?
No, but no.
Extremely fragrant.
I'm going to peak my curiosity with that.
Cardamom, pine oil, orange oil, you can make
a man's aftershave, you know, like a man's
cologne out of that, you know.
Yeah, cardamom is an ingredient used for many
years in many things.
It's very, but anyway, a really good rice
pudding will always have some cardamom, you know,
like a mulled cider or a nutmeg.
I mean, a, you know, eggnog, any of
those things, if you add some cardamom to
it, it really makes the flavors explode.
That's another white people thing, eggnog.
So, all right, so anyway, yeah, learn about
cardamom, C-A-R-D-A-M-U
-M, I think, cardamom.
I believe so, yes.
Yeah, learn how to work with that, either
powder or pods.
If you crush the pods, they look like
pistachio nuts, very soft.
You crush the little black seeds in there.
If you're never familiar with cardamom, you might
be, just get some open, you'll be amazed
at the fragrance.
That's really good with rice pudding.
And the thing about rice pudding, it's really,
again, hard in a Western culture, is have
you ever had rice pudding with real whole
milk?
Because the milk that they've, and especially in
the U.S., it's not, you're not allowed
to have whole milk, you know, because it's
too nutritious, you know.
Again, they, your own government hates you.
Why?
Because look at what they're doing to your
food.
If your own government was supporting you, they
would make it mandatory for everyone to have
weapons and weapons training to protect yourself, right?
It's just insane.
They're poisoning you, they took your money away,
they put religions that are based on demonology
in front of you.
I mean, it's just insane.
So again, talk about an acid trip, and
everyone's just sitting around, and they're patriotic about
it, too.
To a piece of cloth.
No, to the whole concept.
Well, yeah, and that too, you know.
Really sad.
All right, so what else on the food?
Let's see.
You went to Gammon on many things here.
I know I'll be listening to this again.
Well, let's, are there any questions in chat
or anywhere else?
We are out of questions in chat, and
it's pretty much just staying.
And again, just to end off with the
beginning, the conclusion should tie up.
Started off talking about Western countries, the white
culture, white people, food, all that stuff, how
difficult it is, and the reason I brought
it up, I wasn't anticipating on speaking on
that too much, but one has to, because
three quarters of the battle, you know, unless
I'm going out to the backyard and picking
stuff that I'm growing, which is growing beautifully
all on its own, didn't plant anything this
year, but when three quarters of the battle
of going out and acquiring food ingredients and
other things is countering the white people culture
when it comes to food.
You know, the prepackaged, lack of freshness, lack
of quality, lack of variety, you know, it's
like I've got to sometimes go out of
my way to find an Asian or European
market, right?
So, yeah, so I find that if I
were in a different culture, it would be,
I would just go to, I probably wouldn't
be cooking as much.
I would just go to the nearest food
vendor, street vendor, and get excellent food, you
know, in most cases.
Right.
So, and if anyone's lived near a Chinatown
or a Russia town or whatever, you know,
any other culture, you'll notice that the food
is quite palatable and delicious, right?
Well, I think you did a beautiful job
on this one, Greg.
Lots of information to go through.
A lot of things I'll be trying.
Yeah.
Oh, good.
Definitely.
And I'll report back.
I don't know which would work for you,
but try it out.
Oh, we'll figure it out.
Yeah.
Especially the idea of the diffuser, which I
think is going to be a good dish.
Yeah.
Mandatory for thin pots and pans.
Well, then the fact I have, I cook
with flame, so that is definitely going to
be an asset.
And for electrics, for anyone really that has
thin, it's, yeah, the best tasting food always
comes from wood fire or coal fire.
Second would be gas fired and then oil
fired, you know, because there are actually some
bakeries that still use oil fired.
The really old ones, they haven't upgraded.
They've upgraded them to gas, but it basically
has a turbine and they have a big
oil tank out back, petroleum, and it shoots
it into the turbine at high speed and
high pressure.
So it burns cleanly.
So the bread or whatever they're baking doesn't
taste like the tailpipe of a car, right?
Have you seen the old oil fired bakeries?
There's not too many around anymore.
No.
And then there would be electric.
Yeah.
And then electric would be at the bottom
for cooking.
And you can taste that.
The scientists are total idiots, of course, otherwise
they wouldn't be there.
They'll tell you heat is heat and it's
not.
You can, you know, cook the same ingredient,
take a potato, cut it into three pieces,
cook one of it over electric, in water,
one over electric, in water, one over gas,
and one over coal.
It'll taste completely different.
All right, I've got, there's no emails.
Do you ever bake bread or just flatbreads?
Oh, yeah, mostly.
Well, I made a pizza the other day,
which is the same bread dough.
Basically, I made a yeasted bread.
I use a quick yeast.
Yeah.
But no, I haven't done that in a
long time.
Flatbreads would be the way to go because
you don't, you're not concerned about the complexity
of introducing yeast into the body.
You know what I mean?
Yeast is, fungus is a complex creature.
I would say flatbreads are the most digestible,
the easiest, and the most economical because they
require the least amount of heat.
You know, you're going to use a penny,
two cents worth of heat to make a
bunch of flatbreads and you probably use 50
cents to make a loaf of bread of
energy.
So they're very frugal in terms of energy.
Let's say you're camping and you had to
make a yeasted bread.
You'd need a lot of wood.
You'd struggle.
Yeah.
Where if you had to make flatbread, well,
will it burn for 30 seconds?
Right.
Done.
Yeah.
And non-brominated flour would be another asset,
I would believe.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Fortunately, here we have, there's a place, we
have bread that they grow the wheat just
outside of town.
I remember you saying that.
Yeah.
And they mill the flour.
It's like, it's like the brown, when you
eat that bread, it's called barrio bakery.
When you eat that bread, it gives you
the euphoric feeling as soon as you bite
into it.
Wow.
Yeah.
Like spring water when you have good spring
water.
That's like that.
And at one time, all foods were like
that.
No matter what you ate.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Again, that's the harp on white people again.
But I've traveled through places in the country
and stayed with white people and I felt
sick.
And I was I knew I was cringing
at what they ate.
But then I realized that I feel sick,
dull, light, you know, lackluster feeling low energy
is because of what they were eating.
And then once I got back out of
traveling and even just making beans and rice
on the back of the van, I felt
better.
So even elaborate meals, I just it was
just a very bad experience in the American
culture.
And if you are listening to this, and
you have an American cultural upbringing or practices
currently abandon them as soon as possible, especially
before your next meal.
Start learning how to prepare food, simple food,
quality food.
And yeah, give up all that white people
food or sad.
And make that transition rather gentle on yourselves,
because it's going to be some adjustment to
it.
Oh, yeah.
Well, the body what happens is people call
it detoxification, which is not true.
There could be intestinal lining like plaque, you
know, someone would get plaque building up on
their teeth, you can have plaque building up
on the intestinal wall, right like below the
duodenum or the duodenum stomach, small intestine, not
so much large in the colon, mostly large
intestine.
That's, that's what you would detoxify.
But there is no such thing as detoxification,
like the, the new agers are trying to
tell you, right?
What's happening is your body has tuned in,
literally tuned in to the frequencies and the
field effects and the inductive effects of digesting
crap food of inducing energy from it.
And once you change it, the everything the
frequency changes, you know, like, for example, on
a, you know, when you let's say have
a good turntable and a tone arm and
a cartridge and you play a crappy recording,
right?
And then you play a good recording, they
sound very different, right?
Recording quality.
And yeah, so basically, that will be noticeable.
Yes, you'll suffer, you will suffer either, like
extremely, it'll slow down your bowel movements to
the point where you're uncomfortable, or it'll speed
up your bowel movements to the point where
you're uncomfortable, your body doesn't know what to
do, right?
So depending on the kind of food you're
eating, staying regular is good.
Yeah, don't want to be full of brown
25.
No, no.
Yeah, lemonade.
Here's another thing I want to introduce what
I do here see the living in the
southwest.
citrus season is in the middle of the
winter for the rest of the place, right?
So what everyone maybe where you are Bruce
is like high in snow, and Arctic temperatures.
I'm picking limes, lemons, grapefruit, oranges, right?
Or just outside, right?
Thinking that it's like, or, okay, so what
I do there for a lemonade, I take
the whole lemon, I cut it in half
or quarters, I put it all in a
blender, I try to trim off some of
the ends if they're rough or thick.
And I put in the blender, the entire
lemon seeds, everything just to make sure I
wash the outside real good.
If you're going to buy a lemon, or
citrus and do this with the make a
lemonade, let's say, make sure you scrub all
the wax off.
Because citrus, they wax it so look shiny,
right?
Or it's an edible wax.
But you know, I usually do borax water.
If you have non scented dish soap, scrub
it real well.
And you put the whole blender, the whole
lemon in the blender, you could do half
a lemon, depending the 26 to 32 ounces
of lemonade, this will make throw some ice
cubes in there.
And I throw some mineral tablets, you know,
like mineral supplements.
Right?
And some honey and some sugar, and a
cardamom pod.
And I blend it all together.
And and then when I when it's all
blended, it's not too thick, not too thin.
I pour it through a screen, a sieve,
you know, like, I'd say it's about a
3035 mesh, meaning 3030 holes per inch, right,
you can even be coarser, like a 20
sieve, you know, the little screens that are
in your faucet are 4036.
Okay, that's too fine, it'll clog.
But you know, I have a I have
a, I think this is a more of
a 20 mesh.
So I filter it over some ice.
And when you when you hold it up
to the light, it looks yellow.
Because it gets the color just like you
would had a commercial lemonade, you'd add yellow
color to it, right?
Right, right.
But it's translucent.
And when you do lime, it turns green.
It's beautiful.
It's all natural, right?
Well, but it's filtered out.
Now, the reason I put the mineral supplement
in there is to buffer the acid.
Okay, you know, and the reason you filter
it is to get all the stuff out
even like if you do a banana orange
drink or strawberry, orange banana in the blender,
use a filter, run it through a sieve,
a screen filter, get all the little seeds
and stuff.
If you put a banana in the blender,
it's got lots but has got hundreds of
seeds in it.
Oh, yeah.
And it changes the taste and it changes
the flavor.
You know, I wanted to once open a
smoothie shop will blow away all the other
ones because I would buffer each drink meaning
add some mineral supplement to it.
You know what I mean by buffer because
whenever you blend fruit, it's very acidic.
And the last thing you want to do
is pour cold acidic liquid into the body,
right?
It's going to be uncomfortable.
So you buffer it, buffer the acid with
a mineral tablet.
And then you filter all the little seeds.
And so I always make fun of when
I go out and see these smoothie places
and these fresh fruit drink places said, Do
you guys buffer your drinks and filter them?
And they kind of give me this real
dumb look like I don't know what you're
talking about.
Like, wow, I would open a smoothie or,
you know, a juicing place and it would
be by appointment only you text what you
want, and you pay for it online, then
you come and get it.
You're right.
And it would be seven to $8 a
drink and up up to 20.
Because I would use, you know, really high
quality stuff.
And you would have that drink and you
would remember for the rest of your life.
Like I do pickled lime, pickled lemon, various
fruit combinations, all buffered, all filtered.
So, and I've even done experiments where you
do smooth fruits in the blender, and you
have someone taste it.
Okay, how does that taste?
Okay, then I filter it once as it
tastes completely changed the flavor, then I filter
it again, a finer screen changed it again.
See, this goes back to the cut, how
the cut changes the flavor, bite into a
carrot, it tastes different than if you thinly
slice the carrot, same carrot, and it tastes
different than if you graded it, you could
try this experiment at home.
Make a thin slice of a carrot, grate
some carrot, and then just take a bite
out of a carrot.
Sample each different cut, tastes completely different.
Still carrot, but the flavor is very different.
And it's not, it's not like intensity where,
you know, when you have a hot bowl
of chili with some chopped white onion, it's
delicious, right?
Without the white onion, it's not as good.
Okay, then bite a white onion.
That's not what I'm talking about.
That's not, even though there is a difference,
because when you're biting into an onion, that's
an extreme concentration of just onion.
Well, when it's finely chopped over a hot
bowl of chili, it's delicious.
It makes the chili delicious, makes the onion
delicious, right?
Right.
But there is a point between where the
cut of the onion makes the difference.
You know, how many times have you heard
like, well, I want some onion but thinly
sliced, right?
It tastes different than when it's coarse.
And it's not, it's not as much to
do with how much onion there is in
quantity, it's the geometric form that it has.
So these are the fine points.
And I discussed these, I've done, I used
to do more Skype calls about food and
all this stuff and run people through all
this stuff in private.
But when you do a public call like
this, I know as a rule, almost no
one that's listening to me has a proper
pot or pan.
I know as a rule, that almost no
one listening has a proper knife and a
cutting board or knows how to sharpen a
knife.
As a rule, there are, there might be
some exceptions, you see.
So that's why I just wanted to stress
those major points and maybe bring up a
few others.
Well, we had 15 people out there listening
tonight.
And okay, three times more than we comprehend
it.
Yeah.
So hopefully you took something home with them.
And yes, I know I'm going to be
doing some experimenting.
You've tantalized my imagination.
So that's perfectly done.
Yeah, even though these Thank you.
Even though these are several hours long, they're
very surface based and redundant.
There's so much more that can be done.
But I think basically, looking at where responses
are gotten.
Also, you have to consider that anytime you
go in public, you're going to be a
moron magnet.
When you're saying things that are different, and
most people are not going to react or
do anything that that it matters.
But I know that there's no reason at
this stage in reality to go into detail
about anything anymore.
Because just the general consensus of humanity is
so piss poor.
It's not a matter of tossing pearls to
swine.
It's just a matter of just tossing it
away and nothing is ever going to come
out of it anyway.
So if you did get something out of
it, and you can use it and you
are, let's say, the diligent type more up
more to you, you know, it'll help.
But if there's more specifics that are needed
or ever required, I do private calls.
And you could reach out through the email
and all that.
Excellent.
Perfectly done.
And I want to thank our caller Joe
who's been diligently listening and hopefully he's taking
something home with him on this.
Don't know if he put his phone down
or not.
That's fine.
Oh, well.
So any other comments or anything?
Let's see.
Because we we do burn up a lot
of the bytes we keep a lot of
time on.
I've been getting pretty good at keeping it
crunched down.
And even a lengthy chat between us is
coming out rather reasonable for downloading good quality
yet.
So I've been getting better at that.
Spelling on what you got here.
Banami cleaner.
Banami.
Yeah, I'm going to drop a an image
in it right now.
I'm going to open.
I'm surprised.
I've always I've had this the entire life.
I think places even like Walmart sell it.
I'm going to drop in what it is.
And it you once you see it.
Well, it was instant, right?
And talk about what happened to speed of
light type stuff, right?
Yeah.
Probably saw the image a second.
You heard the keyboard.
Yeah, there you go.
Does that look familiar to anyone?
It does.
You know, and I've walked by it probably
many, many times.
Never considered.
I don't have any chicks.
What's up with that?
Oh, my.
Yeah, it's it's it's basically Falspar, which is
a mineral.
F.A.L. S.P.A.R. in
an industry would have come across that term
or chemistry, organic or organic.
And and it uses some base alkaline surfactants
and Falspar.
That's all it is.
You could brush your teeth with it.
It will swell up your lip because it's
very alkaline pH wise.
It's up there over 10, 11.
It will get anything clean.
It works both against acidic and alkaline things,
you know.
Yep.
Bon Amey.
It's very, very good.
Cleaning counter.
Anything that I want a little extra oomph.
Avoid the chlorinated.
Most of the powder detergents scratch and they
have chlorine in them.
And yeah, Bon Amey is the way to
go.
And I forgot what the initial reason I
brought it up.
I was using it as a polish, as
a sharpening compound.
Sharpening.
Yes.
And it should be wet when you're sharpening.
Always never dry unless you're in a pinch.
And the reason why you don't do dry
is because dry doesn't shed the particles.
It'll clog up whatever your abrasive or pad
or your stone is, right?
Okay.
If you're sharpening, if you've ever done any
kind of sharpening with metal, it's always wet,
even in industry.
If you don't, you'll see a metallic glaze
on the stone and then it's metal on
metal.
So also, I mean, there's many reasons, but
again, I didn't get into too many recipes
or methods or because I wanted to stress
what to do with the tools that you
have.
Even Fresco talks about it.
You can't be telling people do this or
don't do that without them having the tools
to do it or not do it.
And again, I'm not gonna cheat anyone by
telling them they'll figure out how to cook
things well if I know they don't have
a sharp knife, if I know they don't
have a proper pot.
And if they don't have those things, what
to do about it without going out and
getting more, you know, because you may not
have the wherewithal, you might not have the
inclination, and you know, it might just be
wasteful to get more stuff.
So just use what you've got.
You never know when you'll find at a
yard sale and just going through thrift stores.
Yeah, thrift shops, amazing.
Yeah, and if it's metal, even if you
scour it, and that makes it, renders underwater,
you know, in water and that makes it
clean, right?
It'll make it clean.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
So there's your bonnet, and that's pretty much
it.
Well, I want to thank you as always.
This has been quite the enlightening night.
Okay, good.
I definitely appreciate your time, and I'm sure
everybody out here certainly does also.
And a lot to think over on this.
Okay.
I'm hungry.
Oh yeah, well make yourself a potato or
some rice.
Yeah, also one more thing before I go.
I spoke about the yeasted bread and the
flatbread.
There's something called fungus that develops on food.
It's called mold and various other things, spoilage,
right?
Mm-hmm.
And certain cultures and even people that want
to go on what's called a healing or
health diet, if you could pass something over
the fire quickly, that gets rid of those
little micro spores and all that.
Like for example, when I especially do a
food discussion with people, let's say you get
up in the middle of the night and
you want to have some cheese and crackers,
right?
Because you just got an urge to eat
something.
You'll sleep better if you do, let's say.
So you take the crackers out of the
package and they're wrapped in plastic, they're anaerobic
and all that.
There's actually spores of fungus on the crackers.
You can't see them, but they're there.
But if you threw the crackers on a
tray, if you have a toaster oven or
a grill type thing, and you just put
over the flame just for a second, just
pass a cracker through the flame on both
sides, just for a second, just pass it
through, that flame is intense enough to destroy
that little micro fungus that's sitting on the
cracker, right?
We're not talking any dwell time at all
here.
We're just talking about just a quick passing
through.
So if you have a toaster oven, what
you do is you fire it up till
the elements are red, then turn it off,
and then throw the crackers in there on
a tray and turn them over, or just
for a second or two.
That intense infrared is enough to destroy or
to render out that fungus.
And it's there.
It's on everything, right?
You'll see seaweed, what's called nori in sushi
shops, the really good ones, they pass it
over fire.
It's called toasting.
You just do it for a quick second.
It takes the mold off, right?
That's why toasting bread always settles with you
better, a piece of toast than just a
piece of bread.
You ever notice?
Yeah.
I wouldn't say it's why directly, but the
body will, right?
So if you want to get into a
more cleaner regimen and reducing the fungus intake,
now I'm not saying that, you know, if
you're going to have cheese and crackers, it
sounds like an oxymoron because cheese is all
about fungus, right?
Not really, it's different.
The kind of fungus that lives on dry
things like bread, crackers, biscuits, cookies, pastry, dry
things, it's more beneficial to, you know, have
it fungus-free.
Let's just say that.
You see?
Yeah.
And also if you've had crackers opened and
you put them away, they get a little
stale after being opened.
You ever notice?
Stale bread makes the best toast also, right?
Right.
That gets rid of that staleness in grain
products.
Another way to enrich flavor, like if you
enrich the flavor of grains, if you want
to change, let's say you make oatmeal, even
if it's rolled oats, and you want to
change it up and get a little more
flavor out of it, dry roast the oats
before you cook them the way you cook
them with water in the pan just for
a minute.
You get that really, you know what I
mean by dry roasting?
You're going to get that wonderful and then
go ahead and make your oatmeal.
And it'll be like there's a volume knob
on the bowl for oatmeal flavor and you've
just turned the volume up.
You see?
Interesting.
The same with rice.
If you just roast it, I'm not talking
about changing color.
I'm just talking about, just so you get
that aroma, even with rice.
You want to change the flavor of rice,
put it over a warm saucepan dry, turn
up the heat until you smell that intense
rice flavor, and then get it out of
the pan.
And then go ahead and soak it and
rinse it and all that, and you'll see.
Oh, I'm getting that.
Imagine a volume knob of rice flavor turned
up slightly.
All things, even cereals.
You know how people have breakfast cereals with
cold milk?
You ever try it with warm milk?
Even in the summer.
Changes the flavor completely.
How about if you have a favorite cereal,
like I like a maple nut crunch.
It looks like these big clusters.
They look like granola chopped up.
Sure.
Yeah.
Do that with warm milk.
Pour warm milk or hot milk over some
breakfast cereal.
Watch what happens.
Completely different experience.
So now it's like having a hot cereal,
but instead of, when you say hot cereal,
it's like a oatmeal, but now you've got
30 varieties of hot cereal you can have.
Especially if you have the breakfast cereal that
has the dehydrated fruit.
You know what happens to dehydrated fruit when
it hits warm milk?
Completely changes.
It's like eating, yeah.
So try all these different, so yeah.
Well, thank you.
Simple.
Yeah.
You already got everything that you need to
do that.
Very, very interesting.
And it's variety.
If you, let's say, have a bowl of
cereal with cold milk and then have another
day with warm milk, it's a completely different
experience.
So there's your variety again.
Yeah.
You see what I mean?
Opens up a whole different can of worms
there.
Wow.
And you don't want it, yeah, no cans
of worms.
Correct.
All right.
Okay.
Well, thanks everyone, I guess.
Yes.
And thank you, Greg.
See you next week.
Very, very well done.
Okay.
You take care.
You have a good night now.
Thanks everyone.
Bye.
Bye-bye.