And good evening there folks and we're live
with the Greek and how you doing tonight
Greek Hey, well, I'm doing maybe we'll be
doing Good good another week.
Yeah another sonic.
Yeah, it's uh, we have somebody that wants
to call has been trying and I told
him hold off and It's another week not
much to report on other than the usual
mess on this planet The orderly mess there's
a lot to do Always if you know
what you're doing Even if you don't know
what you're doing, it seems like the people
that don't know what they're doing are doing
the most so Yeah, we were talking a
little bit about the weather and yeah, there's
still somebody putting a strong influence on the
equator a diagonal and the the storms keep
Rebounding Downstream and that's something that whoever is
doing that has to do something about it
and have them a little more focused is
all I'm going to say so let's see,
let's just start off with someone who wants
to come in and I'll just bring them
in right now Let's see how that works,
let's see I should be able to do
this.
Let's see.
There we go And we're We're just standing
by so I'm Bruce you're doing well sure
and here we go.
He's on greetings Greetings, how's it going?
Okay, it's going it's going even more with
you here.
So what's on your mind greetings?
Oh, we got a lot going a lot
going on.
Let's see.
I guess we'll start by last time.
I just reported back Talking about the guy
at the water store and he was like
he was using a filtration process process.
He's using silica and magnesium But he's not
filtering it, right?
He's doing everything wrong And then the only
reason why I brought it up was kind
of the guy was kind of taking me
off because you know he's making all this
money off of credits Selling water and people
look at him like he's some type of
guru.
That's perfect.
That's what people are inherently stupid and They
resonate with stupidity.
So if you don't give them something that's
stupid, they don't resonate with it You know,
you've heard them say well, it doesn't resonate
with me, right?
You know, it's dissonant but but nonetheless we
can get into a couple of questions about
it One thing is like when he's using
magnesium and silica, there's various types of that
Like I'm sure it's not magnesium as such
elemental.
I'm sure it's an oxide It probably looks
like a white pellet or a white powder,
right?
Yeah, yeah, all right, so it's an oxide
it's inert that has a catalytic property Actually,
I migrated too far without the base unit
But then the silica, you know, it goes
all the way from various Forms of silica
all the way to a silica gel, which
is those desiccant packs you see, you know
Mm-hmm.
So again, you know, I would give the
guy a headache or anyone should give him
a headache if he's doing something like that
But anything you do to water is it's
like a form of art, right?
It's your way of doing it So does
he have a right to do it by
all means, right?
Is are you ending up with a high
quality water?
I could tell you not really is it
better than Or different than most waters.
It'll be dead If you Mark you're popping
in and out there Greek.
Oh I I shouldn't be how about now?
Actually, I'm gonna mute for a moment and
just make an adjustment.
I'll be right back Okay Hey, it's going
good, how's yourself?
You're doing well Yeah, beautiful day out here
Thank you for all your your hard work
out here putting the servers keeping the momentum
going.
Oh, it's my lover My pleasure.
How's the Tai Chi?
Going well every morning every night Sounds good.
It sounds good.
What else what else is new out there?
Oh, let's see.
I've Just went to my grandson's concert last
night he plays the viola and Informs me
that he has mastered the device and wants
to move on to something bigger So I'm
gonna invite him over to grandpa's house this
weekend and we're gonna sit back and jam
and take that myth away from him You're
gonna prove to him that he's not a
master I heard I don't know if this
is true or not But the law of
mastery you have to do something for 10
,000 hours to be considered a master not
anymore No, I think the 10,000 hours
thing was just to keep people discouraged about
it Yeah, I mean there's people that haven't
been alive for 10,000 hours that have
mastered things, you know, I mean I would
suggest You've heard of the term like people
that are normal or well adjusted if society's
really fucked up You have to be pretty
fucked up to be normal or well adjusted,
right?
So Yeah, but anyhow we started off like
gangbusters out of the door about the water
And I just wanted to suggest that there
are still people discovering Greek speak and Applying
it.
I just got an email today about someone
applying What I discussed about the water the
basic principles and they've noticed a tremendous Quality
and change and all that and I just
want to put out a rhetorical statement slash
question If there's just a small handful of
basic principles regarding anything whether it's water food
Economics spirituality, you know me religions and the
mind and all that there.
I think I've covered them In terms of
basic form and I just well I've said
this before anyone has license to take this
stuff and and develop it write a book
Do a website or and and no one
has by the way, so that's why I
constantly that I know about Who's that audio
boy?
He was in the process.
I think he's still he's trying.
Yeah, he's trying You know, but you know,
but still to develop Just the the locusts,
you know The center point of the principle
of all the things that have been covered
through Greek speak not because it's my stuff.
It's just stuff and you know Right, but
the thing is it goes back to the
reference I'm just visiting this planet taking notes
and so far the report is very bad
very poor right so so in essence If
anyone wants to pick up and develop it,
you know But again, you know what I
mean by I'm implying it's you know on
a media form But on the non-media
form, I think there's a lot of people
that have it is they're using it quote
-unquote in their personal lives You know Yes,
well, I can get more done.
I'm not really big on the media.
I mean But I can get more Voice
heard more with people and stuff So this
is one of the reasons why I'm calling
in I feel like you know the information
the groin the reason the Greek speeches, you
know, you cover every subject and it's awesome
It's great.
There's no place else like this online No,
or offline, you know Well offline would be
like a very old a really good university
library Not to be confused with what they
teach in the university or their textbooks You
know, this is like all archived, you know
Annals of things that can be done by
humans that are not But you said you
could what you could do it more directly
with people in in person, right?
Yeah, so, you know Listening to you and
I just take up an art school when
I took up an art school or a
Martial art or discipline and I had an
injury.
So I didn't want to do full-life
jiu-jitsu or Any combat really so I
was like, oh, it's just do yoga Flexible
did it was doing it started teaching it
Trying saying Greek speak and everyone's just loving
it, right?
So now there's this holy yoga thing coming
out and then they asked me To talk
about the holy the holy yoga and if
I can be the class and I was
like, oh my gosh Well, this is all
mmm.
I mean, it's gonna be all Christians in
there and everything So-called Christians.
Yeah, but there's a way that I can
I think I can Kind of maybe do
it, but I'm gonna have to say like,
you know, tell them like hey I'm not
trying to be a guru or a priest
or anything like that I mean I just
want to tell you guys if you guys
are gonna go look at the scripture and
everything Like what to be done and I
might just I don't know, but I don't
know what I'm really gonna say I'm kind
of just avoid it, you know Here's the
here's a simple thing If you know you're
gonna be thrown in or saturated with a
certain group thing because you know There's really
no such thing as a Christian Christianity is
what someone thinks or does not what they
are and So it's based on how they
think and they do so what your class
is what you're imparting is how people can
think or do also right yoga is First
a state of mind and then the actual
movement, right?
And if you know any of the yoga
master teachings, you know, they have this very
little on them But basically the cardinal principle
of the yoga mastership teaching was do it
in it.
So it's comfortable, right?
You don't want to strain yourself.
I always hear about people recently someone in
the yoga class and They they started turning
red and they couldn't breathe in the posture,
right?
That's against that's against The core principle which
is to do it comfortably, right?
I have what that's what I've learned about
it I don't know what it's morphed into
or you're actually, you know Imparting but this
is what my I've gotten from the master,
you know writings about yoga.
So No, yeah, you always want to do
it comfortably.
This is this is hot yoga and Yeah,
I don't know there's a lot of weird
stuff go well the hot yoga yeah Berkram
or something is it like that?
Yeah Yeah, yeah He's like that whole me
too movement thing.
We got caught in but not so they
all like his name, but this is a
Kind of a hybrid of Bikram and of
the nausea flow, but I did it to
my own music And it's like that's fast
-paced and then that's also a body school.
So like you do have the weights in
and then Body conditioning or body school.
Yeah, cuz it I Don't know stretching is
so overlooked in modern athletics and no one
stretches anymore So, you know you get all
these big half of all players come in
and they can even get their biceps to
their to their ears And it's just yeah,
it's just kind of You know just stretching
that's what I like to think of it
just, you know breath to movement and stretching
Mm-hmm Yeah, so I don't know I'm
trying to board that class or I don't
know what's gonna go on with that but
I Don't know.
Yeah Talk to me objectively Yeah, if you're
interested in any ladies in the class Make
sure they do goddess pose and happy baby
to keep them limber in the midsection but
anyway No, it's it's an interesting thing but
back again to the Christians It's their mindset
there in here's one thing.
I define anybody that is religious even if
you go to the Orthodox side of Where
you know, they're even more rigid It's the
same whether they're liberal or Orthodox.
They're ignorant Right because there's no way humanly
possible And I mean humanly meaning you can
see you can hear you can smell you
can read you can study You can you
know take in information and do comparative analysis
on things, right?
Like two people telling you two different stories
only one can be true or both are
wrong, right?
Yeah, there's no one in any religion on
the planet anywhere and any level that can
say that they belong to any organized religion
and not be ignorant You get it because
if you pick any religion Anything, you know,
there's thousands of them and I'll show you
anyone even that it's what they believe is
false just by going to what the the
writ Says about what they should be doing.
It doesn't matter whether it's east-west north
-south religion.
It doesn't matter So So right away when
you have the brand of religion come in
regardless of its Christian Jew Muslim, whatever Mormon
anything, by the way, you know, you've heard
me say the Muslims are the Mormons of
the Middle East, right?
Yeah, Mormon isn't just stupid.
Yeah, so Anything anyone you know, here's the
thing, you know how they say science is
a religion, right?
Same thing you can go and look at
if you're an electrical engineer or a physicist
You go look at like the granddaddies or
the gods of that field of people who
started it and everything that they're telling People
that's in their textbooks now or in university
class is contrary to how the field was
originated, right?
Like there's you know, like electricity is no
electron or anything like that, right?
So so this is a condition.
So when you again when you're dealing with
the Christians, it's a human condition thing It
it would to when you said you you
had the Christians coming and you don't know
what to do to me It's the same
thing saying hey, I'm teaching yoga And I
have a bunch of physicists coming and I
don't know what to do because they're idiots
No, the you know to say you're a
physicist is Embarrassing if you study what physics
is about, you know, yeah, right or let's
say, you know A whole bunch of heart
surgeons embarrassing to you know, so it's the
same thing any group think You see it
doesn't have to be bad.
It just happens to be bad It's a
group think is not bad because let's say
you had a society that was compassionate Sympathetic
and lawful and as part of their group
think right?
Is that is that a bad thing?
No, that's actually quite wonderful.
And that's how it's going to be in
the future It's just that this type of
group think that humans are experiencing is not
good for sure.
So anyway, good You know, yeah, I was
just gonna I was gonna tell them instead
You know, maybe that one time not to
have I've been listening to a lot of
a lot of Greek speak Like a lot
a lot and you know Like there's only
two people on this planet right now that
can even get down some solid information about
Scripture And that's you and Sam So, I
don't know.
Maybe I can motivate these people to go
look or something I don't know.
I want to get something going on because
I know that all I think what has
to be done is a whole new thing
has to be done because this is like
In other words, you know a real conspiracy
has to be formed Meaning a conspiracy where
you know people come together that word is
you've been used improperly in other words Okay,
you know when You certain products they you
buy like let's say like I know the
guy who started the 24-hour computer Helpline
like if you remember back in the early
90s if you bought a computer and you
needed help you had to wait for business
Hours and this guy said nearly 90s.
Why don't we why don't we do a
24-hour computer helpline?
So technical service, so if you buy an
Apple, you know, whatever anybody could call any
time of day What a great idea and
that really boosted the product, right?
yeah, so in other words if you're going
to put out solid information you have to
form a group or Some kind of thing
where people can go anytime anywhere, you know,
especially online and and and get You know
what they need right and that I don't
think that exists because let's say Sam and
I are discussing Scripture you have to go
through three hours.
There's no out, you know of audio and
maybe you'll get it It needs to you
know, you need to create an outline it
has to be in written form you have
to write about it, you know still and
You can do an introduction or synopsis.
These things need to be formed in a
conspiratorial form I think your idea before with
the YouTube where you had the hyperlinks embedded
in video So that they can write and
move it on which I'm capable of doing
and we'll put my services available any time
for that Right and I've been looking at
several by the way when you say about
scripture there's a couple of sources, you know
Of course, there's the anyone who's a realist,
you know, I mean by realist, you know,
you don't make stuff up It is good.
But the thing is they spin off like
I mentioned a few like there's Ernest L
Martin and the David C loss and the
Michael Heizer's and all that but they always
spin off into into la la fiction lands
Are you getting it's what I call Sifting
through poop to get edible corn.
No one is serving fresh corn on the
cob with warm butter, you know You know,
it's it's right when they get to that
point that they go to la la land
It's all because of wanting to raise revenue
for themselves That's right.
All right, and also they trust in in
the scripture or the creator or the creator
All right, right.
He says I'll take care of you.
So Yeah, so they give a lot of
lip service and then they go back Because
I've spoken to the people I've even had
correspondence with well, I've had corresponds a little
people I've mentioned except for Ernest L Martin
because he died before I got into this
but they basically won't touch the the the
reality the the real reality that It's a
non-religious issue and the reason why they
don't do that is because They can't see
how they're gonna grab get enough people to
support themselves financially Twitter boils down to so
yeah, well, yeah, and what's even sadder is
Putting out the real information will will will
you know Well, let's say okay.
Let's say you were well-endowed Let's say
you had a lot of financial backing and
all of a sudden you put out real
information.
You'll be bankrupted Right So thinking that you
will put out real information and grow it
financially is stupid not on this planet.
It won't happen ever There's a lot of
people out there saying they have the truth
and you listen to know like they just
left out like 99% of what's critical
to Foundationally to what they're saying so forget
it Yeah, so the thing is how patient
are you right?
Yeah, trying to get Not right not too
patient right now, but I'm working on learn
patience Learn patience.
That's why I mean, that's why I say
why bother Yeah, why bother teaches you patience,
right?
Because you're gonna bother you're going to do
like you're going to do something You're gonna
learn tolerance patience Many of the other Actions
that would come along with that Right, and
you're not here's the other point.
You're not being patient for them You're being
patient for yourself until you you have to
be patient until you run out of heartbeats
You go into sleep mode literally And then
you wake up Brought back.
That's the patience.
I'm talking about because here's the thing and
I've said this before I should just do
a talk on it alone, but If you
are Full of altruism and hope in this
the way in this setting that you're in
right now born into this world There's gonna
come a time in the near future where
everything's gonna look real rosy and you're gonna
fall for it right Right, that's the big
deception.
Are you gonna fall for this perfection and
everyone listening don't fall for that either You
still have to be more cautious, right?
So so that's why I mean there's nothing
in this incarnation at all you have to
wait for the gods to because To rule
in other words, no matter how good it
gets here You're still going to be ruled
covertly by the gods and overtly by evil
men.
Have you ever heard that?
saying that absolute power corrupts Absolutely.
Absolutely, right?
They never finished that and the whole thing
is absolute power corrupts Absolutely, and all great
men are evil men or I mean meaning
as powerful men, right?
right, so What I mean by why bother
and be patient means until you're done not
till the situation changes so in the meantime
You're doing yoga and you have a bunch
of people coming and Yeah, okay, you know
what Life's not bad go to the beach
Can't well, it's not good either.
I mean, it's it just is it is
what it is But here's the thing what
you could do is just focus on one
thing You know how people they give advice
that when they're going to speak publicly and
they're nervous or perform they just focus on
if you speak to like an Actor and
ask them.
Well, how were you when you first started
performing like I was really nervous So I
just found that when I got up on
stage, I focused on one person's blouse or
an empty chair through the whole show That's
all I focused on so I wouldn't be
nervous, right?
Yeah, so Yeah, I don't think I think
Greek speak is an antidote to stupidity.
So if Christian equals stupid No matter how
smart they sound It's it's not good.
It's like Star Trek where the The matter
was a Scotty Oh captain, it's the matter
and time matter pod, you know when they
matter and antimatter come together they explode Right,
yeah, it's not gonna work.
Yeah.
No, there are some exceptions.
I'm just giving you the rules, right?
Yeah And don't be yeah and don't be
hopeful or altruistic because with whether they're Christian
Jewish Muslim or whatever Mm-hmm stupid people
are dangerous not because stupid people are dangerous
is because they're inherently evil Think about that
for a moment They're not good people Yeah,
you don't know about Stalin right having a
surrounding himself with stupid Yeah, yeah, you can't
fix them.
It's it's part of the cosmic censorship.
It's That it goes and deeply akin to
the earth as well But It's just the
state of being but in essence These are
the rules that I'm discussing and and a
lot of general generalities are based on a
rule based mindset But there's always an exception,
right?
so Yeah, if you fill a group with
if you fill a group of a room
with a group of people You're not going
to be thinking about the exceptions you think
about the group, right?
So yeah, go ahead Yeah, you have to
look at the I mean a crowd assessment
to who you're speaking to But I wanted
to talk about World War two You know
there because he was to this guy was
telling me about his past life and everything
and no such thing I know.
Yeah, that's what I was telling you So
I was looking at him like I didn't
tell him that that I was listening to
story not in my head You know trying
to be polite and then so I brought
World War two and he's like Do you
really want to know the truth about World
War two?
Do you really want to know?
There was this guy gonna tell me right
now and then he comes to take me
to like the sidebar and he's like it
was A false flag.
They put false flags over it all around
it.
Yeah, sure a lie and I was like,
okay So that's what it pretty much what
it was Yeah, of course.
Yeah, all wars are that way the last
real wars were I think of maybe 500
BC there hasn't been any real In other
words, what is the purpose of war?
I mean that there's a spirit behind it
But I would say that like if you're
familiar with the sovereign state principle and The
Westphalia principle of sovereign nations and all that
ever since all that, you know I would
say since the middle medieval ages the earth
is in pretty much lockdown by a Say
a few thousand people run the whole planet,
right?
They're King.
They're King makers.
They're president makers They set up countries they
break up countries and those are the people
or the groups that control all that World
War one and World War two were just
cullings Yeah, you know culling is you know,
you've ever live in a You know a
rural area and there's too many, you know,
people can't use the roads because there's deer
too many deer Well, they just you put
a thing in the paper You know the
next two weeks everybody's got to go out
and shoot deer because we got too many
deer Right Ritual type deal, you know, just
because there's too many of them.
Yeah, right and not too many because of
the earth No The earth can handle right
now as everything is the earth can handle
ten times more people gonna roughly 70 billion
people as things are Not mentally, but you
know physically just with the infrastructure and all
that It could handle ten times.
So no it too many people in terms
of mindset Like let me give you another
thing about World War two and maybe before
I do that, let me give you When
people say that they have a past life
and it could be as real to them
as anything else is real to anyone else
that is a spirit that comes around and
Convince because they could put thoughts in your
mind That that you were there that you
were right and they could be very accurate
because those spirits are were there So if
you run into someone let's say non hypothetically
because this is something that happened and They
can evidence to others that they did have
a past life because of XYZ or ABC
all the way to Z There's a spirit
that is giving them that information But it's
these spirits.
They they like to be covert They don't
want they want you to remain ignorant of
the spiritual world, right?
like like Intelligence agencies, right if you've ever
been around people that are in the intelligence
agencies Oh, even their own parents and family
members don't know sometimes I remember the movie
true lies, right?
They the wife husband wife lie to each
other that they were in intelligence agencies, right?
Yeah Okay, these spirits don't want you They'll
do it and go to any length to
prevent you from understanding the spiritual world and
they'll go to every length to convince you
Of what popular norm keeps you away from
understanding the spiritual world city these people if
you put a gun to their head And
say I'll pull the trigger if you don't,
you know, tell if you don't admit that
it you don't have a past life They'll
say pull the trigger because they did that's
how convincing they are to humans Because now
what spirit is telling this guy that when
I'm talking to him, so what makes yeah,
yeah.
Yeah.
Well, it's watching And they and they have
a hive mentality.
They could well that spirit could be watching
you says I don't know anything about this
guy Is there anyone out here that does
you know?
And they like they put it up on
the net like on a chat board and
all the other spirits look at is yeah
I know something about I'll be right there,
you know, and they do it instantly, right?
Yeah, that's why that's so convincing and But
by the way There are repercussions if you
spill the beans too much on how the
spiritual world works You can you can you
can invite some calamity to yourself because it's
like let's say you've had a list of
CIA agents in In in Iraq and you
printed it online You don't think you're gonna
get any repercussions like you got a knock
on your door within two days or three
days Right.
Yeah, if you just have same thing or
let's say in your local neighborhood You had
a list of all the undercover detectives and
you printed it out I mean, you'll have
a knock on your door soon.
So it's the same thing with a spiritual
world if you give up too much You'll
get a knock on your door knock on
your head or something And I don't want
to get into personal stuff, but I first
had knowledge of that Greek I got a
question.
Well, so what is the balance on something
like that when presenting information?
I mean, there's got to be a general
yeah, so General but but it but it
works it works It works really a general
is enough to get most of the work
that people will ever have to do done
Let's say you run into a posthumous tribal
member that lives in the snow-capped mountains
of Afghanistan, right?
He's never seen a tiled bathroom or a
toilet or a shower before you invite him
over He walked he he walks into the
room and he's like, I don't know.
What the hell is this, you know, and
He wants to wash his his clothes in
the toilet He doesn't know and you tell
him real quick generally you see this right
here.
This is the bathtub That's the drain on
the floor if you turn these two valves
This is hot water.
This one is cold water and you pull
this you'll get the water coming from here
That's enough information for him to literally take
a shower and the toilet on you sit
down on it You do your your stuff
liquid or soft and then pull the handle
that is so simple But that's all anybody
needs to know about using a bathroom.
How many people three, right?
We'll see that the bathroom is more complicated
than that none I mean, I mean, yes,
if you're going to design one build one
or get into something on a different level
Absolutely, you have to know more about how
it works Okay, so so that's what I
get into, you know, you've never seen a
bathroom before.
Okay, this handles the hot water This is
the cold water uses the soap.
That's it.
You're finished.
Okay.
No, it's actually not finished, but it's enough
It's so utilitarian.
So that's what I get into.
Basically.
There's a spiritual, you know, it's it's not
another dimension Like many people like to say
it's just unseen And that's one thing people
have a hard time where they get caught
up in what I call the dummy load
or what's you know There's only one demand.
Everything is happening at the same place.
It's just that you can't perceive it.
Just like for example It's like these you
can't see that but it's well even less
You can even bring it closer.
Sometimes you go in in homes or public
spaces, especially public spaces You see like a
white fixture with grill cover on a very
small and that's a co2 Or see a
carbon monoxide mom, right?
Right, right.
You've heard of carbon monoxide monitors It's like
why do you need a monitor effect?
Well, because it's tasteless odorless and colorless.
It'll kill you.
You can't smell it You can't taste it
Actually, you can't taste it.
It's a metallic If you get a lot
of it, it's a metallic flavor on the
top of your palate, but it's so subtle
You wouldn't you wouldn't react, you know, right
so but anyway You know, there's so many
colorless think of gas the the gaseous realm,
right?
How many gaps how many gases are colorless
odorless and tasteless that can a be beneficial
to you like oxygen or B?
Well nitrogen also and or carbon monoxide, which
is a compound you see Spiritual world is
just like that It's unseen but it's there
real but it's counter spatial.
I put in some links in the chat
yesterday about hyperbolic geometry I seen that a
very very tasty stuff there.
Yes Because that's how I read from talk.
Oh I didn't know that was she a
TED talk.
Was that a TED talk video?
That's all in the middle of the page
if you went.
Oh, yeah Yeah, yeah, she had a Ted
talk is a fascinating woman and who would
have thought you know Yeah, TED talk is
part of the Trilateral Commission the technocrats but
But anything educational like that is but yeah,
I'm not that it's all bad.
But yeah, I wasn't aware of it it's
discreetly that it was that but So anyway,
this is the spiritual stuff very simple there's
nothing to do what you believe in what's
important is that you've heard it You know
And then take it from there Yeah, whether
they believe it or not or like it
or not as irrelevant You know, that's why
like when I I appreciate Like when I
did the Ocelli and the Greek stuff, you
got to really Thank Ocelli for that because
this that really stretched him out far.
Oh, yeah, because He's just used to not
just singling him out, but anyone out there
there.
He's used to agreement You know, like if
if enough people agree on something it's true
and real, right?
I'm trying to show him as that's that's
the that's not true.
Like the majority is always wrong Show me
once when the majority was, right?
Speaking of the majority I want to go
back to World War two what people are
not familiar with You might have heard of
all the protests on television during the Vietnam
War Right and in Europe there were protests
about the Iraqi war right and all that
well, you don't hear anything about the riots
and Protesting about the u.s. Going into
World War two After the Pearl Harbor.
No, you don't know look it up It's
really hard because it it's the new the
newspaper it took the newspapers to get the
people to do it because you know and
the Frank Capra why we fight made movies
about the bad Japanese and all that so
it was a very Being propagandized now World
War two was the heaviest propaganda campaign since
the Civil War There wasn't much of a
propaganda Unleashing during World War one because it
was only a year long for the u
.s Only went in there most people think
it lasted years even an old lady.
I ran into recently I Did some furniture
for her and she says Oh World War
one was pretty long.
Why is it knows a year?
She goes no, it's not I'm like I'm
not gonna argue with her.
I'm not gonna even go tell her look
it up You know, it's only one year
so The Civil War in America is the
largest propaganda that you ever see now in
America I think I mentioned this on last
Sonic people hang their flags what they call
the u.s Flag, you know with the
50 stars and the stripes or 13 Mean
evil spirited people What's that?
They're kind of mean?
Yeah, they are Well, they're they're patriots they're
they're sick so anyway That didn't that ritual
didn't start until the Civil War because the
north The feds sent a bunch of people
in the north telling people to put these
flags on their buildings They're like no, that's
the u.s. Flag.
That's garbage And and they're like you better
put it and they started beating people up
or paying others off to do it.
You see.
Yeah Oh, that's not very yeah.
Yeah.
Look at I've been seeing a new flag.
It's a black and white and blue flag
And American flag style.
I don't know what it means.
I've been seeing that around The Isis is
black that's that's that's Isis is us this
or you know American couple weeks ago how
every government wants to Really overthrow Or rule
overtly and then they're trying to get the
people weren't they just gonna rule over the
anyways the government like how the gods are
Gonna do that Well the gut there is
no go the governments are you could just
look at what it is If it's like
if I don't if I show you something
you haven't seen before and don't tell you
anything about it You have enough sense to
examine it, right?
Yeah, but first and then form, you know
what you think it is, you know, and
usually most of the time people are right
If you look at the way you interact
with the government It's basically a bunch of
stupid people working in offices or uniforms And
then you have all these forms whenever you
hear about into your interaction with the government
is going to be a form of some
Time paperwork whether it's a traffic ticket or
all the way up, right?
Now anyone who has a third grade education
whether on any school They will tell you
that anything any noun that is written in
all caps is improper They will fail you
you will have to take the third grade
over if you continue to do that Right,
all these government paperwork is all improper paperwork.
It's neither legal nor lawful So it's some
kind of and if you if you study
what it is, it goes under the CUSIP,
which is the Convention of Universal Securities and
Investment Protocols, it's basically all financial stuff based
on Non-hypothecated, which means no collateral presumed
collateral unsecured credit based Financial instruments derivatives, you
know all this fiat stuff So what you're
what you're interacting with the government is basically
what the what you call the government they're
doing nothing more but collecting your signatures and
and monetizing them through various Organizations for the
people who own your country Okay, this is
one thing that's confusing The country is owned
the country meaning like the land the water
the animals the buildings the people are owned
privately the government Job in every country right
now is To monetize all that just like
YouTube hits you ever like YouTube more YouTube
hits and then they monetize you, right?
the purpose of the government is to get
as many hits as they can on paper
and deliver it to the owners so they
can give it to their financiers like the
Rothschilds and the bankers so they could process
it as credit and and Create paper money
out of it and money on account.
I Think I've never really broken it down
this way before.
It's very simple What you call the government
in any country is nothing more than a
financial instrument collection agency Uh-huh, and they
also have what's called security forces.
They have military they have police they have
sheriffs.
They have citizen watch Right, it isn't wrong.
I have oh, yeah Yeah, they tell you
I think someone just put a video and
chat, you know white people calling the police
about black people doing stuff Yes, right, right
See something say something so so basically you're
Yeah, it's very very simple it's almost if
I break it down to simply people don't
get it It's kind of like what you
see.
This is a toilet.
You sit down you do your thing You
pull the handle that's it, you know, as
long as you don't put anything.
That's at least Less than half the size
of the hole on the bottom So to
make sure everything goes down If you start
putting things in the toilet that exceed half
the diameter of the outlet you might clog
it, right?
That's all you've got to know.
Nope.
No So the real kicker is how do
you get The people that go to work
and everything after they wipe out the population
and you would oh, yeah the psychological Yeah
the enemy when any any government or the
owners the From the the people who own
the the country and then the guard see
people think the government owns the guy It
doesn't the government is there to collect like
I said all of your signatures because they're
worth money to that Right the guy that's
all the government does the government doesn't own
the country or rule the country, right?
It's like you go on to a factory
you have the foreman or the manager of
the factory He doesn't he doesn't run.
He doesn't own the country or the building
or pay the renter or right?
He's there to manage it He's they're just
administrators.
That's why it's called the Trump administration the
Obama administration the Roosevelt the Kennedy administration.
They administer it, right?
They have nothing to do But but also
see they have a set of guidelines that
the attorneys made up under the Lieber code
and they say well are these?
Inhabitants or citizens or residents or whatever they
have to act a certain way and this
is how we want them to act today
It's different than yesterday.
So we have to let them know a
little bit and if anyone goes beyond You
know the fringe of this behavior limitation you
beat them up or we put you in
a cage or we shoot you It has
nothing to do with law That's all it
is.
Yeah, you're pretty much you wake up and
you realize you're a slave Well, you are
a slave and you're not a slave because
there's two ways in order to know You
wake up and you realize there's hot water.
You have to have cold water right now
Everybody's under this condition.
You're not gonna in other words to say
you wake up and you realize your slave
is very difficult In reality because you don't
know anyone who is not a slave Who's
free show me somebody who's free.
That means you don't have a birth certificate.
You don't have any licensing You don't have
a surname and you don't Reside in a
territory that's owned by this system Show me,
you know, there are some people still in
North Korea, maybe Places of let's say in
Afghanistan I would say places in Afghanistan and
a couple of places maybe in the Congo
or Somalia.
They're free people In other words, they're not
registered they're not oh, you know, they don't
you know what I mean?
Yeah, and you can't be registered with all
this stuff and then say you're free because
that doesn't go away Like give me an
example of personal example I years ago when
I discovered this it kind of shocked me
and for moral reasons I called up the
the authorities like various authorities the Social Security
Administration the Health and Human Services the US
Treasury and I said look I I want
to cancel all the all this stuff and
And and I got up to some higher
level people and there so listen, you can't
really cancel it.
Just don't use it Because I knew also
it's a fiction Yeah, right.
So so just don't use it is the
is the in other words too late In
other words, you can't on it's like if
you ring a bell and make a recording
of it You wish you didn't ring it
will at least stop playing the recording because
the bell is rung and it's finished, right?
Yeah playing the recording over and over and
over So it's a little late for that
and also if you are free for example
And you come to a country like the
US or Mexico or Canada or a hundred
ninety other countries that is owned You you
have no business.
You're a problem now Because that's why they
say illegals can't work I'm not saying that
the people from Mexico come to us are
really free But when they come here, they're
they're not Entitled let's say or it can
be privileged like the people, you know given
Privileges given what they can and can't do
So for example when you have someone who's
illegally immigrated to the US work and you
give them a check or cash They'll say
hey, this is a note.
Let me get some money.
They can't so now they have a beef
with you They could say look I worked
a week cutting the grass or raking the
leaves.
I'm not a citizen I'm from another country
and you gave me this fake money.
I need some real money No one can
give you real money for that now.
They got a problem.
No, yeah, I just stole your labor That's
why there's a problem with immigration But people
are so stupid Hopelessly so that there's no
way they'll ever see the real reality So
they have to turn on the news or
the Internet and see what the newspapers or
the church or whatever is telling them Yeah,
so much of this caravan coming up.
Do you see that?
Well, yeah, that's again for anything that's in
the news anything and everything is there to
distract you Yeah, it's it's it's gotten so
obviously bad now That it's not even You
can see it in the TV like Amherst
is almost fake Like how they set it
up Well, the caravan is not necessarily real
because I mean it is real But it's
not a real threat because I was speaking
to someone that was in Intelligence services for
Mexico and then he switched sides and came
to the u.s. And he says there's
never going to be a war between Between
Mexico and the u.s. Because there's less
than a million That's like maybe like 200
maybe 50,000 Americans living in Mexico or
a hundred thousand But there's 30 million or
20 million Mexicans Living in the u.s.
And he says he personally knows 12,000
that would be armed and ready to fight
You know, or you know know someone who
can command 12,000 commando types that are
living in the u.s. Immediately So there
will never be a war because the u
.s. Already lost by numbers, you know, yeah
Yeah, and the only reason you have the
people coming up to the u.s. Is
to prevent a revolution or unrest in their
country It's it's formulated.
In other words, there are factions and groups
in Mexico and El Salvador and Colombia that
tell people that are poor or You know
have a let's say quote-unquote criminal record
whatever here's some money or go talk to
this guy and go to America You know
the people that can start like that that
can like be like a would it go
kinder?
What do you call when a spark and
a dry box?
What's it called?
Kinderbox kindling Yeah, they were people that could
see the more charismatic and the more character
someone has The the more people will follow
them and he's easier you could start if
you have a like here There's in this
city here.
There's a sign tosser He's like one of
the best in the country wins awards Like
the guys who stand in front of malls
and they have a sign and they toss
it you've seen them, right?
It's called a cat in the hat man
or whatever He's like one of the best
in the world really you can throw the
sign up 20 feet have it spinning He'll
do a handstand and grab it right make
people love them Yeah, right So that guy's
got a lot of character charisma and show
quality and he lives out of his van
or something, right?
He's very poor.
Yeah, he can organize with that kind of
character and charisma He can organize a hundred
people around him as his followers very easily
That's how the gangsters operated back in the
day.
They were very charismatic full of character people
won't like them Even though they didn't do
good things.
You know what I mean?
Yeah Those are the people that are looked
for By you know people there's watchers, you
know in in all these South American countries
and they look for these people Even the
quiet types and they say go to America,
you know It's not you know back in
the day when Ronald Reagan was in office
he had a deal the Mexican president says
look my all my services intelligence services and
Analysts and think tanks are telling me that
we it's possible.
We could have a revolution.
This is in the 80s late 70s early
early 80s.
We we get we're like 1% we're
like a Pubic hair away from having a
revolution or civil unrest in Mexico I need
for you to take a million of my
people to Reagan and Reagan was like, okay
Let him come.
I Did not know that.
Oh, yeah Back in the day and they
never stopped I mean that that was the
big influx and then they'd let you know
through this is old That's why if you
even watch the news like even though with
the last administration even with this administration People
who work at the Border Patrol.
They're like they deliberately leave open areas You
know, they'll have a concentration of Border Patrol
and then they'll leave an area where like
two guys are patrolling a 50-mile strip
Now if you've ever driven 50 miles, you
know So you can drive a highway speed
it takes an hour.
But if you're patrolling you're not going at
highway speed you're crawling That's that's two days,
you know So in other words, you'll have
a patrol if you want to cross the
border You'll see the patrol guy and then
you won't see him for two days right
this is deliberate a Porous border is always
deliberate Yeah, I Wouldn't give it any and
also, you know, this is winter time winter
time is a time when the agricultural process
and you know plantings growing and and and
Reaping is over.
The harvest is over so now winter time
traditionally what people did is they did anything
that was That they could do that.
They couldn't do during the agricultural process So
now in the winter time is when you
put you build a barn, right?
You don't build the barn in springtime and
the farm, right?
you don't build it in the fall because
it's right you know you build a barn
in the winter like when harvest is over
was Planting is over when summer is a
you or you don't travel when you're a
farmer you agriculturally You don't travel in the
middle season, right travel when the season is
over Yeah, so the main manifestation seasons are
over right now You're in the season of
what happens is you do things that normally
you wouldn't do during the progressive part of
the year Production production time of the year
you dude you do travel.
That's why for example this Khashoggi guy This
it's like a lot of times.
I see this and it's like the gods
are like It's like a I see like
a comic book of the gods What's going
on?
You know like a Marvel Carl and I
even Marvel cuz Marvel's like superheroes He's but
like a comic book.
So the comic book I see is Khashoggi.
What is he doing?
He's traveling right he sees this is not
he's outside of indigenous country in another country
where he gets killed, right?
Well, what do you do the winter right?
So I bet this even though it's hypothetical
if it was spring summer or fall He
would have been killed in his own country
You get it because it's winter time.
He's killed outside of his country because that's
when you travel.
Yeah But it has nothing to do with
his ability to travel because you could travel
anytime.
I'm just saying The the nature of the
seasons and people's behavior is is I see
it as a comic book of the gods
what's in the news?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah Yeah, I mean it's fall right now
and then it's coming into winter And in
springtime, well, yeah harvest is over.
I would say right there's still some harvesting
the oil You have for example, like the
real slow growing which don't exist that much
anymore, but still do Wheats and things like
that, you know, they're still harvesting to a
degree by the way Sure, yeah, and I'll
keep going I mean the winter rye as
well plants planted now and it's through but
generally the spring summer fall is You know
the planting building up breaking down and then
winter or the things that are normally done
that you wouldn't do during that planting growing
and harvesting The other thing I just took
cut in since we're a little bit on
time I mean not time that we don't
have time, but so I'm reckoning by tonight
to wit the full moon Starting at noon.
I I would suggest today.
That is the first day of the ninth
month So of what I'm reckoning, so So
I can't to see mine yet But well,
it was it was rather full This morning,
let's say at dawn and almost full last
night and if you look at the by
the way the moon Websites, you'll notice it
grows.
It changes at about 3% per day,
right?
Because roughly 30 days per month three point
three percent times 30 you see so when
you look at it And it's like a
97% well the next day it'll jump
to another 3% and the day before
was 94 you ever notice that it goes
by 3% chunks because Of the nature
of the 30-day cycle divided by yeah,
right.
No, okay, so So go ahead We'll call
you yoga man or or Bruce and go
ahead for anything else Yeah There's always a
bunch of stuff that I cannot talk to
you about and I always seem To freeze
up.
I do have a little random question.
Why did they call Bali?
the island in Indonesian the island of the
gods Well, because which one isn't the island
of the gods, I mean it's is the
gods I mean which island doesn't have a
god It's a dummy load.
That's a challenge doesn't yeah, which island is
not part of a grouping of gods or
vice versa Isn't there a deity over each
nation?
Yes, 70 were initially installed.
Uh-huh.
They're the main ones right now is justice
ball-backed and mollack Well this well each
one.
These are old old gods Right, so you
would have to go and search The the
categories of Genesis is an easy way to
look at all the various lineages of people
The 70 nations and such and look at
their history and you'll see who they are
Most of them have been forgotten, but it
doesn't mean they've gone away Mean there's a
new gods or that their old gods are
coming back old gods are coming back They've
always been here except for the ones that
have probably most likely been killed And then
their new god-like creatures that will be
unleashed and have been unleashed Right They're like
to be called angels because they have a
very you see the spiritual realm just like
the physical realm is defined by what?
they do Like you could say if you
want to really bit generic you see these
are all humans or how else can we
define them?
Well, you know, we have a way of
talking about race, you know, Asian white black
brown, whatever Latin Right, but really what what
you do is you define them by what
they do.
This is a farmer This is a factory
worker.
This is a bus driver.
You ever notice that?
Yeah, okay So the the way you define
the in Scripture, you've seen you'll see that
they they're all spiritual beings But you define
them as what they do like this one's
the boss.
He's the head God, right?
And then you've got this one.
He's a messenger is an angel very has
very little authority unless he's give it's given
to him All right, then you have all
these various other demons and things like that
so And you define them by what they
do like there's a God and a spiritual
being behind death and that's personified by the
grim reaper You see that often in popular
culture Right, and you got one that brings
disease you have one bread that brings ones
world that that bring dreams Good dreams night
terror.
There's dreams and there's night terrors nightmares and
night terrors right, so Yeah, I mean and
it goes on and on there's a God
behind the birds is a God behind the
bees Right the God behind the flowers a
spiritual entity.
Let's say Yeah Well, you know Greek think
I'll let you guys leave let you guys
go back to talking Um, you know, thank
you so much for paying us information I
want to develop it more, you know something
up and maybe not get too ambitious or
do it But at least I so I
can get shelter and clothing and food or
something.
Yeah.
Yeah Because right now I'm out surfing and
I'm all over the place.
No, that's fine.
Yeah, that's fine.
Welcome to planet Earth Yeah, welcome to earth.
I Will I want to call again and
you guys, you know, there's a lot more
to talk about but I guess we'll just
keep it I'll just keep it kind of
Mellow again today, but thank you guys.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's good to have another voice come
in.
Thanks Thanks for sharing your time.
Yeah, no worries.
Maybe we do a private again or soon
If you're down, I don't know but there's
a lot to talk about there's so much
stuff I don't want to bring up, you
know You know now he was listening never
because you said what there's always one bad
person that wants to do something with this
information well for every good Project there's a
Anywhere between three to three hundred that want
to turn it into something malevolent in other
words if you're working on a project to
clean up water So people didn't have a
healthful life and and you start me going
public There's going to be anywhere between three
to three hundred Others that are going to
pick that up and figure out how they
could turn your methods to make water toxic
Not overtly toxic, but it'll still taste good,
but it'll be toxic to you, right?
Yeah.
Yeah So, I mean I've seen enough industry
and enough people in various fields that whenever
you bring up ideas are like wait, wait
Wait, we let we don't talk about this
Anyway, we want to monetize that we need
to we see we need to you know
What I mean, they you know that no
one wants to put out anything that's going
to help anyone even I've even seen family
of people all over through the years Wishing
other family members to do well, but when
when they do well, they get upset You
know, so basically what they're saying is do
well in life, but just do but don't
do better than I am doing Yeah, basically
humans are scumbags generally speaking Yeah, and
yeah the best thing is that when you
once you can transcend your own family members
if you're unfortunate to have a big Family,
you know what?
I mean?
The most fortunate people are orphans believe it
or not not socially because you know If
you were brought up an orphan, you probably
had a hard time because you know, you're
probably subject to predation and pranking but Because
the the way the demonic spirits have twisted
what family is and you know So anyway,
that's an I've discussed that before.
Yeah, my grandma.
I think my grandma's a witch Either way,
you know, I tell people like your family
is a bunch of assholes and they're like,
yeah, you're right You see I I told
you that it's accurate and I didn't even
have to meet them, right?
How do I know?
This is planet Earth Yeah, so if you
were say if you're cooking so if you
cooked pork, right and you know You cook
pork.
So would it smell like human flesh the
board?
Yeah, pretty much.
It's no it's Only Most in other words
if you went to the morgue, but let's
say you you said, you know so this
this car blew up and as he blew
up and pieces of flesh went everywhere and
you went to and and instead and you
should I picked up the flesh and but
you really didn't and It we just put
a bunch of pieces of pork in there
and he gave it to the pathologist.
He'd say oh, yeah, this is human meat
It's crazy because sometimes we're you know, you
had to walk down Main Street and it
just smells like pork and it just like
smells like pretty much just death and You
know people next to you like, oh I
get so hungry and you know, it's society.
I don't know So the headhunter one is
the best.
Oh, yeah Yeah, they've got there.
They're all ready for cannibalism, right?
Especially the well, I mean who isn't eating
any pork except in the Middle East really
but there would be camel The a lot
of camel By the way, you know if
you go to the Middle East and they
ask you if you want meat on it
and they don't specify you it's going to
be camel meat, but Just like in Spain
if you get a hamburger, if you don't
specify beef, it's going to be horse meat.
It goes without saying, right?
Yeah, most people are ready they're primed for
cannibalism right now because of the pork taste
the flavor they have Yeah, I got it,
um, you know, I was just I mean
growing up and I was younger and then
I was like the first thing I had
to get off of was Yeah, yeah, that
was it Malcolm X or one of his
of you will say to pork well that's
half dog half cat and all rat Yeah,
pretty much I mean it's not that's a
stupid thing to say in a way but
at least it got them away from it
You know, yeah and pigs eat each other
too.
Yeah, that's People like to eat pork, but
anyway, yeah.
Yeah, that's that's all in scripture too, right?
Yeah.
Well people eating people in in Kings.
There's a story about a woman Asking the
king for advice.
He says sure what do you need advice
on?
It says well last night we had an
agreement with a woman We'll eat my baby
tonight and her baby tomorrow and tomorrow came
and she disappeared with the baby.
What should I do?
Or they just eat it right or no,
yeah, so he went to the king for
advice It's like, you know, we made an
agreement the my baby tonight and her baby
tomorrow tomorrow's here and she took off with
the baby We're supposed to eat.
What should I do?
The King's like what?
Yeah, that's your problem, you know, anyway Well,
so then have you read that?
Have you read that in Scripture?
Yeah, the king is walking on the walls
a time of famine He's wearing black sackcloth
And when he heard that he rent his
clothes he tore his clothes because he was
it's like wow This is that this is
what the people are down to right?
that's insane because Well, that's just all comes
from what then if it's internal input who's
given the internal input to do that The
creator no, and that's where the good and
evil comes to the same source.
So what is a giant?
Oh, yeah What's that this is a giant
test No, it's not a test it's a
practical.
Yeah, it's a test in sense of It's
practical, you know, it's pretty meaning it's happening.
In other words, it's stated That if you
don't If you agree to do this and
you don't then this will happen to you,
right?
Yeah The old famous, you know, there's a
lot of You know obvious Obfuscation and deleting
you Marie Antoinette, you know the famous saying
she got in trouble that you know Because
she sold the people didn't have bread teach
because we'll let them eat cake then right?
That's not what she said When they came
to people don't have food to eat She
said let them meet their children and then
they change it to brioche because that would
be too harsh Because she what she did
was she went against the elitist group Because
it's very common in elitist circles when you
tell the any elitist or you know, like
the Nobility that the people can't eat don't
have food to eat.
You say well fine.
Let them eat their children.
They have children, right?
This is a this has been going on
for a long time, but they don't want
that to be known Because it's just one
more thing, you know to hate the nobility
about That's how the nobility think I mean
I'll even say let they eat their children
anyway Well spiritually they do right?
Yeah, exactly It's worse to eat them spiritually
like an emotional prison as a life sentence,
right?
Yeah, hey I Guess so, you know, I
mean the emotions I Try not to why
just you know falling in love you but
what you say about love is the best
thing I've ever heard Doing the right thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, very few people know what love is
and then and they can't Because you won't
feel once you know, what love is you
can't reckon it You cannot compare it to
what you see around you at all.
You'll see that there's no love at all
So Talking I mean sometimes you get I
get into these long arguments with the women
at the Yoga studio, but even there at
the studio, it's so It's just so pagan
pretty much.
Okay That's the nature of Of it right
now.
That's just how it goes It's pagan eating.
Okay, it's the very it's different though Like
we went back to let's go back to
Christianity, you know, when people say I'm Christian
Oh, well, what Christian like Roman Catholic, you
know Latin American?
Mormon You know Protestant Presbyterian Seventh-day Adventist
What Greek Orthodox Eastern or the what Christian
because there's no such thing what every you
notice how all those different types of Christian
I mentioned are also connected To a geography,
you know, you notice I right.
Yeah, and you know how each year there's
an attribute in other words There's a God
assigned to each one of those geographies.
So those gods are like, oh, yeah, this
Christianity stuff is great, man It keeps people
ignorant.
They're never gonna learn anything about the spiritual
world right on.
Um, well, that's what I want, you know
here All right, tell them if they're good
they go to heaven and tell them if
they're bad they go to this Dante's Inferno
Right, and and he worshipped this guy knelt
to a cross wearing a diaper regardless of
what color he is or whatever And there's
only one God Okay, and that's it.
That's perfect man.
Keep people Doug They'll never gonna find out
what we do to them or how we
you know, what that we're you know, well
never yeah, it's perfect It's like Stalin Such
stone I have the I have the etymology
dictionary right now and it says paganism is
a One of a people or community professing
a polytheistic religion So yeah You've got to
realize that all ref whether it's not it's
not whether I like it or not But
the a lot of the reference materials you
have to be very careful on Seeing that
if the meaning is based on What you
know certain core things that they don't want
you to understand like all of the religions
that they say are non pagan are pagan
like Islam Judaism and Christianity are pagan and
they tell you that Anything anything pay if
it's pagan if it's not if you look
up paganism generally, they'll tell you well Paganism
is anything that's not Islam, you know a
monotheist, you know Christianity Judaism There is no
such thing as monotheism ever.
Yeah, that's a stupid thing.
That's been invented recently Yeah, it also says
Latin peasants and then it says right village
royal districts and it says see heathen First
cinema sure, but where do they get the
right to say that because they don't know
you see here's the the twisted reality There
the roughly 70 gods that were put over
the nations and Yahweh the chief God decided
to take one nation So to to be
at parity with the rest without overpowering them,
right?
Just I think I've given the example of
children playing a board game or a physical
game and here comes the father He says
I'll play with you children You know I'll
take a game piece just like you and
I won't I promise I won't pick you
up and throw you across the room Right
a game like twister or something So he
plays like the rest do you know on
a minor minor level just to show that
he's not out that he still exists You
know practically and so he took Israel that
way, you know But now that he that
is really he's like, okay, Israel can't can't
hang You're out now It's just all these
other gods and we really don't know who
they are specifically unless you research it And
it's just like researching the nobility that runs
the planet You could look up, you know,
Bill Gates Rockefeller Rothschild and all those people.
They're just like the bottom of the barrel
You'll find as much information as you want
on them allegedly But the real people that
run and own all the countries you find
very little right and that's all part of
the plan Yeah, yeah You're not going to
find information on those that really because give
me an example Google is their company right
or the in other words it's a company
and they understand the so if someone let's
say you got a list of all the
names of the people or some of the
people that own most of The countries or
some some territories as they call it and
put it online Google would immediately take it
down and shut your stuff down immediately They
would just block the search the input.
Yeah, exactly on your and then come after
your input This is high priority stuff.
Yeah high priority Just block it or just
remove it out of the search queue And
right it's done.
You're censored Yep, and it's the same with
these gods That's why I keep pointing out
you ever notice this justice thing and this
is just ironic how it talks about this
female goddess religion being Malevolently prevalent in the
world and yet every country has adopted this
justice religion that you equate with law Why
why do you equate it with law because
your law comes from your God, duh?
You know So Yeah, the justice has it
all That's a real nasty and the people
ask for it.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, you know if you're hungry eat your
children You're doing it.
Anyway eat your leg You know eat your
arm Yeah, right.
You don't want to do that.
No, but that's what they want to hear
And now people like it's like the gambler,
you know, they're self-loathing.
They like to lose this oh Yeah, the
majority is always wrong People are bad people
are evil Inherently, whatever, you know what inheritance
is when someone dies or leaves they leave
something for you and you take it as
your own, right?
Yeah, and it trusts Yeah, or however, yeah,
it's bequeathed to you.
So, you know You've got let's say a
very normal couple.
They have children there There their children are
going to be normal most likely means fucked
up like they are evil bad Whatever pagan
whatever you want to call it And their
children and their children inherited it goes on
But if a couple is normal Which is
fucked up or whatever and they have children
and you take them away when they're born
or like after you know Six months after
their weaned or nine months actually five years
was the Norm in the old world for
children to be weaning, you know drinking mother's
milk Breastfeeding up to five years old.
That's why in Leviticus It was after five
years old that a child can be taken
as a slave, right?
Okay Yeah, I mean now it's just like
formula out of a can but but if
you let's have a normal couple in any
part of The developed world and which is
fucked up and you take their children away
and you bring them into a lawful Society
or a lawful upbringing.
They're not going to be fucked up.
You see so it's not Genetically bred in
I think after a long time Certain things
certain characteristics can be carried over Genetically like
if one leg is shorter than the other
or the way you look right you take
facial features I don't know how much of
it is is truly behavioral if it's all
external input You know There was a research
study done on Chinese children will always learn
Chinese faster than Western because of the thousands
of years of breedings that way and it
didn't experiment it took a black child a
Chinese child a white child Latin child and
As they raised them and they all learn
Chinese equally You see yeah So it's not
inbred, you know language and behavior and things
like that But some of it can be
based on certain physical attributes, right?
Yeah, I mean whatever you go the model
doctor, right Yeah, some of it can be
and also the you know, the way you
tune in, you know Well, you know anyway
back to Jack Fesco that when he mentioned
how people You know if you live in
the south, you know, I'm gonna get me
a nigger, you know or something like that
There's a cultural influence and I think there's
a lot more in percentage That goes to
the person being who's being raised then it
does actually from the actual parental parental units
It's a society, yeah, I don't think the
society does almost 80% of the raising
in one way or another Right because the
parents are not secluded and even if they
were secluded in rural They would still have
enough contact with society where they would bring
it home.
So to speak right exactly, you know Even
if they went out into society once a
month, there would be enough of an influence
Yeah Which is yeah Because I've been around
people that grew up in rural very rural
farm areas and they'd go into town or
be subject to other people, you know in
a social setting Once a month and they
were just as acclimated to the normal society
as fucked up as everybody else was.
Yeah Because they were actually about dryer sponge
they took it they took it in, you
know, you see a really dry sponge Just
sucks everything up you faster.
Oh, yeah.
Yep She's well agrees actually Now I'm gonna
try call back next week.
I have thank you actually works out I
don't want to talk, you know I love
Greek speak because you can you know Talk
about anything you want from actually I used
to be an apprentice before I got into
yoga for an electrician And that's when I
first started listening to Greek speak and you
can't bring can't talk about that for like
an electrician Creek spit.
Well, what do you say electrician?
You mean like a house electrician boat electric
commercial guy electrician like that?
Okay Yeah, I'm quite familiar with that.
I've done quite a bit of that, you
know, basically You're getting back to the the
number one thing.
I think is acceptance Do we just have
to accept the fact that we're in a
world of pagans?
the rarity of meeting somebody with any Real
knowledge Is rare Right, and it's by design
and by influence because the last thing you
want all the way up to the Creator
is a fully aware Population they're gonna say
what do we do?
Let's let's get off this and and they're
gonna there's too many Spiritual beings out there
that they're gonna summon to do things for
them and the whole place will be a
real mess Because a lot of the lower
a lot of the lower spiritual entities find
certain evocations Irresistible like you've seen it in
the pop culture where you know There'll be
like a Disney film and they find some
amulet or something and they say a few
words and the spirit comes and is Why
did you are who's calling me?
Yeah, you see that popular culture.
Sure.
What do you I'm here now.
What should I do?
Right, or they already have some inward knowledge
of it and just evoke it To the
rest.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah, there's all sorts of It's the
same.
It's the same thing like years ago.
It was this guy said I want to
shut down Manhattan I said well There's no
one really very few people live in and
everybody commutes the way you shut it down
is by Shutting down the bridges you do
that go print out a few thousand $20
bills in color and as you go crossing
the bridge Open the either the panel in
the floor or the back window and dump
a box of thousands of Printed 20s out
the window and everyone will get out of
their cars.
They'll stop in the middle of the bridge
just to pick up this money That's how
you shut down Manhattan, right?
So yes Or at the subway state.
Yeah, everyone will just stop to pick up
this money, right?
You see so what does that have to
do with shutting them in it?
Well, it's not it's it's what you know
How people behave, you know people that are
fishermen like people who do fly-fishing see
people who put bait on a hook are
trapping It's like setting a trap that that's
not real fishing is like fly-fishing Luring
where you you don't have any meat or
protein on the hook.
It just looks like a fish You make
it look like a live fish.
Yeah, you see in each which fish that
you're going for is a different lure you
see so And I just did a couple
of emails that people bring me so I
said that's not what you are that's what
you do start learning to separate that and
you'll start seeing with clarity and then Because
you have free will and choice and you're
semi, you know evolved enough to see that
you can educate yourself now You'll handle it
that way But if you're convinced that you
are something whether it's alcoholic Christian or Electrician
or whatever then it now you're screwed because
you just put yourself in a box It
doesn't exist and that box that doesn't exist
is as thick as six feet of concrete
go figure.
So Yeah, so If you start looking at
what people think what things do that's how
Right.
That's how you control them on the on
the back end on the front end.
You have to know what they really are
All right, so you can develop new methods
on what they do and this is what
the think-tank stuff is based on You
know figuring out like, you know I've heard
like they have now an amnesia frequency like
men in black like it pump it out
you either From some kind of focus device
could be omni-directional and it's electromagnetic pulse
that affects the brain It does some cooking
also heating but it clear it wipes memories,
right?
There's been around since the 60s, but now
they want to make it so it's you
know more available, right?
So it's a small wavelength Yeah, they do
it electromagnetically.
I think that if you if you knew
how to do it a theoretically you would
have some pretty serious manifestations health-wise also
not that the electromagnetic one doesn't but So
anything's possible and the only reason you why
would you want to wipe someone's memory?
Where's the memory?
I mean, you know, it's their ability to
receive the memory right because it's happening in
a cloud, right?
So they're damn they have the only way
for it to work with Electromagnetics is they
have to actually damage part of the antenna
It's just like certain array certain antennas, you
know, each component or length of the antenna
is for a certain frequency So if you
have like an ham radio a certain antenna
length and you cut a foot off of
it Now you've lost that frequency band, you
know Your game you could still get it,
but you won't have any gain let's say
right it's about game and Then frequency of
course Which is the resonance of your antenna
and all that and six foot is the
magic number and then you know How it
goes if you know, I won't get into
ham radio, but right so discussion but And
earlier today I was even telling someone, you
know There's only a handful of principles that
you can learn meaning two handfuls Let's say
a dozen or so principles about the physical
world that you can apply to everything else
So if someone shows you an invention or
a doohickey and tells you what it does
you're like, oh they built it using this
this And that right Just like the concept
if you understand how the airfoil works the
Bernoulli's principle and air wing the bottom of
the wing is flat and The top of
it is curved So when you put air
across it Where it's flat the air will
move quickly and where it's curved the air
removal at a lower speed and because it's
moving at a lower Speed it has a
lower pressure equates lift So you could be
stranded on a deserted island with a bunch
of natives and as long as you can
form an airfoil You can go to the
cliff and jump off and fly away You
can make it out of bamboo and animal
skins or whatever palm leaves as long as
it would had entire structural integrity, right?
Oil is an airfoil Yeah, Bernoulli's principle is
very simple and you know as pressure increases
velocity decreases as pressure decreases I'm sorry as
pressure increases velocity decreases as pressure decrease decreases
velocity increases is another principle to throw in
That's where the vortex forms.
That's why if you look at a lot
of airplanes Especially the small ones they have
little things called vortex generators VGs Little fins
like little tabs on the wings to prevent
it because the vortex is going to happen
anyway So you make it happen where you
want it to happen?
So, you know if you have like a
small even like a Piper Cub, you can
you can cut your takeoff Requirement by 20
or 30 percent with VGs and also your
stalls, you know, you could your cruise speed
will be reduced So there's more there's more
concept to it.
You know F equals P over V is
a simple mathematical equivalent So this is like
I'm giving you one example of a handful
of things that you can teach Young people
or anyone who wants to learn everything about
the world, right?
Yeah That's what I wanted.
That's where it's at Yeah, and the other
thing is, you know, I've said, you know
Greek why don't you do is it?
Well, I have to speculate on it.
I could easily put all this together easily
It's a lot of it'll take me about
six months to a year and I've sort
of said I would do it But I
decided not to because it would be speculative
Spend a lot of work put this out
do a subscription based or a membership base
so so influx of credit could come in
so it could be used to grow the
project right and Or sustain it and and
then if I do all this and it's
speculative Well, how many people are going to
join how much credit is going to come
in?
You know, it's like, you know, I don't
I don't want to speculate, you know, I'd
rather just go Paint, you know do wallpaper
someone's kitchen for 300 bucks.
At least I know that you know, I
do this I'm gonna get that right?
Yeah, I don't want to speculate like I'll
put all this stuff together Put it out.
Maybe who's gonna buy like people who write
books are speculating, you know, well, I sold
a million copies I do do you think
you would oh, I don't know, you know,
it's speculative, you know It's like and then
when you look at your audience, you're like
humans.
No, they're not gonna get this, you know,
it's just too simple But to prove the
point wrong in a in on on a
general level Is look there's people that That
still email then people like yourself and other
people say man.
Look, this is great stuff.
I like it, you know, so great Yeah,
you know Only a few dozen maybe so
Yeah, well, you know sometimes in there you
get nervous to call in because you know
what you say about no real man left
You know, sometimes I feel like I'm talking
to the smartest smartest guy I left on
this planet I'm not smart.
I'm just less stupid mom maybe Yeah, right,
but but here Yeah Yeah Getting back to
what you were saying before It's it's how
how are you gonna train the pagan to
have a mindset and that and that you
almost have to start So simplistic like teaching
a baby with well And no because yes
and no yes, yes That's the principle but
no because are they cosmically censored and if
they're cosmically censored there's no you can do
Cosmic censorship is an example.
And then there's then when they censor you
Cosmically the got the gods What what they'll
do then they'll say okay.
Do we give them like which package of
censorship?
Do we give them just the general censorship?
So they're like bipedal cattle or do we
give him the stubborn element and the rebellious
element also like the college professor who's Teaching
about the moon landings and you say well
There's no evidence of it and also all
the evidence that they show proves that it's
false and the college Professor says that even
if the astronauts confess that they never went
to the moon.
I would still say they did Yeah, then
okay.
So that's like not only do you have
the stubborn and the Arrogant now, you've got
the twisted mindset like they're just playing crazy,
right?
That's a thrown in also so for example
you Bruce and I think you're absolutely correct
Yeah on that, you know, like I say
out of ten that I've ever Lightly and
I do mean lightly spoke about it Maybe
to Come back for more and I and
I leave it at that I don't want
to know if they still do or don't
or how right it's up to them.
Yeah.
Yeah, and also they'll come back Yeah, if
they're more social they want to talk together
and because you know, it's like scripture with
the council, right?
There's wisdom exact right if you don't understand
if one person might know a little more
about the other and show it a different
way But you got to realize that most
people are crazy meaning they're they're just insane
And they and the really insane people are
the ones that seem normal initially because that's
how they invite You know the the contact
right, right?
Because if someone's totally violently crazy and they're
always flailing and foaming at the mouth and
their eyes are bulging and their skin You
know is totally cut you're gonna keep your
distance talking about the kind of crazy like
like a doctor a lawyer Judge a priest
a rabbi those people are crazy Also be
in other words a they wear the facade
That you know, they're they're representing Yeah, they're
representing something and then you approach them and
you if you if you're just like one
of the cattle they seem fine But if
you're critical thinking and slightly well-informed, you'll
see these people are nuts Oh, yeah, because
they're just you know, they'll just tell you
it doesn't matter what you're saying Just do
this and you're like, wait a second.
I thought you're an attorney or I thought
you were a priest I thought you're a
you mean it doesn't matter Right Yeah, but
you've been pretty spot-on on this and
everything I was listening to Greek speak in
2016 and it was a recording with you
and have Charlie 2015 and then you pretty
much brought up nonchalantly like oh, yeah, that's
that whole, you know pedophilia room and stuff
That's gonna come up Pretty soon in the
media and not so much later and it
was going on at the same time in
2016 the whole Pizzagate thing.
So you call it out afterwards.
I called it before.
Yeah Yeah, well or yeah even I was
a little yeah, I was a little bit
more even prior to that I say you're
going to see that there's going to be
a normalization and an outcoming of this really
disgusting repugnant stuff like cannibalism and child molestation
and You know just all this stuff is
going to start coming out and it's and
it's not going to overturn society It'll be
it'll be in society.
You'll know about it, but it'll be like
a big deal and that's exactly, you know
It takes a year and a half to
take place for a presidency to get any
certain stream effects and a year and a
half Later almost exactly that's when the whole
immigration things are to come up again Mm
-hmm, well, they've been floored it came in
hard and then it went away just like
that.
No Trump is Trump is just a there
at okay the whenever if I told you
like Let's bring up a company like coca
-cola or whatever, you know Like the president
of coca-cola this the president of coca
-cola that eventually you're gonna be tired of
hearing about the executive aspect Cocoa and you
want to know well, what is coca-cola?
How does it taste?
Is it good for you, right?
So when you talk about the presidency, okay,
he's a president of what well, what is
it and is it good for you?
Big for United States.
It's not none of it is good.
It is such a distraction As a matter
of fact the the up until Lincoln the
presidency was considered a very minor role in
people's minds In other words if you before
late before the Civil War American Civil War
if you brought up the presidency to anyone
here They were like, well, I hope he
just does a good job and keeps his,
you know, just keep him worried He you
know, just he's got to do what he's
got to do.
That's it You know people then were concerned
about the bankers Well, they were better off
There's a trip that was a time of
tremendous wealth and expansion because if you're poor
you can't expand right, right?
You know, you know if you're really poor,
you're not going to move And and and
and develop something somewhere else Whenever you hear
about all these migrations because people are poor
There's always someone on the other side that
has to have the wealth to accommodate them
You know poor people don't move to other
poor people neighborhoods, you know I mean they
try to you know, go to somewhere where
they can get something for worth the effort
I mean there is cross movement like that,
but not in that would change, you know
a national status There was tremendous wealth being
poured into the country extracted from the country
then and all that, you know But you
see then by the by the mid 1800s.
It was time for The Westphalia thing to
kick out, you know Which is the idea
of nation-states and make the US a
sovereign state Which is privately owned all these
because what people don't know you could look
this up.
This is in not non-conspiratorial reference material
all of the colonies all the states were
Corporations by the way, that's why Which one
is it Rhode Island's considered a plantation right
or which one is it?
Yeah, yeah, they're farms are either called farms
the Commonwealth's Yeah homes that yeah, that's what
they're still called there were corporations Yeah, yeah,
and they had administers that were governors and
a governor is just a captain of a
ship when a captain of a ship Gets
off his ship and creates a settlement.
He's now the governor Yep Right a captain
of a ship today when you hear he
was a captain of a ship Well, it's
either a cargo ship a tanker ship or
a cruise boat or a Navy Admiralty, it's
all it's all commercial.
Yeah, it's all commercial.
Yeah So what happened you had the 13
colonies operating the way they did which were
13 corporate projects they expanded under some kind
of Semi-unified government under the Articles of
Confederation there were Confederation people don't even know
what the word Confederation means this means a
group and The idea was That obviously these
people don't know how to handle such a
level of economy and economy is not money
money It's just what you use as a
means of exchange the economy is different than
you had managers back then to or presidents
In the confederacy I call them managers But
and and then you had the various nobilities
that were heavily entrenched and involved with the
states, and they said yeah We we want
it all.
It's just you know this this country stuff
is bullshit It's territory time you know Canada
u.s..
Mexico is one piece That is also the
same part of the rest the whole side
here And I've given a little bit of
information Right now the everything from Canada all
the way down to Chile is owned by
one group except for Uruguay And no one's
asked me why and that's another That's interesting
and the reason why I'll tell you because
it goes the system goes through the Universal
Post Office And Universal Post Office is is
a different ad in Uruguay has a different
aspect to it You the the in other
words in you know see an empire when
you hear Empire.
That's a ruler over the whole world As
I the Kings are below the Emperor always
So when you in order to have an
empire you the first thing you need to
okay, you cannot say you have Established an
empire until you've established what most people say
military because they don't know No a post
that's right to get information and documents back
and forth So if your post goes so
right now, can you mail anything to anywhere
in the world yes, or no yes pretty
much?
Okay, because you have a Universal Post Office,
and that's how those are the codes just
like zip codes Yeah Uruguay has he is
the center of the of the post the
Universal Post Office for this side of the
world Oh, it's a neutral kind of spot.
Yeah Anyway, there's more discussion There's there's a
set of uniform laws and things that they
use there's nothing to do with you And
or anybody that that'll affect you, but those
that just want to know so let's say
someone came from another planet Say hey, what's
going on here at least you could give
them the scoop So that you already have
a Worldwide system in place It just needs
a worldwide leader right and and you're waiting
for him.
He's about 20 years old.
He's in his 21st year now Yeah, he's
of a Syrian extraction too, yeah, he's in
his 21st year Into
their nations, right What do you mean by
migration and the people in the nations, please
give me a little bit more on that
Yeah, well Israel here's interesting thing if you
study you got to look at everything both
the secular which is the the dumb shit
and and this and the prophetic There's a
very strong undertone From the political powers that
be that Israel will not exist after 2021
2022.
They're gonna break it up right Anybody who
doesn't know this or whatever just look it
up on your own as a I don't
want to get into that discussion this is
like, you know, the The political groups that
you know people the power brokers.
That's what they want to do, right?
They see there's more value in the entire
Middle Eastern region than just focusing on this
little country and by the way the same
people who own the United States also own
Israel but That would be pretty easy to
see right, right.
Okay, right so That's going to be that's
going to change and it has to change
right because it's a you're right because in
other words if you read in Zechariah and
other prophecies that it will be Israel be
taken back as as An individual piece or
part that is separate from the rest of
the world, right?
prophetically Jerusalem when it says Jerusalem, it means,
you know, the basically the Judean and they're
gonna be subjected to the Palestinians Well for
yes, if you look at a repeat of
judges, yes, they will be if you look
at Netanyahu being 12 the 13th or 14th
Judge or Prime Minister of Israel were repeat
Samson And if you look at Samson's time
the Palestinians or the Philistines are the ones
that had an upper hand, didn't they?
Yeah, yeah That's where you get well Remember
the story where Samson he wanted to prank
the wheat fields the Palestinians because they were
taking all the wheat he tied the tails
of two foxes together and lit him on
fire, you know, like the animal rights people
now would freak out and Threw them in
the field and you know, they let the
field on fire.
You ever see Firefox Yeah We think it
comes from Like Facebook and and there's a
Masonic logo if you could look at the
F in the blue I think I posted
in chat once yes, and Google Mail is
the apron the Freemasonic apron Right.
So this goes so now this goes back
way before anything like that So it's not
only the it's secret society So in other
words, you're seeing that the the message is
put in front of you Yes, the show
the dumbed-down secret society crap from Freemasonic
shit, which is what it is And then
you have the biblical stuff.
So I mean if you told someone Firefox
is a biblical Extraction, you know what, you
know, but what it's also well, what does
it symbolize?
It's tearing up the Philistines, right?
so Now Samson faces a tragic end he
loses his life and takes out more Palestinians
Right.
So this is right now is Samson right
now is probably young then too, right?
well, the Prime Minister the is going to
be another Prime Minister like all merit is
making trying to make not really a comeback
but Criticizing that this type of behavior should
end but it's going to get worse.
In other words The the current political the
sovereign state the corporation known as Israel is
going to get even harsher With the the
group of people who are not a sovereign
state, by the way Are the Palestinians right
because they say is they're not even a
nation, right, but they kind of are in
a way They're they you know, if you're
you get a birth certificate from Israel if
you're born in there, I think But you're
not an Israeli.
They just administer Mm-hmm.
I'm not sure Yeah So anyway, it's gonna
get worse All those people that live in
the West Bank are gonna perish if they
don't move You know, there's hundreds of thousands
of them there.
There's over a hundred thousand Palestinians living in
Lebanon as refugees huge camps You don't hear
anything about that But Anyway Their paper is
also very silent on that which I find
odd.
Oh Yeah, because that you don't really have
a media yeah, you know the the Internet
is is really like I say a cross
between the phone book and The television and
the telephone and the television really and maybe
a little access to some reference material It's
not like the Internet is not like it
was 12 15 years ago where it was
all HTML white pages, you know, you know
Stuff that made semi made sense But What
what's interesting is this coming of the next
prime minister and the prime minister after him
that was going to be very much against
well, I should say Extremely hostile to the
modern-day Philistines, which are the Palestinians Coincides
with this Israel being dissolved by 2021 2022
That's in on the books, by the way
by the You know this the societies that
control, you know, like the medium societies, you
know Like the groups intelligence agencies and that
be what people call the shadow government What
Shelley was having a really hard time when
I was trying to explain this to him
There is no shadow government.
You have the Government for public consumption, which
is there to just collect financial papers improperly
illegally or whatever Then you have the shadow
government Which is basically those that control them
and then you have the owners that make
all the decisions.
He couldn't get that most people can't because
once they do then of course, obviously you
realize that everything you think you're knowing saying
is a complete lie, but The essence of
what I'm saying though is this coming Round
about what the the Palestinians which is going
to be very bad is going to change
Israel Yeah, and it coincides with the 2021
2022 dissolving Israel as it is Like, you
know Kissinger said that The Trilateral Commission.
This is Council of Foreign Relations the Bilderberg's
The the English monarchy says Israel has to
go.
I Mean they will give them till 2021
2022 and that's perfectly lines up prophetically with
what I just mentioned the next Prime Minister
interesting Yeah, I don't get into I think
I brought up enough.
I put out enough Information that if anyone
really wanted to make a project of it
would come back and say hey I want
to talk more and no one really, you
know is doing that which is fine because
I keep my peace and quiet But if
you go back and I don't give it
all in one shot But I have talked
about the future of the Middle East and
how it's gonna Come about before a long
time about ten years ago.
I was talking about this.
Yeah, there's no that question There is over
here.
That's gonna happen over here.
You don't know how it's gonna happen, but
over here They're just gonna get okay the
more technically advanced so sort of technical access
to society has the dumber they're going to
be That's very simple, I mean, I'm just
visiting taking notes I don't read when I
read look at an advertisement or news I
don't look at it like it concerns me
because I'm just visiting right so I can
see it objectively, you know what I mean?
so countries that have access to like very
robust grid systems meaning power and information grids
and and And also, what do you call
amenities?
Like, you know big cities and lots of
travel air airplane trains buses cars cheap fuel
Power grid information grid.
Okay, those people are gonna get dumber and
dumber and dumber to the point where if
you went to sleep now And woke up
three years from now walked outside.
You'd say these people are so dumb That
that you you know that it's just unbelievable
in just three years how stupid they got
right?
Yeah, they're nothing more than cattle walking up
on their on their hind legs This is
the you're gonna see a very rapid progression
of the stupidity and dumbing down of the
more technically advanced countries, so when you look
at like, let's say the Pacific Rim in
Asia the North America and Western Europe where
they have robust information and power grids Most
people are gonna get what it took to
do in 10 years to dumb them down
or 20 years or 30 years They can
do now in a year or two Right
So by the time this rolls 2021 2022
rolls around 2023 the people are going to
be so much dumber than now that but
it'll be fast But gradual gradual in other
words, it'll be light speed gradual And I
mean, it's good you're gonna see a gradual
ism that happens so fast and so acceptable
That you it'll be shocking and it'll seem
normal even anyone listening to me.
That's aware of it Yeah, no wonder why
the anti-christ is gonna be so easy
to come up The chemical chemical and the
cosmic censorship, yeah will be ratcheted up But
but then it's going to be open regarding
religions you see because the Benevolent gods hate
all of the religions that exist right now
and I can speak for them on this
because this is how it's been Memorialized All
of the religions that exist today in the
forms of spirituality are repugnant repugnant means like
disgusting To the benevolent odds and even to
the malevolent gods they are also but the
malevolent gods like it and permit it because
it offers a cover and a Distraction and
keeps people ignorant Right.
Yeah But even even the worst most malevolent
demon will say yeah Christianity and Islam and
the Mormonism and the process that shit is
disgusting man But I I'm glad that it's
there because it provides a good cover for
me You see what I mean, right?
Yeah, and there yeah, I hate it when
I do This kind of talk because you
know what you ain't gonna get this kind
of talk So Now I can't now you
see now it's like I'll go I can't
say go look that up because you have
to really be familiar With the whole piece
the whole thing the whole landscape see Right.
Yeah, I'm just gonna remember what you said
in the past And it's gone off what
I see right now, you know, I Try
to develop those eyes and ears Well, look
like where I am you see You have
to be able to explain it Like where
I am today, there's an incredible thunder and
lightning storm I mean where the Thunder shakes
the ground and if you're standing on a
slab on grade house with no basement You
know the where the concrete slap the house
was vibrating that kind of Thunder I mean
physically moving like wow this is a serious
and the power went off to like three
two one and it came back on and
Okay, so you know how the ether goes
from low to high that means that the
power that was reflecting down all the power
lines And the transformers jumped off the reflectors
known as the conductors the wires and to
go into the Scott sky Now if you
because it was represents a low potential compared
to the potential that was occurring in the
heavens in the sky, right?
But if you use the bullshit physics and
theory that they tell you well if there's
so much power in the sky Why doesn't
it reach down and conduct through the wire
and overload them the wire?
It doesn't do that never does that the
reason why you have transformers exploding is Because
all of those coils in there It wants
to jump off the coil and go into
the sky and it has to go through
all this oil and insulation To do that,
right?
And there you get the blackout because yeah
the power that they're that's reflecting and going
down the wires From the power station through
the whole city wants to leave that and
go because it represents a low potential You
see and this is so simple once you
know, it goes from low to high so
a bullet Flies through the air and things
because it has no potential anymore.
See people would think the opposite They think
a flying bullet has a lot of potential.
It has no potential.
It's released all of that's why it could
penetrate You see so once you understand this
principle now you can develop armaments weaponry To
do to be a very destructive Efficiently once
you understand low to high principle and once
you understand, you know Once a missile or
a bullet is shot out of a barrel.
It has no more potential You get it,
but intuitively it doesn't sound right because it
what do you mean as a potential thing?
I'll go right through the wall and kill
me.
Yeah, that's because it has no potential.
It's going to the higher potential, which is
you Yeah You saw how it flows Yeah,
so once you understand this it's it's backwards
what we've been taught now you start to
see how the universe really works how physics
and nature really works and Just like you
know the method like Ken Wheeler says, you
know, mother nature is not a crack whore
with a calculator She doesn't nature doesn't nature
doesn't do math.
There is no math in nature.
There are no numbers on a flower you
can That's why I have always said math
is nothing more than rational communication if you
go into the store and you say I
need eggs The store people the clerks will
look at you.
They say yeah, we have eggs, you know
That's the conversation ends right there.
And if you say I need eggs again,
they're gonna say this person's crazy But if
you come in and say I need a
dozen eggs, I'll say well here it is.
Let's do it Good.
You're rational now.
You see you need to give them There's
a need Eventually the more you elaborate on
something there is a certain numeric or mathematical
aspect to the conversation that's going to arise
to form rationality That's why they they even
have let's say a number chapter and verse
on scripture because it's very rational If you're
studying scripture to say go to Matthew 24
Matthew 24 verse 3, let's say right.
It's very radical.
Boom.
You go immediately and you can discuss that
aspect of it When that's all you can
do now, it just sounds like the McDonald's
commercial to all be fatty special sauce, right?
So so anyway Yeah, so then the bullet
goes through like a piece of wood or
whatever so on the because it has no
potential, right yeah, no potential, but the front
side is There is no front no back
the bullet The bullet doesn't care whether it
hits the front or the back.
It's just that it hits the wood Again,
stop thinking about the front.
There is no front.
Yeah What happens have you ever seen the
the high speed like the 50 to 10
,000 frame per second when a bullet heats
a piece of steel?
It vaporizes the steel on contact It turns
into vapor right just like electricity you ever
change a car battery with a wrench That's
too long and you bridge the terminals by
accident Not a happy situation And then you
pick up the wrench and part of the
wrench is gone But you'll never find it
because it became a little miniature Hiroshima, right?
Yeah Or a breaker box, you know Well,
yeah, but a bus you ever seen somebody,
you know changing a bus wire or something
something heavy, you know I say bus it's
a heavy piece of metal and shorting that
out in the in the aftermath, you know
And by the way, you ever you ever
been around a very heavy-duty electrical short.
It has that certain smell doesn't it?
Yep Yeah, if you are out at the
Nevada test sites when they were new doing
the nukes or Hiroshima or nine or at
September 11th in Manhattan, that's exactly the same
smell you have So that what that tells
you is atomic and nuclear and thermonuclear is
nothing more than what electrical phenomenon not nuclear
like they say or new or your Electrical
stuff is nuclear a vice versa, right?
Wow What do you think a highly dense
metal ball?
That's Purified very dense.
The density of these radioactive materials is very
high and All of a sudden, you know
like the old trigger mechanisms that the did
not the Germans develop I was gonna say
Nazis, which was the rifle mechanism to get
the uranium off.
What did they shoot?
They shoot a bullet?
Literally down a rifle at a certain speed
if it's too fast It won't work if
it's too slow and work to create what
they call a chain reaction to create to
start the fission, right?
That's how it started and then later on
they got away from the rifle System and
they decided to use implosion with reflectors.
They said of having a bullet hit the
mass they have Explosives formed in the form
of a sphere It would like a cutting
charge.
It's directed inward and then you surround the
whole thing with water That's that's why it's
called a hydrogen bomb There's nothing to a
hydrogens because they use water to increase the
yield and then now that not not that
is not only nuclear Now it's thermonuclear.
It's assured.
In other words guaranteed to create extreme heat
around the environment All these is electrical phenomenon
in the nuclear Armament and the nuclear devices,
you know that they that detonate and by
the way nuclear bombs and devices do not
explode That's a misnomer.
They detonate They've what they call the explosion
or the aftermath depends on the environment the
surroundings of the environment Right Right there what
you call an explosion is because it's so
hot that the surrounding air go explodes Not
the bomb the the device itself is in
other words.
These things are so simple and so miss
They're thought of so poorly I'm giving that
as an example not to talk about Atomics
and nuclear how that stuff really works and
what it is, but every subject is like
that the misdirection the Keeping it concealed, you
know, there's an art form to it and
obviously we're witness to it.
Yes, there's a spiritual Aspect to it.
Yeah, but anything that humans and when a
human opens their mouth Stupid shit's gonna come
out of it just to Matt, you know,
you got to start filtering I mean, this
is how you're gonna live your life on
earth I think it's better to be ignorant
and not paying attention Yeah discern Yeah, but
you're gonna if you learn to discern and
you could do that you're gonna be you're
gonna find yourself isolated You know, you're back
to that same story about the Persian and
the water Exactly drink the cool.
Would you rather know?
Yeah, right Would you rather know and be
unhappy or not know and be happy, right?
It's good knowing Yeah, and there's always a
group of people that are just downright evil
and like I want to know and I
know it's shitty then I want to jump
back in and Be divisive and predatory and
take advantage of these dumb fucks, right?
Right.
Voila.
You've got attorneys doctors banking establishment government people.
That's a priest rabbis There you go The
number one Hmm You see, this is very
simple man.
Look if you have the attitude that you're
just visiting taking notes The likes and dislikes
of the inhabitants is irrelevant Yeah, whether you
like something or dislike it is irrelevant is
do you see it for what it is?
You know and note it and note it
as such.
That's all that matters And it's very simple
you could look at what they call New
Testament writings even the Christ who was really
the chief over this Creation as it is,
you know the remodel he's like there's nothing
here for me.
There's nobody here for me Pretty fucked up
over here.
I have nothing here.
No interest here as it is right now.
I Mean don't you get that when you
read, you know what he said and Joel
But even the even the but the Christ
really who was the you know, the Let's
see chief administrator.
He's like there's nothing here for me men
places too screwed up everything everyone Yeah Some
hard hard tea triple tea you gotta love
it.
Mm-hmm All right, Greek.
Well, um, I got to get ready, but
thank you so much Bruce.
Thank you also as well you guys have
an enjoyable night and Thanks for calling and
then next week, okay I Thanks, all
right, there's anything else some that's good to
have another voice and I'll just Like that,
okay, so I don't know if there's anything
just go back into the office here Yeah,
usually there isn't I think Mm-hmm What
a fascinating discussion Okay, one of us you
increase my research again Which will be which
will be good I think enlightening myself is
is definitely an intro Again, you know, are
you you know, all right.
Well Yeah, so so you enlighten yourself and
now what you find yourself in a either
either you do it in a way Now
you're deeper.
You see you're deeper in the shit or
higher above it, you know, you gotta bring
yourself higher I accept it for what it
is out.
There is on you know, I'm happy with
with what I find out I you know,
I don't let it get to well Let
me just say this then I find it
unacceptable So I have to isolate and insulate
myself exactly exactly what is unacceptable.
Yeah, I do that quite well Mm-hmm
visitors are welcome and very rare So I'm
well either way Well, you know and here's
the thing the you know Just to like
fresco when he did tutoring on art and
other things.
He wanted the most screwed up school children
He didn't want the ones that did well
All right.
So in a sense Being around the most
screwed up people in society is probably your
only chance Yeah, because they haven't accepted but
then again Some of them are so you
can't polish a turd No, you see it's
still a turd on the other end So
some people are screwed up and it's meant
for them to be screwed up.
So either way You know, you have to
use discernment again and don't let it don't
take it personally The only thing you could
take personally is that you run out of
heartbeats you go to sleep and you wake
up at the resurrection all those things You
can take personally you can even take personally
that you are incarnated in this manifestation now
You can do that as well And live
up to it and literally what I mean
live up to it You mean don't let
yourself be on the downside of it because
that's what it's designed for or allowed to
be right?
So Okay, we'll be done for a while
let's just it became more of a robust
Call with three and getting some input and
hope he does well And you as well
Bruce, so with that said, thanks for all
you do.
Yes, and we're almost exactly Appreciate your conversation
as always Okay, good.
Good, and we'll do it again next week
Okay, you take care now.
Okay.
Thanks much.
Take care.
Bye.
Bye