There's a light over the ocean.
And greetings folks, we're live with the Greek.
And how are you doing tonight, Greek?
Greetings.
Doing okay.
Yeah, we'll just do another Sonic this week.
See if we can catch up on stuff
casually.
I hope people realize that I do not
go out of my way to do any
of this.
If any of this public emanations or anything
puts inconvenience on me, I don't do it.
So it's basically a very casual setup.
I'm not into making projects or writing books
or anything like a lot of morons are
thinking they're going to educate anyone or share
the truth.
Actually, they don't even know what that is.
That's why very often when you show someone
Greek speak, they can't handle that triple T
rating.
Right.
Anyway, they want rated S.
Rated stupid.
It's not just rated T, it's triple T.
So what's interesting is you have to always
look at why are you doing something?
I call it self-assessment.
What are you embarking on?
I'll bring up a point.
I've been looking a bit on the Internet
lately because I'm trying to put together a
couple of reference things for a project.
It's interesting, there's a lot of stuff towards
Christians now regarding Biblical stuff.
Like Christianity doesn't touch this or the church
doesn't.
What these morons don't know, meaning the Christians
or any religion, you could actually do the
same thing.
There's a lot of it going on with
the Koran also, with Muslims.
Not so much with Buddhists and Hindus because
they're already too far gone in terms of
a cognitive understanding or studying anything.
But what's interesting about the Christians is that
if they keep doing this studying, they're going
to find out that the truth and scripture
and history is 100% against Christianity.
In other words, there'll be nothing left.
You know how I keep saying that Christianity
is 0% Biblical?
It's true.
There's nothing of it as Biblical.
There's a difference between having the appearance of
it.
It's just like when you go to the
bank to get a loan.
They are not lending you anything.
Zero.
There is no loan there.
It's really hard for people to comprehend that
because, well, it's been going on for so
long, everybody does it, nobody really knows what
you're saying.
That's not the point.
The point is, Christianity is 0% Biblical.
If it was 1% or 5%
and you were rational, you would have to
grant them that.
You'd have to say, well, it's Biblical here.
You can also say that it's a product.
You do know the reality of Christianity is
geographical.
It changes geographically.
There's a God under each geography or each
nation that rules it.
Even then, they can't see that.
The whole thing because there's a couple of
people out there trying to do lectures and
things.
I want to make a comment because sometimes
I'll pull up a YouTube on metallurgy and
it'll say recommended for you because I'll look
up stuff of the period.
There'll be some guy doing a lecture on
how the Christianity tradition is contrary to Biblical
stuff.
I want to put a comment.
I'm like, if you actually knew the truth
and you told people the truth, no one
would listen to you, number one.
Number two, there is no single thread.
Actually, there are a couple of threads, but
there is no single thread that you can
pull that would unravel that entire cheap sweater.
You know how a cheap sweater, you keep
pulling it?
There's not just one thing you can pull
on.
I tend to find that the best thing
to pull on for the Christians is there
is no crucifixion.
I noticed I just now went up to
chat a little bit.
Was it you?
I was surprised.
I saw that a while ago.
Actually, that was from the 90s, wasn't it?
I didn't even read that.
I just saw the title.
I think that was recent.
That's what kind of caught my eye.
The overall setting, the context is true.
There is no crucifixion.
It was a stoning, but the rest of
it is a dummy load.
We can discuss why it's a dummy load
and how it's set up to be a
dummy load, spiritually also.
I remember that from the 90s.
Not in the 90s, but I remember that
early on when I was researching.
When I saw it, I said, no, this
is not the correct approach.
What's wrong about the approach is very simple.
It's trying to cite some kind of synoptic
apocryphal work or something.
You don't have to do that.
He did throw a lot of that in
there.
You don't need any of that.
No.
You just get it out of scripture itself.
It stands on its own.
That's the dummy load.
Right there, meaning it's not time yet.
You could plant the idea there was no
crucifixion and it was a stoning, but people
will say, that's not in the Bible.
That's from this thing here, but of course
it's in the scripture.
No one will see it because no one
studies it.
That's why I started off saying, if I'm
taking a nap and someone says, come talk
to give them some Greek speak, I'm like,
hell no.
When I wake up, maybe if I feel
like it.
Because there's no reason.
You have to know where you are.
There's no purpose for it other than just
for myself to say it.
Like I said, there's no one that can
articulate this that I've ever run into all
these years.
Maybe one or two people.
Actually, someone that I'm no longer in touch
with maybe did.
I could say very clearly no one can
articulate Greek speak or these topics at all.
I've got to give a little bit of
credit A for effort, or E for effort,
to 6187 or whatever.
He says he tries to do it and
all that.
That's fine.
Yeah, I guess he does.
E for effort.
As it stands, I could clearly say how
simple any topic is.
It's not one thing or another.
It's can you look at anything objectively, reduce
it very quickly, simple terms.
That's why when we discuss scripture you'll notice...
And get to the point.
If you want to know the verses, go
look it up because you have computers now.
Even before that there were topical references you
could use before computers.
I'm not going to give verses and whatever.
You go figure it out on your own.
That's the two old beef patties thing.
I'll give you the overall picture, which is
what you're lacking on anything.
That overall picture is lacking until there's clarity.
You've got to come up for some real
tacky music for the triple T rated Sonics,
right?
You know how they have triple X rated
music?
This is definitely triple T stuff.
The humans are in really bad shape.
I'm having some coffee.
I'm going to mute out in a second.
Go ahead and entertain everyone for about 30
seconds.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to make some noise.
I'm just going to mute.
All right.
Make some noise.
That I can do.
Let's go with that.
Okay.
That was quick.
And easy.
I had everything ready except for the grounds.
That happens.
Yeah.
And being crafty to put the cone right
over the glass instead of the carafe.
Hopefully people have already figured out that coffee
machines are for shitty coffee, right?
Because they ruin the coffee.
Unless you have one of those special ones,
if you could put up with the synthesized
results, even though they're good coffees, those Koreg
machines, the little pods you put in there,
push a button and a needle with hot
water penetrate.
Okay.
Those are very specific for that.
And they still use that same concept where
the water goes through it at pressure.
So I hope people have realized that the
way you make tea and coffee is not
the way that it's portrayed in the conventional
convenience modes with machines and things like that.
And you have very good sonic events based
on that alone.
So help yourself, folks.
Also, go back on the chat.
I think there's not much going on.
That's an interesting book.
If you know Greek speak, you'll get more
out of it.
Because it talks a lot about the ether
and how things are.
And if you know scripture, you'll know that
you'll get more out of it.
Because there's so much unknowable.
You know they say you only use 10
% of your brain.
It's actually like 1%.
The brain is fully functional.
It's just that they're telling you that the
only stuff you know is what's put out
by the state and the attorneys.
That was the other subject that I wanted
to bounce into if possible.
Celebrityism.
The art of celebrity.
How it's affected culture.
How it's manipulated.
The tools of the mystery people.
Those are the showmen.
That goes back to the circus.
The church.
The stars.
You'll notice that.
That's the circus.
Circus was a sacred place in ancient culture.
It was always a deity behind it.
That's why when you read...
How many times do stars come up in,
let's say, old sacred works?
Always.
So that's why they call themselves stars.
They're tying you into...
It's just a dummy load.
But at the same time, when you read
about ancient practices, that was done around entertainment,
as well as being sacred.
And how it controls the mobs, and what
it gives the mobs to think about.
The Gustav Le Bon stuff all kicks in.
It's like the perfect connection to the hive.
And also Alexander the Great, if you want
to call him that, did use entertainment.
He didn't do what the Romans and other
conquerors did.
He came in, and he just convinced a
group of people.
Literally convinced them.
Or persuaded them, I should say.
Whether it was through intimidation or finance or
whatever means.
And the initial projects that were put in
place by the Greeks Macedonians, when they went
through the world, was entertainment complexes.
Every area that he had conquered, supposedly, had
an amphitheater of some sort.
There's a place out in Afghanistan, middle of
nowhere, and they've dug up this Greek small
amphitheater.
He did it through entertainment.
That's why it's gotten to the point since
Walt Disney that now universities look at what
they are doing in entertainment and put that
in their textbooks.
Like the Kennedy assassination.
That was a television for the public.
Made for TV.
9-11 was literally a made for TV
event.
All these false flags.
By the way, speaking of false flags, you've
got to tip your hat to Iran.
I was watching the news, they had a
military parade shot up.
And obviously, I don't know if you've been
around ever or seen a real film what
it's like when people are getting shot at.
Or what they look like when they're shot.
Well, I have.
I'm not going to get into those details.
And if you saw the typical grainy footage
and the certain characters, the way they acted
with Iran, because typically these false flags are
used as a pretext for something else.
So the Persians are like, hey, they could
do it and it works for them to
justify things.
Why don't we do it and use it
to justify what we're doing?
It's very obvious in your face they did
it with the Plasco building.
Two years ago they imploded using a...
The interesting thing about the demolition charge, the
nuclear demolition charge that they use, well, first
of all, it wasn't really nuclear as it's
discussed now.
It was more of an atomic, which doesn't
go high yield.
Like the Murrow building in Oklahoma, that was
an atomic charge, not a thermonuclear.
In other words, if anyone understands how these
devices work, the atomic is a straight up
implosion of fissionable material.
The thermonuclear is an initial charge of fissionable
material setting off a mass of specially treated
water.
That's why they call it a hydrogen bomb,
not because it has anything to do with
hydrogen.
It's because it deals with a form of
water that starts with a T.
Actually, it's water that makes it.
So they did it with the Plasco building.
It's interesting, I researched the Plasco building pretty
closely and I didn't save it, but at
one point the NNSA got interested in the
Plasco building.
The NNSA is the National Nuclear Security Administration.
Why would they be interested in a small
office tower fire in Tehran?
And all the firemen were told, get away
from the building, it's going to be destroyed.
Not all the firemen, but the key people.
And also, after it fell, they were clearing
the debris and they're pulling out hunks or
masses of molten metal.
And it's 2700 degrees to maintain that.
So they were showing the world that we
could do it too.
The Americans did it and no one figured
it out, obviously.
Not no one, but the majority.
And we can justify whatever we want also.
So the Persians go back, if you remember
citing scripture in the Book of Daniel, that
was one of the toughest principalities of the
time to deal with.
So I just want to bring up that
aspect of Persia with the military.
Because right away, see, they're justifying the shooting
at the military parade to go after US
and Israeli interests.
Just blame it on them.
And the response was interesting.
The Americans said, look in the mirror, which
is the perfect answer.
Because look, yeah, we do it, you do
it.
Basically, you see yourself in the mirror.
There's no one else doing it.
It's very interesting when you can see how
much is being disclosed.
Oh, by the way, I'm reckoning around the
second day of the 8th moon, maybe the
third at noon.
I think it was the second, yeah, already
at noon.
It was the 8th moon, which was a
very bright moon.
We'll see how we get into a 13th
moon.
If not, we'll look at the possibility of
an intercalative year later.
So just beware of the dummy load and
other things like a dummy load.
Because if you're going to hide a dummy
load, you can't put a label on it.
Dummy load.
But humans are in really bad shape and
have been in bad shape.
People think it's contemporary, and it's not.
So I would say that it's chronic.
Chronic means you don't know the cause, basically.
When you say something is chronic, it's another
way of saying we only know about the
symptom, we don't know the cause.
Otherwise it wouldn't be chronic.
They would treat the cause and it would
go away.
Right, because they don't know the cause.
Instead of touting their ignorance, they just say
it's recurring.
Of course it's going to be recurring.
Also, someone put in about any Mexican or
Latin recipes.
I think that's interesting.
They probably have a propensity towards that flavor.
That's the wrong thing to ask me.
I don't.
I find them to be very primitive culturally,
Latins.
I should say that because I'm not talking
about European, I'm talking about the Americas, the
Caribbean, North and South.
I don't like very low base type unless
they have an influence from French or Italian
or other influences.
Because you've got to think about it.
The Caribbean and the American Latins, they did
not exist prior to the Jesuit-Catholic invasion.
The Jesuits and Catholics invaded the indigenous peoples
and then interbred with them.
They turned the countries into penal colonies.
Brazil, places like that were penal colonies.
So the worst of the worst of Europe
came over and interbred with the surviving Indian
stock.
That's your culture.
I personally don't like Mexican food.
I don't like Latin food.
I find it to be refreshing if you
come from a culture, let's say an area
geographically where it's a convenience food.
For example, if you live in New York
in the 70s, 80s and 90s, a convenience
food was not a fast food or McDonald's
or whatever.
It was going to a Dominican or Puerto
Rican restaurant because you got a big plate
of rice and beans for three bucks.
It was more than a pound or two
pounds of food.
You know what I mean?
The Mexican food back in the day, you
got a burrito which weighed more than a
pound for a few bucks.
You still can find them.
You have to look though.
You have to look.
They'll pack you full.
In other words, you need a pound of
food per day, but if you go buy
a burrito and it's a pound and a
half, you bring it home or if you
have the whole thing for lunch, your boss
is not going to be happy.
You'll want to nap after that.
To me, it's kind of like whatever.
My suggestion was study the food of Mexico
City.
Here in town, there's a lot of Mexican
in southwest Arizona, but it's the northern part
of Mexico, which is the poorest part of
Mexico.
It's crappy food because the quality, they don't
know, but they're just poor people.
They're just glad to eat, put something in
their belly.
There is a Mexican restaurant here that it's
not open anymore.
It was the cuisine of Mexico City and
the white people that went there didn't know
what to make of it because they didn't
have burritos and things like that.
They didn't have the mushy rice.
It was actually very well prepared, French influence.
You had butter sauces with white wine and
garlic.
You see what I mean?
It's very different.
If you have a propensity or you do
like Latin food, when you say that, I
don't think of it for myself, but I
know when people ask that question, tacos, beans
and rice, burritos, that type of stuff.
If you go to the east coast of
all of America, it's Dominican, Puerto Rican, Cuban.
It's just filler food.
I've been around people that are from that
culture.
They're pretty ignorant as a group generally.
They go for cheap flavoring.
Their food is loaded with salt and MSG.
It's always overcooked to death.
I don't like Latin food from that respect.
If you find a hybrid, let's say influence
of Mexico City is a quick one.
Argentina is very different also.
I would research and study that.
Personally, what I like to do is Eurasian
mix.
I like Asian recipes, all of Asia, and
European and Middle Eastern.
Basically, Eurasian, Mediterranean,
Eastern cuisine, Mediterranean, I call it.
I personally don't.
If there was a street that had Italian
food, Middle Eastern food, Israeli food, Mexican food,
Puerto Rican food, Cuban food, I wouldn't look
at the Mexican food or the Puerto Rican
food or the Dominican food.
I wouldn't even look at it.
I wouldn't even consider it if the other
ones were there.
That's me though.
The reasons I'm giving you, I think, are
founded in a qualitative nature, not a taste
factor.
I would clearly suggest if you want to
understand the height of what could be the
height of Latin food on this side of
the world, it would be the food and
culture of Mexico City, which is French.
It's always an interesting subject to tell people.
I don't cook Latin food.
I mean, other than beans and rice, I
do enjoy that.
It's better than hamburgers.
Beans and rice gets kind of tired after
a while.
Let's say you were living...
If you were going to live on it,
you'd be like, okay, well, it's always good
to have it around.
But other than beans and rice, you're going
to have to look for some Mediterranean influence
or something like that.
Again, if you've ever been to anyone's house
that's Puerto Rican, Cuban, Dominican or whatever, the
Mexican, everything's just overcooked.
This is typical, not always, but for sure,
if you expect the food to be overcooked,
overflavored like with synthetic flavorings, you will not
be disappointed.
They don't know how to cook meat.
They don't know how to cook rice.
I mean, it's just as a general group.
There might be an exception.
I've never met one, and I've always been
seeking out culinary adventures.
That's what I say about that.
Is it because I personally don't like them?
No.
I just don't like the quality that they
put out.
I like to say, well, I like American
food.
What should I do?
I say, steer away from the whole thing.
Don't even bother.
Yes, is it possible?
There are now in New York City some
gourmet comfort food diners.
They have a mac and cheese.
They have American meatloaf.
It's like $35 for a meatloaf plate, but
it's like Angus and Kobe beef with organic
sourdough.
You know what I mean?
It's like really high-end ingredients, but still
that's a very rare exception.
My suggestion is if you like the umami,
food that tastes good without using synthetic flavors,
I would suggest gearing towards obviously being cross
-latitude, but a Eurasian, Mediterranean diet.
Figuring out what people in European countries eat
and figuring out what people in Asian countries
eat.
Making a mix of that.
That works by the way, north and south.
When you flip over the...
Let's say you're in Australia and it's cold.
Don't bother looking cross-latitude on Australia.
You're going to find a lot of ocean
and a bunch of people that are eating
extremely local indigenous fruits and vegetables and crickets,
basically.
You're not going to do well on the
southern hemisphere cross-latitude.
You're best flipping up to the northern hemisphere
and just like I think someone I see
is learning about Korean food.
Yes, the best thing about Korean food is
and strictly the best thing about Korean food
is resetting one's positive intestinal flora and fauna,
which would be they use a lot of
pickles.
A lot of fermented vegetables and fish.
There's a pretty good Korean barbecue place here.
It's run by a bunch of old ladies,
literally.
The youngest cook is 75 and there's one
that manages about 90.
Looks like four of these old women.
Yeah, they're really slow though, so you got
to go on an off day.
I walked in there recently and there was
half the tables were full and half of
those half people had menus open, which means
they haven't ordered yet and we were sitting
there for 20 minutes still and no orders
taken.
In other words, going to a place that's
operated by the youngest person is 75.
It sounds good, but it practically isn't.
The service is not going to be good,
right?
But anyway, we ordered just a simple rice
dish and she comes with a platter with
five smaller dishes of various pickles.
Pickled root vegetable, pickled cabbage, a steamed spinach,
a pickled fish cake.
So, you know, the pickle and fermented foods
are biologically active, right?
That's what yogurt is known for.
Preserved foods are biologically active.
And they tend to reset the ecology and
environment in one's gut, let's just say.
And the gut I define from the back
of the throat all the way down to
just before about a couple of feet before
it makes its way out.
I think the large intestine, the very end
of the colon, I wouldn't think is part
of your gut and your mouth isn't, but
the back of your throat is I would
suggest.
It's your gut.
Because you have a pain in your stomach,
you kind of feel it all the way
up there, you know.
And it will naturally close and contract so
you don't eat, you know, if you're not
hungry.
So I would say that's your gut.
So that whole entire area is where you
have that, I call it positive intestinal flora
and fauna, fungus and bacteria.
Undefined as people would like to define it
using their orthodox sciences, meaning they're there, there
is an active layer on the body that
assists symbiotically your body to maintain proper digestion
and transmutation and induction of food.
So pretty much that's the spiel on that.
And if anybody else got any other spiel,
which is German for speak, I guess, right?
Or Yiddish, actually.
Sprach.
Sprach is Deutsch for speak.
Yeah, so again, back to the food, there
is a seasonal change.
I would suggest Mediterranean, Eurasian.
Right, exactly.
And the food is not getting better.
I'm seeing things in the open markets, you
know, that the livestock shop at that I
never imagined would be pre-cooked and vacuum
sealed on a shelf, unrefrigerated kind of thing.
Like, you know, I've seen that.
I've seen things vacuum packed and pre-prepared
things that I never imagined would be such.
Like pre-cooked rice vacuum packed on a
shelf for sale.
I mean, that's like MRE stuff.
You know what I mean?
Like meal ready military food.
And people are buying, they don't know.
Right now it's down to just livestock management,
whether you're whether it's the sniffles, the cold,
food, government, education, religion, all that stuff that's
out there that people are dealing with or
involved in is simply livestock management.
They're like nothing more than livestock at this
point.
Human livestock.
Odds and ends.
I have greetings.
Just tuned in and wanted to try to
pop a question in.
Recently listened to an old talk show and
the Greek briefly mentions his involvement with manufacturing
copper tools for working with soil because the
way of iron tools discharge the networks in
the soil.
Just wondering if there's anyone out there who
has put together a good report on the
subject.
Can't find anything on the rectangle.
Thank you.
Yes, I've done that before.
I actually have them here.
I could post some photographs, but not necessary.
I think Shawberger basically came up with the
idea through observation on how ancients used farm
implements or what they were made of also
and how they used them.
Yeah, there's a PK Institute in Sweden I
think makes them still.
Basically non-ferrous.
Plastic would be just as good pretty much.
Just non-ferrous because you're cutting.
I've done some pretty good remedial work with
it, but I haven't taken photographs.
I might have photographs actually with a pecan
farm and other things like that in question
I should say, but we have done experimentation
and the direct comparison in some cases is
outstanding and sometimes it's very minimal, but it's
always better with the copper implement.
If you want to get into a more
materialistic observation of what happens just like here
because of the way iron tools discharge the
networks in the soil, one way to consider
those networks also is to consider them like
a small capillary void in the soil.
If soil is not hard packed that means
that there's air space in it, right?
And those air spaces after the soil settles,
let's say even if it's loamy soil natural
sediment in the forest develops these vertical chambers
that go to the surface like a pore
all the way down and those chambers that
have air in it tend to leach.
You ever see how crystals leach to the
surface?
If you put a wet cloth on a
piece of metal like iron or copper you
come back a couple of days later you
notice that the oxides have leached to the
surface through the cloth.
So what will happen is you will have
these copper and magnesium and other non-ferrous
metals from dragging these tools in the soil
coat these capillaries in the soil and that
coating, that non-ferrous coating in the soil,
the air space of the soil is the
beneficial because it's also, it prevents certain fungus
from multiplying, it attracts water it's cooling, a
very simple methodology to consider for commercial farms
and I've given advice several times years ago
and it's worked every time with commercial farms,
let's say with citrus, if there is a
heat wave right, a heat wave coming, I
suggest they replace all of the irrigation nozzles
or if they have a water truck with
a good brass, magnesium tin alloy brass or
a pure copper nozzle and the water that
goes over that nozzle at pressure will tend
to have a greater cooling effect than water
that goes over an iron or plastic nozzle,
so it will reduce the harm of a
heat wave on citrus plants.
The opposite, when there is a frost, you
often hear of a frost threatening let's say
Florida citrus crop right, what you do there
is you irrigate with an iron nozzle, not
a steel, now iron when you say iron
it sounds common, it's very difficult to find
pure iron almost all, like an iron, a
very soft iron still has carbon in it,
pure iron is very difficult to find but
a soft iron nozzle the water that goes
through the nozzle will tend to hold heat
and radiate heat itself because of the iron
it will have a warming effect and prevent
the frost from damaging the citrus, so there
is one aspect of it.
At this point if you do have iron
implements, you can coat them with various types
of industrial paints, there are some really good
epoxy paints by the way, like garage floor
epoxies, have you heard of those?
There is the re-tub for the bathtubs,
the two part any paint or coating that
is two part part A, part B, the
catalytic that's an epoxy, that's far more durable
than a regular paint.
I've had some success with coating iron things
with epoxies it will have to be done,
re-coated obviously, because the edge will not
maintain.
What you could do is take, if you
have let's say iron shovels or whatever, or
iron implements on a farm is epoxy coat
them, or epoxy coat them, right?
Also there is pool epoxies, you know, they're
all over in the 70's it was $500
a gallon, now you can get an epoxy
for less than $50 a gallon, or $80
a gallon, so it's really come down in
price and avoid the polyester resin ones, they're
not that strong but if that's all you
have you could use it, you know, it's
the stuff that you make fiberglass resin out
of but what you can do is, I've
done this in the past also on larger
pieces is we go and source out a
brass strip literally just a strip of brass
or copper and form that, drill holes in
it, and use brass screws on the edge
of the implement, the cutting edge because that's
the part that's going to continue to wear
after the body of the implement which is
iron is epoxy coated.
Now you could, I would suggest using stainless
steel screws because if you use the brass
through the iron you'll get galvanic corrosion and
it'll corrode off but I haven't really witnessed
that because the brass pieces tend to wear
off and have to be redone before the
corrosion sets in, so stainless steel screws with
a brass edge or copper on the implement
another thing you can do if you really
want to harken back to primitive days you
build the body and the tool itself out
of wood, completely out of wood and just
the very edge has a copper or brass
strip attached to the cutting edge because that's
the part that will wear so now you
have a wooden rake, a wooden shovel, a
wooden hoe with just a metallic edge because
the body of the tool is there to
support the load, not do the cutting, and
also hold the shape of the tool.
So, well just like what were the first
cars made of?
Wagons, right?
What are wagons made of?
Wood.
Everything was pretty much made out of wood
it was simple, and if you needed an
edge on it, well you put on the
appropriate edge that's another way to, now the
differences could be small they could be great,
it depends on the soil, again with the
tools if you're in a desert environment like
I am, what you do above ground there's
some kind of demonic force in the desert
that no matter how much you try to
mitigate the soil, amend the soil, you know
it's this hard calcified soil, as hard as
a rock with high clay, you dig it
up and you add manure vermiculite, things to
make it light and loamy, and two weeks
later it's hard as a rock again, it's
like as if the earth just ate all
the nutrients out of it.
Yeah, it's amazing how the desert is that
way, and you think well, from a materialistic
physics and scientific point of view that shouldn't
be happening.
If you amend two feet of soil, it
should stay amended unless there's erosion, runoff but
it just seems to be something major, so
the thing to do out here in the
desert is I just do above ground boxes,
I get like building rafters, 12 inch timber
and I build a box and then import
soil, and I do gardening that way so
in that case there may not be that
much of a difference with the copper tools,
because I don't need tools, because it's already
a big planting box and I don't think
that would make any difference because I have
tried and broken quite a few tools trying
to amend the desert environment.
There are certain things that do well in
the desert certain plants yeah, he's
just up to shit, what he did, he
decided to pour sulfuric acid on the soil
to amend it, and it foamed and burned
the soil, not burned with flame, and he
noticed this white powder forming on everything, and
it's not monatomic by the way, there's no
such thing as monatomic, but it's a name,
it's popular, people when you say that they
know what you mean, it's a form of
transmutation so it's like a proto material, proto
meaning first like a protozoa, meaning one cell
yeah, he was doing cotton and feedstock and
other things like that but he got, he
comes from a long family of farmers up
in the Phoenix area but he got absorbed
by the new agers so he got, they
finished his ass off pretty quick David Hudson
yeah, actually he anyway, I don't need to
get into the whole monatomic story, I have
some of his stuff those powders, I have
the real deal, the old, I have some
rhodium actually I could put it on a
camera, only you would see it, or I
should take a photograph of it I have
the stuff that was made in his lab
it's this ultra light fluffy powder lighter than
anything maybe I'll put it on camera, maybe
you could see it Bruce let's see if
I can get it, it might be kind
of dark in here but let's see got
it?
I'll tumble it so you can see how
light it is it's
really light yeah alright, this is from Hudson's
laboratory this is about 20 some odd years
old it has to be polycarbonate, if you
put it in glass it will start going
away to who knows where, it just disappears
and if you put it in polyethylene it
will dissolve the polyethylene or make it really
hard and brittle so it has to be
polycarbonate ok, so yeah, I
guess so I would suggest there's a lot
I could suggest regarding copper tools the concept
regarding the copper tools was based on a
form of futurism when you say futurism what
does it mean?
Well, we need to stop using as much
iron and use copper and non-ferrous materials
for better farming in the future, for the
future generations you don't have a future, sorry
I'm not breaking the news to anyone, I
think everyone inherently knows that by now but
yeah well, you mean the copper
monetizing or the iron monetizing?
yeah, well the thing is, the problems that
humanity has is much bigger than anything they
could realize, I should say in other words,
it's beyond their control but it will be
more clear later, at this point you don't
want to eat plastic food or toxic food
and if you are gardening and you want
a higher yield and all that, that's another
thing for yourself, but from a futurist or
a social point of view, they're screwed, that's
for sure so again, just to make a
suggestion if you are gardening and you want
to use non-ferrous implements put a coating
over it, put a non-metallic edge or
a non-ferrous metallic edge on it, brass
strips are pretty cheap and easy to get,
the best place to go is a metal
recycling place yep, you buy it by the
pound versus by the fitting, by the piece
that's pretty much it, aluminium should be okay
to a certain degree but I would suggest
stay away from aluminium because once it does
once the body recognizes it internally it shuts
down your electric brain, literally it shuts down
your brain piece by piece and it causes
a lot of disturbances in the body which
could lead to what's called overactivity, which is
another term commonly known as cancer which is
an overactivity of cells that's the simplest thing
when you discuss cancer, it's overactivity well how
do you know it's overactive, well because you've
got something growing where it shouldn't be and
it's growing fast and harmful so can't
hear Bruce by the way, I can hear
you do you want to reload the call
or maybe somebody, actually I've heard emails about
people not having problems with audio while we're
streaming so I think it's on their end
if I can hear you, yeah if I
can hear it's going on the stream do
you want to mute out and check the
stream real quick or say something and mute
out you should mute out, oh you're now
coming through yeah you might want to check
it out otherwise I don't see anything else
yep they won't hear you saying that but
let's just call it a short one this
time and I think we've covered enough for
this week thanks Bruce and Bruce says goodnight
everyone and see you next time, thanks Bruce,
bye bye