And greetings folks and greetings Greek and how
are you doing tonight, sir?
Good, how are you doing?
Excellent.
You ready?
Yes.
Oh, good.
I don't know if I've ever really been
excellent on this planet.
I think the excellence will come later.
It's very difficult to achieve that.
No one wants that.
You know how people say, I want you
to do well, and really what they mean
is just don't do better than me, right?
Right, right.
So when you tell people you're doing excellent,
it's kind of like, oh, why is he
doing excellent and I'm not?
But, yeah, and they hate, I was having
a long Skype conversation yesterday, and people really
hate knowledge, you know, and if they didn't,
you wouldn't see people portrayed as nerds in
Hollywood or people made fun of because they
like to study, right?
Right.
And so if people hate knowledge so much,
what are they teaching in universities?
Nothing.
Yeah.
Just a rite to passage.
So I got an e-mail that basically,
I think it was this morning.
Oh, and by the way, before we get
to any of this stuff, let me see
the chat.
There's a question there.
I don't know how much I should scroll
back, but okay, we'll look at the chat
in a minute.
But it's the 7th month, and we had
the 10th day recently, according to Reckoning, and
it was a day or two ago, right?
Right.
So, yeah, just to mention that.
I don't know if that means anything to
anyone out there, the 10th day, the 7th
month.
By the way, that was also the day,
if you go back to September 11th, 2001,
I think it ended on what they call
Monday noon.
Yeah, that's when they nuked, they did the
450, almost half a megaton of underground nukes
in Manhattan, right?
So 300.
Yeah.
Actually, they were pretty big nukes, you know,
to do that.
Yeah, something of that size, yes.
Yeah, so that was a couple of days
ago.
So these idiots, they think it's coming up
in a week or so.
But anyway, yeah, it's the 7th month, and
this is Reckoning also, the year change, I'd
say around 20 years into the 7th millennium,
roughly.
I could say 21 years into the 21st
year, 20 years for sure, as far as
one can reckon, into the 7th millennium.
So 6020 plus, right?
Roughly is where we're at.
So, let's see.
I'll go just through some questions.
Greetings, Greek.
Hope all is good with you.
Thanks for your continued efforts.
And skip through that.
Let's see.
I've tried.
Okay.
Here are some points that might be worth
addressing.
The Onoff, the mothership left at the time
of the flood cloud, written in Exodus.
Another thing is the Tower of Babel.
Definition of evil in concordance relates Hebrew word
ra.
Does this relate to the ra used in
the pantheon of Egyptian deities?
Chronobiology is an area of study.
How it relates to Sabbath, scriptural Sabbath.
Actual functions, purpose, design of organs, practical ways,
you know, human body organs.
Other practical ways beyond water and eating seasonally
to improve them.
Fixed appointments, current moon cycle.
Explanation, moon, stars, planets actually are.
Things of note occurring where it is quiet.
Thanks again for all you do.
All the best.
Okay.
That's interesting.
I've covered a lot of that.
I think I've covered quite a bit of
that in the past, but I'm not in
a bullet form, you know, going through a
question and an answer is, I think, more
succinct, right?
So, I don't know.
Let's see what's in the.
So, the answer to that email is, yeah,
we could.
That's basically a redo and maybe fill in
a little more detail.
All right.
So, if we go back.
Weight loss.
If there's a sonic tomorrow, maybe topic can
be about weight loss.
I think that was last week.
That was last weekend.
What's going on here?
It was quick.
Let's see.
I think I did an answer there regarding
some caribou custodian 33 year old about the
beast in Revelation.
Yeah.
And this is the thing I've been having
private discussions with.
When it hits people that what you read
in scripture is real, you have a different
way of processing the information that you get
than if you think it's just something that
it's religious or mythology, which is what society
puts on people.
And there's a big difference between saying, well,
I know it's real.
And, yeah, we've been misled and we need
to reexamine the scriptures.
There's a big difference in that and really
realizing when it hits you that it's real,
you know, like you ever heard of like
a bunch of people going to do something
dangerous.
And one looks at the other says, don't
don't be afraid.
He says, I'm not afraid.
But he really is.
You know, still saying he's just saying I'm
not afraid, but he's full of fear.
OK, so people are still full of I
don't know if this is real.
I don't know enough about it.
You know, I don't know.
It's religion and mythology.
So when you put that when you really
it could take a week, a month, a
year or never, or it could take a
long time for some to realize that this
is real stuff.
Right.
You have to realize that you're not going
to find anyone that's going to convince you
of it.
If you have the reality of these things,
unless you internalize that they're real, you know,
and then you have something to work with.
So let's see other questions here.
Why bother one place plan to receive this
information?
OK, electrical tape, LX tape work agreement.
Really convenient for nicks and cuts.
Thanks.
Oh, that's compression.
OK, 618.
Anything that you see in here worth noting?
There's a sonic.
Today's possible topic.
What can be known about the character in
the car?
The atmosphere, the adversary.
Oh, well, look around you.
Even if you don't know scripture, the more
you study, you know, everything's fake.
But you know, it's it's dazzling.
Right.
Like the medical establishment.
Oh, these guys are so high tech.
Look at their equipment and their hospitals.
It's all bullshit.
It's all fake.
Right.
The money system.
If the if the U.S. dollar is
worth zero, what's a billion times zero?
Right.
Zero.
And then the other part of that was,
could there be some discussion on that?
Nana or Nahash mentioned in Samuel, who was
the men.
Yeah.
Bass wanted to covenant with.
That was a northern part of the territory
there.
And they ended up fighting him or avoiding
him.
OK.
Also, tips and who's quieting the mind, thoughts,
et cetera.
Hmm.
All right.
Well, go to the email or the Nakash
is very simple.
The reason I had brought up someone had
mentioned reading.
I think it was Samuel Kings.
And I brought up the name.
The reason is because these names come up
and descriptions and a name is a character.
Also.
Right.
Like I once knew a medical person I
visited once a long time ago and his
name was Baker.
I said, well, you might be a doctor
now, but your ancestors were baking bread.
Right.
If you run into someone whose name is
Smith and they're, let's say, you know, working
in an office.
Well, guess what?
Your your ancestors were probably Smithies, which is,
you know, working with metal.
Right.
And figure metal and or machines at the
time.
So the character is in the name as
well.
Nicknames tend to be one's character.
Right.
You know, if you call someone hiccups, you
know, as a nickname, here comes hiccups.
Well, guess, you know.
Yeah.
Says a lot.
The nickname says a lot, doesn't it?
Right.
Yeah.
Hmm.
So anyway, what's interesting about that is that,
again, if you is what you're reading in
scripture real or not, and if it's real,
what are you reading?
What can when you read scripture?
You know, here's the thing.
We can go through and answer all these
things point by point, but that doesn't really
help anyone.
How do I know?
Well, I've been doing this kind of stuff
for a decade and a half and I
see the result of it.
Right.
And I'm not surprised.
I just, you know, see the result.
And the result is, do you have the
proper mindset to handle any information?
Right.
That's the difference between, like, the grunts and
the special forces in military settings.
The grunts, if it's not part of their
boot camp or their training, when they're confronted
with something, then they have to rely on
common sense that they learned on their own
or they don't know what to do.
They panic.
Right.
Or they're like, you know, we need to
call someone to tell us what to do.
Where the special forces, their mottos are improvise,
adapt, overcome.
So usually when you say improvise or improvisation,
it means to make things up.
But this is not the way I want
to say improvise.
What I mean by improvise is, well, first
of all, it doesn't matter if it's scripture
or what it is.
If it's information, what is it?
You know people say, I'm getting information, I'm
getting knowledge.
Well, really, what is it?
Communication.
Right?
Okay.
If you're going to a library and you're
looking up a subject that you want to
know more about, you are seeking communication on
that subject, are you not?
You are.
Let's say you want to learn about, let's
say, radio, how to set up radio transmission.
Okay.
And you walk into the library and all
the books are in Russian and you only
speak English or read English.
Well, you have all the information.
What's wrong with you?
The communication isn't happening.
Right?
Because you don't recognize the language.
It's all you're holding in your hand.
Yeah.
You know, if you're an American and I
drop you in the library, let's say in
Athens, and you want to look up a
subject, we can't deny the material is not
there.
Of course it's there.
You're just not having effective communication.
Right.
You need a translator.
You need to get into a form that
you can use.
So when you read, for example, scripture, since
a lot of these questions are scriptural, regardless
of what it is, and this will answer
the character of the Nakash and all this
other stuff.
Well, what's being communicated in the five books
of Moses?
Well, Greek, that's pretty obvious.
You know, we can do an outline of
what it's about.
You know, people try to wrap their heads
about the information.
You know, well, it says, well, this is
odd in creation.
Look at day one, day two, day three.
If you focus on just that, like a
laundry list or a recipe, you know, a
pound of sugar, a pound of butter, a
pound of flour, if you're looking for that
type of thing, even then, if you've never
baked before, regardless of the recipe, it's going
to be pretty screwed up the first couple
of times.
You know that, right?
If you've ever done any baking.
Because baking is more, like if I said
make mashed potatoes, well, you're not really going
to screw it up.
It might be less tasteful.
It may not be as good as other
mashed potatoes from someone.
But if you try baking, you're going to
burn it.
It'll be underdone.
It'll be, right?
Right.
So the recipe, again, doesn't really, you need
to develop the skill on what you're looking
at.
So if we look at, for example, the
first five books of Moses, most of these
questions in the chat and the email are
in regard, I would go back to either
the first five books of Moses or what
Zechariah, I keep, I haven't hammered it too
much.
Like I've hammered Assyria a lot.
You know, watch for a new Assyria.
But the book of Zechariah is very important
in understanding Scripture.
I think I might have mentioned this a
few times.
And he says, if you want to know
what's coming, I'm paraphrasing here in the book
of Zechariah, look at the prophets of old.
That doesn't mean the latter prophets.
That doesn't mean Ezekiel, Isaiah, Habakkuk, and all
these other guys, right?
Who are the prophets of old?
That would be from Moses and after, right?
It would be Samuel, Joshua, right?
Elijah, right?
Eliyahu, right?
It won't be Isaiah, Jeremiah.
Those guys are later.
Okay.
All right.
So when we go back and look again
at the first five books of Moses, what
are you looking at?
What's being communicated there?
What's the setting?
Very simple.
Well, we know that it's penned by Moses.
Well, when, where, and how, and who?
Well, who is Moses?
When?
Well, it was around, I'd say, 1500 B
.C. around there.
Who was it?
Who were they?
They were basically post-exilic Egyptian slaves or
freshly exiled Egyptian slaves.
Were they not?
Yes.
Right?
We're talking, yeah, we're talking 1,000 years
after the flood, roughly.
Mm-hmm.
So right there, there was a lot that
happened before that.
You know, we had the height of the
Akkadian Babylonian Empire.
We had the flood.
We had the pre-flood civilization, Adamic civilization,
pre-Adamic civilization, before you even get to
Genesis and the first five books of Moses.
So when you actually look at the five
books of Moses, they're pretty down the line.
I mean, not completely down the line, because
they're still a millennia and a half away
from the Christ, you know, first century and
all that.
There was a big influx of interest in
this, again, for 200 B.C. So what's
going on, this is what they call historically
the end of the Bronze Age also, which
there's no such thing, but, you know, when
they say Iron Age, Stone Age, Bronze Age,
what that really means is a bronze-based
society, right?
Right.
So, you know, this is not the Information
Age, because if you go to Chad, right,
or places like Burma, whatever, you wouldn't think
you're in the Information Age, right?
People walking around with machetes dragging palm trees.
Right.
Essential, still.
So it's an information society or not, mostly
you can say so.
All right, so what's going on when you
read Genesis?
It's a recap, and it holds particular information
regarding how the people that are chosen to
carry this information are going to regard their
deity.
Should I say that again?
No, I think that was pretty clear.
Yeah.
The reason why Genesis, Exodus, Leviticus, Deuteronomy, Numbers,
is written the way it is, Numbers, Deuteronomy,
is written the way it is, is because
it's to develop a mindset that was dictated
at the time for how the people that
are to hold this information, and also chosen
to be their deity, how they're going to
view that deity, which happens to be the
Creator.
Because I think I've mentioned in a previous
Sonic that the Creator brought himself down to
the level of the sons of gods, or
the patriarch deities that rule over the nations,
to actually take one nation for himself.
Right.
It's kind of like if you see a
family of children, and they're all playing, oh,
what's some game that everybody knows?
I don't think people play family games anymore,
but it was Twister, Risk, Monopoly, right?
Oh, yeah.
You ever see when a whole family's playing
a game?
Okay.
Yeah.
And here comes the dad, and he says,
well, I'm going to play with you guys.
I'm going to play with you guys, right?
You ever see a parent?
He comes, and he takes up either a
game piece, or he gets into the game
just like one of the children.
Right?
Right.
Instead of going up and reading the Wall
Street Journal, or TV, or doing something, or
smoking his pipe, or whatever, he comes down
with the children, and he takes on a
level with them.
This is what's going on.
Very important to consider this, right?
Okay, because when a parent comes down and
plays a game with the children, even though
this is not a game, I'm using that
as an analogy, he can't use his full
will and exercise all of his power.
He still has to kind of play in
a level that fits in and doesn't overpower
the rest of the people.
Right.
Right?
So when you have the Creator grabbing a
nation, later on, of course, because this doesn't
happen until later, right, around this time that
we're discussing the five books of Moses periodically
in history, or the historicity of it, when
he, let's say, grabs these people, and they
decide to also have him as his patriarch
or national deity, he's acting still the way
the other gods that are over other nations
act.
He's not showing his full power.
You know, he's not like playing Twister, you
know, the game, and he picks up the
child from the scruff of the neck and
throws him across the room.
Right.
He'll just nudge him like everyone else does
in the game, because they're all eight-year
-olds, let's say, right?
So when you're playing a game with a
bunch of six- or eight-year-olds,
you don't use all your full adult power.
You tone it down, and you just kind
of nudge someone like an eight-year-old
would.
So what you're looking there is, how much
information do the gods of the nations provide
for their people, or the people that they
have auspices over?
Very little.
You ever notice that?
What they do is they set up a
temple complex or temple area, usually in a
city that's given geographically, and they make offerings
to their god there, basically.
This is what happens through all, let's say,
quote-unquote, pagan societies.
So that's why you had something similar in
Egypt.
In Egypt, yes, and in Israel, you had
the temple complex and all that.
All right?
I mean, if you look at the temple
complex for Yahweh, that is not much more
elaborate, even though it was considered more elaborate
than the pyramid complex, believe it or not,
because it was a site to behold at
the time.
People don't understand that today.
But it was not more elaborate than in
most of the other temples you saw.
He could have commanded a temple that was
one square mile at the base and a
thousand stories high, made of stone.
You can do that, reaching beyond the clouds.
But why?
Because he's playing Twister or Monopoly with a
bunch of six-year-olds.
And these six-year-olds are not the
people.
These are the other gods.
Have I ever gone into this analogy of
why things are the way they appear to
be?
I think in pieces, right?
In pieces, yes.
Okay, so how many times have you heard
me say, how easy would it be for
the gods and the Creator to pop in
and say, these are my laws, everybody do
it, everybody on your knees.
I'll be back in 50 years.
Yeah, to check on you.
How easy would that be?
Could they do that?
Of course.
Well, they don't do it.
There's a plan, right?
Hands off.
All right, so when you go back and
you look at something, what can be known
about the Nakash, right?
I'm presuming that's the Nakash that's in the
Garden of Eden, he's asking there.
Right.
Because when I read stuff like that, usually,
you know how many times I've said that
most people's spiritual father, you know how the
Catholics call the priest father, because you get
your spiritual lawyer from whoever you get your
spiritual law from is your spiritual father, right?
Right.
So when I see people asking about the
devil, I'm like, yo, man, you want me
to talk about your pops?
You know?
Yeah, yeah.
Because I'm not saying that this is this
person specifically, his pops, but what I'm saying
is that's the position he's taken, no one
thinks about it.
But if you were to think about the
information that's given, you can also deduce, you
know, there's a saying that says half the
truth is still a lie.
But if what you see is all true
and it's not really fully embellished, you can
still develop the truth because you have enough
of the basic meaning, right?
Right.
So what I mean by that is if
you go back to the setting of the
Garden of Eden, did Eve say anything or
was it written, holy shit, man, holy shit,
Adam, man, right, instead of Batman, holy shit,
Adam, man, look, the snake, there's a snake
is talking to me, wow, that's freaky.
Did you get any of that?
Well, you know what's really weird about that
is you have that one particular species advancing
quicker than the others, taking on a dialect.
But it's not a snake.
Correct.
If you look at, just like I had
a discussion recently with someone that Nephilim doesn't
mean the fallen ones, it doesn't.
Nakash is a term that's defined as also
meaning shiny, bright, it also means divination or
Prudent?
Well, yeah, sharpish, like the British might say.
It means serpentine-like.
You know how someone says business don't lick?
Yeah, you know how in the business people
say don't do business with him because he's
a real snake?
Right, right.
What does that mean?
I mean, you know, well, they're into detail,
they look for weaknesses.
Loopholes.
Flattery, whatever.
Strong in character but not high esteem, morally.
Okay, but if you go back and look
at what's going on with Eve, I mean,
obviously she probably saw creatures or beings, this
is a celestial cosmic being, anthropomorphic.
If you look at other writings within the
time, there's allusions to these serpentine beings that
are still anthropomorphic and the serpentine is in
character, right?
But then again, are you reading Genesis and
is it real or are you so full
of iconography and imagery from society of Adam
and Eve, these two naked people with a
fig leaf and you see a snake and
an apple, right?
I mean, that's just as far as removed
from the text as you see this guy
nailed to a Roman cross wearing a diaper
with long hair with a crown of thorns.
That is as far removed as that, right?
Or anything, or the flood where the seas
will be in the middle of the waters
lift up and I mean, that is, right,
okay, so forget all that stuff.
And the thing is people say, yeah, I
know, but do you really?
The answer that I say is no, people
don't.
People still think this is something, some kind
of a mystery, which it is.
It's a secret, by the way.
I've argued back and forth with people.
There's no such thing as a mystery in
Scripture.
It's a secret.
We have used the word mystery to mean
unknowable or unknown until it is.
These are secrets.
That's why, for example, when you read about
the end times, there's something called a mystery
of Babylon the Great, secret Babylon the Great.
In other words, there are secrets held within
the Babylonian community, you know, archivally, that are
being used against men and they don't know
it.
Like, for example, in modern times you could
look at chemtrails.
Well, we know it's happening.
Those are not natural contrails, but it's a
secret.
We don't see any information on who's sponsoring
it, who's flying it, exactly what's in there.
It's not advertised.
But I assure you somewhere, in secret, there
is an entire logistical plan, an entire financial
plan, an entire, you know, you could see
what's been stitched together from logistics, design, all
the way to practical, all the scheduling, finances,
and chemical, and a list of whoever's involved
somewhere, that exists.
But we don't have access to it.
All we see is planes making lines in
the sky that we know are not clouds,
for sure, natural, or water.
But that just doesn't happen randomly.
There is a plan, and with a lot
of detailed information, somewhere.
So when you read about Mystery Babylon, that's
what it's really talking about.
There are secrets, Babylonian secrets are held, which
ties back into the Tower of Babel.
But if we go back to the Nakash,
who he is, you know, there was no
problem with Eve and this being, right, at
all.
In other words, this was a common thing.
This was common to see, that type of
being.
It was actually so common, that the conversation
was struck up without much introduction needed.
Right.
You notice that?
So that means this was a common being.
It's kind of like, you know, if you've
ever been in a big city, you see
the people emptying the garbage cans of maintenance
people, or whatever.
Sure.
And, you know, it's easy to say, hey,
good morning, and you have a short conversation
with one.
You know, it's not like some alien came,
you know, if you see a guy in
a reflective fire suit, you don't, it's really
odd, you know, you're like wondering something odd
here.
These were very common beings.
Now, how do I know that?
And how do I know that for sure?
Well, because this detail is begged.
In other words, when you read about the
interaction between the serpent, Nakash, this being, divine
being, with Eve, the interaction between Eve and
this being is as common, and as relaxed,
and as ordinary as ordinary can be.
Right.
Right?
And that's how I know why I'm saying
what we're saying.
And also, later on, I mean, if you
even read in what's called the New Testament,
the Christ actually encounters this being again, before
the being takes him up to the mountain,
right, to make all these offers.
He encounters him almost in an anthropomorphic form,
like he's walking with him, like he's encountered
with the Nakash.
Like he's walking in the valley, and this
being comes up to him, you know, anthropomorphic,
and says, hey, you, I want to talk
to you.
Okay.
No big deal.
Right?
So the character there, well, the character is
very interesting, because it is a level, it's
not a very low-level character, it's actually
a pretty high-level character, which dictates a
lot of, dictates some level of authority or
credence to the other divine characters.
And he's against mankind, basically.
There is a war in heaven, there are
serious problems there, just like there are anywhere
you can encounter, you know, from getting the
more information you gather about whether it's a
heavenly society or earthly society, there's always conflict,
let's say.
But he's not a low-level being.
And he's slick enough to have an entourage,
right, or millions or billions of other beings
go along with this plan.
Which, when you study Scripture close enough, you
actually see it's not just this character, the
sons of gods are also against man.
For example, if you look at this justice
goddess religion, that is not a positive thing,
because, you know, people fear that.
You know, if you look at all of
the gods, they think very little of man.
They don't mind deceiving them, right?
All of the nations like that, in that
condition.
They were supposed to lead mankind into the
consistency of the right thing to do from
the Creator.
So, that's why the Psalm says they will
be killed like men, which is very humiliating,
because now they rule over men spiritually.
So, again, the character of the Nakash, I
mean, what character would you assign to someone
who's out to get you that is not
just a complete, you know, vagrant.
He actually has some notoriety within his society
and all that, and he's out to get
you.
Like an attorney is out to get you,
right?
They try to use everything they can, right?
So, I don't know, the character.
If you want to understand scripture, you've got
to understand what's going on around you, because
ultimately, if you don't understand what's going on
around you, you're going to have to put
up a separation wall and say, oh yeah,
this is our everyday life on planet Earth,
and now I'm going to study scripture.
You know, let's get behind, you know, this
is something totally different.
No, it's not.
It's a continuation of all these things.
And anything is.
You know, again, going back to the e
-mail, some questions about the Yanov and the
cloud, and, you know, that's like the presence
of the mothership, let's say.
Well, how many times do you read about,
in scripture, the gods presenting themselves on Earth
as they are?
Is that a good time?
Do they break out the Budweisers and the
Coronas and the Pinatas, and they have, what
do they call when the, what's the white
trash thing they do when they have the
football game, the tailgate party?
Is that what they do, the tailgate?
We have a tailgate because the gods are
here.
Or is everybody running from fear, you see?
So let's say the gods were around for
a couple of thousand years, almost a thousand
years for sure, hanging around.
Is that a good time to be on
Earth?
No.
It's pretty shitty.
That was a really, really tough time for
people on Earth.
Hey, by the way, even it's written in
Noah.
This guy's going to give us some relief.
Because finally, what's going to happen is going
to be so much interaction between mankind and
these lower entities, and of course man is
going to be enticed into learning more of
this technology and doing more with it, that
it's really difficult to live here on Earth.
And we heard that the Creator is going
to drop a flood to end this bullshit.
And when he drops the flood, he's going
to pull away.
So we're going to have two good things
happening.
First thing, he's going to make a flood
to get rid of all these scumbags, billions
of them.
And then they're also going to pull out.
That's a good thing at that time.
For the gods to pull out their presence,
their overt presence, because it's a hassle having
them around.
Because it's potentially extremely dangerous to be around.
Imagine driving down a road and having 300
kilovolt power lines all over the road.
You know what I mean?
Very dangerous.
So how many times have I said, basically
right now, people don't know this, but you're
in a veritable Garden of Eden right now,
regardless of what you hear publicized about environmental
problems and all that.
Well, first of all, it's almost like a
Garden of Eden, because the weather is relatively
stable.
You don't have disasters, you don't have earthquakes
that open the ground, and fire comes out
and burns black smoke for 40 years at
a time, swallows up half a million people.
You don't have any of that.
You don't have the gods coming through, you
know, tearing shit up for a long time.
So it's very, very, very peaceful.
Again, the adversaries, they want to fool you.
Oh yeah, war and starvation.
It's all just another cover, because there's no
reason for it.
It's just your ignorance.
You know, I was having a conversation recently.
When you read in any society, in any
time in human history, well, especially the past
100 years, I should say, not any time
in human history, the past 100 years, the
modern system, the success of the economic system,
the success of the medical system, the success
of the education system, the only reason these
systems can tout a success is because you're
failing in understanding what they're doing.
In other words, the current medical system is
a complete farce.
And the only way it could be considered
a successful medical system is because you have
failed in understanding anything about medicine and how
the human body really works.
That's why they're successful, because you're a failure
in that subject.
The economic system, what?
It's all fiat.
There is no money.
And the only way it could be successful
is if you don't know that it's credit
and you don't know how it works, you
see.
The only way the education system is successful
is if you failed in understanding what it's
really about.
The only way a religion is successful is
if you fail to understand what it's supposed
to be based on.
So, whenever you hear of a success, it's
really based on the failure of the masses
in that topical nature of that matter, across
the board.
Yeah.
So, whenever you hear about these successes, they
actually represent the failure of the masses to
comprehend.
Basically, this is where I used to hammer
a lot.
Pranking.
You ever hear about the attorneys and the
doctors, the government and the bankers, they're all
pranking you.
They have nothing to do.
It's just a prank.
When they go to school, their job training
is how to prank you.
Kevlar underwear.
That's right.
You know, if a headhunter opens a bag
and shows you five heads and you say,
does it upset you that you have that?
He says, yeah, it does.
My brother's got ten.
So, they're immoral.
And the biggest problem, really, for those that
are running these sovereign states is they look
at everyone and they classify them as scumbags
or morons and they're like, oh, shit.
Guess what?
Well, they're having babies.
What does that mean?
More scumbags and morons when they grow up.
There's no change that's going to happen.
Because the people are scumbags and morons because
of the system they went through and they
have children and they tell the children to
have allegiance to that system.
Where it's all voluntary, believe it or not,
to a certain degree.
So, that's why when you hear about human
depopulation, it has nothing to do with too
many people being upon the earth.
You could have a trillion people on the
earth, no problem.
Not the current system that you have now,
the way you manage water, food and all
that.
But when they talk about overpopulation, it's like
they're just getting tired of the same breeding
program.
But they're not going to change the breeding
program, I mean the education, the medical and
all that other stuff, the economic system and
all that, because why?
You're quite happy with it.
Peaceful culling, I believe they'd call it.
Just bear that in mind.
So, it's basically the children.
And they always use the children anyway.
Do it for the children, right?
It's just like if you have a fair
assessment of this society, and you're like, oh,
it's pretty shitty and the people are pretty
shitty.
And you're like, but you know what's even
worse?
They're having babies.
Oh, shit.
I mean, you get more of them.
The same ones coming around again and again
and again.
How does it end?
Well, it will end.
You see?
So, anyway.
It's not that having babies is bad.
You're told, the early man was told to
do that.
It's that they're so stupid to see what's
going on.
But anyway.
And they have a new creature, a new
being, and they put him exactly in the
same spot that they were.
And this is irrelevant of what Jack Fresco
says, you're a product of your environment and
all that.
No, no, no.
This goes beyond that.
Because the environment, it's too rigid to change,
to improve at this point.
And it's not because of the leadership, it's
because of the people themselves.
Okay, so.
If we go back, let's just do a
recap.
Everything in scripture is pretty much from 1500
B.C. and on.
Except for maybe the book of Job, and
some other writings, perhaps, that are alluded to.
So, you're looking at what they call Bronze
Age, Post-Bronze Age writings.
Even though something in the scripture might refer
to a couple of thousand, or three or
four thousand years prior to it, the setting
of what you're reading is that time period.
Now, what is the setting?
Again, post-exilic slaves, people are pretty much
on the run, and then eventually they're not
on the run when they go to settle
some land, when they evict a whole bunch
of serious scumbags, and giants, and other hybrids,
and things like that.
So, the time period is quite important to
consider the information in.
So, you have to have a very heightened
sense of alertness when you're reading the five
books of Moses, and the alertness should always
subject your mind to the setting.
These are people that were, quote-unquote, exiled
out of Egypt, or left Egypt, of a
slave background, and here they're being set up
by the Creator acting as one of the
gods of all the other nations.
Very simple.
Everything else falls in place, unless you want
to start looking at the ultra-subtle aspects
of what it means when the gods overtly
present themselves in their true form.
Have you ever looked at, for example, sci
-fi, when they talk about matter, anti-matter,
when it comes together, bad things happen, right?
Yeah, similar to that.
So, consider it essential to have a peaceful
environment as men are, and as gods are.
You can't have both in the material world
at the same time, overtly.
The gods have to take a position where
they are covert.
In other words, they stay unseen.
Then you can have peace.
And that's very simple.
That explains a lot of the settings and
situations that you see.
So, you piece it together, and see how
it works for you in your travels.
Because ultimately, everyone that's going to be studying
this, or listening to what I'm saying, still
has what they consider, what they grasp personally,
on the subject matter.
What I have said, and what I still
say, there hasn't been a counsel of any
kind, a viable one, a truthful one, or
an accurate one, one that's based on precision,
to grab the scriptures, and summarize them in
whole, what they're about, and present that as
a communication to people, so they don't have
to wonder about all the details.
No one's ever done that, by the way.
I'm the only one that's ever done the
simplicity of it.
There's Christian writers, there's Jewish writers.
The Jewish writer says, I'm going to drop
some Talmud on your ass, alright?
Or the Christian writers, oh yeah, we're Christians
now, yeah, sure we are.
You've got all this crap.
Or you'll have these narrow subject matter lines.
I was speaking to someone recently, and I
listened to a podcast, I think it was
Heiser, or someone like that, and this asshole,
I had sent him a correspondence a long
time ago, he's supposedly an expert in the
New York Times, yeah, that too, probably, Old
Testament, and I said, well, you consider yourself
to be a Christian, but there's no crucifixion,
right?
That's all a fraud, and he sent me
a message back a while back, and said,
oh, that's patently ridiculous.
He won't look at it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then you've got the other Christian people,
oh yeah, the U.S. Constitution, what a
great system, what an asshole.
If you read the Constitution, it tells you
that slavery has to be no involuntary slavery.
That means it has to be voluntary.
Well, I could trick you into volunteering, right?
And the other thing it says, there's no
slavery unless you're convicted.
Well, it doesn't say rightfully convicted, so you
could falsely convict someone, and now they're a
slave, you see?
The Constitution is a pretty shitty document.
And it also establishes justice, which is really
fucked up.
Yeah, yeah.
It says it in the first 17 words,
to establish justice, right there.
You know, I was at a Constitutional convention
a while back, and I stood up and
I was speaking, and I said, the Constitution,
these are all Constitutionalists, right?
Old farts, these old patriots, diseased, of course,
because patriotism is a disease.
And I said, well, the Constitution is pretty
screwed up, and I would wipe my ass
with it, and they all wanted to really
get upset.
You know, they were like, oh, what did
he just say?
And I said, no, no, no, no, no.
And they were like, okay.
And I said, no, no, what I meant
was, you need to crumble it up first
a few times, and then wipe your ass
with it to make it softer, because that
parchment is really hard.
And then I ran out of there, you
know?
Oh, good one.
Yeah, anyway, that's what they get.
So they don't want the truth.
So no one comes out, you know, real
harsh stuff like that, because I don't know
what they're trying to do, get people to
like them.
I don't want people to like me, basically,
because I've seen what comes along with that,
and it's not pleasant.
In the state that they're in, in the
state that humans are in right now.
It doesn't mean I don't want to interact
with people for gainful experiences.
You know, if I need spark plugs and
you've got spark plugs, let's make a fair
exchange.
If I would like some food and you
have food, let's make a fair exchange.
Other than that, I don't want to know
anything about you.
You know what I mean?
Unless it's something worthwhile.
Because you're a surface-dwelling earth inhabitant.
Unless you're actually on a path of better
things, and if you are, then keep to
yourself again.
So it's a very difficult situation.
So that's why in places in scripture, it's
like, yeah, if you're born here, you're basically
screwed.
Right?
So what do you do in a screwed
up situation?
Now here's the other thing.
There's a very subtle thing that's brought up
always, and it's about gaining knowledge and truth.
It is best...
Well, okay, let me just put it this
way.
There's something subtle and also prominent about gaining
knowledge and truth.
Now, ultimately, if you gain knowledge and truth,
you don't want to be here.
I mean, it's best to make your life
short, get it over with, and you know
what's coming.
That's where you should focus on.
But on the other hand, if you don't
have knowledge and truth, you're going to fall
into all the worries and concerns around you,
which are farces and fraudulent, and you're going
to be pulled back and forth like a
rowboat that's loosely tied, and you're going to
be inefficient.
I mean, how many times have you heard
people getting ulcers because of financial worries?
It's like, what?
There is no money.
What do you mean you got an ulcer
because of financial worries?
That's ridiculous.
But is it better to have an ulcer
because of financial worries, or is it better
to really know that there is no money
and people are killing each other for something
that doesn't exist lawfully?
Which one is worse?
They're both pretty shitty.
But for me, I would rather know.
Because then it is crap.
It's like the headhunters.
If the headhunter is having a national holiday,
like the Americans had one recently, I don't
care how happy they are.
They're headhunters.
But at the same time, if I didn't
know, I would say, man, this is such
a fucked up society.
How can we still have a holiday?
I don't know.
I guess I'll just do it.
Some people would rather be that way.
People have outwardly admitted, I don't want to
know Greek.
I'm not saying what you're saying is not
true.
I just don't want to know.
I want to be happy in my little
bubble.
I remember you saying that.
I've had more than a dozen people say
that in the past few years.
I said, that's fine.
That's respectful.
That's a certain level of honesty within that
person's comfort that they like to maintain.
Because if I said, Bruce, there's a button
on the wall.
Press this, you'll be uncomfortable.
Press this, you'll be comfortable.
Why?
You'll be comfortable, of course.
You have to tell me why.
It's not that simple.
Just to preface a lot of the information,
before you even tried to have a conversation,
is futile.
They're unworkable at this.
Humans have been unworkable for thousands of years.
It's much better and easier to just gather
them under a real simple premise and then
control them.
If it's time to have them just kill
each other, push a button, get them instigated
to start killing each other.
If it's time for them to live in
peace, have them live in peace.
Because it just doesn't work any other way
in the way that it's set up.
Because everything is a farce.
And essentially, the gods that had taken dominion
over the regional areas, over each nation, they
were out for malevolent stuff and deceit and
farce from the beginning.
So any form of cultural or tradition, no
matter how old or how new, that people
hold on to is based on that system
of their patron or matriarch deity.
So it's a pretty shitty system.
So how do you maintain yourself?
Your life is with good food, good clothing,
good shelter, good conversation.
Have at least one or two people around
you that love you.
You know, do the right thing.
And you can trust.
If you can achieve those things, you've got
more than anyone has ever gotten here.
And then you just pass through.
And then later it will come to understanding.
There's a level of ambassadorship that people would
consider.
Yeah, in scripture, tell people the truth about
reality and all that.
But how do you couch it?
I mean, what level do you want to
tell them about?
If you're asked, you should.
Yeah, answer the question.
It should be done.
So this is pretty much the mindset.
If you have a pretty good understanding of
the current society that you're in, when I
say current, you have to look at it
in hundred year chunks.
You have to go back a hundred years
also.
Pretty good handle on medical system, economic system,
agricultural system, governmental system, religious systems.
All the various systems that you interact with
or know about.
If you have a pretty good handle about
what's really going on, and if someone asks
you what's going on, you still have to
at some point give the option or throw
in the detail, it's around this time.
Because there was no blood pressure 200 years
ago.
Tests in medicine.
But you think of some of the ways
things repeat, how different societies repeat over time.
You got the rise of the guns and
stuff and all that, and I was just
kind of noticing how much this society reflects
the old Western days in a lot of
ways.
Not really.
Because in the Western days, if you had
a beef with someone, you'd go out and
you can duke it out, duel it out
to the death, and all the authorities wouldn't
get involved.
Because you were free.
This is before the sovereign state.
The sovereign state came in 1871, by early
20th century it was in, everyone's enslaved now.
You can't do what you want.
Like if you get into a car accident,
a bonafide car accident, not on purpose, and
the people in the car are hurt, the
state sues you for damaging state property.
And you think it's the barrier you crashed
into.
It's not, it's the people in the car.
And they're serious about that.
You're pretty much finished.
You're worse than the Egyptian slaves right now.
Do nothing.
Like last week I mentioned, an attempted civil
war revolution by these patriotic idiots would be
fun to watch.
You should film it.
It would be a Turkish shoot.
I'm sure the oligarchs that own the United
States of America would say, oh yeah, let
them go.
Get the FBI in there to help them
get some guns.
And they won't just go in and wipe
them out.
Make sure you get it on film.
A human snuff film.
There's going to be no civil war revolution
or anything like that.
So you're too stupid.
You're better off with what you've got right
now because at least right now you can
maintain a certain amount of peace.
But I've never met a quote unquote patriot
or whatever that I would substitute even the
lowest current government official with.
The lowest current government official of the corporation
is 100 times better than any of these
patriot idiots you ever run into.
Any of them.
Even the guy who empties the waste baskets
in any government office is better than any
of these patriots by far.
Because he knows it's a corporation.
He knows it's bullshit.
So anyway, he knows that everything's finished.
To a certain degree because he's exposed to
it every day.
But that would be interesting to watch if
these idiots, patriots, try to get something physical
going on.
It's just going to be a snuff film.
Look at Waco and all these other things.
Screwed up stuff.
That was something totally different in a sense
but I'm just giving an example.
There's no way out.
You'd be exterminated.
There's nothing you can do at this point.
In any country, believe it or not.
Now it doesn't mean that let's say the
US can go into Syria and say that
Syria is having a civil war.
That's bullshit.
Up until two years ago, I had correspondence
with people in Syria.
They were in Aleppo and they said they
have to leave.
And I understand why.
If you look at Aleppo, it's mostly blown
up.
They were like, these people are not Syrian.
There's no revolution.
These are Malaysians, Vietnamese, Australians, Turks.
There's no one in there from Syria.
Very few.
That's different.
If you go down the line of all
these questions, what context are you looking at
it in?
Again, anything in scripture that you're going to
look at, you're going to look at it
in chunks.
What was going on?
What do you know about the time of
Moses and after?
For the setting.
What do you know about the Creator taking
the place as one of the patriotic or
patron deities, let's say, patron deities of all
the other nations, bringing himself to that level
for Israel and acting that way?
Let me put it this way.
It's very plain.
The Creator is not acting like the Creator
when you read in scripture.
When he asks for a certain people, because
you don't have to be an Israelite to
do it.
Anyone who wants to do it can do
it if they commit to it, is the
law.
By the way, living your life lawfully is
like reading scripture is studying, let's say in
university, and doing the law is the lab.
When you take a course, you need some
lab or hands-on.
When you do the law, food, clothing, shelter,
according to the law, and you act according
to the law, keep time and all this
stuff, that is your hands-on experience with
scripture.
That's very dangerous, by the way, to any
organization, because there is no organization that knows
what the law is.
They mouth-flick, they do, but they won't
do it.
It's very dangerous to the establishment also.
Very, very dangerous.
And Dimitri talked about that, the ideology.
They tell you, oh yeah, Christians don't have
to do it, or no, the Jews, we
do our tradition, but no one is touching
the biblical law at all.
They can't, because they know that this is
the way things are going to be later,
not the time now.
It doesn't mean you can't have hands-on
with it, because it's the right thing to
do from a moral place.
But again, if you consider the Creator has
taken, brought Himself down to the position of
the sons of God to rule over one
nation, or one nation has allegiance to Him,
and anyone else can as well, and is
functioning that way, even with the temple complex,
even with His law, whether it's divine geography,
or human geography, earthly geography, or all that,
He is acting, He has brought Himself down
to the level of a patron deity.
He's not acting, the Creator is not acting
like the Creator in Scripture.
It's very obvious.
If He's the Creator of the universe, can't
He just speak things into existence, immediately hop
on?
Who would fight the Israelites?
No one would.
If He presented Himself in full power.
Even when Christ came to the earth, He
presented Himself as, I have to do this
thing you don't understand.
You'll understand later, if you remember reading that.
And He steps out.
It's like guerrilla tactics.
Got a job to do?
Go and do it.
I'm not going to advertise it.
If a few people know about it, it's
okay.
By the time anything can be done, I'm
out of here.
Plausible deniability.
And He knew there was going to be
plausible deniability about what He did because He
said so.
He said, well, if they say, look, He's
in the desert, don't go, it's not me.
Look, they're going to say, it's me at
the mountains.
No, don't go, it's not me.
That's the plausible deniability.
Look, He's still here.
He went to India.
He's really a Buddhist.
That's not me.
So they knew about the plausible deniability.
Once you understand that there is earthly functions
with humans acting in a national way, sovereign
or semi-sovereign, and they each have a
patron or matron deity, that is the order
of things now.
And when you speak of the gods, the
most you're going to get on in any
overt sense is a patron deity.
The Creator is not acting as the Creator.
The only time He acted as the Creator
was during the flood.
And also when they wrapped things up, and
it was written about the on-off, the
dark cloud, and rolled out.
Rolled out of town.
Then you know it's that.
To that level.
Now, after what's called the millennium period, what's
coming, we're in it right now, it just
hasn't manifested a strict beginning of a change
yet.
In other words, the gods have not returned
overtly.
Which is more than the gods returning.
It's actually the war between, if you read
ancient texts, especially 2nd or 3rd century, there
were some writings, Qumranic writings, and other writings,
and people who wrote the Dead Sea Scrolls,
and others, we're talking about their interest, in
the end there's going to be a war
between man and the gods.
And obviously it's not going to work out
well for man.
But that is the scenario that's coming.
Even when this scenario comes, there's going to
be a reorganization, and the full power of
the Creator on Earth will not be realized
until still 900 years from now.
Plus.
But at least we'll have overt contact with
the gods and resurrected beings.
So if you want to know the overt
power of the Creator, read like Zephaniah, or
read like the ends of parts of Revelation.
All that.
So, the other aspect right now, that's why
it's so difficult, this is the knowledge part
again.
If you know who the Creator is, and
you know exactly what's going on, which is
quite simple, it's not easy, but it's simple.
You have a human society of various varieties,
and types.
And there's a patron deity over each type,
nation, or territory, or region.
And the Creator doesn't bust in as the
Creator.
He comes in and he sets himself up
as one of these other patron deities over,
let's say, Israel.
If they want him.
He says that, basically.
If you want me, I'll do it.
And he does this as a witness to
everyone else if they want to know who
he is.
But he's acting on that dynamic.
He's not acting as the Creator at this
point.
And again, if you ever read the scripture,
what do the Christians say?
The only begotten son of God?
It doesn't say that.
It doesn't say he's the only begotten son,
because then who are the sons of God?
What it says, he's the monogenous, the one
of a kind, like a genus is a
type.
Right?
He's a monogenous of Elohim, meaning he is
a one of a kind.
What's his one of a kind?
His one of a kind is not to
rule over a nation now.
One of a kind is to show the
people that are human that resurrection is possible
and he's going to prove it.
That is a prototype of sorts.
That was his job.
I shouldn't be saying this kind of stuff
because I'm going into things I'm saying I
shouldn't be talking about publicly.
But these are things that are like, it's
like imagine a neon sign 50 feet tall
and everyone's walking around.
I didn't see that neon sign.
What are you talking about?
It's 10,000 watts and 50 feet tall.
How can you miss that?
Cosmic censorship is a bitch.
So basically I just laid out all knowledge
in all scripture and all knowledge basically of
humankind for the past 6,000 years and
the past half hour.
Not all the knowledge but basically how to
perceive it.
Right.
What I call the world order.
The world order is you have groupings of
people.
There are gods over each group of people.
The creator takes his place as one of
those grouping of gods.
Not as the creator in full power obviously
until a time later and this is what's
going on.
Period.
What else is there to know?
It's pretty obvious if you look at the
medical system it's a farce.
Through these eyes that I'm mentioning.
Basically they're not really scientific.
What they are is they're pushing a religion.
Blood pressure is like an easy Achilles heel
to show what kind of a fraud the
system is.
If blood pressure is so important why aren't
vets using it?
If you ever see a horse or dog
get a cuff a sphigometer on it and
check the blood pressure and say oh he
needs some blood pressure medication he's got hypertension
what they don't get stressed out too?
Of course they don't do anything.
Horses get stressed out.
They're very emotional animals.
All animals are very emotional.
Contrary to things that naturalists wrote 200 years
ago.
It's all farce.
Viruses and whatever science you see.
Years ago if your vision went bad they
didn't prescribe glasses they gave you a list
of dietary things to do.
Are you familiar with that?
No I was not.
Old medical books had categories on poor vision.
It was all dietary and exercise and breathing.
Not glasses.
Right now I see 8 year olds getting
glasses.
Glasses?
Their diet sucks.
They've never eaten real bread or real cheese
or real fruit in their lives.
There's no reason to get into that in
any kind of remedial status because it's not
going to be remedied.
These people don't need better food.
They need to be gone.
Not because I say so.
The gods say so.
And the people that own them say so.
Getting a little tired of your asses.
So there's all the questions in the email.
I think this indirect direct approach of what
is really going on on this earth I
think should help answer most people's questions for
a long time.
The aspect of several questions what else can
we do about the body other than good
water and eating seasonally?
Well then it gets kind of like more
specific and it also gets more into what
do you want, a DIY manual on brain
surgery?
You don't see too many of those, right?
Right.
It gets specific.
There are many things you can do for
the body but the thing is there's something
called diagnostic.
You have to diagnose properly.
Even a car.
You ever go to a mechanic who can't
diagnose a car?
They start changing parts and the problem is
still there, right?
You always want to go to a mechanic
who says you don't pay anything until it's
fixed.
Right.
So a lot of dealers say it's $900
and it didn't help.
Well it's going to be another $1200 for
that.
People go for it.
So that mindset is what I'm talking about.
Basically if you understand how to diagnose the
body one easy way to proceed with understanding
it is why throw away everything that's been
gathered in knowledge about the human body for
thousands of years?
Don't throw all that away.
I would say the eastern arts are easier
to look at than the western arts which
have been completely subverted because of the Christianity.
Right?
The church.
They didn't want any of that, right?
But if you understand on how to diagnose
the body I would suggest the easiest thing
for the western mind or the mindset to
comprehend is macrobiotic diagnosis.
I don't like to suggest that because they
call it macro-neurotics.
They're too dogmatic.
Learn about lymphology.
How do you get a semi-stagnant fluid
like the lymph fluid moving in order to
invigorate the health of a body?
Because if the fluid becomes too stagnant that's
where you get most diseases or if it
becomes a carrier for things to fester in
the lymph system.
So how do you get the lymph system
moving?
Jumping up and down on a trampoline.
Stretching.
Massages.
Hot and cold alternating baths.
Barometrically.
You know how people say I'm going to
go for a hike or a walk?
Well don't walk horizontally, walk vertically.
Climb something barometrically.
If you walk up a steep hill let's
say or a mountain which is a thousand
feet tall it might take you half the
day to go up and come down.
You have a barometric change.
That decrease in pressure as you go up
expands the body and as you come down
contracts it again and you get a wonderful
lymphatic charge.
The old Austrian doctors even today, not so
much, you might have heard when people were
sick they said just go up to the
mountains.
There's a cabin up there.
There's a retreat.
Go live there for a week.
Have you heard that before?
Go stay up in the mountains for a
week.
See how you feel.
Come back.
That's the barometric method.
Baro means pressure.
Again, there's a whole discussion.
I personally, like I got an email recently
and it says, Greek you sound like you've
lost enthusiasm.
You sound like you get mad and you
even sound bitchy.
I didn't answer it back but I'm thinking
like who cares?
I've been speaking publicly for over ten years
on the internet for more than seven now
and I do get people still contributing a
little here and there to get coffee and
cigarettes.
I appreciate that a lot.
Some more than others.
I'm not going to market this.
I'm not going to be like Ray Kroc
of McDonald's and persist and persist and persist.
I'm not going to stay up and write
stuff.
Why don't you get it together?
You're talking about the same stuff all the
time.
Why?
I'm talking to eternal second graders.
If your people are going to be in
the second grade for their whole lives why
should I talk about what's in the third
grade?
It's ridiculous.
There's no support for this type of thing
to grow it as an organization.
And I don't mean in a standard organization
but where people can organize information and we
can present, let's say instead of doing a
sonic like this why not buy time on
a server and have eight hours of audio
files categorized on various conditions of the human
body and how to remedy them or diagnose
it.
You know how long it takes to do
that?
I ain't doing it.
I'd rather watch Netflix or sleep or ride
my bike.
Screw y'all.
What am I, Mother Teresa?
I'm not here to forget it.
And of course, again, I do appreciate the
contributions for the coffee and cigarettes.
But there's no support for what's right and
moral on this planet in a general sense
where it can be mobilized.
So, sorry.
After the resurrection that'll be taken care of.
It doesn't mean that everything I do is
successful.
It doesn't mean that I'll run into someone
that has a health problem or whatever and
it'll be solved.
But this way of doing it is astronomically
beyond what you're going to get anywhere else.
Even recently, someone said to me, I went
to this holistic doctor and he told me
about a condition.
I said, wait a second, before you tell
me what he told you to do, did
he take your blood pressure?
He said, yes, he did.
I said, all right.
Well, even if you don't tell me what
he did, it doesn't matter.
Because he's a fraudster.
So, yeah.
Interesting how it happened.
I ran into someone who's a German immigrant.
He's quite wealthy.
He imports wines and things.
Recently I was at a sushi place.
He was like, hey man, how's the water
stuff going?
I said, I'm not doing it anymore.
We had the best water in the world.
I stopped nobody.
People were like, it was the best water
we've ever had.
But so what?
He said, what do you do now about
the water?
I said, what do you do about the
water now?
I said, well, if somebody asks me to
do something about water, I say, hey, what's
wrong with drinking out of the toilet?
What do you mean?
You're asking me how to make water better.
What's wrong with drinking out of the toilet?
Go drink out of the toilet.
Leave me alone.
This is the reality, and believe it or
not, this is what the gods think of
you too.
Sorry.
So from that perspective, I think that even
the most rudimentary basic Greek speak is a
thousand times over anything else you've ever heard.
Not five or ten or a hundred times.
A thousand times beyond.
So be happy with what you got.
Sorry.
That's all you're going to get.
Why?
Can more be done?
Oh, a lot can be done.
But is it going to happen now?
Because I'm not going to volunteer to do
it.
Period.
There's no support.
There's no backing.
Nobody wants it.
Remember, it's super wealthy people.
Oh, they pat you on the back.
Oh, you're doing great stuff, man.
Great.
I could use maybe $10-15 million to
get a building and have some dorms, get
people from all over the world come and
share their experiences.
Yeah, I'm not really interested in that.
You just go ahead.
So the people that have the wherewithal, I'm
not talking about the people listening to contribute.
Yeah, you send some money in an envelope,
whatever, that's fine.
Great, I'll get cigarettes with it.
But I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the people that have the
wherewithal, you know, six, seven, eight figures to
put together a real system of disclosing good
communication, good information.
Don't want it.
It has nothing to do with what one
individual wants to do.
It has to do with where you are
in the setting on this earth.
It's shit.
So, if you want better water, what's wrong
with drinking out of the toilet?
Scoop some out of the toilet, put it
in the fridge and chill it.
You already know that chilling makes it better.
Period.
I mean, can stuff be done?
Oh, yeah.
Tremendous amount of stuff can be done.
Actually, recently I said, oh, I want to
do a sonic event again on water because
it's really easy to up the quality.
I'll tell you right now.
You ever see these home good places they
have for wine connoisseurs?
When you open a bottle of wine and
don't finish it, it's a cork system or
a plug system that you draw a vacuum
on the bottle of wine.
They've been around for like 50 years, but
now they're really cheap.
A company like Rabbit or VIN, V-I
-N, make them.
In other words, you open a bottle of
wine, something non-carbonated, they give you a
rubber stopper and it has an orifice that
seals like a sphincter, a one-way valve,
and you put a pump over it and
you draw a pump on the wine bottle.
You familiar with that?
No, I'm listening intently, though.
OK.
What you do then is if you decant
your water into something like a wine bottle,
which is roughly a 28-millimeter opening, you
get one of these vacuum systems.
It has like three or four stoppers and
a pump for $10.
You have an air gap over the water
level in the bottle, blue bottle, dark-colored
bottle, amber bottle, where you put it in
the fridge.
Pull a slight vacuum on that water and
then chill it.
Actually, when you pull a vacuum on the
water at room temp, you'll notice there'll be
a half-degree temperature drop right away.
What does that tell you when water starts
dropping temperature on its own?
It's going towards a healthy condition.
In other words, if you start treating water
in room temperature and you notice that as
you're treating the water, the water is actually
dropping its own temperature, you're like, wow, it's
invigorating itself.
Now that you bring that up, when I
take mine out of the fridge and I
slowly open it, you can hear that vacuum.
Right.
If you induce that vacuum from the beginning,
also there's an ethereal thing.
When you create a monotone or a monoform,
the way you eliminate the life ether is
with a vacuum.
For example, really good medical-grade fridges that
they use in high-end restaurants, you know
how you open and close the fridge door,
right?
Well, these are different.
When you close the fridge, you hear a
little pump and it draws a vacuum on
the entire fridge and the gasket kind of
seals real tight, prevents bacteria from growing.
And you just don't go up to this
fridge and try to open it.
If you remember the freezers, you fired up
a freezer in the Midwest where you can't
open it, right?
Right.
Because the air holds it tight.
So these restaurant fridges, you push a button
and you hear a pressure release and then
you open the fridge.
We're talking about $30,000 fridges now, small
fridges.
They're medical-grade or whatever.
So these real high-end fridges, they always
pull a vacuum because the bacteria and the
fungus will not grow.
Right.
But that's not why you're doing it with
water because when water flows underground, there's no
atmosphere there.
And through capillary action on the real narrow
crevices is a negative pressure.
You know what I mean by capillary action?
You ever put a straw in a glass,
you notice the water level in the straw
is higher than the rest of the glass.
That's because there's less pressure.
So the water discussion part two would be
learn how to pull a vacuum.
Now, if you could pull a vacuum on
the water and then inject some CO2 gas
and still maintain the vacuum, like if you
can pull four or five inches of vacuum,
let's say, in a system.
I think I posted a photo of a
mini-fridge with an eight-gallon blue vessel
in it.
We pulled five inches of vacuum and then
we injected CO2 slowly until the five inches
of vacuum dropped to two inches of vacuum,
meaning there's still a vacuum, but there's CO2
in the vacuum.
CO2 will not go into the water.
That helps the water digest.
And when you do that and start vortexing
the water with a silver impeller, you'll see
the temperature drops a degree and a half
by itself, just with that condition.
Chalberger talked about that.
When you get the water moving properly, it
will start to drop temperature on its own.
It's kind of like a sick horse in
the barn.
Look, he's standing up on his own.
It means he's getting better.
So there's more we can discuss on water.
I just give out that little part.
So you get some water out of the
toilet, put it in a wine bottle, get
one of those wine vacuum systems, draw a
slight vacuum on it.
You go on YouTube.
VIN, I think it's V-I-N, Rabbit
is another.
There's a couple of other ones depending on
where in the world you live.
You can get them anywhere at a home
goods section of a store, department store or
home store that has wine stuff.
Between $10 and $20 for an elaborate one.
They have electric ones.
You put a battery in that is not
necessary.
It's like a hand pump.
It works with a check valve in reverse.
You get the idea.
You put in a rubber stopper and the
valve, the fitting of the top of the
stopper fits on the pump.
As you draw on the pump, it pulls
the vacuum in the bottle.
You remove the pump, it stays sealed.
You get the idea.
Very simple.
Anywhere you go in the house, you got
the systems that put a vacuum on a
wine bottle?
Yeah, yeah, come right here.
Get the cheapest one.
They work better.
Start pulling vacuums.
You're going to see, talk about invigorating water.
It'll mature faster.
Also, for those people that are not sure
about the water quality, especially if you're getting
it out of the toilet, if you draw
enough of a vacuum, it destroys the pathogens.
Because the pathogens explode.
Right.
That's part 2.1 of water.
There's many other things we can do.
But that's a very simple one that I
have not included in water talks previously.
Because still, why bother?
That's pretty much it.
You're living in a condition right now, in
a divine condition, where things are very simply
the way they are, because it's based on
secular geography, secular racism, meaning you have the
different races and nationalities, and also cultures and
traditions.
And there is a God over each one.
And the chief deity, the Most High, has
taken his position in interacting with humankind as
one of these patron deities, not as the
creator himself, which he will in the future
reveal himself to be.
I don't think I've ever repeated myself and
gotten into that kind of detail on a
sonic.
I have mentioned that before.
And I haven't addressed everything in bullet point
form.
But essentially, any question in scripture can be
answered if you understand, and I said this
in a call recently, this is what all
of the theologians, all of the scholars, all
of the religious leaders of every religion, academics,
your parents, all your religious institutions, friends, family,
don't want you to know.
In other words, when this knowledge starts to
form, they pin it down.
It's like, no, no, no, it's your opinion,
don't do that.
It's called heresy.
If you know what the soul and the
spirit is, and the human bodies also, if
you know how to keep time, if you
know that there are gods over nations, you
will understand everything in scripture.
I mean, comprehend it.
And if it seems like you don't understand
it there, well, that's because it needs to
be harmonized.
In other words, you'll be reading a verse
that makes sense, and you'll see a verse
that doesn't make sense out of nowhere, and
then it goes back.
That's called interjection in literary mechanism, they interject
the thought.
Well, that's because it needs to be continued
somewhere else, so you need to create harmony
there.
A good bit of research is to, when
you look at nations, do a research on
the word nations, being divided, being organized, being
good, being destroyed, being formed.
And you'll see when nations is being used,
goyim is one way in Hebrew, or laos
in Greek.
So when you look at all being formed,
you'll see all the dynamics.
So if you understand the basic premise of
things mentioned, basically defining the basic terms in
scripture, like one of the most paramount enemies
in scripture is this thing called death, which
the gods and angels are subject to also.
So what do you know about death?
What's the remedy of death?
What is the key of death?
Someone yesterday said, what are the keys to
death?
Well, that's the resurrection, but the resurrection is
not that simple.
You can look at the examples, basically keep
your mouth shut, because you don't want to
argue with the adversary, right?
Screw up and be thrown on the lake
of fire.
You'll still be thrown on the lake of
fire, you'll still be resurrected, but it's a
different outcome.
Then you have the various levels of honor.
The highest honor is to be part of
the first resurrection.
That's why when Christ says, I want you
to be like me, it's not this Christian
demonic shit that people talk about.
It's because I want you to be part
of the first resurrection, because I'm the first
to be resurrected from the dead.
And just because I'm the first, it doesn't
mean that there still isn't a first resurrection.
So anyway, this gets into the more advanced
matters.
If you're asking questions like the ones that
I've been seeing for the past few years,
I'm not going to get into the advanced
stuff.
And I'm not going to berate people for
not being ready for it.
And how can I judge and do that?
But yeah, I can do it.
It's my right to do so.
I don't see anyone ready for more competent
discussions, period.
So, sorry, would you rather me lie and
say, well, maybe we'll do it in the
future?
Maybe?
No.
Right now, as it stands, no, there's no
competent discussion, beyond what we've discussed or heard
in Greek speak, necessary.
Because you've got to keep things in context.
What it's like, someone I know has been
listening to Greek speak for half a decade,
and he's so excited to get in touch
with me, to tell him what this holistic
doctor told him.
And then I asked him, did he take
your blood pressure?
He said, yes.
You mean, didn't you, like, why don't you
at least tell me, he invalidated himself by
doing that, but by the way, this is
what this idiot said.
You know, so what do you do?
What do you do?
I mean, you just kind of sit back
here, like, yeah, I mean, when I go
get smokes, I'm like, hey, you guys got
any other cigarettes that are pretty good quality?
Or when I, you know, take my time
making coffee, make sure you have clean clothes
and good food, and the rest is just
like, eh, why bother?
You know, what's interesting, if you look at
Scripture, you know, someone said, Greek and all
that stuff you just said about the gods
and the Creator taking his position, like, this
is how it is, ah, that's European.
You know what?
Okay, look at some supporting stuff, for example.
When you read in Scripture about general prayer,
what is the general prayer?
Praying for what?
Peace.
Does it say pray for a democratic republic,
or whatever?
Or a good king?
Or a monarch?
Or here, this, or whatever?
No, you pray for your peace.
It doesn't matter if it's the National Socialist
Party, or the Nazis, or Stalin, or Hitler,
or Roosevelt, or Trump, or Obama, or King
Louis, or King Henry, it doesn't matter.
That's just secondary, tertiary crap.
Just pray that there's peace around you, right?
You know what I mean by peace?
It's not like tremendous bloodshed, where you can't,
like, enjoy a meal, or a cigarette, or
a coffee.
You know, how can you make a good
coffee if you hear blood-curdling screams of
people hanging from the street posts?
You're not going to make a good coffee
when you hear that.
No, you're not.
It doesn't matter who's in office, or what
type of, because it's screwed up.
So, in essence, you're buying time.
You know, you're basically a number.
I've said this sonically before.
You're just a number.
There's a certain amount of...
I mean, I've looked at...
It's so funny when I think about it.
I mean, I can't describe the character of
people.
There's no sense.
It's just shit.
When you look at the people around you,
it doesn't matter if they're relatives, friends, acquaintances,
people at the bus stop.
It's just crap.
And if you don't think so, you're not
paying attention.
Why are they here?
What the hell are they doing?
There's a certain amount of bodies, spirits, souls
have to come through this incarnation.
A number.
And if you study scripture, they're into numbers
big time before we go to the next
level.
Like someone recently said, Oh, this guy had
a child he should come and see.
I said, Why?
That little baby's going to grow up to
be a scumbag just like his parents.
I don't need to see him.
Actually, it's going to be very upsetting to
see him.
I'd like to snatch the baby and take
him somewhere where the people are lawful and
knowledgeable and clean and godly, let's say.
So anyway, that's the real reality, not the
reality that people like to indulge in, which
is a farce.
Can a farce be a reality?
Of course.
You're in it.
All right, anything else going on?
Just a fellow who put something in.
Could you please talk a little bit about
depression and contemplating suicide?
What are you waiting for?
I know you have in the past, but
maybe just pretend it's someone you care about,
not just another number.
Oh, that's a good question in a way,
but here's the simplest thing about that.
Depression is, you know how you've heard me
say, could boredom, people say I'm bored, that's
another popular, boredom and depression are undefined.
In other words, it's like taboo to address
them directly.
Let's take boredom.
If you address boredom directly, could boredom be
a form of anger?
I'm not talking about general anger that you
associate.
It's like you don't like the situation, but
you don't want to express it in a
way so you say it's bored, right?
Do you know how they say, is itch,
you know when someone has an itch they
can't scratch medically, that goes into the category
of pain, right?
If you go to the medical technician and
say I'm itchy and I'm uncomfortable, he treats
that no different than he would treat a
pain.
He's going to give you a pain killer
kind of thing, opiate or something to suppress
that.
Steroid.
So can boredom, now can depression be a
cocktail of truth and fiction or farce and
truthfulness?
In other words, could depression be a product
of, you know certain things are true, like
if you don't show up at a certain
time tomorrow your boss will fire you, that's
true, and then there are other things that
you think are true, but you know they're
really not and they're a farce, right?
And you're mixing the two as being sustainable
in your life.
Got to say yea or nay.
if you have a comprehension and understanding that
the culture that you grew up with is
moral, forget about anything else, is even just
moral, you're going to be depressed.
Yeah.
If you think that there's a moral right
in anything that you see around you or
anything is objectively moral, you're an idiot and
you're going to be depressed.
There's not much in the ancient writs about
suicide.
It's actually an honorable way to go when
certain conditions prevent anything else.
Right?
Like, you know, or at least to initiate,
you know it's time for us, we'd rather
take ourselves out than let these guys take
us out.
But you're not in that condition.
Nope.
You know, I don't think any, even people,
you've heard people hanging themselves in prison.
You know, that seems justifiable to a certain
degree.
Why don't you take your clothes off, run
naked down the street before if you're considering
suicide.
So many other things you do.
Put on Netflix.
Go get yourself a cocktail.
You know.
Take up, find a hobby.
Study a little.
Distract yourself.
You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Depression is no such thing.
That's one of the things.
Oh, you sound depressed.
No, no, no, no.
Depression is a mix of fact and fiction.
I'm not mixing fact and fiction.
I know the reality.
Greek-speak and the stuff I do is
a complete anomaly.
Forget it even happened.
It shouldn't even exist.
I'm not saying that it's wrong to do
it.
But it's definitely not right for this society.
Period.
So it's an anomaly.
You know, it's kind of like a Fortean
thing.
You know, like a woman walking her dog
in the morning and the sidewalk opens up
and a guy comes out of it.
You know, it's like, holy shit, what the
hell just happened here?
I know what I saw.
But everyone will laugh at you if you
tell them that, right?
Right.
Or I saw, you know, a guy walk
right through the wall.
I know what I saw.
Yeah.
It's an anomaly.
These are anomalies that I'm talking about.
Yeah.
So anyway, next thing, if there's nothing else,
let's call it for now and make yourself
useful, people.
That was the last one there, Greek.
Yeah.
And to address all the points on the
email, basically, another three minutes here maybe, basically
the cloud at Exodus, the Tower of Babel
was not just a tower.
Go read that again, that section.
The people gathered.
They knew about the sons of gods.
They knew about the divisions that were about
to happen.
They didn't build a tower first.
They built a city first.
It's a city of Babel that was put
together.
And then the Tower of Babel is simply
like a temple area or a temple complex.
When I say complex, it's because it's a
school, court system, and library system, and offering
system.
Right?
Right.
So what do the, have you ever heard
of, for example, okay, at this time, you
had a group of gods that were interacting
with people.
If you go look at, for example, this
is Tower of Babel stuff again.
If you go look, for example, even popularized
in Hollywood and show traditions.
Have you ever heard of like, oh, you
say this thing, abracadabra, whatever, and you summon
this genie.
Right?
Or you recite this ancient thing and you
summon this demon.
Have you heard that before?
Oh, yes.
It's in Hollywood and all this.
And it's in reality also.
In demonology, whatever.
Right?
The Catholics have their own thing or whatever.
So, okay.
Well, apparently, I mean, we're not that smart,
but we're not so stupid to not realize
that this type of accurate summoning is irresistible
to certain spiritual beings.
Did you ever get that kind of hint?
Yeah.
It seems to be irresistible.
Have you ever seen even some Hollywood, they're
like, when they summon the being, he shows
up and he's like, why did you call
me?
Right?
I'm here.
You know, basically that's what I do.
When I hear this, I come.
Right?
He doesn't say, you might say, why did
you bother me?
Right?
Alright, I'm here.
You did it again.
Right?
I'm here.
What do we do now?
Okay, so in other words, there's a certain
type of summoning or quote-unquote offering.
There's a system of sigils, which are, you
know, geographical things that can be written and
formed.
Right?
Corporations use them.
Yeah.
That are irresistible to certain spiritual beings.
And that certain spiritual beings could be billions
of them.
What kind of crap do you think they
were fixing on doing?
Because in Babel at the time, when they
were building this white brick structure, it's not
this stuff that you see popularized in the
art.
By the way, do you know the temple
in Jerusalem was referred to as the Tower
also?
Right.
Anyway, if you go and study, not necessarily
in Scripture, but typically when we're in Jerusalem
and you see the Tower, it's incredible.
Right?
The big white limestone.
So anyway, if you want to know similarly
what the Tower of Babel looked like, go
look at models of what the Temple in
Jerusalem, Yahweh, looked like.
It's not a mystery, what I'm saying.
Well, it is a secret, I should say.
But if you can put a couple of
things together, if you've got at least two
or three sharpened pencils together, you'll see how
everything works out very neatly that way.
But it wasn't to summon the Creator, it
was to summon a veritable plethora of gods
within the spiritual society.
Because it does say that now they're going
to be doing things that we can't stop
them, they're going to be like us.
Right.
Right?
It's very simple.
So simple.
Just knowledge of it has been lost.
Okay.
So, you see, because people have not adjusted
their mindset to this being real, yet.
Fixed appointments to this current moon cycle.
Well, Leviticus, it's very simple, when you look
at the things that are appointed to be
the holidays or days of Yahweh, those cycles,
the days of the month, are based on
the lunar cycle.
Yes.
It doesn't have to say that specifically.
Well, it doesn't say moon.
Well, it kind of does.
It's called the Kodash.
There's various ways of saying it.
You could go look at parallel cultures at
the time.
You know, for example, there hasn't been one
culture on the earth yet where archaeologically they
have not found precision polished observatory quality telescope
type lenses.
Every society on the planet, they have found,
archaeologically speaking, ancient relics that depict astronomical viewing
optic pieces.
Are you familiar with this?
No.
They recently just found one, like the Vikings
had a high-powered, accurate telescope.
Yes, the Vikings.
Okay.
Explanation of what the moon, stars, and planets
actually are.
That's a whole other discussion.
I don't care to form anything too elaborate
voluntarily on that, other than the stars are
an interesting thing.
They're a point source counter-spatial light emission,
meaning that if you don't have resistance, they
don't appear.
Right?
Just like a battery, you need resistance in
a circuit for it to work.
If you don't have resistance in the circuit,
either nothing happens or you short the battery.
Right?
Right.
You ever drop a wrench across the two
terminals on a car battery and the wrench
vaporizes, doesn't it?
Not a good thing to do.
So you need a certain level and the
resistance that allows, you know, if there's no
resistance in a light bulb, it doesn't light
up.
Right?
That's how it works.
So you need a resistive element to view
the stars.
Right?
And the planets are basically globes or spheres,
and someone wanted to have, about two years
ago, I put together a list of stuff
to talk to flat earth people about.
Then I said to myself, why?
It's like trying to talk to Christians about
the Bible.
These people don't need an argument or a
debate on flat earth or Christianity or anything
else.
They need some psychiatric drugs and they need
a straight jacket and a lollipop.
So I stopped.
But there's so many things that can be
discussed on what the planets are.
They're very, planets are very simple.
You know, how many times do you hear
inferences of the gods putting things together with
a high level of efficiency?
We're not going to form a big rock
floating through space.
It would be like the most intricate clay
pot you can imagine.
It's layers.
Very lightweight.
You know, even a whale is extremely lightweight
for its structure.
If you look at a skeleton of a
whale,