Good evening, everyone.
I've got Greek with me.
How are you doing tonight?
Hey, doing well.
I figured we'd just do it, keep some momentum going.
By the way, regarding the stream, I got an email recently about someone catching some viruses on the...
listen to my radio, and I went over there, and it did have a lot of junk.
It did run into a very high, what do you call it, source-intensive peeking around cookies thing.
So I had it.
I wonder if maybe we should talk about this off the stream, because there's better things to talk about, I think.
Certainly.
But I wonder if we should, or you might want to change the way it issues into the public, because I had a link to it on the Uncommon site, and I took it down.
Right.
Now, I wonder, because one of the services, and I think it's the one you're talking about, the talk, was it talk, something like that, and it's more...
Let's just stick to the one we're currently using.
Yeah, the one we're currently using, because there's two flavors.
There's the web-based, which is just a browser, and then the other one, which you had posted, which puts advertisements in there, or sometimes they'll pop up a quick advertisement, and then you have to literally X out of that advertisement in order to get the stream to continue.
Right.
I was totally unaware of that, but we could just stick with the web-based one, and maybe for people listening, that's the one I would choose, rather than using...
I'm glad you brought that to my attention, because that's...
Yeah, I didn't respond back on the email, because I think the person basically said something on the email, like, I clicked on one of your links, Greek, and I got some programs I can't get rid of now.
Well, that's...
Oh, great.
One aspect of that is basic, where I would say, well, then you better figure out how to use programs like iobit and ccleaner, and I should drop a link in the chat, how to remove a computer virus and malware.
There's a guy who did it.
He just put in some really good programs.
The only thing is, if you use one of them, if you haven't used an application or a program in about two or three months, like Malwarebytes or something, we'll remove those programs.
Yeah.
But here, I'll drop a link in the chat.
And there's some real sticky guys out there, or sticky malware out there these days, and they're getting better and better as time proceeds.
As a matter of fact, it's funny that you kind of brought that up.
But what they do, they still use the same old methodology, though.
Correct, correct.
Which is, they try to come across as something that the computer...
Right, right.
Like a photograph or a graphic, yeah.
And then they unfold.
Look at the old days.
You were able to send text in a JPEG, and if properly encoded, you could do other weird stuff.
Yep.
What was it?
It's routing, yeah.
Macro was an old thing, and that was a notorious little creature.
It could be used for good or bad.
But I'm glad you brought that to my attention.
I will certainly make an attempt to see if we can just strictly bring this to web-based.
There is no advertisements that I know of that I've ever seen pop up online.
You won't.
Right.
It's always clean because they know, basically, they'll see that, they'll sniff out that you're the administrator, and there's no reason to intimidate you with it.
And browsers inherently always had that problem that the minute you used them, you're assuming that you gave permission, depending on some of the attributes, like Flash or something like that.
My server, actually, one of the reasons that it was down was I had to delouse and get some things straightened away.
It was kind of acting buggy, so I took it down to make sure that that was addressed.
Okay.
Anything else going on?
Let's say it's outside of the...
I just haven't looked into anything in the chat.
I haven't been around.
I noticed, just in terms of, let's see, for gossip's sake, I see you've been, let's see, chatting here a lot lately, and I see that I'm scrolling up like 20.
We have a couple of new people, Reluctant Observer, Zeromit, MTX, who's that?
Okay.
There was a couple of questions that some of them posted.
I don't know if I should scroll up since the last time I've been here.
Question for the Greek.
You mentioned in the past about the Native Americans coming to disbelieve on their gods, which led to their inevitable destruction.
Has the same happened in Western world, or has it been replaced with Justicia?
Or, if so, is this a global displacement of the past gods?
I see someone here.
Hi, Emily, 29, female.
Rate my naked photos on sex dating.
Oh, yeah, that one popped in there.
Where is that question in time that you just read?
Is that recent?
Yes, I'll pop it to you.
I see.
Oh, here, actually, I think it's 2.41.17 p.m. today.
Question for the Greek.
That one you mentioned in the past, the Native, the one you just read.
It's just interesting to read it.
I get a little more sense of it.
But I heard you say, okay, regarding the replacement or the, what do you call it when you supplant something?
Yeah, of course.
It's kind of confusing.
I think I've given enough recitations on how the gods work and how humans work that one could piece it together, so I'm not going to answer that question because it's already been answered.
Right.
Basically, that's a question that is just answered in itself.
I mean, yeah, the answer is there as well.
So, yes, the answer to that question is yes.
Yes, so.
It says, or if so, is this global displacement of the past gods?
Yes, across the board there, yeah.
The day the sun stood still, can you elaborate?
Yeah, not now.
That takes too much time because you have to understand the movement of the stars.
Greek mentioned that he would revisit the day the sun stood still.
You know, it's interesting.
There's so little knowledge of astronomy, even by astronomers.
Is that so difficult to imagine?
There's so little knowledge of medicine by medical doctors, and there's so little knowledge of money through bankers, right?
Speaking of bankers, I see there's banking questions here.
Yeah, Othello was relaying his fun times with the banking establishment.
Wow, that's interesting.
Regarding the day standing still, I mean, I still have people that don't know, you know, speak to me that don't know the most basic stuff about astronomical movements.
I'm not talking about the bullshit NASA stuff, you know, what space is and the solar system.
That's all bullshit.
But just the basic astronomical movements, like, for example, people are just, I think just because since I've been speaking, getting practical knowledge of what the purpose of the sun and the moon is in terms of other, you know, in terms of reckoning other than just providing heat and light and something to look at or other forces that imbue nature.
So, yeah, that's a, yeah, I could do that one day.
I have to, I have a lot of notes on it.
So, the banking, someone did some banking, they refused.
Is this the one of the lowest times I'm living in hell?
Yeah, yeah.
Checking account with my, oh, that's the problem with the language here.
My endorsed check, you see, right away this person's going to have problems.
Without title 12, section 401, or why would you do it without, with demand of lawful money.
I don't get that.
My endorsed check without title 12, section 401, with demand of lawful money.
Okay, you can just do lawful money only.
That's a demand also.
Just like, you know, when you go somewhere, you know, they say only this, right?
Like, you know, like if you have the blue ticket, only blue ticket here, only red ticket here.
That's a demand, you know.
Right, right.
Okay, they refused doing business with me because I won't sign the electronic pad.
What?
Okay, no, you don't, well, you don't kind of do it like that.
They said we cannot control P.
Oh, that's print.
It's not part of the system, so whatever it is, I signed void and scribbled my name.
That's another problem, my name.
They had three checking account options, direct deposit only.
I don't do direct deposit.
No one does direct deposit.
But anyway, option deposit with the bank teller.
I never got into what direct deposit really is, did I, Anasonic?
Yes, you did.
Okay, well, this is, I've done this with, this person here knows just enough to be dangerous but not to do it properly.
That's an open criticism.
That's okay.
You know what I mean?
A little bit of information is not good.
It's like telling someone who hasn't seen an automobile before, well, here's the key, here's the pedal, here's the steering wheel.
That's fine, but it's not a, that's, and if you read later that they crashed the car or they ran over someone, would you be surprised?
No.
Yeah, this is something else.
But that's okay.
This is, you know, this is fine.
This is not on the KN82.
However, this is normal.
That's normal to go through that.
Actually, when I started rummaging through this stuff, I had, was like that as well.
And what that is, is you're not, you want to look dumb but be smart.
It's better than being, looking smart and being dumb like a professor or an attorney or a judge, right?
Right.
They look smart but they're dumb.
So, what you want to do is look dumb.
I mean, it could even go down to the point where you have to study enough to know what they have available to them.
So, instead of asking, you're asking and telling at the same time.
Right.
You know what I mean?
So, what you do with the, with, for example, you should write lawful money only per title 12 section 411 because that gives the legal basis for something to look up.
USC, just write 12 USC S, you know, 411.
You know how to write the section.
It looks like a dollar sign but it doesn't go through the S.
It's just the top and bottom.
Regarding the electronic pad, you just say, I'd like to do the written one because my accountant and attorney say I need it for tax purposes.
Correct.
Got to use the same lingo, Adam.
And if they ask you, why are you using this section?
That's just an old banking convection.
I do it for tax purposes.
Right.
Whenever you see tax purposes, they shut down.
They're like, okay, yeah.
Yeah, he's got permission.
Yeah, the electronic pad, okay, the thing, okay, there's something called the Paperwork Reduction Act, which they did after 9-11.
Actually, it started before that.
And that was to start, okay, let's just jump around a little bit.
They may not know as much as we do, meaning what people listen to Greek speak about what's coming on the world.
But they do know there's not a lot of time left.
You know, the ones that are in control.
We're not talking about politicians.
We're not talking about Trump or Merkel or Putin or Saddam Hussein or anybody like that, right, or Fidel Castro.
They don't know.
I mean, they're just puppets, really.
They're leaders of the people, and when you're this simple, you know, slave type, that is as high as you can go.
Just like people who are into religion, they can only go as high as what's put in front of them.
They can't go to the next level because it requires five minutes of study.
Right.
And to have awareness, actually.
What's going on is they know that people are money.
You're just a collateral.
Let's just say it that way.
Right.
And they like to play games, and when you're playing a game, you know, if you're losing, you take more chances than when you're winning, right?
And if you know the game is going to be over and everything else around the game is going to be over, you might as well play.
One of the things that the powers that be like to play with is what's called monetization.
And just to go back to this person's experience at the bank, which I've read at least 100 of these in the past 10 years, similar things, is this.
It's very simple.
There is no money.
There is no bank.
The first problem that you might encounter mentally is this person didn't go to a bank.
And I see when I scroll down, also you mentioned you have a bank.
There are no banks.
And what I mean by that is the Emergency Banking Acts from 1933, 1934, 1938, 1946, 1965, 1981, all those Emergency Banking Acts have never been resolved.
They're still in effect.
In other words, they're closed.
All the banks are closed.
They're just there like an office.
Like when you go to a movie theater, they have the little ticket booth.
That's in the movie theater.
What you have, if you pull out a 20, pull out a 20.
Do you have a 20 note or one of the newer notes?
Hold on a second.
Pull it out.
I want you to read what it says on there.
It doesn't say Federal Reserve Bank.
What does it say?
Note, I believe.
No?
Let's see.
I don't have a 20.
I've got everything else.
I've got a stack of them here holding the door open.
Federal Reserve Note.
Actually, you have to look on 100.
Sorry.
On the 100, it says Federal Reserve Note.
It's the one where they have it parked over to the side and the signatures are on the same side.
It says Federal Reserve System.
Oh.
It's a system.
Yes.
The banks have been closed.
Whenever you see the term bank, it just means they're leaving it up because people are so stupid that you might as well not.
Okay, so the system is about monetizing you and your behavior.
Now, you can monetize something that you own.
That's why no government or corporation will deal with you unless you produce a social security number, which is attached to the title to your body, which is the birth certificate.
Right?
It's just about property.
They don't care if you live or die.
The only thing they care about is can they monetize you.
The problem becomes when they make more money when you're dead.
Ha ha ha.
That's why you have bad food.
That's why you have bad medicine and bad law and all.
You have no law.
Also, the term legal through history, you could look this up.
It's kind of hard on the Internet.
Whenever the word legal was brought up, it had to do with property, contracts, or slaves.
Free people use the word law.
And if you go in society, all they care about is what's legal or illegal, right?
All right.
So get it out of your mind that these are banks.
Get it out of your mind.
What they're doing, it's an elaborate hoax, right, not on you.
There's a difference when you're hoaxing someone.
It's a hoax for you because if they didn't hoax you, you wouldn't know what to do.
So you need the hoax.
You see what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
To keep you comfortable.
So if you think you're going to go and mitigate for yourself this condition, because you're not going to change anything, right, and deal with it in a way that it's real, you're going to end up with unsuccessful.
But if you know, like, for example, here's another thing.
When I see the cops beating somebody up, that has to be that way because if it wasn't, if the state that the people are in right now, there would be utter chaos.
You need to have brutality to manage these idiots.
You see what I mean?
Right.
It's the same old thing.
But he's not beating up.
It doesn't offend me when I see the cop beating the guy up for no reason because he's not doing that for me.
He's doing it because it's an example of what level society is on.
Right.
You see what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
When I see the church and the priest and all.
Instill that belief.
Well, yeah, to maintain the social order that exists.
See, the people that are running the show, which no one, I mean, for sure, people on this listening don't know who they are because they haven't done the research.
It's not hard to figure out who they are.
Who they are doesn't matter because whether you know who they are or not, you're not going to be able to affect it.
Right.
But they are honorable to a certain degree.
But let's go to the next subject because banking requires you have to be a really sharp listener, like before the mini televisions, you know, the iPods or whatever they're called mini televisions now also, and the rectangles and all that.
People were judged, like in engineering circles, if you saw an engineer with a lot of pencils in his pocket, that's like the guy who you go to when you want to discuss problem solving.
Right.
The guy who had a chocolate bar and his glasses in his shirt pocket with one pencil, he's the kind of guy you put aside and you wait until you figure everything out and then tell him and don't count on him getting it.
So that's why I always joke around.
You want to find a guy with at least three sharpened pencils in his pocket.
That dates me to the child of the 60s and early 70s.
I was brought up on slide rule until the Texas Instrument and the HP-11C came out later, a little $200 calculator.
Remember those?
Reverse pulse notation.
Texas Instruments.
I noticed that the nerds were nerdy for a reason because, you know, these outcast types, right?
Right.
So if you understand that being not part of this society and dealing with it on a higher level, based on the level that it was set up for, then you'll be successful, you see.
But if you want to go in and do things your way on a system that is set up to be the other way or similar to what you think, it's not going to work ever.
Yeah.
There's a lot to discuss on the banking.
And I think I'm the only person on the Internet or the rectangle that's actually come out and discussed – actually, I know this for a fact.
People have searched what I've been saying for years and they haven't found any of it.
But I can prove it on how money is really transferred from account to – you know, when you deposit a check for $100 and then you see that it's taken out.
I mean, write a check for $100, let's say.
Right.
And you see they debited it.
You think that they actually took it out of your account and sent it to someone.
No, they didn't.
You see, they still have it, but they can't show you that because – right?
So, there's no – because this is on a need-to-know – let's say 99% of the stuff that I've discussed is not useful to 99% of the people.
You get why, right?
Right.
Because it talks about how things really work.
Now, if most of the people have been bred and raised to believe in hoaxes, regardless what the subject is, the anti-hoax material doesn't jive.
Right.
But anyway, running head first and all feet and hands forward into something that is not what it really – what you think it is is going to always cause trouble.
Right?
Like, if you run into them and you think they're a bank, you're not going to succeed negotiating or doing business on the terms that are favorable to you.
Just like, for example, if you don't know how to drive a car and someone shows you – or operate – let's just say operate an engine-driven wagon.
Right.
And someone just tells you, this is the brake, this is the gas, this is the steering wheel.
You think it's a car.
No, it's not.
What that really is is a shaped and formed metal and glass and rubber with a reciprocating engine that simulates hundreds of – or a hundred horsepower at least, that represents a hunk – a two-ton or one-and-a-half to two or three tons sometimes – a hunk of metal rolling down the road, which in ancient times that would be called a siege work.
That's something that you use to take down a crowd of people or drive through a wall.
You see how – I see them as weapons, cars.
They're not really transportation devices because of the potential damage that they do.
Not that I think they should be weapons, but they potentially – I see them as doing more harm than good once the thing gets flipped over and it goes into the lack of responsibility, lack of control, right?
Right.
You see?
I don't – people say it's a car.
I'm like, yeah, to me it's a ton-and-a-half or two tons of metal and things formed that can track and roll on the surface of the earth.
It's not very good at stopping.
And the basic – what they call Newtonian physics, which is bullshit anyway, takes effect.
So just like would you be surprised if someone had never seen a car before and you told them this is the steering wheel brake and gas, go down the road, and would you be surprised if you heard the next day they ran into something and damaged?
Not too much.
No, you wouldn't be surprised because they were just introduced to it and they didn't contemplate really what's going on.
No.
Okay, the same thing – here's another thing.
Let's get a little semi-cryptic now instead of full-on cryptic.
When you go to the doctor, it's the same thing with dealing with the banks.
When you go to the court, it's the same thing with dealing with the banks.
When you go to university, it's the same thing you're doing with the banks.
You get it?
Yeah.
The doctor is not a doctor.
It doesn't matter what color Robey wears or whatever.
He works for the state, which is a part of another system that most people know nothing about.
The university works for the state.
They're there to satisfy the need.
The court, same thing.
None of these things that you see around you – how many times have we discussed the church as the circus?
There was a high level of reverence and sacredness connected to the ancient circuses, the same thing that they're doing right now.
Are you living here and part of it, or are you visiting here and don't want to be part of it?
There's a big difference, right?
Right.
It doesn't mean you're not going to partake.
For example, today I was asked to prepare a dish for a potluck thing for somebody.
It was a white people thing.
I was like, do you want to go?
I was like, hell no.
There's no way they could produce any good food, and I was correct.
That sounds like you're very pessimistic, right?
Well, I'm realistic.
Actually, I brought back some samples of the stuff.
I was like, oh man, I was right.
Could I be surprised that there might be white people having a semi-decent edible potluck?
It's possible.
It might have happened, maybe, like Halley's Comet.
Blue moon.
Yeah, which doesn't make sense either.
Blue moon is two full moons in a month, right?
Right.
It's an oxymoron.
Either way, I would suggest that once you start looking at things as they are, the thing is you might want to ask for what they really are, not what you think they are, based on what's presented as their usefulness.
Because something like a bank is presented as being usefulness to you, and if you have to use it, well, you could go this route that we saw in the chat, or you can contemplate it.
And also, you might have to go to what's reasonable.
I found when people first start learning how to deal with money, the difference between money and credit, because you're not going to get either, really, because you're being screwed with the credit also, and I've never really got into how they're screwing you with that.
That's a whole other level.
But once you start seeing what's going on, I would say two to three banks is what you're going to be going around to, shopping around, talking to them and all that.
Don't go into one and settle in just because you don't like to let them do what they do, right?
I know for a fact there are some people that have been working on Wells Fargo.
Wells Fargo, by the way, they're in the spotlight now.
They're getting spanked for many years now for a lot of money laundering stuff.
Here they all are.
Right.
Anyway, the money laundering aspect is all the drug dealing and all the pedophilia and all the human trafficking and all that.
You're not allowed to do that, but that's because it's their bread and butter.
You see?
Anyway, not that you should want to do it.
But anyway, Wells Fargo, they've been worked on in several ways where if someone comes in and is quite polite and quite reasonable and it does get over to legal, they do comprehend the USC 12411, 411.
They do comprehend that, right?
The worst ones would be like Chase, J.P. Morgan, and Bank of America.
Those are the worst that I've heard of.
A lot of the smaller ones, all banks seem to charge around $15 a month.
Anyway, commercial banks can charge as much as $75 a month for a commercial account.
I had one of those a long time ago.
To make a long story short here, doing the thing with the bank is like saying, Bruce, where can we find a church to go to that is proper?
That's like Blue Moon.
It's an oxymoron.
It is.
Just by the nature of what we just used the description on, right?
Yeah.
Another thing, I think I've been giving out enough information just to make people dangerous, not useful.
I mean, at one point there was someone I was working on, even though I knew it wouldn't be a success, but it doesn't mean you don't stop, just like the white people with the potluck, right?
Right.
You do it anyway.
Regarding the Title 12, Section 411, and he had to go to some government office, and he wanted to use cash or whatever, and he did.
I said, why don't you just slip him a piece of paper with all the serial numbers on the cash and give it to him?
This person, after working with him for quite a long time, still didn't get it.
I said, what happened?
He said, well, I gave him the paper and the cash, and she asked me, what should I do with this?
And the paper had the Title 12, Section 411, and the serial numbers, right?
Right.
I don't want to put you on the spot, but are you aware of how to properly document cash?
I remember the conversation well, yes.
Okay, good.
All right, so he gives it to the clerk, and the clerk says, well, what am I going to do with this?
And the guy responds, well, I don't know, whatever you want.
Wrong answer.
The clerk just crumbled it up and threw it away.
Ooh.
What's the right answer?
That is for your records.
Right.
So the person I've been talking to about this for like a long time still didn't get it.
So, I mean, how long do you talk to someone, like if you have a baby, how long do you try to keep them, how long do you work with them until they learn to walk?
Well, whether it's a week, two months, or five years, or seven years, right?
Right.
But these people are not babies.
These people are not babies.
I wish I was a fly on the wall.
Why does everyone want to be a fly, right?
Right.
I think I heard this from Seinfeld.
Why don't you just walk in like a man?
You're not a baby learning how to walk.
Right.
So I realize it's not wasting time because it comes back on me in a way that's good.
Like often, you know, I'd go on these calls and even sonic events, like, Greek, why are you still doing this?
You know, no one's really listening or understanding anyway, you know, these morons, right?
I'm like, well, you ever think that I'm actually doing it for selfish reasons?
I'm practicing, maybe, you know, for something that might be real important in the future?
Mm-hmm.
Right?
Right.
So, but, you know, that's why.
It does take a level of investigating before you even try to take that step forward.
Oh, yeah, most people never get it.
You know, when I say never, it's in the condition you're in.
Now, if it was 200 years ago, it would be people won't get it for 200-plus years.
You know, if it was 1,000 years ago, you could say people won't get it for 1,000-plus years.
But fortunately, because of the time period you're in now, you're going to get it, but you're not going to get it the way you think it is.
You know, you're going to have to be given a new body, and I mean spiritual body as well.
Mm-hmm.
You know, so it's sad, but, you know, it's not.
It's not.
Would you rather know the truth and deal with it however?
You know, everyone deals with information differently.
Some people might panic.
Some people might be apathetic.
Some people might get angry.
Some people might get sad.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
But still, when you get the truth, you react to it in everyone's capacity, emotionally, emotional capacity, according to the character or spirit of that individual.
Correct.
And I've noticed that most people have the dumb bug or the stupidity so deeply entrenched that it's best to just leave it alone because their lives would be simple.
It wouldn't be a point ever.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So their lives would be much more simple.
But on the other hand, let's just make a long story short here.
Anyone who does try it and has a hard time with it, it's better from an altruistic point of view or from an honorable point of view, it's better to have known.
Anyway, I think most people will say, well, I can't do it like you, Greek, or I can't do it like this guy.
Well, would you rather have not known about it?
They still say, no, I want to know.
And you learn from your mistakes.
And hopefully it doesn't affect you too bad.
Yeah, you're not going to really learn from your mistakes.
No, very few people actually do because you have to have a very good memory and you have to be a good record keeper, meaning mental records, to learn from your mistakes.
I see most people just repeating the same.
I see most people doing what they're doing is a mistake.
So most people, in other words, they don't even know what they're doing is the mistake.
And what they think is the mistake is really not.
It's usually an insufficiency that wasn't taken through.
Right.
Unless you actually make a bad choice, like you're on a TV show, like the price is right and you choose the wrong curtain or something, right?
Correct.
Then it's different.
So I really enjoy law discussion, money discussion.
And when I say law and money, that goes back to scripture, of course, and all that.
Not in a rabbinical sense because they sit there and split hairs on everything.
I like to look at the scope of it because these things like law and money are far-reaching principles that go into everything in terms of motivating people and human behavior.
That's why, for example, when somebody sends me something regarding someone, no matter how good it is, if they don't know how the money system works or how law works, there's only so much they can do.
Like look at Jack Fresco.
He had no idea on how the money system worked.
Right.
I mean, not any more than anyone else.
Well, it's paper money.
Yeah, whatever.
They don't know how it works.
So that's why nothing ever worked out for him.
And I'm not saying that's why, but if you knew how the money system works, there's no way this would work.
It's so entrenched, so deep.
Or the law.
See, most people don't know law because they're not entitled to it.
If you have a birth certificate, you're not entitled to law.
You're entitled to what's called rights.
Because you're already, you're just a piece of property.
Right.
You see?
Yeah.
So there is none of that.
Since when are slaves entitled or property entitled to banking?
Huh.
That's like an old thing.
Never.
That's why the banks have never, they never bothered reopening them.
Yeah.
Now even a college professor, if you took this to Harvard, would say, the Greek is ridiculous.
Of course the banks are open.
That's how stupid they are.
So if your academicians, your high-level intellectuals are stupid, what does that leave you?
Not doing too good.
Yeah.
So again, you know, why bother?
So I see that going on.
So what else have we got in the questions?
But anyway, kudos to the person who went to the bank and did it, but they didn't do it right.
Well, they didn't do it right, no.
They didn't do it wrong either, because actually they should have just walked in like everybody else, because the result on the end was the same.
Right.
And they're probably going to get shafted by the taxman if they don't comply.
Oh, yeah.
So they don't know how to do it.
Yeah, you better learn how to keep records.
Real good.
Because they're not, see, you don't have to be honorable with a slave.
There's no reason for it, because they're just peace property.
You don't have to be honorable with a car.
You know, so what?
You crash the car, big deal, there's insurance for it.
There's no honor, but when you start acting like you're not a slave, but not a rebellious slave that's freed on his own terms, but on the real terms, which are lawful terms, then things will work.
But not the way you think they are, but they will work out.
You see?
Because what happens is, also another thing here, most people are too used to dealing with people that are too low on the bottom rung or the ladder or the totem pole.
Whether you're dealing with medical, scientific, academic, banking, legal, religious, most people you'll be dealing with the bottom low level leadership administrative.
You're dealing too low.
So your priest, your minister, is too low level.
He's the grunt.
When you're dealing with the bank, in the banking community, they have the grunts do the new accounts and the tellers.
You just want to open the bank account with the manager.
You call in.
I'm such and such, Mr. Such and Such.
I'd like to find out who's the manager's name.
I speak to him.
I'd like to set up an appointment to initiate business with your institution.
Right.
Not your bank.
Because also if you look up, I can't get off this bank thing.
Banks are not banks.
They're considered...
What are they?
Institutions.
You know what they are legally?
Well, yes.
But legally, what are they called?
An association.
They're not corporations.
Yes, they're a national association.
Yep.
What else is a national association?
Sierra Club.
Burl Scouts.
Yeah.
Boy Scouts.
Look up a list of national associations.
They're not...
Now, these national associations do have corporations.
Yes.
That's why if you have a credit card, you never get a bill from the credit card company.
It's always a corporation that is using the credit cards.
That's another thing I need to share one day is how to really stick it to these guys from that direction.
But, yeah.
When you get an American Express bill at the end of the month, that has nothing to do with American Express.
That is someone using their letterhead.
And it looks authentic.
In a corporation, yeah.
Yep.
And not even by American Express's permission, but by the permission of the attorneys of American Express.
There's a difference now.
Yeah.
Imagine having an attorney, Bruce, run your affairs, and he starts doing stuff that you are not supposed to be doing.
Does that ever happen?
All the time.
I've seen that happen.
Yeah.
Oh, my.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
What else we got?
Question for the Greek.
Sounds painful.
Same with my bank.
Oh, you got a bank.
Let me see.
Rephrase.
Same bank would I go to.
Okay.
Good.
Yeah.
Because if you have a bank, you shouldn't have a problem.
If you have your own bank.
Right.
See, that's why the language.
As soon as I see my, this, I, that.
I got away.
I caught myself right away.
That's slave talk.
Yeah.
Enoch.
I'll leave that.
Yeah.
Enoch, you know, there's a lot of controversy on it.
It's all wrong.
Book of Enoch?
Book of Enoch has nothing to do with Enoch other than it is an oral tradition that has been written.
Mm-hmm.
Book of Enoch, Book of Yashar, which is the Book of the Upright, Yashar.
Right.
The Book of the Upright.
Those are literary records of what the priests spoke about during the First Temple era.
Yeah.
Okay.
Just like, or maybe earlier, slightly earlier, during the time of judges as well.
That's like having a book on what the, you know how firemen stay overnight, say 40 hours straight, 50 hours straight at work.
Mm-hmm.
They don't go home for three days, right?
You know how that works, right?
Or fishermen.
Right.
Yeah.
They have plenty of time to talk.
Imagine the firemen putting out a book on, you know, what things we talk about at the firehouse.
Okay.
It doesn't mean it's not worth reading if you're interested in firefighting, but it has a lot of juicy stuff.
You're not going to get anywhere else, right?
Right.
Because it's people that work in it.
So that's what you're going to get out of it.
Okay.
All of it is, I mean, I'd rather read that than read Melville, you know, or any other human author.
You've got to keep the context.
It's a literary work.
It's not inspired directly.
It's not given, there's no angelic dictation given like the prophets were.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
So Enoch was taken and not dying.
No, incorrect.
Enoch has died.
Anyone that has been taken up into heaven has died unless it tells you they haven't.
And the secret to that is very simple.
Either you look in scripture where it says that this one will remain until, right?
Or it tells you that there's a spirit of that person.
So there's two people in scripture who have yet to die, not died.
One is because it's direct order to remain until he's coming.
Right.
And the other one is because there's a spirit that holds them.
So if I said Bruce, Bruce got taken up, the company car, right?
The company car, the whirlwind, right?
Right.
Yeah, came and got you.
And it was also said that he will return in the spirit of Bruce.
Okay.
Or the spirit of Bruce will return.
Right?
That's where you get the term spirited when someone is taken away.
Right, right.
That person is still alive.
Okay.
Right.
So there's two people that have not died because one has been actually discussed thoroughly that he will remain until a certain time.
And the other one was spirited and the spirit of that person needs to return.
Because, okay, I think I've done enough in the past few years of sonic events to give an idea of the order and how things work, right?
And just to recap really fast, if you see a god, you die.
The closest ones to the most high, even his direct angel has that effect.
The one that is his body double.
Right.
If you see him, you die.
Walking with someone is not necessarily seeing them.
True.
I remember once in the 80s there was a politician.
They closed the whole road down and he was going through in a limousine.
I'm not going to say it was very high level in America.
And I yelled something out.
He rolled down the window and he says, come on, walk with me here.
I've got to say something to you.
And I did.
But did I go in the limousine?
Was I 25, 30 feet away?
Yes.
Wow.
You see?
If I tried to touch him, what would happen?
Secret Service would shoot me dead, right?
Oh, yeah.
Get it?
Yes, I do.
Same thing here.
If you see the gods or are in their presence, you will die.
Period.
Doesn't matter who you are.
Thank you for the clarification on that.
That helps.
Well, no, that's fine.
There's two people that have been retained and it discusses how and why.
And it's not Enoch and it's not Moses.
Right.
And I think that's God.
Now, do you know who they are?
Or you don't have this rhetorical question, don't bother answering.
Okay.
There are two people in scripture.
And they will make an appearance again while most people who are listening to me are alive.
Hopefully.
To some degree.
Right.
Yeah.
And also, it's not going to be one of these secret appearances because apparently the whole world will see them.
It says.
So when it says the whole world, it's through the little mini television you put in your back pocket or your shirt pocket.
Yeah.
Okay.
So let's see what else have we got here.
That's most of it.
The rest of it is you.
Let's go further back.
Is there anything else?
We've got 13 people on the chat.
Yeah.
There's a question about the biological vacuum.
We've got Emily call in.
Yeah.
I was going to say the last time when you hung up, a person called in just maybe 30 seconds after you hung up.
So that was bad timing.
Let's see.
Haven't you noticed?
Hey, haven't you noticed?
I think I know who that is.
Okay.
Judeans are Judeans because they live in an area of Judea.
It does not mean they are ethnically a tribe of Yehudah.
Yahshua, Joshua, the 12 tribes of Yehudah.
Okay.
Are you guys familiar with that message there?
It's pretty long for a message.
Yeah, that's right.
Judaism is a culture and they made it a religion.
Very good.
Someone's on their toes.
There.
Yeah.
The Jew thing is a tradition thing.
All of it is a tradition.
If you go and talk to them about anything, they're like, eh, we don't care about that.
This is tradition we're keeping.
If we were all screwing each other up the anus long enough and it became a tradition, you'd come here and that's what we would be doing.
You see, it has nothing to do with any law.
Whatever they pick and choose is what they do.
If you want screwing up the anus, that's the Catholic Church.
Sorry, by the way.
The Jews do a lot of it, too, and it's religious.
Sleepaway camp.
Yeah, I was molested during sleepaway camp.
Oh, yeah.
I've never been to that.
Shit's been going on since time immemorial.
All right, let's go back.
I think we're going back to about a week.
Not much.
There's tons to talk about.
I'm constantly researching and contemplating and meditating on stuff.
I think just doing the sonic event is just keeping some kind of momentum with no purpose other than it's there to do.
I think it's therapeutic for at least one or two people.
I get emails regarding that.
I've got bragging rights on saying I've got more on the rectangle in the order of a hundred to a thousand times more than what anybody else has put out ever.
In terms of subject matter and accuracy and precision and all that.
More than a hundred times.
I've looked at stuff.
I'm like, this is ridiculous.
In other words, not because I'm special.
Anybody can do it.
The Greek-speak stuff, what I just mentioned in terms of bragging.
Anyone.
You don't even need a cape or any superhero powers or anything.
It's real basic stuff.
Once you get a hold of the basics, you understand that there's not even complexity in a negative sense.
But this wonderful fabric of things that weave together, everything is intertwined.
Most people have no idea that the medical system is run by the legal system.
In other words, they say they don't know that.
But they do hear it constantly.
If you've ever been around a doctor, he says, legally, I can't say that.
How many times have you heard that?
Just the very order.
The same thing with your food is controlled by the lawyers and the bankers.
By the way, there are no bankers, so the lawyers are the bankers.
Whenever you have a problem with a corporation or financial institution, where does it go?
Legal.
Yes, they're the ones running it.
And no one cares to notice.
They have noticed that, but no one cares to notice it.
Probably a lot of intimidation, I would think.
With words.
When they bring out the guys with the guns and the brutality, that's because you failed with the words.
Right.
You see.
We need another Greek or an Italian or a Spaniard.
Forget about Greek-speak.
We need Spain-speak or Italian-speak.
Why don't we get somebody else out there?
Why does it have to be race or nationality?
Nationality, yes.
Just have somebody else come here and start talking.
You're not going to get it from all these other idiots.
So we need a non-idiot to get on the rectangle and do some sonic events.
Yes.
Which is hard to find.
It doesn't exist, by the way.
You'll have some people here and there.
Most of the stuff that's good on the internet, by the way, on the rectangle, is very narrow.
Shallow, some of it, and some of it deep.
Very, very restricted in subject matter.
Once they go outside of the subject that you deem to be good, they fall apart like everyone else.
You know what I mean?
Right.
Sorry, guys.
Humanity sucks.
What is dwelling on the surface of the planet other than the insects and the animals and the trees and other misanthropes?
If you're misanthropic, I don't blame you, but I don't think you're that smart anyway.
I'm not talking about being smart.
Are you noticing anything?
The answer is no.
I see it all the time.
No matter where you are in the world, it's the same.
It's getting more and more homogenous.
What you do have underpinning that homogeneity is the various different traditions still underpin it.
In certain countries, if something was never done, you're not going to find it there.
Especially if it's something that's going to be introduced that goes against their traditions.
Like, let's say, pigs in Israel.
You don't even import them.
You're not going to see that.
Right.
Or photos of people with the bottoms of their feet showing in Muslim countries, because that's showing the middle finger, right?
Otherwise, they're being more and more homogenized.
So, no questions or anything?
I think we'll just make another short one.
Otherwise, I'm going to have to start volunteering subject matter, which I'm not doing anymore.
No more new subjects, I think.
If people have questions, that's fine.
But I'd like to just get off this planet.
My spaceship doesn't look like it'll be finished any time soon.
A couple of times, I thought I had it right.
Where do you go?
Anywhere but here.
When you're in a real shithole of a planet, or you ever see a movie where they're in a bad neighborhood, it's like, go!
Where are we going?
Anywhere.
Just get out of here.
Just get out.
Yep.
And it's more of what they're not doing that makes it a shithole than what they're doing, believe it or not.
Because the possibilities of what can be done, that is not being addressed, is much greater than the bullshit, crap, vile crap that they're doing.
It's much better, and much more variety, and much more possibility.
We've got a call coming in.
Hold on.
I'll take that guy off the air here a second, Greek, and I'll let you continue.
Is it a Skype or a phone call?
It's a phone call.
Hold on.
If you've been on before, tell us you've been on before.
Otherwise, we'll call it a day.
Hey, Greek, we've got a call coming in.
Yeah?
You think you could hear us?
One second.
I'm going to patch us through.
Okay, there you go.
You're on.
Go ahead.
Can you hear them?
Yeah, I'm getting an echo here.
There we go.
What could he possibly say?
Okay, go ahead.
Yes, I believe so.
Okay.
No, I don't hear anything.
Do you?
Greek, can you hear Valerie?
Oh, it's Valerie.
Great.
I'd love to hear Valerie.
No, I cannot hear Valerie.
Okay, there we go.
Now we've got you.
No, I can't.
Okay, now I hear Valerie.
I think we've got you.
Now we can hear you.
Okay, you're having troubles there.
She's having trouble.
One second.
We'll get you in there one way or another.
Okay, how about that?
I'd like to hear from Valerie.
Well, I had asked if I could call over a regular telephone.
Sure.
VoIP phone, and it's really not working on my end.
Okay, but could she hear us?
Yeah, I believe so.
Can you hear Greek?
You're breaking up really bad.
Oh, okay.
Just call back.
Just call right back.
Okay, okay.
I'll try.
Okay, bye-bye.
We'll see if we can get her in here, Greek.
Yeah, I think Valerie is somebody that contemplates and is working on the crap.
Most people are quite happy with their crap.
Okay.
Hello?
Is that a Skype ring?
I hear it loud and clear.
I like it.
I like the effects.
Yeah.
There we go.
Good.
Well, I'm going to try to get on my Skype because I hear my voice echoing in the phone.
Okay, duplexing.
I apologize.
Can you hear us?
I'm going to try to get on my Skype and call in.
Okay, see you soon.
Okay, okay.
Okay, we'll get her in here.
It's a deplorable thing, but it works.
Everything on Skype is recorded.
Everything, everyone, all the time.
Yes.
Everything is, and it's not for any malicious reason.
If you ever met any of these older government types, not the young ones, they're too brainwashed.
The older ones, which I realize it's all been bullshit, especially people in the military.
I still can't believe how people thank people for your service.
If you've ever spoken to anyone in the military that actually did anything or was half awake, they'll say, oh, it was all bullshit every time.
It doesn't matter what war it is.
Even the Civil War.
There was a bunch of stuff in the early 2000s, Civil War letters, and stuff that they were putting up as archives and basically talking about this is all bullshit.
They took all that stuff down.
It's all bullshit.
If you understand the NSA, CIA, and all that, it's all about monetization.
Right.
There is no crime.
The worst crime that anyone committed in this world is what?
To be born in it.
Right.
You're a criminal when you're born.
What the hell do you do?
You didn't have to do anything other than that.
Just be born.
Yeah, how do we know that it's a criminal affair?
Not because I say it.
It's on paper.
Where do you see that?
It's a criminal affair.
On the birth certificate, the mother is the informant.
Mm-hmm.
That's your crime.
That's right.
So anyway.
And whose planet is this anyway?
Right now, legally.
Satan's planet.
Ha ha.
What's that laugh in South Park?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
And those are things that people will never, ever, ever, ever even comprehend.
Ever.
Yeah.
Sad.
Makes the spaceship look really good.
It really does.
Oh, yeah.
Food, clothing, shelter, folks.
It's just a show.
I wonder if she's going to try to contact you or...
I think you.
Oh.
If you just...
I don't know if you could shoot a message to her.
I think I have someone here, according to the contacts, that might be...
I don't really remember.
I only have about 25 or 30 people here, I think.
I don't really remember what her handle is, the handle she uses.
Yeah.
I can't remember right offhand either.
But we had another lady that wanted to call in and didn't and dropped off.
You said you fixed it.
And actually...
That was Nicole, I believe.
I'm going to add her to group call, see what happens.
Okay.
Because it's the same handle.
Right.
I'm calling her, so...
Okay.
Yeah, so if she picks up...
There we go.
Valerie.
No sound.
Check the mic.
You could just hit the green button and get off, Valerie, and do a mic test.
Skype test.
Yeah, do the Skype test, see if you're working.
I'll drop it in the text box for you, Valerie.
Actually, if it doesn't sense a microphone in a speaker, it won't even allow you to log on or use it.
So I just dropped in Valerie in the text box.
Yes, I see that.
Echo, yeah.
Echo test, yeah.
Give her a few seconds to run that through.
Well, she's still on, she can't run it while she's on.
Right.
She can't run it while she's on the call.
So I'm going to drop...
Drop her, and then that'll get her off.
Yep, she dropped.
Okay, on her own.
Okay.
Nephilim, complicated.
Yes, very.
Complicated, but I would resolve it as, if you understand the sons of gods, if you understand other manifestations other than human manifestations.
Yeah.
It's within that understanding.
Now, the comprehension there is minimal.
Because it goes back to the, when I say pre-Adamic, Adam means red, by the way, or flesh in general.
You know, let's play around a little bit.
I've been around a high level Eastern Orthodox Byzantine religious order leadership.
And I asked them about the biblical stuff, and they said, no, the church that we have, it came before the Bible.
And I had to think about that.
I didn't say, no, it didn't.
I didn't act belligerent.
But I thought about it.
And what's interesting, why he said that, and he knew I could handle it, and maybe use it later.
Well, because what we call the Bible started with Moses, right?
Right.
And that would have been roughly 1500 BC, so roughly 3500 years ago.
You know, on the outside, 4000 years ago, not really, but yeah.
Right.
So it was 3500 years or less.
35 was conservative.
Do me a favor, go and look up what is the Byzantine year.
Okay, but before, in the meantime, for people listening, the Byzantine Eastern Orthodox year, what year is it?
Because biblically, we're in the year 6020, around 6020 since Adam, right?
Right.
But what is the Byzantine year?
I know the Assyrians have something that's more than 6020.
The Byzantine year is around 755-something.
How did they get that?
How is it 1500 years more than Adam?
Right.
Well, the seventh day was the day of rest.
And the sixth day was the day when man first comes on the scene.
So they're starting their calendar when the first man comes on the scene.
Okay.
From the sixth day.
Right.
Right, which is the seventh, right?
Remember, it's six and a half.
Six and a half, right.
They're starting their calendar before the seventh day of rest, before Adam was made, when the first man was made on the sixth day.
You get it?
Because 7500 years ago puts you right in the middle of that sixth day.
Right.
Yep.
I wonder what she's doing here.
Anyway, okay, so just go right over that like it was no big deal.
No, no, no, I was just seeing if there was anything in there.
Yeah, okay.
But you see the stuff that's going on right under, I mean, obviously the Byzantine year doesn't mean jack because they're a bunch of idiots anyway.
But at this point, it's an interesting thing to note from a coincidental coinciding with, right?
Right, and they entrenched themselves with getting their stuff out.
Well, anyway, anyone that's done more than a day's worth of research cumulative on the biblical text knows that Adam was around 6000 years ago, and the year would be around 6000.
So these guys go back 1500 years.
They bypass the whole seventh day, which was the day off, and they go into the middle mark, the high mark of when mankind was created.
Because remember, Adam is not created, he's formed.
He's right.
Yeah.
And fortunately, I've been having some interesting discussions recently on Skype regarding that.
People that know the Hebrew as their native, and they're going back and they're telling me this thing shows up more than you've even spoken about Greek.
It shows up here, it shows up there in Hebrew, right?
They see it, that there's a big difference between being formed in the garden and being created man and woman.
Right.
See, because man and woman were created, and they were given a job, and their job was to what?
Take care of the garden.
No, no.
Oh, be fruitful and multiply, right?
And then there was a day of rest.
And they were not named either.
They didn't have any names.
And they were made at the same time.
And then there's the day of rest, this thousand years of rest.
And then there's another guy that's made by himself, and he's given a name.
He's the only one that's made male.
And he is given a specific job, which is to mow the lawn, prune the trees, take out the garbage, right?
Right.
Take care of the garden.
No woman was made.
And he was not created, he was formed.
And this scenario of being created and formed, and the formed comes up again in Genesis 5, and in other places.
I've been having some pretty interesting discussions regarding that, with people whose native tongue is Hebrew, by the way.
Not someone who's running back and forth in an interlinear, you see, so.
And you can see what's being discussed in an interlinear as well.
So I just wanted to throw that in there.
Okay.
I don't know about the difference between Adam and the other.
But I don't think they know about it, but it's suggested in their year count.
Let's just put it that way, right?
Right.
Did you find it, Bruce?
It's around 75-something?
I came across some other stuff that did not go.
Byzantine calendar year is?
Oh, hold on.
My fat fingers don't work here.
Yes.
Year 2000.
Okay, time and date.
Oh my goodness, what do we got here?
That didn't work.
No, hold on.
Roman, Byzantine, Western.
Oh, I got everything but Greek.
Sorry.
And people that I know.
Somehow, I did not get it correctly.
Well, if I'm giving it to you on a silver platter and you don't get it, what do you think is going to happen?
No, no, no.
I was looking it up.
I know, I'm just joking.
It's just a commentary on humanity.
It's still fine, Bruce.
In other words, if I spoon feed you and you can't get it, what are you going to get on your own?
Right.
Well, I was trying to find it on this stupid rectangle and needless to say, I ran into it.
It's just a general commentary.
It's okay.
I know you've got a lot of other stuff you're doing, but in general, anyone could find it.
I shouldn't say anyone, but it is discoverable.
Okay.
The Assyrians go back 6,700.
They don't know what they're doing.
There's no reason for it.
They have their own reasoning, but it doesn't add up.
Just like two dimes and a nickel don't make a dollar.
Right.
But either way...
Oh, here we are.
7526.
Roughly.
Yeah, it's about the halfway point of the sixth day.
Right?
Yeah, that would put you on the sixth day of creation, 500 years in, where these cats were running, or men and women were already quite into their groove.
So how does that tie back in?
You want to go back 10, 15 minutes?
Say, well, a memory serves us with the Nephilim and the sons of gods, and who was Cain afraid of?
Right.
And why did he go to the cities of refuge?
What cities of refuge?
If you study the cities of refuge given in the law, those are cities that were established back then.
What was the mark put on Cain?
You see?
It's not a mark, physical mark.
It's a mark, meaning it's a methodology.
You know?
Why wasn't Cain put to death if it says that if you kill someone you're going to be put to death?
Right.
Well, because it has to be qualified.
Well, it's easy if you know the law.
If you kill someone maliciously, you're put to death.
But if you kill them by accident, you're not put to death.
You can't no longer exist there because their blood might be avenged.
Right.
So did Cain say, I'm going to go out and kill my brother, or was he just angry with them, kicked his ass, and he happened to die?
The second part.
So if you don't know the law, you will never understand these things.
The other thing is, you know, it was about offerings.
And you have to think that the gods now are dwelling amongst the people, right?
There was no supernatural thing for them to do an offering.
It was a very interactive thing.
You know, something was left by his door.
You know, anyone could research what I'm saying, but I'm just trying to bring up the points to look at.
Sin was left at his door, at Cain's door, and he refused it.
Right, I'm using the King James Version.
Okay.
So what was sin?
A ram.
How do we know sin is ram?
Well, it's defined in other places, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Let me just add a little more to that.
A ram is not sin, but when there is sin or shortcoming, remember sin is a shortcoming, it was left.
In other words, to compensate for the shortcoming was a ram, to be sacrificed.
Mm-hmm.
When you bring an animal to be offered, that represents the shortcoming.
Right.
That's one thing that people have a hard time comprehending, is the word sin.
It just means shortcoming.
You know, if you say you're going to be, let's say, somewhere at 9 a.m. exactly by the wind-up toy, if you're there at 9 a.m. in two seconds, you just sinned, you were late by two seconds.
Right.
That's how precise it is, right?
Or if you go to an archery range and you said you're going to hit the bullseye and you don't, guess what you just did?
Shortcoming, right?
Right.
It's just a shortcoming.
But the level of guilt and malicious intent behind the word sin within the Judeo-Christian, actually all of the religions that do use that, is malicious.
It's inaccurate.
It's just like recently someone was trying to have a conversation with me regarding consciousness and unconsciousness.
I'm like, dude, there's nothing to talk about there.
That's so stupid.
Consciousness means you're awake and unconsciousness means you're asleep or dead.
What the New Agers are trying to do, and I guess I'm branding this a New Age thing, they don't want to use the word ignorant, censored, stupid, stubborn.
When you say, oh, this guy's not conscious of it.
No, he's not conscious of it because he's ignorant.
Right.
Just use the proper words.
Ignorant, unawares, uneducated, stubborn.
Not unconscious.
Unconscious means you're unconscious.
Using the same word to define it.
Yes, it means you're sleeping without dreaming or you're dead.
You know how the New Agers say, oh, consciousness, man.
What consciousness?
Qualify it.
There's no qualification.
See, they try to mix the quality and the quantity.
It's just bizarre.
Humans are just bizarre.
Okay, Valerie, are you coming?
She dropped off.
Well, she's not showing.
So let's just say maybe we could do it next week.
She hasn't texted either.
Maybe Valerie could work on her Skype etiquette.
Okay.
If she doesn't have a keyboard either, just give us a message.
Give her maybe another minute.
Sure.
Just use a keyboard if you can hear us.
Or when you're trying to get the audio and the visual stuff together, use the keyboard to let people know you're still there.
Otherwise, we don't know what's going on.
Great.
Yeah, we call it virtual etiquette.
Mm-hmm.
Otherwise, I'm going to just call it whatever.
Another useless sonic event, let's just say.
Spinning the bytes and the bits, right?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Oh, I see someone did put in 7525.
Thank you for doing that.
Mm-hmm.
So yeah, they know.
I don't think they know anymore, but they know enough, but not enough to invite them on to do a sonic.
I don't want to talk to any Byzantine whatever.
Mm-hmm.
There are people that know more than what's noticeable, but they're not talking.
No one's talking or speaking, you know?
Mm-hmm.
All right, man.
We'll see you next week.
All righty.
Take care, Greek.
Bye, thanks.
Thanks, Bruce.
Bye now.