And greetings folks, we're live with the Greek
and how are you doing tonight greet?
Doing okay.
Yeah another week seven days.
I should say because things go by the
eighth month is almost over You know things
go by on a on a daily.
I guess I tend to look at things
By the you know monthly and yearly as
well.
But as you get older the years are
just General groupings of events.
They're very short.
I noticed so They go by fast they
go by fast So we're gonna talk a
little bit more about food Yeah, as I
have in the past.
See I know the sonic events that I
did on food a while back Early, I
didn't do one with Ocelli because I think
that would have been a deer in the
headlights But I did one or two.
I did one or two with Seth Yeah,
and I wouldn't do anything like that with
Freeman because he doesn't fly.
So either way Going for more instruction And
you know all the relative stuff that people
think about learning how to cook is irrelevant
if you lack the mindset Right and essentially
the mindset is what is food and it
passes through the body?
It doesn't get absorbed never you've never absorbed
anything And if you have you've been quite
ill and you probably didn't make it so
you wouldn't be listening to me.
Well Right now it is that's why it's
so critical when they do subdermal stuff like
hydration, you know injections IVs and all that
The body can take it but you know,
there's a lot of subdermal, you know But
basically an IV of any sort from drug
addicts all the way to the hospital doing
a hydration drip with saline no matter what
you do in that respect again, it shows
that's a completely unnatural and Subdermal, you know,
even a mass trauma wound where opens the
skin the body can survive it, right?
It's not conducive to the body.
Okay, so it's yeah So, you know, so
basically nothing ever goes in and out.
It just passes through think of magnetic tape
like the old Right, so just passing over
a tape head and get all the music
and all the dynamics that you need Essentially
that is really a difficult thing to settle
in.
I mean I've had Maybe I should say
several scores, but over a hundred discussions with
medical people And not just like I'm not
talking about nurses and people who empty the
garbage cans in hospitals I'm talking about the
heads of the hospital the head of trauma
the head of universities that that on the
regent level that teach Doctors right the heads
not not just the regular doctors Yeah, and
they acknowledge they can't acknowledge it.
They they did not no one ever Ever
in the medical community has ever said that's
not possible.
That's not how it is They always lean
towards it being the truth and some of
them see it Actually, I got a couple
of doctors to quit so they had seen
seen it But right they will never acknowledge
it because it goes contrary to their bullshit
Which is what it is bad science or
BS right right?
So why what does that have to do
with food well?
In conversation when someone eats food, and they
feel better they feel invigorated They feel satiated
they feel strengthened.
They never say I feel like I absorbed
it right not even not even in common
language Yeah, no one ever feels anything passing
through their body or even even in common
parlance the way people speak It's not possible.
It's it doesn't exist So think of it
as a form of induction Whatever that is
you can look it up.
It's a term So there's many many attributes
Resonance right, but resonance is not Hertz Ian.
It's not Hertz Ian like in the right
people talk about frequency It's proximity Yes, and
the closer the proximity well you see you
also get juice or energy from the environment
That's why people in the country tend to
eat less Right when you go camping you
might get really hungry in the beginning because
you're you adjust you're less stressed you're changing
environment But then you notice as you're out
living in the wilderness.
You don't need as much food right most
people do right?
That way another thing is Years ago back
and maybe 30 years ago or so when
I first started learning about this I met
a bunch of people that were into something
called macro biotics, and I said what you
know I said You know about macrobiotics said
no, what's that?
You know and so we'll come check it
out And it's just a way of thinking
in a way of it spawned out of
Japan Yeah, Michio Kushi, Georgia Sawa and Shizuko
Yamamoto later on I was pretty Well acquainted
with Shizuko Yamamoto.
I volunteered at the macrobiotic center in New
York City Oh, and after after about being
there for a short while a few weeks
or months.
She invited me over for dinner I came
back and no one wanted to talk to
me and I said why what's going on?
I pulled over this one.
I said what's going on He says well,
you know we've been working here volunteering for
years.
She never invited us over for dinner You
you show up in a few weeks.
She invites you over for dinner So and
I Made some desserts from Michio Kushi back
in the day And he says is the
best microbiotic desserts I ever had he told
me about three or four times and after
that I stopped baking but anyway Give you
a little history about microbiotics I mean I
used to it just like any group Gustave
Le Bon they become very narrow and they
lose focus And they forget why they're there
and just to make a Point of it.
I used to run into people that were
into macrobiotics, and they said they were macrobiotic
I said you look too healthy to be
into health food because usually these people look
terrible right you know or you look right
Yeah, or Mac.
I started dubbing them macro neurotics.
They're very dogmatic You know I had someone
who overcame a pretty strong case of cancer
came over here years ago He traveled a
cross-country in a you know RV It's
actually a distant relative but The point is
he beat the cancer that they said he
would die it with a macrobiotic diet And
he was over here And I was preparing
a meal and I used some local that
you know some veg from the garden other
things is that's not microbiotic I'm not gonna
eat that I'm like what are you talking
about you see they're very dogmatic even though
he had success So I'm just giving a
little shades of story here just to back
up the mindset now.
There's nothing to do with microbiotics I'll give
you an example It's just a mindset if
anyone wants to research that and I keep
repeating the terms so you could look online
It's very little viable on the internet about
it by the way if you want to
look up some old If there's anything on
Herman Ahara or Georgia Sawa, maybe None of
the modern people they're assholes.
Sorry to use that term But that I
would go back to the old ones of
course Like in other words if I had
to bring someone on and discuss macrobiotics I
say I can't because everyone I think that's
worth discussing it is dead so again another
situation here Okay, so But even then around
that time I was I was in some
guy started a boiler room sales You know
what that is like a very high pressure
high pressure Sales on the telephone, but not
to people it was to industry he was
selling various forms of insurance and various forms
of like financial stuff to industry companies that
you had to you had to do be
more than five million a year to 150
million a year Company right back in the
80s.
Yeah, you deal with small Do you know
small it's five million a year still small
business, but that's where he started He's like
a venture capitalist kind of guy, so he
wanted me to work with him.
He says come on and and And Make
a lecture I could tell you where the
office was it was in the Trump Tower
so anyway It was just built so some
people came to visit and this was like
he was going to merge with a group
and He wanted to beat him up on
the price in other words on the merger.
You know they wanted to Put some money
together and do something, but he wanted to
come upper hand it so he says to
me He says look we're gonna go we're
gonna take them out to lunch And it's
you myself and this other guy that worked
together and listen We're gonna order for them
bloody rare steaks if they eat meat Like
very rare make sure that we suggest they
eat the steak And they suggest they eat
it rare And we're just gonna eat vegetarian
make sure you don't eat any of any
meat for the you know a day or
two before we do This and I didn't
know so so we sat down and we
did eat vegetables and salad and We and
these guys did there were three or four
of them more than us And he ordered
made sure that they ordered rare steaks Right
and the meeting worked out really really well
And then like after a couple of weeks
went by when the dust settled.
I said why did you do that?
It says oh yeah, what when you eat
rare dead.
You know animal meat like that your body
Your body goes into a serious change internally.
You know there's adrenaline in the meat.
There's blood You know if you can't eat,
but when you're eating the vegetable Whatever your
body's you know in a much calmer state.
You know even like scripture.
You're unclean right right, so I was like
Oh, man, okay.
That's that's like a real interesting bit bit
of trivia right and I saw it work
I mean these guys kind of confused.
I mean about not not Openly and overtly
confused, but definitely we're not on their a
-game right right So I kind of I
kind of settled that back, and then I
found out about Macrobiotics I started putting things
together, then I found out about like what
veganism one day someone said hey Let's go
down to Tompkins Square Park men the Krishna's
are going to be there to have great
food But I mean those guys and you
know robes and all that and it was
the best I mean you know no animal
no onion either because they don't do onion
they do hin instead They think that onion
a bulb is as it brings you down
spiritually, so it's like ah it's gonna be
yeah You know it's probably would be like
macrobiotic pretty plain.
It has to be high quality to taste
good And I ate I was like wow
this was so delicious So then I started
looking for vegan restaurants and that type of
stuff so back 30 years ago I'd say
like between 84 and maybe 86 88 89
I was on this food Discovery it kind
of just got thrown at me or I
ended up being in certain situations that gave
me a different perspective And it basically leaned
Towards not meat is bad, but you know
no meat low meat no meat or low
meat and fish and Understanding the the energies
behind it right now, so and then of
course it came The level of experimentation one
does when you like to prepare food Even
though I grew up in a traditional Greek
family.
I never liked the way the food was
prepared I think the people around me when
I was a child as adults were not
good cooks But they were traditional was still
good, and I mean non.
You know like I Grew up in an
upper-middle-class Jewish neighborhood and most of
the people around did like the food I
didn't think it was that good so at
nine years old.
I started cooking on my own when no
one was around right well So I'm getting
a little bit of this cross-section of
when I'm discussing food.
It's coming from this historical past.
Yeah You see so now you could put
it all together Roughly 30 years ago I
was made aware that Raw meat or rare
meat or meat has a negative effect on
someone's psyche or spirit or mindset when they're
in a critical situation The other thing I
learned about was this thing called Macrobiotics when
the people who started it or brought it
here were still alive and Also various other
experiences at Bacchus Let's say New York City
where there was more of this quote-unquote
alternative food type stuff which again Harkened back
to extremely traditional transplanted methods you know like
ancient Japanese ancient Indian Brought into and you
know the American society, so this is the
perspective of where I learned and how I
continued And it's not I'm rigid about it.
It's that I am I find that the
the high-grade originality that exists in that
type of methodology the Macrobiotic thinking Mediterranean cooking
Asian cooking is high grade What I what
I did was starting to prepare you know
basically whole foods and mostly vegetarian stuff You
know for I was I would say pretty
much five or six years no animal products
and then another several years no meat at
all ever and Occasionally maybe once a year
you know in there.
I might have a burger Because I I'd
go to like Shakespeare and company What's a
burger famous burger joint or Jackson Hole or
whatever and someone would meet and like okay?
I have a burger a lot It's not
even appetizing and I would eat just like
a part of it not a whole you
know one just to taste it And I
was glad that I didn't eat meat because
I noticed the the effects on me, right?
So so again, I've been through this and
I can tell you the fine fineties not
enough in a sonic but I'm laying out
the mindset because I Might say certain things
I might sign harsh to people and subjective
well.
He doesn't like this.
That's his problem I do and he says
this is this and as I know I'm
trying to be as objective as possible and
and show you a Gradation scale high grade
medium grade low grade right because at the
same time when I started preparing foods For
example if you've seen in the chat Of
various aspects I noticed that there was a
higher grade in Mediterranean in Asian No matter
how well you and a lower grade of
course as you got down And it was
culturally involved like Latin American food Caribbean is
lower grade and the lowest grade the white
people food Which in that case is just
doesn't have to be Because if for example
if you want to cook Mediterranean and Asian
you're gonna get you can get most of
it Grown here in the u.s..
Most of its sourced here matter of fact
some of the better rices in the world
or here are Lundberg And they're from California
Right a lot of the really good Japanese
rices are grown in California or Kentucky not
so much anymore But that's another by the
way You know if you ever watching you
Vietnam movies where they show rice patties and
swamps that shot in Kentucky Kentucky's full of
those kinds of it looks just like Vietnam
in certain places right really well Yeah, yeah
like apocalypse now right yeah shot in Kentucky.
Yeah, okay.
I know one of the actors.
Yeah, it's okay anyway So so when I
discuss the high grade and low grade It's
from preparation observation for of the culture the
actual Preparing of the dishes and the way
again back to how the culture presents it
so the for example if you're in a
big city And you go to a macrobiotic
restaurant things will be prepared much better than
if you go to a Dominican or Puerto
Rican restaurant Or South American restaurant, that's for
sure Across them if you go to a
Jap Okay
Okay you there Great I'm gonna have some
Cheese and bread while we're speaking if you
want to pop this back in at any
time.
That's fine with me We just go on
where we left off Sorry about that folks
internet dropped Yeah, that's okay.
That's that's what happens by the way for
example playing YouTube playlists now They shut it
off after an hour.
Are you there, and you have to turn
it back up?
I have it on in the background see
what they'll do is You know like the
drug dealer gives you stuff for free the
internet they're gonna make everything really easily available,
and then they throttle it back and you
watch the Slave livestock complain.
It's a rule.
It's not even your stuff, man.
Yeah, it's like you know Like I know
this old old white guy, and he he
invites his self over for dinner right because
he knows where I am He invites himself
over for dinner.
I'm like no you can't come over.
Sorry.
What's for dinner tonight?
I'm coming over I Mean that's you remember
you know it's like screw you Occasionally you
know he'll say he'll buy ingredients up, but
he never does I mean this is years
ago But it's very sure so for example.
Do you remember when they were cutting people's
channels and all that they all got really
upset yeah Censorship no, it's not using someone's
private stuff scumbag Anyway, did you not your
stuff?
It's not your country.
It's not you know That's where you listen
to people on the internet our country our
military really Really, I wouldn't want to take
ownership of that Yeah, what a bunch of
idiots.
You know that so screw them so what
they're doing obviously You have to use the
internet on in good taste as much as
possible.
Yeah, but it's put together by Idiots basically
that are what I call them the geeks
the computer geeks And you're that you have
to agree with what they do and also
their bosses to use it That's why I
don't use a smartphone because I it's very
Subjective it you it's this system is written
to accommodate the mentality of a nine-year
-old girl Girl and I can't use that
What is it called the iPhone or the
Android because it has in it the agenda
in it I see the stupidity or whatever
It's to you know is it possibly be
more objective of course yeah, just be objective
not subjective so anyway Before we got cut
off.
I was discussing that many of things.
I want to discuss might sound subjective, but
I want to show Yes, of course it
can be subjective, but I want to show
why and qualify what I'm saying Basically we're
talking about high grade low grade food preparation
Essentially and ingredients by the way you know
So the high grade highest grade style methodology
ingredients And you know methodologies food preparation and
also that you know the ingredients the way
the ingredients are sourced and grown all that
By far as Mediterranean and Asian food throughout
this planet.
Well.
We're talking about this plan Secondary would be
East Indian if you understood how to use
the what they call spices Right not all
Indian food is spicy by the way You
know if you if you comprehend that if
you've been to you know various regional or
depending on what tradition unfortunately when you go
and you're in a Western country and you
go to Indian food Greek food Italian food.
It's it's westernized Right that's of the pallets
adjusted to the palate right okay, so that
would be Mediterranean Asians top grade preparation ingredients
consideration flavor health wise Second would be East
Indian if you understand how to balance the
spices doesn't have to be spicy and the
and then it would be downgraded from there
would be Your Latin based foods, which would
be you know Latin America Caribbean And the
bottom grade would be white people food not
only in America Canada England Ireland Scotland Right
that's why if you go to any big
city.
You don't see an English restaurant.
They don't even want to do English style
pubs Or Scottish here's an Irish restaurant.
Are you joking are you joking?
You know so anyway That's the idea And
this is this has nothing to do with
your personal preferences has to do when you're
visiting a planet And you're contained in a
human body And you say where am I
going to get low-grade to high-grade
sustenance, and that's the order So if we
want to help people out in a way
that you're putting out something That's going to
make things quote-unquote better food clothing shelter.
Why do we want to talk about?
low-grade white people food or Latin food
you know I say Latin because there is
Latin in Europe and Right, but basically American
side this side we don't talk about that
stuff.
You know if you when we talked about
for example How to make perfect rice?
Yeah, you want to go ahead and make
Mexican food go ahead, but now you got
Rice that no Mexican can make Sorry because
they based they do a traditional like grandma
did right mm-hmm So now you know
how to make rice properly Go ahead, but
it's still low-grade, so we're gonna focus
more on the higher grade Mediterranean Asian South
Maybe some Indian stuff to a certain degree
the The focus is not even a focus
like we're going to talk about how to
make and prepare things I think like I
did on one sonic Let's talk about the
mindset and how people can prepare their mindset
when they're eating for example The one of
the easiest mindsets to always encounter in your
own self, or you know keep conscious of
is seasonality Right So when you approach seasonality
from a Mediterranean and Asian point of view
When I say Mediterranean it would be the
entire Mediterranean Rim if you look at where
the Mediterranean Sea is all the countries that
are in there on their borders, right?
So it would be the north coast of
the African continent the Levant You could stretch
it all though.
It's interesting when you go east from the
Levant you goes all the way to Persia
to India again Up to Turkey Greece southern
Greece, you know all that area Italy Portugal
right and of course England is interesting how
England is not in there, so Yeah, okay,
so that is the entire area so that
is a sense of regionality That might be
a little warm or out of seasonality or
across latitudes So if you go up to
Japan and look at where the by the
way in terms of Asian food the Japanese
food is The hot cuisine in Asia by
the way the high level right I mean
Of course you know we could talk about
the lower quality overall of The way it's
considered in Western countries about the Chinese because
years ago the Chinese were unwelcomed immigrants And
they people would say well they eat rats
and things like that right or you know
if you want a good Chinese restaurant You
gotta have white people open it because the
Chinese are dirty, so they've had no they've
had a very bad rap Because they're essentially
very poor like Mexico is very poor most
of the northern part But they also have
a high form of cuisine, which I think
it's a little strange, but you can look
at that Japan and China is across latitude
for the colder regions you see Like You'll
find the use of most popular prolific use
of olive oil in the Mediterranean Will you
find more prolific use of sesame oil in
Asia?
Acquire acquire both of course Sesame oil is
a higher temperature Especially if it's not a
toasted sesame than olive oil olive oil you
should really avoid cooking with it unless you
know how to Should be very low temperature
like if you I've even you can make
dishes like for example if you understand what
poaching is mm-hmm You could poach in
warm olive oil not hot olive oil right
or hot would be no more than 130
Right if you understand right and it kind
of cure it as it has an acidic
flavor and a lot you can do the
same With sesame oil there's something called oil
pulling where you wake up in the morning
and do a teaspoon of oil Yeah Yeah,
you just do a half a teaspoon Sesame
oil raw sesame oil on toasted is the
best because of its new Olive oil might
be a bit acidic What you do is
you just push it around the mouth until
it it feels like it disappears then spit
it out it'll be all foamed up, and
that's really good for drawing things to the
mouth and Re-adjusting frequency like a demagnetizer
on your tape head right when you Okay
There's a some people had really good success
Some people not so great success, but everyone
who does it feels better.
It's called oil pulling.
There's many Theories and concepts about it.
I could tell you from doing it that
you do feel better It helps stabilize the
entire digestive tract mouth ailments skin Just your
overall Vigor increases Sesame oil is probably the
best that I've tried for that So The
reason I bring those to the Mediterranean aspect
up again because sesame oil and olive oil
you need fat Unless you're going to be
steaming and you know doing all that stuff
all the time.
You still you do need fat now You
understand that you?
Humanity has been run and guided by really
we use the term terrorists loosely and conservatively
is accurate for over 150 years you've been
terrorized to the hilt.
I mean there's no where to go as
A human being on this planet with any
kind of Interacting with any you know quote
-unquote entitled class you know whether it's academic
governmental religious.
You're being terrorized essentially, right?
so What I mean by that is that
you know back to food If you're going
to consider what I just said about fats
I tell you fats are bad because you
you know why they tell you fats are
bad because that's what you need the most
by the way For your nervous system in
your mind to work clearly So I'll bring
up the concept of fats first always in
a good food conversation So let that sink
in for a minute Are you still there
Bruce or we drop if you don't answer
back?
I think we drop I'm here Okay So
that's fine All right, well, it's not fine,
but you know thanks.
Yeah, okay?
Yeah, if you might just put something in
the text so I know otherwise I'd rather
stop you find it We're gonna drop again.
Let's say right All right, so those are
your fats in the secondary fats.
You know a lot of people discuss coconut
cooking with coconut Oil and butter and all
that.
I don't really think so.
I mean, it's it's there's a There's a
lot of stuff that's praised around there, but
just think about the origin of coconut and
also You can't live on coconuts.
You know you'll die if you just eat
coconut Flesh and water and fat all right
It's one of the few things that you
will die for sure after two weeks if
you eat, so I'm not putting a negative
light on it.
I'm just saying if you consistently live in
an area where that's warm or you are
seasonally making a Dish that requires some fat
and you find it palatable use the coconut.
It's fine, but I Don't have it for
food at all.
I just have it for skin and other
things you know you could use you know
I never really consume it Personally that's where
the subjective aspect comes in.
I don't find it palatable very well very
palatable So I would recommend more of the
olive oil or the sesame oil For your
basic fat, and then of course you switch
over to Animal fats, and I'm not going
to get into discussing canola oil and sunflower
oil and sesame you could do And rapeseed
you know which is canola and you could
look up your oils your peanut oil is
good for high temperature frying you could Get
into your oil study get into your fat
study if you would I Don't look at
what is on the internet conservatively because most
people That do put up articles about this
kind of stuff are just doing it in
a passing way.
They really don't have much experience For example
I knew an editor of food and wine
magazine, and I saw her compiling years ago
Some stuff to be put into print, and
I said well these recipes you just drew
up you never cooked anything Oh, yeah, we
don't need to cook it.
We just kind of imagine, and then we
get some stock photos, and we put it
up, right?
You know I mean It's kind of an
imagined thing so Be careful when you're looking
at recommendations on the internet Which is interesting
because eventually somewhere down the line you might
find this sonic event down the line So
the the next thing To consider would be
animal fats of course If you're going to
provide an animal free Palate or a diet
for yourself, then you wouldn't consider this, but
there's butter various qualities of butter You know
well, then of course.
There's there's the the strict aspect of fat
like tallow like years ago You know if
you work in a restaurant by the way
even now not years ago You shortening for
deep frying right if you've ever worked in
a restaurant the fryer is filled with shortening
Because it's a much higher temperature than an
oil right so just You know for higher
temperature things that coagulated at room temperature Which
would be like a coagulated beef fat right
or vegetable shortening?
Which is not very I find palatable, but
it tastes good when it's fried right Is
is the way that it's done industrially so
that these things need to be considered as
well?
You know chicken fat by the way goose
fat duck fat Did I say goose fat
duck fat and and yeah and chicken fat
are rendered are considered?
To be delicacies with certain dishes as well.
I mean You can research that depending upon
What side you want to go on?
Again vegetarian or animal right right either way
even if you don't consider yourself a vegetarian
by the way And you say I eat
meat.
I would do very little of it if
if you know what I mean Sparsely And
there's also a scriptural reason for it Leviticus
11, I think I'll just you know I'm
not do a To all these patties you
know you could figure out Where it is
and what I mean, I'll just reiterate if
you touch Flesh of a dead animal or
a dead animal you're unclean Usually it's till
noon the next day till your washer.
It could be up to seven days.
That's not specified in there, but you run
clean All right, so if you're eating a
chicken salad sandwich was chicken is allowed or
beef is allowed right It's a to eat
as you know it's not allowed, but it's
it made us fit and proper If you
eat a hamburger Are you touching and parts
of an animal that are dead or an
animal?
It's dead of course right So even though
you're not eating Unclean meat any meat renders
one unclean.
I just want to point that out again
Let that sink in Because Doesn't it it
doesn't say be vegetarian, but doesn't it indirectly
promote vegetarianism you see that's why I say
that Scripture doesn't say you're ready to eat
a lot of people try to use the
verses Oh, yeah, the green plants and I
was your food and your meat.
You know that I don't know well yeah,
okay, that's fine, but Right well, he doesn't
care about food is even just touching yeah,
right yeah So you can rationalize Well because
there are animal sacrifices that are consumed right
so, but you know, but then there's washing
That's why I say it's within you know
a day But because there's a priest consume
the sacrifice the evening and the morning sacrifice
right which is right there's two sacrifices almost
you know, so Nonetheless, you know, I don't
like here's interesting thing You notice I haven't
really been getting into many much scriptural discussion
because I put out enough To see if
there's enough people to really get into and
there isn't I'd hate to say People still
just want don't they don't want to really
study I find as a general They want
someone to tell them what it says and
which is very dangerous and not very good
but I Don't blame them because if you
read scripture, by the way The author has
an aversion for stupid people Do you ever
notice that if you read scripture?
Well, if you're one of the stupid people
you may not be you just might have
to put it down But if you ever
try to study scripture, you notice like it's
almost talking down to people that are stupid
Yes, there are stupid people doesn't quite say
that but right.
Yeah If you're slow or you don't get
it or you're censored it taught it talks
down and indirectly against those people Keep saying
the wise will understand.
So anyway, so it's interesting how I watch
people who actually Studies it or attempts to
study it versus those who want to hear
what someone else I say about it And
they it's very difficult for them to study
it because they kind of pick up on
that.
But anyway So back to the food on
the fats There there's a whole level of
consideration when you're coming down to fat and
and when we're talking about high-grade preparation
for example If we're going to bounce back
and forth between vegetarian and non-vegetarian The
second thing would be your protein, you know
What's actually it's all protein and starch if
you look at what they call a protein
and a carbohydrate molecule, you know On the
BS on the bad science, what's the difference
between the carbohydrate and the protein?
On the molecule, you know, can you you
could pull it up?
It's what one nitrogen atom It's all both
carbohydrates and protein are the same except the
protein is a little more nitrogen Okay, this
is at an assay when they burn it
up and to see what's in it, you
know in a Lab or whatever Okay, some
plastics are like that too if you look
at polyethylene or polypropylene, right?
It's just one night nitrogen which is you
know nitrogen and Oxygen and it's ammonia basically,
you know, what do you know ammonia, right?
Okay.
So anyway I'll climb When you think of
things as starches and proteins that's a very
easy way to discuss openly but even though
There's more to it.
Like for example in the vegetarian world, you
know There are aspects of legumes or beans
are considered protein like rice and beans rice
as your starch and the beans as your
protein Yeah, and though, you know, it's mostly
starch still, you know, like nuts are mostly
more protein Base so what is it?
You know, there's something about that nitrogen that
they show in the scientific world that makes
it Different, right?
The animal world they basically think of the
animal as a protein whether it's fish fowl
or for or hooves, right?
So You consider that, you know kind of
a setup When you're preparing a dish and
again when you lean towards the vegetarian side
You're still going to consider a little bit
more starch then more rice than beans for
example More starch than you more bread than
peanut butter, you know, if you make a
PBJ So I'm gonna have to take a
break.
I noticed that's raining outside here.
I need to just prepare a few things
I'll be back in about two minutes.
Okay.
Okay Nope, I'll just mute it out cuz
I'm kind of far I mean the Wi
-Fi may not I mean the the headphones
may not reach I'll be give me another
minute and a half or so Okay, let's
kick it again, okay, I just had to
cover up some things I Personally, okay, so
I could tell you objectively and subjectively coconut
Should get the wrap that soy does, you
know, soy has gotten a really bad rep
Mm-hmm, right don't eat soy.
It really should be the coconut for different
reasons Now that's the more of a subjective
more objective is it's tropical It's handled here,
let's think of it this way do yourself
an experiment do yourself a favor do yourself
an investigation Seek out real high quality coconut
products organic whatever high quality Even though if
it costs just don't get a you know
let's get a sample if you can because
it's going to be very expensive compared to
the regular stuff and Taste it and you'll
notice I had to taste nothing like the
stuff.
That's Normally out there.
All right, it's over it's an overused product
set coffee Soy Has a bad rap because
they decided not to grow the higher grades
because they take longer and they need more
water and all that Basically what everyone is
eating a soy and they said it's bad
For you and many different levels is because
they're eating animal grade soy Right.
Yeah, very low grade just like there's low
-grade wheat that causes Gluten intolerance, right?
It's a higher minute.
It's a mineralized gluten versus a more flexible
protein-based gluten So these these labels so
again Subjectively, I could tell you I don't
like the way coconut tastes in food.
I like coconut milk For example when I'm
cooking Thai food Because the Thai the cultural
now if you look at the cultures that
use a lot of coconut milk The other
ingredients in the dishes balanced it out Think
of it if you're making a Thai soup
like which I do I poach chicken And
make a chicken broth and I roast red
pepper and I use kefir lime leaves I
use basil bay leaf sugar and some fish
sauce, which is basically rotten anchovy juice And
I and whenever I make this for quote
-unquote white people They say it's the most
delicious thing they've ever tasted unless they're familiar
with Thai soup And when they do have
the Thai soup to say well, this is
better than I've had out, you know Well
the kefir lime think about lime, you know,
you have citrus lemon and orange if you
ever have lime It's very bitter at lime
is a very strong flavor, right?
Mm-hmm.
If you're familiar with lime, it's one of
the strongest citrus flavors Okay, that goes after
the coconut and then you have the fish
sauce, which is an extremely sharp.
Umami It's like a room imagine a fish
a fishy Romano cheese or Parmesan cheese is
what the fish sauce is like and then
you have bay leaf right or laurel leaf
and The meat you see so it balances
out.
So I've just given it and the sugar
of course and you use palm sugar You're
not cane sugar if you can get it.
It's a different flavor as well, right?
You know when you read about a lot
of these Thai food Recipes or Vietnamese where
there's sugar being used.
It's a palm sugar comes from a palm
tree Different type again different energy, but you
know, essentially if you look at a large
palm, it looks like a cane anyway, I
mean but similar so again, I just gave
an example with kind of avoiding the whole
idea of Saying as coconut milk or coconut
butter or coconut oil good or bad.
Well There's something about good traditions that consider
the qualitative aspect of food combination with good
recipes That balance out all the ingredients you
see So if you're having Thai food and
you're trying to master meth Thai methodologies food
preparation and all that You will see cook
a lot of coconut milk or frequently coconut
milk being incorporated and it correctly done But
if you're going to make a grilled cheese
sandwich and you put coconut fat on the
outside Instead of mayonnaise, that's stupid.
Yeah, you're torturing yourself unless you're into that
Right, or if you're going to make fried
vegetable fried rice and you use coconut fat,
that's stupid.
Yeah It doesn't balance out, you know use
sesame oil or peanut oil Right.
I mean that's in my opinion in other
words for years I've been exposed to it.
I'm like, dude, you've cooked you used coconut
oil on this right?
Yeah, I could tell it just coats my
mouth With like this oily slick feeling and
it detracts from tasting certain things Yeah, you
know don't use it.
You know, it's like well, I like it.
Well, okay try peanut oil or sesame oil
on this instead Okay, as they come back
usually say it's better, but I still I'm
going to use the coconut You know everyone's
people in other words people still have their
ideas I'm not trying to get into anyone's
head I don't want to get anyone's head
and I don't want to know what's in
your head The thing is I just want
to put out the information so at least
people can you know?
Resort to something because there's very little real
talk going on anywhere anymore, so again The
first thing I said about methodology and mindset
is seasonality, right?
When you do seasonality you consider cross-latitude
like for example places like Malaysia, Thailand Northern
coast of Africa are pretty much locked near
the equator All right, and what do you
know about those areas?
Well, they do have seasons They have rainy
season and very rainy season right and and
very very hot and then very very hot
right, right, actually, they do have about a
week's worth of winter, but Nonetheless Those are
interesting places to run to for the the
hot side and then you have the cold
side Which would be northern northern let's say
Russia or which I don't know what they're
really cooking there.
They just Not much just meat they hang
out.
They just shoot a deer and hang it
up in the shed They don't even because
it's freezing there all year round You know
when you want some meat you go out
with a chainsaw right anyway Smack off of
these Yeah, but you go northern China right
northern like Japan right northern Europe you can
end up in bad food territory, but you
see so okay, so again you look exactly
where the The culture or the latitude is
based on the season that you are in
So when it's summertime where you are or
hot Depending on how hot it is or
warm go to the warmer climates pull out
some dishes when it's cold where you are
Depending on how cold again you go to
Cold places and pull out some dishes.
So now you've getting the variety from all
over the world now again Just to go
back to refer back to the concept of
coconut milk and coconut butter and all this
Pulling out one ingredient and Detracting it from
the situation that it exists in culturally and
traditionally like in a recipe is Is I
wouldn't say a mistake, but?
Not good for beginners Right when you're more
on a journeyman a mastership level you can
start experimenting understand the quality One day we'll
talk about how to discover.
What quality is and how do you discover
the quality of the thing right?
Qualitative measurement like if you look at all
your measurements all of your metrics are always
quantities or how many pounds is it how
many inches?
How many meters how many?
What's the temperature?
It's all never a quality, right?
so same with Food so so again if
you're going to pull out an ingredient.
Let's say you say coconut again Whether it's
the milk the butter the fat well Traditionally
culturally the people who have mastered the use
of that are the tie right and other
others as well So I would use I
have coconut milk and other things like that,
and I use them when I make Thai
Recipe food right if I make pad Thai
if I make a Thai soup, right?
But if I'm going to do another if
I do let's say Japanese There's even just
a plain beans and rice or fried rice
or a sandwich.
I would not I would not use coconut
I would restrict it For the simplicity of
getting the best outcome to where it came
from originally traditionally combined, right?
so That's one way to think of your
ingredients.
I would avoid any kind of trend logic
Trend thinking you know where people kind of
say well fat is bad for you Or
soy is bad or coconut is good, or
you know plastic food has to be wrapped
in plastic Otherwise, it's no good, or you
know all this stuff, or you know the
safe.
You know what kills me really in terms
of having enthusiasm Especially with Westerners is the
food safety rules food borne diseases When you
research like you know this plate You know
the reason it has nothing to do whether
it's still going to make you sick even
if it's cooked Those pathogens are still there
So if they tell you this chicken has
to be cooked or these eggs have to
be cooked Or you might get a food
borne illness that is not because inherently chickens
or meat or fish or eggs will make
you sick That's not true.
It's because the quality of it is it's
either diseased from the get-go in other
words the factory has disease They've tainted it
with disease by the way and or it's
just poor you know All around so you
shouldn't be eating it anyway The transportation of
it is caused ill effect also sure sure
so it's a Yeah, yeah very bad question
if someone says that chicken will get you
sick if you don't cook it properly Then
you don't want to eat it cooked or
uncooked.
It's sick.
You don't want to eat sick food So
what does that tell you that renders about
90% of the the aspects of eating
out or what you can buy?
You know, but that's okay You know if
it's not like you're open, I mean, it's
not okay, but it's not like you're open
for a society That's going to be around
for much longer So I mean that's okay.
So just cook it or just just keep
that in the back of your mind qualitatively
Food borne diseases are because the food supply
is diseased The animals the vegetables whatever are
diseased not you know, right?
It's a current condition thing Okay, so in
terms of going back or we discussed the
fats basically and then a little bit of
proteins and starches To go into the aspect
of quality really is where it's at You
know, there's many I was thinking part of
my mind, you know, we discussed certain food
preparations But I don't think that's really necessary
The aspect of I think good food discussion,
you know, I brought up the the various
grades, you know higher grade to low grade
And if anyone wants to consider that they
should you know, look into it a little
bit more When you get going back to
quality a high grade would be Mediterranean and
Asian Mediterranean would be Pacific the Mediterranean Rim
all those countries Northern Africa all of Southern
Europe East West to the Levant and Asian
and Asian the highest grade would be Japanese
without a doubt and then Chinese, of course
in most of the Pacific Rim Area like
Thai Vietnam.
The only reason Vietnam Vietnamese cooking has gotten
popular is because of pho You know pho
pho soup and that was created by demand
by the French occupiers Right.
Otherwise, they were eating pretty Slop and they're
very poor people.
They basically ate Very either very fresh food
or just slop gruel and things like that
when the French got there They demanded finer
pastries finer application, you know, there's also a
Chinese influence because China invaded several times unsuccessfully
because Viennese are overfighting back but Make a
point of that.
There's an there's every country also has an
influence So the highest grade in Asia would
be Japanese.
So what do you know about Japanese food?
Right nothing probably for most people so you
have to study that there's no reason to
do a sonic on that Specifically or Mediterranean
food to do a sonic on that specifically
because what do you know about it?
Nothing, if you don't know anything about it
I don't think I need to if we're
going to discuss on how to master these
things and you're on apprentice level You need
to do a lot of homework on your
own Like a pretty study on your own
But at least we're setting the mindset and
why not just have this mindset and that's
the way it is Sorry, no, but why
why it's them set you see now essentially
for the quality Also, it's something called freshness.
And what does that mean?
Well, you're being bombarded with.
Oh, yeah, it's vacuum packed to seal in
freshness bullshit Impact creates anaerobic condition means lack
of occupy another it breeds an entirely different
set of pathogens Yeah, right look up aerobic
and not anaerobic Now I noticed before we
get on to a little bit more on
the quality side and keeping things Well, actually,
let me just say this thing and then
I want to get into the pickling and
preservation of food because that's important There's something
you're going to someone's house especially white people
you open the fridge and it's jam-packed
to the front and they just eat Off
the front and then they pull something out
of the bag.
I think this is still good I don't
remember when I made it though.
Yes Yeah, right.
There's a three-day rule That's a food
or the other a cabinet with spices in
the back that you never remember buying But
they're there and you look at the date
and they expired six years ago.
Well, that's that's what I call the food
ZM All right, the food museum Okay, you
should Seasonally really if you're active seasonally clean
out your fridge or you know spring Actually,
if you just did it spring and fall
would be enough Empty everything out of your
food storage pantry refrigerator and all that and
go through and throw away anything that you're
not using or give It to someone who
might right because if or you there is
something that you need as a backup.
That's fine.
Keep it there the The aspect of when
you prepare a meal three-day rule Three
you'll see the three-day rule everywhere by
the way in in the legal and law
you'll see it and yeah 72 hours So
in other words, you can you can bend
it likely.
Let's say you make something tonight It can
count.
It doesn't have to count for the whole
day.
In other words tomorrow night will be just
be one day Right, right and then the
next night is two days and the next
night is three days So you could still
eat it on the fourth right because it's
really in it as a dish It's been
in existence only for 72 plus hours, but
that's about the limit Okay All right.
So that leads us into pickling because pickling
pickling and pickles are Food that's prepared or
preserved and stored for more than three days
The 72-hour rule is for foods you
prepare dishes not pickles Before we get into
pickling though, which I've discussed how it changes
something for seasonality as someone had put a
good I'm outside right now, by the way,
meaning outdoors laptop.
I'm all the way on the other end
of the garden here So I might go
inside have the chat on the other.
Let me know if there's anything No, the
reason I threw this in is because there
was something in chat about it was answered
Well, I forgot who answered it really there
was odds and end I or someone.
Yeah, or someone else answered it very properly
that's very impressive to see that someone's listening,
but You know, I give the analogy before
about pickles, but before we get into pickle
We have never discussed dehydration of food Because
when you dehydrate food, which is basically drying
it quickly right There are many ways of
doing it.
You don't have to buy a food Dehydrator
actually if you went out and bought one,
you'd be surprised as an empty box with
a fan and maybe a heating element right
Yeah, even an industrial one that cost 10
grand It's just a big-ass box with
screens and a fan and a heating element.
I mean a tiny heating element, right?
So get creative Basically to dehydrate food successfully
need air circulation.
Yeah, you could do a very simple of
dehydrator if you have an oven I always
like doing stuff stovetop But basically preheat the
oven to 200 shut it off gets all
the humidity out of there Then put whatever
you want to dry on a rack and
leave it there overnight If it's a good
sealing up and then you'll come back.
It'll be pretty drop But you've got to
preheat the oven not hot and let it
cool down without it being open that Pushes
all pumps all the humidity out, right?
Right and also most ovens do have a
vent if you notice in the back There's
a little hole holes and they do vent
out to somewhere, you know If you go
to someone's kitchen you see so what's this,
you know, ah, it's really hot.
Why is it hot?
Well, it's venting out the oven, right?
Okay Okay, so you you got to make
sure that that you can have a little
fan and that you could convert any oven
into a dehydrator So also since we're on
the topic of ovens if you ever want
to get a bitchin You know a kick
-ass broiler or oven for making homemade pizza.
I have a indoor oven a gas stove
It's a Roper stove.
It looks like a restaurant kind of stove,
but it's got a big cavity so all
I did was basically raise the tray the
bottom of Solid panel over the burner and
I replaced that with a grill and I
put aluminum foil on that So there's a
very tiny so now instead of the oven
being 2 by 2 by 3 is now
6 inches by 2 by 2 And it's
sealed.
So when I turn that on the thermostat
says it's 250, but it's 500 When the
thermostat says it's 500 at 750 and you
throw a pizza in there that you just
made it'll cook in five minutes Perfectly, right
Wow Basically kill the volume in your stove,
right?
You know how the bottom of a stove
on the burner, right?
You just move the steel tray up and
you put this the rack where the tree
was so now you got a tiny little
compartment and I'll get super hot if you
have a You know, once you go above
six or seven hundred, you don't use thermometers
anymore use what's called a pyrometer Mmm, right.
That's why you'll see thermometers is digital ones.
They say just eight high They won't read
over five or six hundred six or seven
six fifty.
They go blank you above that You need
what's called a pyrometer Which is different those
go from 700 up to a couple thousand
depending on the rating So if you have
a pyrometer, you could see you could approach
a eight nine hundred.
The only problem is in a residential Stove
when you rig it like that the insulation
and the knobs and the fittings and the
gaskets are not Can't take that kind of
heat for long.
So this is just for an eight-minute
pizza cook, right?
Because pizza doesn't taste good unless it's cooked
at high temperature.
It's got to be over five or six
hundred Even though the The white people pizza
spots tell you it's 450.
That's not real pizza.
That's just slow baked That's just fast baked
bread fast baked bread and pizza to get
different.
Mm-hmm so We're throwing that about an
oven only to make it a dehydrator So
basically need air movement air movement and low
humidity to dehydrate food Obviously the thinner you
cut it the more efficient it will be
dehydrated You can do fruit and meat that
way as well and you could dehydrate bread
It's called croutons or breadcrumbs, right?
You can't make it's different than toast You
know You know breadcrumbs are basically dehydrated by
the way in the Middle East What they
do is they dehydrate loaves of bread and
they throw it in the camel sack And
then when they're going on a long trip
if you have water Submerge the loaf of
bread in the water and it reconstitutes and
it tastes totally different than fresh paper, but
you have bread Are you familiar with that
tech?
Yeah Yeah, yeah, it's really good if you
have that kind of bread will last for
years if you do it, right Like if
you're gonna urgency kid if you have a
first aid kit in the car emergency kit
Do you get some of those biscuits dry
biscuits?
They serve for babies when they're teething.
Those are pretty well preserved Forgot what they're
called.
They look like little miniature slices of bread
here.
Mm-hmm Yeah, yeah, keep those in the
car because they have a shelf life for
10 years Yeah, and if you get a
heartier bread and you just don't you have
a hot drink you just dunk it and
reconstitutes it Those crackers if the the biscuits
for child teething on the someone's they sell
basically on the market if you do dunk
them They'll dissolve.
Yeah, you need to work.
You need a high gluten bread You know
like for example, you know a bagel take
a was just high gluten dehydrate that you
know If you you know, if you threw
it across the room, you'll give someone a
concussion You can't you can't eat it and
you can't crush it.
It's too hard because of the gluten fiber
But if you soak it in water, you'll
get a bagel Like you're not a fresh
bagel, but you'll have a you know a
bagel you can chew on This is an
important staple in Middle East countries If you've
ever been in the Middle East or know
people that do they still traditionally do that?
They'll bake a loaf of fresh bread They'll
slice it and then dehydrate it and put
it away and then when they're ready to
use it They dunk it in hot soup
or tea or water and it reconstitutes it
Yeah, so the so instead of these dumb
white people that try to do the the
They have these trends where they do the
survivalists and the send away for our powdered
this and powdered survival kit and all that
That's such a joke, you know, they're basically
selling you MREs MSG and garbage Yeah, and
you end up paying ten dollars a pound
for it when you do the math, right?
You know ten dollars a pound you can
get rip Yeah, so all you have to
do is know how to actually preserve things
without using chemicals Dehydration is a good way
But the only thing is mold can build
on it mold can build on certain spores
and sugars on meat So you might want
to add like if you want to make
homemade beef jerky or any kind of jerky
or even a You know any kind of
fish or whatever also you dunk it in
salt water first You know You cut all
your strips and you you put yours literally
literally on a clothesline with clothes pins or
something Or thread them through a rope with
a distance between you can imagine what that
looks like Or a string and then you
dunk it in salt water or I do
tamari and sugar which is water salt sugar
tamari which is like a soy sauce and
Some sugar and and then I dehydrate it
like that That's what you know when you
go out and buy a beef jerky, by
the way, that's what it's it's it's treated
It has it's been dunked in a in
liquor of some kind when I say liquor
meaning, you know It's a salty sweet kind
of mixture you ever notice Yeah, okay now
you can also dehydrate notice there was something
in the chat yesterday from memory regarding squash
twice You can dehydrate Kale you can dehydrate
Actually, as a matter of fact the Trader
Joe's sells Kale chips or dehydrated super delicious
if you know what to do with it
or how to do it.
I you could do it by you know
what miso is a chickpea miso or just
me so mix that with water and Filter
it out and put it in a spray
bottle and you spray the leaves of that
when the miso dehydrates is super umami super
delicious But you could you could make chips
you could dehydrate the squash and all that
Right, and what's interesting when you dehydrate certain
foods, you can process them differently in other
words You can let's say make squash chips
and put them in the blender and blend
them if they're dry enough And then you
have this squash dry powder that you can
add hot water to and make an instant
squash soup right this is for for You
know packing stuff away So, okay.
Also when you dehydrate it changes things again
Right, right.
Have you ever had dehydrated?
I've ever had banana chips or plantain chips.
You ever seen those?
They're delicious and they don't taste anything like
bananas.
No, I mean they do You have a
hint of it.
Yeah Right, so we've never got into dehydration
And it's viable traditionally there is much dehydration
if you look at The majority of the
Japanese and Asian condiments are what?
dehydrated Actually, most condiments are dehydrated herbs black
pepper.
You ever had fresh peppercorn instead of no
black pepper.
It's very different Yeah, it's delicious.
You drop it in.
Yeah, okay Fresh pepper.
Yeah, so so all most of your condiments
and the spices and things that people interact
with pasta, for example, that's dehydrated You ever
get a thing of spaghetti right or fettuccine?
That's dehydrated.
It's fresh pasta is dehydrated Does it change
it?
Yes, it does as a matter of fact
that when you have fresh pasta If you
blindfolded me and gave me fresh pasta and
dehydrated pasta, which is nothing wrong with I
could tell you which one was fresh And
which one was it?
right so most people can That's why certain
pastas now are for like raviolis are best
frozen because the filling shouldn't be dehydrated like
a cheese or something Also, you can get
into the habit which I've mentioned before when
it comes to pasta, it's just Clean your
counter put some flour you could use flour
barley wheat, whatever Make a well drop an
egg in water a little bit of water
oil and an egg Beat it in place
in the well right on the counter make
sure it doesn't the well doesn't open and
spill on the floor or spread out too
far and start making yourself a nice little
ball add flour or add liquid if it's
too dry if it's too wet and And
roll it out roll it out as thin
as you can if you don't have a
rolling pin use a wine bottle wine bottles
make great rolling pins and and Then you
score it roll it put lots of flour
and you got your fresh pasta there you
make two sheets And you could you could
make a filling of some sort and put
a dollop Spaced out two inches apart all
around and put the other sheet over press
it down and cut it now you got
ravioli, right?
See what I mean See how easy this
is to make Okay, well often I would
have people Well, it's amazing when you make
it fresh yourself always put an egg in
it don't go with the eggless pasta Always
put or some kind of protein if you
if you're going to this is where your
squash paste comes in right You could put
some Bean paste in it also, but make
a just a point here I always used
to make a well very often fresh pasta
and people is the best pasta I read
as I just made it And they're like,
what do you mean?
We were just talking.
What do you mean?
You just made I didn't see you make
it Right.
I mean, that's how easy when you get
used to making it, you know, someone would
sit down I'm in the kitchen and we're
speaking.
I'm just put the flour out Make a
well put the liquid a drop an egg
in there mix it up with some olive
oil Maybe some salt and raw as we're
still talking in real time right now as
I'm speaking you So also the kitchen I've
set up is not set up with cabinet
doors and all that I have a very
long shelves that slide out So, you know
when you go into a regular kitchen You
have to open all these drawers and doors
to look for stuff.
Everything is exposed, you know, it's just Shelves
that slide out and then of course there's
a front to it, you know for pots
and pans ingredients So basically, you know, you
can open it with your leg reach in
with your hand.
Everything's there close it with your leg, you
know So anyway, I could be in real
time as I brought up the pasta subject
and if the water were going we'd be
eating pasta In another minute.
This is how fast it can be done
It's like second nature.
Yeah, right As a matter of fact, I'll
do it faster I'll have a pasta dish
ready for you faster than if you had
the dry pasta because guess what?
The fresh pasta you dunk in water for
a minute and a half, right?
How long does it take how long do
you have to wait for the dry at
least 10 you say 8 to 10 minutes?
It may be 15 in some cases depending
on how thick it is So in this
case if I as long as I have
all my pasta pre cut and formed in
less than 10 minutes You're eating sooner You
see how fast it is And I want
to bring up also if you instead of
bringing up a whole pot of boiling water
when you want to boil something Just figure
out how tall your ingredients are in the
pot and put much water to cover the
ingredient And then have another pot on the
side like a kettle with water going So
then you put let's say your pasta and
you just cover it with water An inch
or so that comes to boil much faster
than a big pot, right?
Right, and then as it's coming to a
boil you add water from the next pot
next to this way You're saving on energy
and time Because a large pot, you know
four or five quarts takes at least ten
minutes.
Maybe more depending on your burner I have
a pretty strong burner.
It's fast, but most people don't I've seen
some people's stoves at home They look like
a little camp camping stoves the burner head.
You ever see that, you know, it's a
little tiny Okay, so So always make sure
that you're you know, bring out just enough
water to boil That's going to cover your
ingredients and then have a second pot on
the side to keep adding to bring to
the height Alright, so this is how you
save energy right and get into stovetop cooking
All right.
So the pickles now, let's get back to
the pickles because dehydration was an idea that
I think needs to be brought up That
wasn't in terms of pickle That does change
things in the easiest metaphor for that as
you know, what a cucumber tastes like Well,
when you get a pickle in a sandwich
or a burger or something, you know what
that tastes like Can you compare the two?
No, they're completely different Right.
All right How many times does someone say,
you know, I said you want it with
pickle or without pickles?
I want with pickle.
Are they thinking cucumber?
Are they thinking of that tangy pickle easy
to eat flavor, right?
You know the the yeah the tang They're
not thinking like cucumber is like a melon
flavor like a cantaloupe flavor most They're not
you're not thinking when someone says you want
pickle on it Sure, they're not thinking of
that green melon flavor from a cucumber.
You're thinking of this tangy crunchy Maybe sweet
maybe sour maybe so right?
Completely different not only is it completely different
to your palate It's completely different to the
energetic also the way you did you pass
it through the body and the way it
affects the body Right, you can think of
many other pickled foods like for example there
in Japanese.
There's something called umeboshi, which is a plum
You can't eat it raw, but a bit,
you know, you know, even ripe or whatever,
but it's preserved and pickled and salt water
has very good medicinal quality for the stomach
people who have stomach ailments and things like
that or even Balancing the stomach with digestive
aid.
No one would consider eating umeboshi plum unless
it's pickled In Japan, you see there's just
an example.
Well, what is cheese is dehydrated and pickled
dairy, isn't it?
Yeah, well not pickled in itself.
What's different?
It's fermented.
I should say from the concept of pickling
the brine, which is salt and and sugar
or salt and acid is Why most pickles
are done and when you say pickle, it's
wet Right.
Yeah, so it's going to be in a
liquid and that's typically called a brine And
essentially that does change the properties like for
example olives you cannot eat olives Ripe or
unless they're pickled or ripe or raw or
right?
You cannot eat them unless they're pickled I
mean you can try you can make oil
out of them and all right, so so
there are aspects to the Food that not
only are necessary for the food to be,
you know interacted with or consumed or eaten
But they have to be pickled or preserved
a certain way So again, the quality aspect
is main.
I know I haven't really brought up some
new stuff I'm very tentative about getting into
how making to make things even though I
do remember I had excellent feedback When I
talked about making perfect rice and stovetop baked
potatoes, maybe some other things.
There's some very good feedback But the thing
is I realized that okay, so you're able
to make perfect rice and understand stovetop baked
potatoes There's very little energy and all that
that's good.
But do you have the mindset to continue
and move forward?
You know, in other words, I feel like
I just gave fish.
I didn't really teach people how to fish
So the way you learn how to fish
is by study Unfortunately, the rectangle is just
Full of crap.
It's getting worse.
By the way, it was better when it
was just HTML white, you know pay you
know at 10-15 years ago, I Think
that people are up there more doing suffer
more serious and the browsers are better and
all this and less whatever but You still
can go around the world on the rectangle.
You know what I mean and visit the
various Culinary traditions and see what you like
you know it just because they say Mediterranean
and Asian is the best if you have
an aversion to that and you find that
repugnant by all means and you know Sorry,
well, I'm sorry for you, you know, but
that's like saying, you know If Italian shoes
fit your feet fit your feet, you're blessed
right, right?
Then it was shoes made in Spain and
Brazil like some people can't wear Italian shoes
because they're cut a certain way Well, that's
fine.
You know get Reebok's or whatever, you know,
I don't know but If you if your
feet do conform to Italian shoes, you are
really blessed In other words, you'll be able
to wear some of the best-made shoes
ever, right?
And by the way, speaking of shoes out
of discussion someone recently they're young But do
you know that up until the mid 1800s
if you bought shoes you just bought two
shoes There was no left and right You
just had to wear them and break them
in for left and right, right?
And that's why people didn't like wearing shoe
wear And then I you know, actually there
were shoes then they did finer shoes were
discovered to be You should have a left
the left foot is a mirror image of
the right.
Not only that they're very different as well
in length and shape sometimes They started selling
left and right shoes and each, you know
shoe company that did it had their own
way of doing it But you know back
in the day when you watch shoes, you
just bought two shoes.
It was no left and right Yeah, yeah
you put it in it went yeah, so
In a sense.
I am giving you the left and right
though Mediterranean and the Asian so you So
it's not just square.
I'm not being square just you know about
Mediterranean or whatever you use your best Judgment
on that and you'll see Also, you'll find
the people or have the best best health
and longevity not that you need either Actually
good health but short longevity is the way
to go on this planet, by the way
You want to be in good health and
live really short though, you don't want to
live long here I mean you might do
whatever you want, but I'm telling you this
is my I've been telling people for years
My earth adventure is over now.
It's just food clothing shelter I'm just waiting
to you know, you know the company car
just go to sleep and wake up later,
you know, there's nothing here Just deception evil
and bullshit But it's a pretty place.
So I think Some did up quite well
when it when somebody asked him do you
believe that there's In much more intelligent life
out in the galaxy and he says well,
of course there is you know And that's
why they're not coming to visit here Yeah,
very good Mm-hmm Yeah Yeah, it's just
the yeah it's just you know, but the
thing is the level of deceit that I
mentioned and Evil is on a very very
high high high level that the most people
will never see it Or contemplate it so
they don't they can't comprehend this is a
statement like you want to be healthy, but
short-lived, right?
short-lived or short-lived Yeah So, okay.
So on the quality aspect of it, I
think we can go into you know, here's
the fork in the road Well, if we're
going to talk about the high-grade stuff
Give us some stuff to Mediterranean food and
Asian food.
Well, actually you could decide on your own
Don't be intimidated.
For example, if you go to Mediterranean food
and they show you falafel Even I still
have problems making good falafel.
I consider myself to be on a mastership
level when it comes to cooking It's very
simple, yeah, but it's very sensitive and right
so so don't be like what is that?
You know, it's it looks difficult to make.
Yeah, some stuff is difficult, but pick the
stuff that's easy again, something in the middle
to Middle-eastern food is something called hummus,
which is basically ground peas with lemon juice
Maybe some garlic cumin and sesame paste Sesame
paste is a little fuss tahini is a
little it's basically sesame butter But it's finer
actually because sesame has such an high oil
content.
It doesn't form a paste when you mash
it forms that liquid All right.
It's very runny if you chill it it
can get pretty firm, but You know again
with the squash what's wrong with Undercooked steaming
some squash where it's still kind of crunchy
Chop it up.
Keep chopping it up and then grind some
of it down, you know Either in a
mortar and pestle or food processor add some
cumin Tahini and garlic and lemon juice and
olive oil and see what happens for a
dip Right.
It doesn't have to be chickpeas to make
hummus You can make black bean hummus.
I wouldn't it's a little too.
It's a different flavor But still you see
There's many aspects to the combinations Now I
didn't get into really the I did a
little bit in the chat I think I
posted why the low-grade foods are low
-grade.
We'll skip the East Indian East India can
get kind of complex Because the their spice
profiles are complex and they use a lot
of what's called key in many places, which
is basically Rendered clarified fat.
I mean clarified butter, which is the fat
part removed.
So would you go for high temperature?
What I do like from the Indian food
I find to be preferable are the flatbreads
I think I've done discussion on how to
make a quick flatbread it just like your
pasta except your brother you can actually I
see a lot of white people preheat an
oven a Big-ass oven to heat up
a little tiny thing like a piece of
toast or something toast size.
Don't do that Don't do that.
Do it on stovetop.
You can do flatbread on a stovetop.
And if you need that crunch just last
minute turn on your broiler for 30 seconds
and toss it the you know, hopefully you
don't have a I think most plastic handles
on Pans are flame retardant and I have
to consider these things because I'm you know
I because I have like restaurant equipment right
knives and pots and when I say someone
throw the pan in the oven.
I Keep forgetting that they have pans that
are made out of aluminum that are actually
painted with paint on one side with plastic
handles I mean, you know, I Yeah So
I have to consider if you if you've
got you could still do it with the
cheap pots and pans and the nasty stuff
You guys use out there, you know, the
majority of the world has You could still
do it.
But just be prudent and careful if you
see if you see something that's not metal
and you're sticking it near fire It should
be near fire, you know Yeah, so And
if you have If you're impressed because the
pot was large But but it's a real
cheap and how cheap it was because really
thin on the bottom and you're gonna burn
all your food Get get a heat diffuser.
They're real cheap.
They're easy to get just look up heat
diffuser So you could save the the cheap
-ass pots and pans that you guys are
using Just we're using a heat diffuser Two
bucks three bucks, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, and I'll save you else So you
should be used if you have heaven forbid
Teflon or those coated pots and pans now
years ago There were baked enamel coated pots.
Remember those.
Mm-hmm.
Actually they still are like crusade But if
if you have like crusade easy to find
Yeah, they there are they're pricey.
They're cast iron.
Usually it's just like a cast-iron tub.
Those are pretty good Liquor, you don't want
to use a scrape too much heavy.
You don't want to lean into it with
metal It could scratch it, but it's very
good But if you have all these coatings
these synthetic coatings plastic coatings inside your pots
There's a heat diffuser is a must just
to prevent the flashing Have you ever I
showed this to someone once have you ever
left a Teflon pan on the heat?
With nothing in it.
Well, it'll start to it starts to smoke.
Oh, yeah Yeah, and bubble Yep.
Yeah that comes off in your food every
time you eat it at a lower temperature
The bonding it's called the bonding vehicle, you
know, the the binders that they use to
get that crap on there Yeah, so and
it's also what is Teflon tetrafluoro?
It's a fluorinated plastic floor.
Yeah so anyway You ever wonder why people
are so dumb but okay, I Think that's
enough of the roundabout but just to finish
off.
Let's give a dig into why the low
quality the lower grade I say are low
grade the Latin American is low grade because
if you've ever been to anyone's house, it's
Latin American Not all of them, but most
of them Doesn't matter what part Mexico South
America, Puerto Rico, Cuba Caribbean you're going to
be served either too salty, but definitely overdone
slop Ninety nine point nine nine percent of
the time and it's going to taste good
because they've discovered something called adobo or Sasson
or MSG Sorry Their meat is overcooked.
They cook it to death heaven forbid.
You go to a Latin American person's house
for chicken Heaven forbid unless it's deep-fried
Even then it'll be as dry.
It'll be Like sawdust like eating balsa wood
Ninety nine point nine nine nine percent nuts
up somebody's probably might be listening in the
future announcing Greek.
That's not true I'm Latin Cuban or Brazilian
Argentina we make good food.
Yes, you're you're not the rule.
You're the exception now.
Why did I bring this up?
Starts at the home then the restaurants Go
out to a Mexican restaurant, what do you
get slop?
Sorry Slop and none of the food has
any flavor until you raise your hand and
ask the waitress for what?
Salsa, right you ever notice.
I need some sauce all the white people
in the in the restaurant Even though they
have no palate for good food.
Anyway, they're like more salsa, please more salsa.
I'm inhaling this burrito Yeah, can't eat it
without salsa the cheese has no flavor the
tortilla has no flip yes, it's better in
Mexico, but it's still slop overcooked under nourishing
Okay, you get it Yeah, and basically the
salsa and the seasonings that they use as
a vehicle to make it palatable, but the
actual Content itself is not very palatable.
I don't know if you've eaten Mexican food.
I do maybe once or twice a year
Out yeah, because I'm seeking it and it
looks terrible too.
It looks like the an aftermath of some
sort All right, and if you and then
there is the some of the Caribbean foods,
okay are good if you're there visiting But
it's very primitive.
In other words, you're you're in a hotel
somewhere in the Caribbean and it's by the
Oceanside by the beach and you have a
great you have a great meal because the
fishing boat just came in With the fresh
fish that they overcooked on the broiler and
fresh fruit and whatever, but otherwise in that
it's all overcooked slop Not not to mention
their propensity for pork and everything but and
Yeah, you know unclean fish both.
It's also mostly unclean food predominantly unclean But
the thing that I'm hard keeping on on
the American Latin side this part of the
world and the white people food We're not
going to get into Is because I Think
the culture is rather primitive.
I think I mentioned on a chat the
entire Latin American Sands maybe a tiny pocket
that's so rare.
I can't even mention are all hybrids whether
you go all the way down from Canada
to the but the very southern tip of
The Fuego Tierra de Fuego by Chile most
of the people are hybrids They're European hybrids
with the Native Americans that were here the
natives that were here Right, so it's a
very young culture, right, right If you meet
like a Puerto Rican a Cuban a Dominican
Argentine or Brazilian they're hybrids You know, well
on one side somewhere.
They're either 1 5th 1 quarter 1 3rd
Indian the native Mayan Aztec if you meet
Mexicans They're Aztec Mayan right or German and
Spanish French mix Right, and they've developed this
new Species called the South American and the
Caribbean.
They're hybrids Right, so if you go to
you know, and and that's okay We could
you could say, you know The older countries
the older countries in the old world Europe
Middle East or whatever in the Chinese Well,
they're hybrids too.
Yes But they were they were they were
hybridized a long time ago and they've developed
a culture based on XYZ Which is a
higher quality food culture so it seems like
the South American Caribbean and all that area
the Latin culture of you know from Mexico
on down and and the Islands they they
adopted the worst of the native and the
worst of the European and made their hybrid
food as well so Doesn't mean there aren't
any Latin America Latin Americans or Cubans or
whatever that can't cook Well, they think they
do I I'd beg to differ but it's
possible.
They are like Mexico City For example here
in this other was a there was a
Mexican restaurant of Mexico City I said I
got to go there because that's not Mexican
Mexican as we know Mexican Americanized or northern
Mexico.
That's French Food that uses ingredients from the
Mexic the cut this continent, right?
So that was very good actress or finally
done But they still couldn't cook foul so
Anyway, most people have never had foul cooked
properly, you know bird turkey or chicken.
I'm surprised It's thinking of opening a restaurant
that just prepares foul so people can have
it properly done I've never had foul properly
done out Actually, that's not true recently There
was a place called Indian twist that opened
down the street here and they did prepare
some chicken properly believe it or not very
rare Not rare cook, but very rare that
you have fun.
It's amazing.
How Kennedy has lost its ability to properly
prepare foul And that's actually it's it's so
bad that if you do eat foul It's
almost worth doing a sonic on believe it
or not.
That's how bad it is More than anything
else Yeah, yeah, so now most people don't
they eat foul like chicken or whatever that
that's been heavily tenderized and chemicalized Oh, so
it is edible, you know when you're out
Processed food like a chicken sandwich chicken nugget.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about when you have a whole
bird Do you know how to prepare?
The answer is no most people don't they
think they do And even again and the
reason I bring this up is because if
you do any one from Cuba or Puerto
Rico or Dominican Republic you talk to them
you say what Jeff for dinner, you know
a month ago.
I say what Jeff for dinner Chicken and
rice, I don't complain.
Oh, yes a couple days.
I would you have for dinner chicken or
chicken and rice What are you having tomorrow
chicken and rice?
right Broiled chicken fry they get away with
the fried chicken, of course because of all
the fat So even though it's devoid of
moisture and not properly seasoned at least the
fat tastes good I say if you could
deep fry a shoe or a chair, I'll
eat it If it's deep fried, it just
tastes good.
It's the fat that makes things the fat
the salt and how it's cooked I make
it taste good right the mineral So there's
the low grade.
So any sorry, but you know, but anyone
will can easily Acknowledge, I don't forget about
agree or not that again the Latin American
that whole Caribbean is slop Basically, just look
at it go online and look at the
food.
Just look at how it looks even Right
and again, my experience is always overcooked and
They don't know how to season food.
Basically, it's salt and of course a pepper,
you know, there's so frito But so frito
is a different thing Altogether if you why
use so frito if you're going to kill
the rest of the meal and make slop
anyway, so This is not this is the
reason I bring it up is because I
don't pursue that type of cooking I like
a higher form of higher grade of cooking
if I prepared starches vegetables and meats I
don't want to do it the way they
do it, right?
So I it's not and the only reason
people eat it believe it or not is
because it's cheap It's convenient and it tastes
good because of all the MSG They do
buy MSG.
All their seasoning is loaded with MSG and
the white people food We're not going to
talk about at all.
You guys know what it is.
And if you don't that's a that's great
Don't worry about it it's best that you
don't and again, just And just to touch
on the white people food slop Overcooked salt
is the main ingredient for seasoning no concept
of seasonality No concept of energy, you know
how to do anything with it.
Just just my stomach is growling I got
to put something in it.
Yum.
It's good And you swallow it's funny when
you see white people eating white people.
How is it?
I always say it's good.
It's good It doesn't tell me anything about
how it tastes That's why I say the
ghetto style how it tastes this is right?
anyway So again, the high-grade of Mediterranean
and we basically a discussion was qualitative the
little bit of history and on How to
pursue, you know, there's a mindset behind food
food is very very important If you're used
to eating a certain way and you go
travel and the food is better You feel
great and you come back to where you
were and you don't feel so good anymore
You kind of get over it for me
it's the opposite because I'm used to eating
a certain way if I travel I feel
like crap because it's really hard to get
good food and Especially like I think I
put in the chat I've once stayed with
some very wealthy white people for a few
days as a guest and I got sick
literally I mean, I felt like I've been
the stuff they were eating.
I was like, I wouldn't feed this to
a dog I didn't even really eat but
And they could afford, you know, I mean,
there's nothing, you know, but anyway Yeah So
what I've discovered is I'm traveling now not
to seek out restaurants, but to seek out
food markets or a supermarket So I would
see all the people run to a pizzeria,
which was not even a real pizzeria, you
know, like a white You know fast food
pizzeria.
It's not pizza.
I told them What I would do is
go to an Albertsons or a raw Ralph's
or a Safeway or I don't know where
those big supermarkets, right?
And even though they're geared towards white people
food They don't really you it's the general
quality is not very good you walk in
It doesn't smell like anything you ever notice
that we walk into a good food market.
It smells delicious You're going to an Italian
Really good or Asian food market except for
the dried fish smell Sometimes it just smells
good and a good fish in a good
food market go to a whole foods.
Well when they're clean it smells More appealing
like there's food here versus a regular sanitize
But anyway, I would go to these super
these guys would go traveling with traveling and
do things and they would go and eat
this Crappy pizza or crappy steak or crappy
and I'm like no I'm going over here
to the you know, the supermarket, right?
You could even go to a food a
Walmart food area now and make the best
choice possible I go over the vegetable.
I'll get a seasonal vegetable.
It doesn't need to be cooked I go
get myself a block of cheese and I
go get myself some bread and and I
Basically go to the cash out and it's
like maybe two bucks for the bread three
bucks for the cheese and two bucks for
the veg So at around seven bucks, I
have like a really like two meals of
bread cheese and vegetable three meals, maybe right
for seven bucks Yeah, or farther where they're
spending ten or twelve on crap and one
meal you see restaurant, yeah, so so and
that doesn't mean if a Supermarket has a
hot bar or something like that.
Even though I do go crazy for a
wing bar a good wing bar They've been
doing that over here.
They have a Chicken wing bar with all
these different flavors.
There's been one of those when they're fresh
Yeah So anyway, um, like you said before
though.
The problem is is trying to find a
well prepared Without them being overdone when you
see as very great or that they could
now also occasionally might get some good fried
chicken out there occasionally But I'm saying to
the cooking Oh fouled different ways properly most
people don't know That's it's sad because I
can't you know, unless I go to a
really high-end restaurant.
It's not going to be done Even then
it's probably not going to be done right
last time.
I'd follow out a high-end restaurant It
wasn't done though as well as it could
be, you know for what, you know for
40 bucks for a dish you know for
an entree, but So basically when you're going
to eat out I Try to give yourself
good food supply In other words restaurants are
going to provide if anyone's worked in the
restaurant business as other the it just been
around it You know that they get food
from suppliers, right?
And they they're interested in quote-unquote making
profit.
So they're going to ask the cheapest to
get the cheapest Quality its cheapest price for
the best quality But sometimes what happens is
they forget about the quality and go just
to the cheaper But if the customer complains
and they go back to the better one
like, you know When you go to a
store and get a whole chicken, it's anywhere
between like five to ten bucks depending on
the quality of the chicken right a Small
chicken, maybe four to six bucks Well, you
know how much a restaurant gets a whole
small chicken like these Mexican grill places You
know these mom-and-pop restaurants that serve
chickens or you know a restaurant just a
regular restaurant You know how much a chicken
a whole chicken costs a restaurant?
Yep, just under a buck about a buck
the whole chicken.
Yeah, but 25 cents a pound 20 cents
20 to 25 cents a pound That so
in other words that same chicken is also
what you're by.
It's the same quality that you're buying in
the stove right, unless it's a preferential, you
know local or more regional and Higher, you
know higher grade That's how cheap food is,
right?
So Still so the reason I'm saying this
is because you'll notice that instead of eating
out try to Purvey your own food supply.
So when you're out Don't make your first
hunch to go eat out Make your first
hunch to get some food Even if you're
traveling, let's say you're in a engine driven
wagon have a little mess kit with you,
right?
literal literally a mess kit If you know
what that is, look it up Camping kit,
you know, I even have a little portable
stove I I used to cook Yeah and
anything actually not anymore but at any time
I could pull over at the side of
the road to make a meal it would
Be better than the restaurant Ready to go
because I have a little pocket stove.
You've seen the pocket So I was literally
fits in getting you have a little tank.
Yeah, okay so and then they have the
The the mess kit where the pot fits
inside the pan and it has a lid
and you know Stuff right, right.
You got some high quality stuff They've really
have some stuff titanium now for the mountain
climbers because they have to be lightweight, right?
Right, so So anyway, there you go And
also here's another thing to consider when it
comes to quality you eat at home and
you dine out You shouldn't be eating out.
You should be dining out Now dining is
different than eating out.
That's when the sir you You're eating either
way whether you're eating at home or not
at home.
But the reason you call it dining It's
because it's about the service you're being made
to feel like a master just like as
if you you turn on a film and
you see a butler and a hostess and
wherever and they're treating the The manor or
the master of the house a certain way,
you know It's like a hot cuisine like
you're more of like a high society type
thing.
That's why you eat out.
That's not available I mean it is available,
but it's rare that you see it now.
It's about eating out It used to be
you eat it when you dine out right
you see again, so in essence at home
And yeah, yes and it since there is
such a disparity well actually that's very disparate
there is no quality either way at all
at people's homes or out forget about the
dining make the dining experience the effort that
you make at home to make the best
quality in preparation and ingredients And again, I
I didn't I didn't really get into the
the direct How to prepare anything but just
the mindset I think most people still have
a lot of studying to do regarding the
the hot explain the why the why you
do this Yes because it's going to be
the high at the best use of the
ingredients ingredients that are more healthful for you
and also the the meth the way that
it's Put together You know the calm the
food combining just like we brought up someone
asked about the coca Coconut whether it's the
milk the fat the butter The oil I
think outside of where that ingredient has been
mastered outside of Thai cuisine.
It's it's not relevant Right I mean it
makes a great.
You know topical Coconut oil and things are
great for topical and bought you know Condition
things you could use it for right skin
and other things, but I would suggest that
Look at the ingredient.
You know when you look at for example
the sesame seeds it's very highly used in
the Japanese in the Asian Chinese mostly and
Also in the Mediterranean isn't that interesting how
it's crossed and it works well In the
America you see so that's something that like
for example.
I have tahini.
I have sesame seeds I have raw sesame
seeds roasted sesames.
I have black sesame seeds.
I have sesame oil raw.
I have sesame oil toasted I You know
I have sesame in every form Because it's
it goes with Asian and like if you
go to a let's say get a roll
a Japanese roll rice roll It has sesame
seeds on the outside right they use something
called gamaccio Which is a condiment you roast
sesame seeds?
And then you grind a half of you
put half of it aside and the other
half or a third you grind with some
sea Salt you mill it down just slightly,
and then you combine them all together, and
you put it in a shaker So Pete
that's a great way to get people off
of salt people who like to add a
lot of salt to food You have them
use oshio instead now salt also I didn't
talk about as many things we could talk
about the chemical properties You know cooking is
about chemistry and heat you know like salt
attracts oil you know acid Dissolves a nullifies
oil right Like that's why when you have
fried food or oily foods You put salt
on it when you have into a lot
of Asian cooking when you have a high
fat high protein you dip it in tamari
You know I say soy sauce right there
We see like sushi you dip the fish
and that's in the black sauce the soy
sauce because it's salty So what happens is
when the the salt?
Combines with the oil so you don't have
this radical oil in the intestine they stick
to each other Now the the acid breaks
up oil if anyone wants to try this
experiment if you have a good exhaust fan
It would be the way to do it
or not Anyway a small saucepan and heat
up some oil and then I want you
to squeeze some lemon juice on the side
and when the oil gets good and hot
pour the Lemon juice on the oil on
the pan not not a lot of oil
like it's blast But just an oily pan
like a coating on it what will happen
is you're gonna see you're gonna hear a
very loud what you like a flash like
a foot like a like a Steam flash
you're gonna see a vapor that you can't
see through and then the vapor disappears into
droplets And then when you look at the
pan there is no oil.
It's stripped clean Wow So when you when
you combine an acid with a hot oil
the oil will vaporize and leave the entire
surface and it'd be gone It'll it'll be
it'll be it'll be gone and stay gone.
It'll be in the air and it'll coat
everything in the room, right?
Okay, so what it's that's why have you
ever seen You know the British when you
have fish and chips, which is french fries
and fried fish.
What do you put on a malt vinegar?
It tastes great Ketchup has got why does
ketchup on fried food taste good?
What's the main ingredient other than tomato the
main flavor thicker?
Acid if you go to parts of Europe,
they put lemon juice on everything put lemon
juice on french fries, by the way Try
that you'll be pretty Be pretty that's what
you ever had fresh you ever have fresh
sliced tomato with french fries delicious Because the
acid in the tomato and the umami in
the tomato the glutamate flavor, right?
Yeah, so in other words, so, you know
acids and oils And salts and oils different
the acid will disperse the oil And the
salt will combine with the oil and keep
it from Spreading.
Yeah, that's why Fried foods, you know, you
ever have french fries without any salt at
all really bland.
That's so good.
They don't digest that well either Yeah Yeah
Okay, so these are the reason I brought
up this in closing maybe is because that
that's so obvious But you know obvious meaning
in your surroundings, but you didn't know why
right if you can describe how to make
You know, if you were described someone industrial
industrial setting or commercial say how do you
make french fries?
Well, put them in the fryer Wait till
a golden brown depending on the crunch and
then you put salt on them Then you
serve them you just give a description everyone
could give the description why you put salt
on french fries But no one is explaining
You know, I mean how why yeah, exactly
That's why if anyone wants to try that
experiment just do you put a little bit
of oil in a pan or a pot
and then wipe the oil off with a
Tissue or a paper towel or something?
So there's no dangerous amount of volume and
get it nice and warm not hot where
it's burning and then pour some acid in
there Whether it's vinegar or lemon juice watch
what happens and stand back because it will
vapor You'll get oil droplets micro oil droplets
in all over the room and the pan
will be Looked like you just went through
at it with a dish sponge and rinsed
it and wiped and put it ready to
put it away Amazing how this works Right,
yeah, it's best to do it outside But
this so these are these are the things
that also can be discussed for example at
a cooking school type Situation, you know everyone
in their lives that's been out or around
food prep knows that you put you've they've
seen you've seen the Salt-going on the
fried food at the counter of the right
where any place that makes french fries or
they're all you've seen the ass You know
the ketchup on the fried foods and the
in the relishes or whatever.
Oh, but why?
Why you see because when it gets inside
of your body If you if you eat
a fat or an oil without the salt
or the acid whether it be a vegetable
fat meaning Even beans taste better with salt
salt them afterwards, right?
There's a cook faster with that, right?
So what happens if you if you put
fats and proteins in through the body without
the salt or the acid?
Which would be various forms of vinegar or
citrus or whatever?
What will happen is that oil will be
like a radical in the in the intestinal
literally?
Your body will say well, what do we
do with this because it's getting everywhere and
it's messy When you have the protein or
the fat going through the body with salt
or acid it stays Contained or bonded in
other words the salt will bond To the
fat or the protein and the body will
see it together as a very tidy unit
where in the acid will disperse it to
the point where it could mix in with
the Hydrology and the ecology of the intestine
very well and use it differently and use
it again Right.
Sometimes the best is to eat with heavy
fats and proteins to use salt and Acid
you want to put for example Certain foods
again fried food You put salt on the
fish and chips and lemon juice or malt
vinegar and ketchup and salt, right?
French fries tastes better with salt and ketchup
or malt vinegar or lemon juice, right?
Not just salt, right?
Hard Oh, well, it does well initially it
doesn't know what to do with it.
It's like this oil is just a hand
Right.
It's just getting everywhere and not it's not
behaving right?
It's like a free radical.
Let's say in the body You know But
once you combine the salt in the acid
with the protein or the fat that could
be vegetable or animal The body sees it
as a neat tidy self-contained well behaved
package that it can administer what the intestines
do So there's your coconut butter.
Your coconut is a very difficult one to
handle.
By the way, by the way When you're
dealing with coconut fats When you come whether
you combine acid or salt with it, it
doesn't like to behave like other things do
either.
So that's Yeah, to me eating coconut fat
is like Vaseline Coke it's just one thing
I can never Muscle down it's coconut.
It's just Not the harp on it just
to give like, you know, if I give
a make a comment that might sound negative
I'm also backing it up with why yeah
So then that's the important part is, you
know knowing Having some basis on it.
Yeah, we explained a lot though that that
uh It was a wealth of information there
and you gave me some ideas Okay, good,
so I getting some messages here and there
and maybe some maybe nothing pertinent All right,
I think was it was about mindset I
really wanted to clarify a little bit more
of what I put in the chat Which
was the low grade high grade type of
food and what people can pursue because I
think most parts of the world right now
We're set into a seasonal change I think
it's already been established whether you're a northern
or southern that you've established the seasons have
changed or are changing Yeah Freezing temperatures and
I'm waiting to see how many people start
coming down with the Mucusy troubles and all
that kind of stuff, which is always oh
because it's their diet.
Yeah Yeah, it's their diet and then what
happens is if the diet is so poor
the body goes into that Decomposition state where
the pathogens can breed it more.
Well, they actually come from the body You
know, they actually the body produces them, right?
This has been shown in blood tests that
have been suppressed, but you can still be
suppressed in the mainstream But you can still
access them and then once you they everyone
has them.
They're all emitting this this Sick frequency, let's
just say or field and it makes it
even easier To get you know that that
sickness, but they're not they don't change their
diets.
Yeah Yeah, and by the way, they're yeah
No, by the way, most of the diets
Sorry, I'll say most of that Most of
the diets that whether it's the Atkins of
paleo or whatever none of them ever address
seasonality and illness So I just wanted to
throw that out there all the diets that
you hear a dummy load That got sick
and then when they went up by the
fence by other sheep that were Not infected
or something at that time They also caught
this kind of disease.
I was trying to remember Without contact.
Yeah.
Yeah is either based on food or there
were so many sick sheep in one spot,
right?
Emitting it or also the you know, what's
interesting was also the the the study someone
put I didn't watch the video Thomas I
think put a video up on sick trees
That's chemtrails and also what was funny when
I look at I shouldn't say for sure,
but most likely What I want to say
also is when you look at videos, it's
so funny It's if you're actually watching a
video of scientists quote-unquote and lab technicians
and doctors wherever working, you know I'll tell
you what I see All I see is
someone that went out to a laboratory supply
bought all the equipment and the coats and
the clothing and then they went To this
place called University and they memorized all the
bullshit.
They told him and then got something gonna
hang on the wall.
That's it That's all that's going on with
scientists Right, it's all presumptuous The attorneys
tell them it's presumptuous and all of your
scientific studies, by the way I've predetermined results
don't ever think that there's any research being
done because anything that that Is known or
could be known was already is already known,
right?
This is what they don't want people any
if you know anyone in any field that
does research They give them the results.
They want the the experiment to be structured
to have predetermined results Right, why because there's
no reason for research They already know and
now it doesn't mean that everyone working in
the field does but it isn't everything is
known already But they don't want you to
stumble across and rationalize.
It's going to be too problematic There was
an old quote.
I forgot who wrote it It says you
you you are seriously erroneous if you think
that education is for enlightenment It's there to
prevent originality Prevent and prevent thinking and dissent
Who was that that said that?
You said this about 1920s when they because
it before the 1920s there wasn't such a
stand there was a stamp There's public education,
but not like it is now, you know
No Yeah, maybe second find it while we're
here or So, yeah, so the other otherwise,
I don't know what else to comment on
the the mindset I'd never really got into
it It's important to comprehend and again just
to recap You're always going to be better
off Spiritually mentally Spiritually physically with a vegetarian
quote-unquote diet always hands down It doesn't
mean that meat is the animal flesh is
the plague No, the plague is the plague
animal flesh is something dead that you consume
Because of taste or desire or necessity, right?
But if I were to say just a
few things about food it would be be
veggie For sure as much as possible and
the other thing is be seasonal for sure
as much as possible and if you have
Doubts on either one of those especially the
second one Seasonality, what does that mean?
Just look at what's going on in your
environment and what traditions or cultures have mastered
their environments Yeah, well You're not going to
live in Northern climate or the most southern
antarctic or the most or that if you
eat like they do in the tropics or
the Caribbean You're not going to survive even
no Right like years ago.
I knew people that worked on the in
Alaska on the pipeline, which is not like
Anchorage and other places where it's where most
people live there These people working on the
pipeline were in the tundra the places that
was very harsh, right?
And they had a commissary and the guy
what wanted bananas and oranges and they charged
you ten dollars for one banana or one
orange Because they had to bring it up
there specifically And he's like that's stupid.
I want it but those that did get
it got sick Those that did spend the
ten bucks for the you know what they
wanted on the truck.
We're sick So and this is something that
I heard also when I was young and
I started matching the things putting these things
together and again, I hope people get something
out of this Greek speak stuff because no
one's ever been able to put that I've
seen this kind of Concentrated information in one
little package in a sonic so I Hope
you guys get something out of it I
sure have and I think sharing it at
least you know if and it's not a
matter of being popular I know that's this
one this stuff will never be popular It's
a matter of helping one or two or
three or five or ten or whatever But
knowing why You're
welcome, I don't see anything else going on.
I'm out.
I'm in the kitchen right now.
Uh-huh no pun intended If
there's any questions if there isn't yeah, we'll
just Well it takes about 10-15 seconds
to get down the line to them Okay,
we'll just wait a minute No
you gave me a lot of ideas especially
When you know and I only get a
half hour to eat at work And there's
just a lot of times just due to
the choices around there well what they're gonna
do is They're going to fall into the
routine, which is you know well There's a
lunch wagon, or this is where we go
for lunch.
You know the various prepared foods or The
better way is for someone to prepare To
prepare lunch you know a lunchbox literally I've
ever seen an Indian or Japanese lunchbox.
It's a bunch of stainless steel Interlocking bowls
they stack up and the handle straps over
there.
Maybe see what you're seeing that Oh Okay,
I don't know put in Indian lunchbox or
Japanese lunchbox in a search you should see
a stack of Stainless steel bowls about anywhere
between three to six and as you stack
the bowls you know they interlock And there's
a side strap that locks them all in
place with a handle on top And it
goes into is that what it was did
I get the description.
That's clever.
Yeah, okay, so what's cool about that is
Mm-hmm yeah, you could heat it up
very well You know in a steamer the
idea is to have your food there And
then put the whole thing everyone puts the
everyone shows up with this and then when
it's time to eat everyone 15 minutes or
so before everyone sticks them in a steamer
or an oven right mm-hmm or in
the summer You could put you know the
fridge if it's cool cool foods Or You
could separate the hot and the cold before
you eat, you know heat them that way,
but okay Yeah, those are those have been
around for over a century Before the lunchbox
that we were given.
I think were you given a lunchbox.
You're not you're not that old Yeah, as
we were given you probably still had I
had ones with the trains on them I
had ones that had I never had that
I I was this was before the superhero
I never had a superhero's box.
It was either a train.
I remember or some landscape Right I think
one I had one that had the Apollo
mission on it, maybe You're dating yourself now
Yeah, it was pre Apollo.
Yep.
Yeah, I had the one where you had
the thermos in it and all that kind
of stuff And oh, yeah, yeah, I'll add
The Aladdin company.
I remember I was so happy.
I got yeah Yeah, it was a it
was a metal box with a plastic thermos.
They switched to remember them No, because heaven
forbid you drop the thermos.
Oh god Yeah, and Aladdin was All right,
that's fine, I hope people got something out
of it basically gonna study study the Mediterranean
and Asian and your mind get your mindset
in order and You don't absorb anything and
do the legwork.
Okay, cool with that said We'll do it
again in seven days Already Greek.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Thanks You're welcome.
Thanks, man.
Bye