Let's get you in there.
Okay.
Evening folks.
We're live with the Greek greetings and Another
week.
Yeah, okay.
It's it's the third week of the seventh
month for those that don't know actually I
think it's not for those that don't know
because if you don't know that you Probably
won't know I mean, yeah, we're talking about
For those that do know I should say
it's an affirmation Correct.
Yeah, and it's funny how many people say
they I View it as just part of
the situation humanity is so many people have
run into through the years That want to
do quote-unquote, you know, the father's law
what they call, you know The proper thing
or God's law and they can't get time
to me that shows the the mix-up
In society, you know, they're censored and it's
not because I say so and I'll tell
you why If if the world is so
screwed up that we're not supposed to know
All right, what the right thing to do
is it wouldn't be available at all Right,
right.
So what happens is it's available in such
a fucked-up way use a medical term,
correct that Those that really want it.
I mean those that don't Care or censored
are going to see it say.
Oh, yeah, that's not for me But those
that really want it will say oh This
just affirms how screwed up it is and
it affirms that the ones doing the screw
-up know how important it is You know
also, so it's a game right in a
way a game within the censorship so It's
it's pretty interesting, you know typically People everyone
will give lip service just like yeah, I
want knowledge I I like but really they
don't they hate it They hate people with
that pursue those things and again, I always
say how do we know that?
Well, look at your media.
How do they portray people that seek knowledge?
Oh, they're nerds, right?
You know, they even did movies about that.
Yeah, they would they Stereotypical, right, right Where
where they're trying to create a culture here.
Here's the thing.
I was discussing prejudicial aspects of human culture
recently it's not the Race or the co
or the person being let's say black Puerto
Rican Italian Greek Chinese That's that makes stereotypical
Prejudicing accurate because it is accurate.
Mm-hmm It's the culture they come from
so if you had someone that is of
let's say Italian bloodline for 30 generations and
they're brought up in you know farm-fresh,
Iowa Right from they were born there and
raised there You couldn't tell the difference that
they were Milanese or Bolognese or Sicilian.
Let's say right They wouldn't desire any of
the things they would desire what people from
farm-fresh, Iowa do pork chops really bad
starches Campbell's mushroom, whatever, you know, you know
what I'm talking about?
Yes, they would have you go to their
house They have two big freezers in the
garage just in case You know They were
you know, they were they talk a certain
way, right?
Okay, so So very now how how it
how easy is it take that farm-fresh,
Iowa?
Italian Italian you would say and make him
act like his project, you know people who
came before him Very difficult impossible.
Yeah, so when you meet someone who is
let's say American black or American or Puerto
Rican or Chinese from those and they hold
on to those Cultural they're raised in a
family that speaks the language and eats the
food and uses those traditions their prejudices that
you have against them and Stereotypes that make
the the prejudice and stereotypes worthwhile and accurate
is not the individual.
It's himself It's the collective that he comes
from An example again would be like if
you ever watched Star Trek the Borg it
didn't matter which Borg it was It was
that you had Borg Because there were a
collective right, right So now the cosmic censorship
transcends that by the way Cosmic censorship doesn't
care about what culture or what stereotype you've
been enlisted in Or you've enlisted yourself and
were born in You see the difference because
it's more divine or cosmic Right.
It's straight.
I just want to throw that Yeah stuff
to people and speaking of cosmic.
There is a major cosmic Superimposition on the
planet right now is sort of like on
the western part of the Atlantic Ocean Manifesting
it's or expressing itself as a massive hurricane
about to go into the East Coast.
Let's say that again Sure, there is a
large cosmic imposition Meaning it's an ethereal disturbance
out in space and I mean way out
there about three-quarters of the way to
the moon and it's so happened to have
landed on the Western Atlantic and it's manifesting
itself.
I think hurricane Francisco.
It's expressing itself You know, it's interesting is
I so there's a lots of people know
I can take that It's something I sound
cocky close your ears If you're not used
to hearing the Greek speak at this point
because it's going to get a little crazy
There are plenty of people that know what
that I can take out that hurricane I'll
have to do is that I have a
hurricane abatement device.
It's about 20 feet long and The reason
you you make it that long is so
you don't have to guess am I really
hitting it, right?
And yes longer bigger is better in some
cases because there is Resonate, you know there
are factors to be considered where size is
important just like in the Newman machine, right?
Like I have lots of windings and stuff
and expresses what?
The Joseph Newman machine does but it doesn't
do what?
7,000 pounds or 40,000 pounds of
copper does it just doesn't so right and
I've had long Discussions with Trevor on this
and no matter how much we touted what
we were able to do We said well
ultimately, you know when we told stories about
big weather guns, we were all like yeah,
that's there's no replacement for that No, there
isn't so anyway How many people are getting
in touch for me to get rid of
it none none I think steering it around
will be kind of fun in the meantime
It should it should hit the coast with
the cumulative power of about a megaton You
know, it would it could do what a
megaton, you know, a Few hundred Hiroshima's would
do right in terms of damage.
Yeah, it could at a category for So
I think steering it around, you know, it
might be fun, but I'm here's the thing
It's I'll make one for free, but it's
a mil 1.5 million to take it
out.
How's that?
Anyway a fair asking price.
Yeah.
Yeah, if you want hurricanes, I'll make them
all day, but to take them out.
No, it's 1.5 30 grand if you
want to talk about it So and this
if you're like you're doing this for money,
but no, I'll just give it away It
doesn't matter but you got to give something.
No, I can't just sit there, but no
one's even calling So it's interesting That's another
part of the censorship because you know, what
are you gonna do say it's Americans No,
there are plenty of people over the world
You know, it's look prejudices and stereotypes are
super accurate Right.
I mean if you ever listen to American
black people talk about each other You'll be
like this doesn't sound right because it's god
-awful talk Right.
Mm-hmm, right, but you know heaven forbid
you're not black talk about them like that
now you're gonna be you see Yep, so
you're in trouble because you're not entitled.
It's with any group, right?
But once they let you and you can't
actually I can I've Back in the day
had acquaintances that were very black ghetto American
black and I could talk I could say
anything because they know me Or I was
invited in the group the same with other
cultures, but here's the interesting thing cosmic censorship
doesn't work that way No, you never get
a bunch of people getting together say how
come we don't see this even though it's
obvious.
What are we gonna do?
They never do it's kind of hidden under
the rung which is why it's cosmic censorship
You know, which goes back to why it's
the third week.
Yeah, the seventh being that that it's that
day a reckoning I guess the folks have
Memorialized oh, yeah, we have all September 11th.
That was last week.
Yes.
It was Awfully I Just couldn't help but
notice when I when I was just scanning
different news articles in the place where they
had everybody Placed the the rubble the people
the dust was in a place called fresh
kills Yeah Nobody had in any way shape
or form expressed any outrage at naming that
that Well, it was fresh kills.
It's been fresh kills for a long time,
right?
But I mean if you're gonna Yeah, it's
been fresh kills for 50 years before you
know, I know but they're not gonna Just
wrong They're they're not the people the average
human is you could put him on a
giant anvil with a giant cartoon hammer And
he'll just say well, what are you doing?
Yeah, you know You know, they're so stupid
There's a very small exception in humanity that
will ever see anything at any time in
human history If you don't believe that statement
go read the book of Numbers for example,
actually don't bother but you know what?
I mean, right talk about grumbling and complaining.
I mean that was like the epitome of
it, right?
Oh god Yeah, you know, there's a there's
grumbling in every book.
Well, you know Exodus or whatever but book
of Numbers tops it so you know, I
mean Forget it.
They're finished.
Here's the thing This is this has don't
take it personally.
This is amongst the gods You know, you're
you're basically aligned and oppressed by a national
God, you know I think someone in the
chat earlier put about what do you do
about praying for dinner and silent and I
wrote Well, that's the sinner dinner that he
can't fix that You only get away from
those people, you know 20 years ago.
You might say well You might want to
put an expressive body of knowledge together to
give to Christians.
What's that idiot?
Oh, what's his name?
Martin the guy who wrote 101 questions that
earnest Yeah, yeah that Christians don't know I
mean that kind of stuff you could have
gotten away with and in half of that's
accurate the other half's not by the way
But now is just got to get away
or insulate yourself from them.
You know, there's a guy That I know
here in town and he bought this one
of these McMansions, right, right, but he got
it like half of what it could have
been if it was in a better location
It was at the end of the subdivision
and there's this huge 250 kV power line
going by and I mean like right you
see it's right there.
You could hear it and everything Like what
do you do?
I said, well, you're gonna have to put
up some where you sleep put up some
mirrors on the inside Walls, you know in
the mirror.
You can't tell it's a mirror.
It's facing the parallel You just put it
up against the wall.
You see the back of the mirrors paint
over it Whatever and we had some dowsing
rods and they were spinning around like you
remember those old model airplane propellers He wound
with the rubber band right and you let
it go.
Sure.
You know, it was a pretty fast Propeller,
that's how fast the dowsing rods were spinning.
Holy sweet when I went under it.
Yeah I mean it was like those airplane
propelled there was there was spinning at about
60 about a 60 to 100 rpm I
couldn't stop him.
That's a lot, you know, and he was
like, how do you do that?
Yeah, I see where the field was going
I said this feels drilling down into the
ground about 30 feet and going up about
500 feet and you're within it everyone else
here is within it and If you ever
knew anything, let me know and I'm like,
oh, whatever I'm not gonna mention anybody has
this family has the biggest funeral home business
here in town I'm like, well, you know,
yeah, if I do DD if I do
DD services, I won't be the one calling,
you know anyway So, oh my god, but
the censorship is yeah, that's an interesting thing
So back to the sinner dinner praying at
that any public prayer is absurd Scripturally doesn't
what there's a difference between prayer and calling
out But when you say like the America,
this is the but also Okay, I'm presuming
the person who wrote that is American So
that is mostly an American thing.
See like when When you Okay, how do
we catch this?
For example, I used to do a lot
of these roundtables right back in the day
70 years ago more and when I'd say
something So you denying Jesus?
I'm like, well, where were you born?
I was born in America.
Okay, what you go?
You ever go anywhere else?
You know, how'd you learn?
I learned it here Okay, so you're talking
about the American God and the American Jesus
You know, whatever comment they give you right?
They don't know that There's these people are
you know, they're so far removed and they're
censored so if you're having a conversation in
Greece and Someone you know says what are
you talking about?
That's you know Jesus where as well, where
were you?
But okay, you're talking about the Greek God
So what's there is no when you look
at Christianity?
There is no universal Christian God No matter
how much they say it because you'll notice
it changes from country to country If we
read scripture, we know that gods have been
aligned and issued over certain countries So when
you say God in France, that's the French
God not the American God.
I know this is hard for people to
understand It doesn't matter.
They're not gonna stand much ever anyway, but
it doesn't mean we can't bring it up
as a fact right now Why is it
a fact?
Well, you know because it's stated as such
And I'm just reporting on it as being
a fact, right?
So right There there are many levels to
All this so back to the guy with
this I call it the sinner dinner, you
know, right, right You know because everybody's a
sinner if you're Christian, right?
So, yeah If you have no desires, how
can you sin?
I?
Don't know they ask that a Christian you'll
freak out because he doesn't know what sin
is Because the American God in the American
Jesus doesn't permit that kind of thinking It's
a lot in short Yeah, it's the fool
Analogy Recently, I want to see what Ken
Wheeler was doing that to the fat tattooed
bald guy I think he did a video
what makes a fool and you people aren't
gonna like it what I'm gonna say I'm
like, oh man, it's you gotta listen some
Greek speak if you think you're harsh but
he basically calls everyone a fool pretty much
except for like if you want to know
what how quote-unquote Intelligently activated someone is
socially ask him what books they've read And
most people have never read a book But
you know, but still, you know that lets
you know a lot about you know Good
because the book is not like a movie
you have to sit there I mean it
could be so you could read a book
in two hours But it's a more of
a commitment and usually if you're gonna make
that commitment You're actually moving you're putting more
energy into it than most other things.
So, mm-hmm Yeah Unfortunately, or fortunately, there
aren't too many people go out there calling
everyone morons and idiots or whatever fools It
doesn't matter as long as it's done, you
know, so, you know later on people can
see we were so foolish Yeah, I told
you so as well.
How come nobody said anything?
We were all so stupid Back to the
sinner dinner though.
Yes It's which is easy.
It's not an easy thing because it's the
sinner dinner You know, the sinner dinner is
a typical Christian thing.
There's a movie called founder.
It's about the guy who started McDonald's I
really like that film who's the guy who
was in deedle Michael Keaton?
I think Beetlejuice and all that great, right?
He plays a pretty good Ray Kroc.
They try to stay historically, correct And the
whole thing about McDonald's being the name because
everyone else had a name like burger this
burger that right, right?
Sounds very American authoritative and he wanted to
follow the line He saw a painting of
a family in church doing the Pledge of
Allegiance to the flag in church, which is
perfect I mean they that's their God, right?
They have the Right the Patriot the father
God the Patriot Patricia patristic Aspect to it.
Mm-hmm.
They have the the circus the church They
have the American God there and the American
Savior and the Constitution and you know echoes
all of the deification of being an American
Right, you know, that's their cult their tribe
so When you sit down to do dinner
To stop that the prayer there would have
to lead Understanding why and when you understand
why then that all that other American stuff
falls apart.
I mean It's not even like a house
of cards.
It's like smoke.
You just open the window a little and
it all goes away, right?
And this is a very very dangerous ideology
To those, you know the powers that be
the powers that control the what you call
United States of America or France or Canada
or Mexico?
Now on the other hand if you go
to a country like the most Catholic country,
I would suggest this is an opinion But
actually it's vetted by many If you do
research into Christianity, yes, I actually did research
in Christianity a long time ago And everybody
vetted guess what which country in the world
is the most Christian country in the world?
And I'm and don't it's not Italy or
the Vatican.
That's where you'd think Which is the most
Mexico Yes, that's right.
And they're dangerous.
So they even get a little sauce They
had the War of the Crosses for years.
Yes, you know if Protestant they'll kill you
You know, they'll burn your house or they're
you're not allowed and if you go and
study Mexican Christianity It's all based on like
the de los muertos.
They have these very macabre Or you know
angel of death stuff going on.
Oh, yeah Smattered with yeah, it's really all
that, you know, so that's their version.
So if you said that's the most Catholic
in the world Objectively, no, but they say
it is we branded as such that you
could say that Mexican Catholicism is Very radical.
Yes, because you'll have a French Catholic in
Spain Catholicism is very strong also Italy places
like that, but that is Mexican, you know
for Mexican Catholicism versus you know Or Christianity
versus Italian versus French and the dumbest thing
I've ever heard is Christian say well, that's
Catholic That's not Christian.
Oh, that's not real Christianity Right.
Oh boy, you know this stuff that they
make up with You know hit your cross
Yeah, and there is no cross I've spoken
academics that tend to have lucid moments about
studying scripture and message of and I tell
him there's no crucifixion I give him one
like oh, that's absurd.
Well, I know it's absurd to Sleep on
a park bench and eat out of a
garbage can of course, but you know Find
another way to make a living, you know,
yeah You're not going to make a living
doing what you're doing telling the people That
everything they you know, basically the core beliefs
about the gods and the Christ all that
is false You know, they just skirt around
There was an issue.
It was a very lascivious comment What is
when you skirt around instead of going for
full insertion?
But anyway, they can't do they don't yeah,
they don't know how to yeah, so anyway,
uh Yeah Anything else by the way pulling
up?
I don't know we could go different ways
or make it really short We can we
can go however you would wish to make
Greek Hmm.
Let's see.
I was just taking a I have no
desires anymore I have no desires as an
old song was it the public enemy, right?
You got no desires your father was tired
But you know, whatever look enemy number one,
uh, I I I don't know Yeah, go.
I don't want to talk about September 11th.
That's another planet.
I would be interesting And it I would
just just go to Dimitri Kalas of his
Exactly.
I'm just I'm surprised that nobody is celebrating
that man on this day, you know Oh,
no Planet of scum scumbags and now it
is You're not gonna to be in it.
That's the rule now there I didn't say
that it's not possible to not be a
scumbag or an asshole on this planet or
an idiot or more Well, it is possible,
but it's very rare To to achieve that
condition or meet anyone who has you know,
right?
Yeah, yeah, it's it's quite interesting Do the
perspective?
Do the meanings of the Greek alphabet letters?
Or letters alpha have the same meanings is
Hebrew No Yes, and no.
Yeah, they all Gematria, yeah, it clicks in
usually after the fourth or fifth letter it
falls apart, right?
alphabet Right.
Mm-hmm.
I'll affect gamma Dalit right a alpha beta
gamma Delta right ABCD and then after that
they kind of start right Changing Yeah, but
what's more important?
What's never being addressed is as a universal
language that all countries had Around what's called
the Bronze Age?
You'll find it if you look up Minoan
rain Language or they they tell you they
can't Translate that you know as several there's
different types of Greek ancient Greek Wow, and
they'll find similar script everywhere in the world
and I mean everywhere Australia Antarctica China Around
that time period and the reason why they
tell you they can't translate it is because
it's forbidden because that will prove without a
doubt that the whole world was under a
single measurement and Literary system around the time
of let's say after the flood.
Oh And before the Tower of Babel Oh
Do that interesting Mm-hmm something else to
peek into Mm-hmm It's
alright, I think Greek speak is like something
people like to get off on You said
you wanted to correct a few things about
my parchment that I sent you No, that's
fine, no, no, not really.
Oh, okay.
Okay All right.
Look good.
Everything was fine.
Okay, we were just talking about signing the
signing.
Yes.
Yes That's not your signature.
The reason you you know, if someone says
would you like to eat some human feces
you say yes or no?
That's up to you But the typical answer
is no, right?
Why didn't you say?
Yes, because I'm not approving of that, right,
right So if someone produces a Legal document
that's totally self and you know, it's just
an unconscionable thing.
Why would you sign it?
What race would you write white on it?
Yeah, but you don't but you remember these
people The people that you're dealing with are
like robots Right, right.
It's the God see them as that, you
know In other words, how much compassion would
you have for taking a robot and crushing
him into his bare?
Basic material and throwing him into a pile
Nothing, right very little Compassion for that most
foot.
Yes.
That's how people are.
That's how they're being viewed cosmically So that's
what's being sent to you when you start
getting up more into the satanic realm, which
is the attorneys and the administrators They're more
on the the Satanist aspect, you know, which
is like we know what's right, but it
has nothing to do with you So shut
up, right?
But I would admit it Yeah, still you
still it's still void what they're doing is
still void.
Yeah And if you go up to those
that control the entire system that don't make
themselves known They will always always also lie
and hide what they're doing because it's unconscionable
and you void it with them all the
way through You know, do you want to
you see so everything is pretty much should
be voided on its face Now for it
now, she shouldn't be like if you're gonna
deal with a Living being that is honorable
because there is nothing honorable in any of
the controlling situations whether it's medical legal Governmental
religious none of them are honorable.
None of them for sure It might seem
so because that's part of the idea, you
know And they never have been and never
will be that's that's the beauty of the
reality of Seeing the simplicity of things, you
know How simple it is, you know that
and that those are the rules the exceptions
are few And exceptions are show so few
that not being well-versed in the exception
is no fault, you know, you won't Like
in other words if you're looking for a
decent honorable human or man or woman And
you don't know what decent and honorable is
don't worry about it Because even if you
did know you the chances of meeting them
is very rare you see right, so the
The aspect if you're dealing with a decent
horrible human you can get into an agreement
that's written as well, but you do it
Honorably, right, right, but these people are not
herbal.
They never have been it doesn't matter whether
it's communist Russia American capitalism or democracy or
Republic whichever one they wake up in the
morning tell you it is today or some
African tribe You know, they're not honorable either,
you know, you know if you go down
there if they see you're a foreigner They
send someone out, you know, like you have
to give us money before you come here,
you know, right?
To take pictures or whatever, you know And
it's not even it's not even that it's
like they know you're you're scumbag So we're
dealing with scumbags and they tell you they're
at least they're honest in the way.
They'll say this is how we deal with
you Because you've always been known to be
like this it doesn't mean they'll chew they
won't change their ways later It's like once
they get to know you.
Mm-hmm, but it's a rotten system.
It's always been rotten This is nothing new
That's why a lot of these patriotic morons
in any country like oh we have to
go back go back to what you have
no knowledge of history There's nothing to go
back to there's no you can't show me
an exemplary model of human society at all
It's because it's a continuation process, you know
how people say the creation, okay Did it
happen?
Yes.
Is it happening?
Is it going to keep happening?
Yes, it's it's an ongoing process.
What do you mean?
Creationist or evolutionist that either way you go
there.
It's a continual process.
You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm Yeah, so So until this process
continues further a lot of the things that
I bring up we're not going to come
to fruition It has to be far down
the line more You know in terms of
human nature whether you're dealing commercially or legally
or lawfully And by the way lawfulness is
off the table That that is a people
think that legal is law and it's not
right.
That's the law of the subject It's and
legal is based on policy If you research
what's called a sovereign state the definite the
academic definition is three things One is it
has absolute complete control over whatever territory it
states that it's a sovereign state over The
second thing is to maintain order and the
third thing is to provide services Nowhere in
there doesn't say you can vote or elect
or what type it doesn't matter if it's
communist socialist Now some people say well, I
like America because it's capitalist that came from
a communist country.
No, it's the same exact system It's just
that it's both legal systems.
You just didn't like the policies over there
But America is not any more lawful or
less lawful than where you came from.
It's the same.
It's not lawfully based It's just that the
people that happen to be running it that
everyone agrees with is not what you like
the way you want to live You see
presented different Right, it's the same thing.
Mm-hmm And it's the same with all
the religions they have to be in accord
with with you know How you how you're
going to maintain order and provide services for
the people?
These are not things to be debated These
are things not even things to be looked
at with great depth either because the deeper
you look You know the human instinct as
you want to Commune about it or console
about it.
There's no one to talk to about these
things, right?
You could talk at people about it.
They'll stand there.
Yeah.
Yeah, whatever it's you know, they'll try to
discount it or ignore it or want to
change the subject but and Discussing and delving
into the matters of the state of humanity
is not fruitful in many ways because there's
nothing you can do to change It the
best you could do is insulate yourself.
Just like the guy who lived by the
power lines Right, he is planning on moving
but I said, what do you play?
Well, I don't I don't see it So,
you know in 10, you know 10 years,
he still might be there Let's say maybe
right if things are within the order that's
acceptable for people still live in houses by
then.
But but I would suggest that Any any
condition you insulate yourself from it doesn't mean
removing yourself or like a diver goes into
the water He insulates, you know, the neoprene
right the suit insulates you from the water
and all that, right, right so There's nowhere
to go now anyway, there hasn't been for
a long time, you know moving around different
locations, right?
Other than just maybe being in a constant
state of movement is another possible Bring, you
know, he's always traveling in RVs and things,
you know, maybe maybe I don't see that
as being viable but Because the problems are
spiritual and cosmic Just like this Hurricane that's
coming to the Atlantic right now.
That is not a hurricane people looking at
the wind and all this others that's a
imposition of a of a vortex in space
on the earth It goes up very very
high and it it changes geometric form.
It kind of looks like tulips You know
like so if you go beyond if you
look at the hurricane right now It looks
like a tulip and put in profile right
gets wide in the middle narrow at the
top narrow at the bottom Right, then we
go up to the atmosphere.
There's nothing there but beyond the atmosphere again
It appears this massive field and you could
you know years ago NASA had infrared imagery
of the sky and all that and you
could see it when it was a hurricane
They try to shoot down those visible light
But when they use infrared or ultraviolet you
see this big storm over the storm out
in space Wow Yeah, and this is not
that you know, it's like none of your
business because I can't explain it Oh, it's
probably something along with the lens, right?
right so So congratulations you guys on the
East Coast Tomorrow maybe you'll steer it around
depending how I feel I Don't they see
when they say it's going to go north
you just bring it south, right?
Right, and then when they say it's going
south and you bring it another way speed
it up slow it down make it stop
Yeah, make them a little crazy.
But unfortunately, this is downwind of me.
In other words, it's east So it's on
on the it's upwind of the flow downwind
of the flow and it's difficult to control
without It's quite an elaborate operation.
I have to aim West To start manipulating
the jet streams that are behind me But
I have to manipulate them and block them
in the way that I don't diminish them
too much So then they flare up later
and then they interfere with the hurricane.
So it's very it's kind of cocky We
could get into it very basically the flows
of northern Hemisphere go from west to east
so this hurricane has ramped off just like
that almost looks like a The equator being
a highway and you have an exit ramp
that goes off the highway That's what this
hurricane looks like it did because this hurricane,
you know The equator goes from east to
west and it takes this exit ramp off,
right?
Right, and it's but still moving east to
west against the flow So simply aiming and
doing certain basic one-on-one protocols is
not going to do much of an effect
On it.
Actually the easiest thing to do is to
beef it up That's really easy.
You could to bring that up to a
category 5 by the way Pop a link
into the channel.
I have a rather interesting website reader that
I like using.
Oh good so They're saying it'll make landfall
the next few days right now The jet
streams that are haven't even come to the
west coast of America are making their ways
across And they're going to either contribute or
diminish Right.
So those need to be addressed You know
before they get there and then the hurricane
itself needs to be addressed from below Which
if we were to start messing with it,
there'd probably be earthquakes in places like, Georgia
and Oklahoma Because we have to go through
the earth That will excite the ether the
earth, you know I think we've described there
vaguely indirectly that you can make the ground
shake with the same Equipment you use to
affect the weather the So we can make
the ground shake and Divert this thing around
or make it go away or whatever for
what?
You know when you've done this over a
hundred times and you know, what's going you
know, and you know The F it has
an efficacy rate of 90% Success, you
don't do it anymore.
You know, it's just like you're a retired
NFL you retired NBA now, you know You
don't play, you know, you don't need to
do it anymore, right?
You can move on to the stick Yeah,
I put that on Rams lighter Satellite in
there, which is a rather nice satellite.
I gotta say Yeah Okay, good.
Yeah, they've changed it around unisys has been
changed.
Mm-hmm Expressed and all this those have
been changed Less information harder to harder to
manipulate in terms of you know vantage points
and cycles, you know I mean, I was
gonna dig around in there.
That's for sure And they've changed the way
the maps look also the proportions.
Yes country had looked different now.
Mm-hmm But I see what you mean
about your your steering oh I haven't done
anything and I'm probably not There's no reason
to study it they're actually if it's not
tamp with If it's not tamper with it's
gonna do what the forecasters say.
They're pretty accurate, right?
Based on their materialistic sense.
Mm-hmm, you know, it's based on you
know statistics what it's things have done before
they you know Ensemble models, but if I
start messing with it, they're gonna say we
don't know what way hurricanes do this, you
know But you know and when it gets
real extremely just ignore it, you know, yeah
I'm tempted to play around with it You
know But here's the thing Years ago working
with someone they introduced some people to us
as could we explain weather work this and
you know If we explain it to them,
they're too anxious Right, and all they're gonna
do is create weather disasters Mm-hmm not
to mention his name by you know, Harry,
but anyway, right so All they do now
is create disasters ever since these guys came
online.
All you hear about is India Monsoons and
Japan this and this is just really bad
disasters when I was just doing it was
just a few people There was no bad
weather for like five years or like where'd
all the hurricanes go or when they'd appear?
It's like they disappear.
Like how did that happen?
Mm-hmm No Mm-hmm You guys are
you're on your own now But here's the
other the reason I brought up the guys
messing up the weather now as also many
other groups are You know with even more
power behind them would which are not that
smart But you know the easiest thing to
do let's say I started tinkering around with
it right right now The first thing you
notice if it's a cat for it's gonna
go to a cat five.
It'll just get inflamed It's kind of like,
you know, you've got a sore on your
knee and someone starts examining it You know
after you've settled in on the pain, they're
like, ah, that really hurts.
You just get worse.
Yeah Yeah, so you have a little excitement
Yeah, anything anyone does well, actually most of
the people that think they know what they're
doing don't know fortunately or unfortunately Either way
actually if they knew what they were doing
They'd stop and want to learn a little
bit more before they did what they were
doing But my point here is that If
yeah, it's very here's the point an amateur
weather person actually the one who understands how
the ether works is going to be very
disappointed if initially without guidance because let's say
they have the intent of Diminishing that hurricane
they won't it's going to just flare it
up.
It doesn't mean all is lost Even if
I start playing with it now, it'll probably
flare up to a higher category for a
short time Mm-hmm.
That's just what the it's just what it
does.
Anything does that, you know go poke around
on a living thing What does it do?
It moves more, right?
So Yeah, but the way to take this
out is very simple start manipulating all the
fields and the way of a Jet streams
that are not even across the u.s
But get them out of the way, so
you don't have any interference You got to
go deep underground below the hurricane which is
going to shake anything in line That where
you're shooting and also you have to go
at the hurricane and above it In line
below in line above it, but when you
go when you aim at the hurricane do
not aim at the center That's not what
defines a hurricane The definition of a hurricane
are basically the rotating arms Right, so what
you want to do is diminish one of
the rotating arms and it goes off balance
and it just becomes a storm So the
eye will still be there, but it won't
act this one Actually a long years ago.
I knew someone in New Orleans and they
were starting to evacuate Cheverstown or someplace, you
know, it's like outside of New Orleans.
Mm-hmm, and there was a in the
National Guard came in ready to tell 25
,000 people to evacuate and Person got in
touch.
We could do something about that and I
said sure well, we totally cleared it out
and The eye was still visible.
It was sunny weather not no wind no
clouds But the eye was still visible in
infrared because that's like the the counter space
part, right?
But there was no storm.
There was no wind So most the amateurs
would go for the eye They go, but
if you take out one of the arms
of the hurricane, it could no longer be
defined as a hurricane, right?
So that's what you do you aim for
that and then once you take out one
of the arms Actually, you just take out
about half or 30% of it It
starts to fall apart very quickly loses symmetry
Kind of like if you took out a
big chunk of your car wheel, right?
It'll lose symmetry very quickly the whole tire
peels off right and actually that's what happens
when you take off one of the arms
You'll see a radical spreading out of the
other arm.
It loses its concentrated geometric form It spreads
out really over a large area and then
you just go after that as a regular
storm You just take pieces out of it
You know and then you put a block
over the area that you want to protect
and then the people, you know Are told
evacuating they go out the next day.
There's not a cloud in the sky, you
know, you know what happened?
And then the weather engineer the weather Meteorologist
say well, we need a better computer model,
you know Yeah, so I I Mean, you
know, there's this technicalities like to do a
weather op like that Which is more than
4,000 miles away or 5,000 kilometers
away would take at least a few hours
of planning half a day of assembling Various
sets of tubes and grounding devices and then
you have to man it for about 30
hours.
I mean constantly Constantly adjusting.
Yeah.
Yeah So yeah It's exciting.
I mean you could hear I'm talking about
it like it.
I just want to do it, right?
Yeah, I'm not gonna do it.
No for what?
No, you know They're ridiculous they could have
their sinner dinners instead But nonetheless I'm gonna
make this turn off the AC and Make
a cup of coffee and go into the
office or if there's anything else Haven't had
much on the emails.
I have to check that again just This
week.
I've had a four-hour conversation with a
surgeon 30 years surgery And we was all
technical stuff regarding.
Well, not all technical mostly regarding Procedures and
cases and mm-hmm things like that in
the in the surgeon was admitting that yes
now I see When I consider the vacuum
Like for example if part of the head
is removed You know the skull to get
into the brain Mm-hmm And if you
don't put the material back the skull back
because you're due to possible infection simply at
times that they don't do it You'll see
a tremendous amount of suction Forming and that's
how you know, it's healing right, you know
various devices now that are talking about creating
suction also the ineptitude of the administration Person
also admitted very heavily On what we've discussed
maybe loosely on the new order of barbarians
1968 the medical system you changed like what
they call Obamacare a lot of doctors don't
want to practice anymore that that was already
Just a new order of barbarians where he
talks about how doctors will behave.
That was a plan back then Right, basically
picking them technicians and you know decreasing services
because they want you dead basically, you know
This is another thing I haven't really gone
I've been looking at it but the a
1 number 1 a 1 priority of any
government a Sovereign state in the world right
now military is how to get a condition
where the military it kills its own people
You know, you want to put that whatever
phrase you want you heard?
So in other words the American government's number
1 a 1 priority is how are they
going to create an environment where the?
American military can start killing Americans the same
for Canada the same for French the same
for Iraq the same for Russia all of
them Because the the owners of the countries
that's what they want They want to start
eliminating the populations of the earth It doesn't
matter if it's with food water military, you
know military is the best and easiest because
you can control it Now the interesting thing
is it has to be simultaneous if American
military was convinced and they agreed start killing
Americans Well, the people in Canada might say
oh Why aren't we doing anything about it?
Let's go help them.
Right, right So, you know or right so
and they could they could try to keep
it secret or whatever But it'll get out
and it might cause friction.
So you have to have all the countries
doing it at the same time Right.
So, you know like the Iraqi military started
eliminating all the Iraqis You know, so what's
going on here, you know, they they pulled
off something very similar to that in Libya
But they couldn't really keep it going, you
know, don't believe anything in Libya Libya was
complete farce what's been put out there?
That was that country was on the up
and up and it was destroyed by NATO
the national was it the North Atlantic terrorist
organization?
So I'm not speaking out against any sovereign
state United States Canada Iraq or this is
just they have no They have no say
in what I'm telling you, this is what
the their owners are Doing it's kind of
like something.
Yes.
I'm saying this Cadillac, you know ended up
in the lake It's not because the Cadillac
wanted it.
It's the guy who was driving it drove
it into the lake, right?
Right, you look far doesn't you know, the
the government and the the apparatus administration is
the app is just that it has no
say You know, it's the owners of the
of the apparatus that have to say and
there's number one Priority is to do what
I just mentioned by the way, and but
they that they understand they're not stupid They
understand it has to be done on a
simultaneous fashion at least within a region Like
they could probably successfully get the Canadian military
to kill Canadians American military to kill Americans
Mexican Military to kill Mexicans all the way
down the south this whole hemisphere.
They could probably get away with that Right
because where are they gonna run to right
and also they contain it, you know Europe
they could probably get away with it.
Also, maybe Yeah, but because remember Europe is
really Western Asia when you think about it.
What it's Northwestern Asia Mm-hmm.
So Asia's, you know the center of the
world, you know, you got East West North
South Asia right in Africa, right?
You could probably get away with it on
the what's called the African continent.
So this is what I'm say probably So,
you know look out for these things.
This is the the agenda, you know, that's
the number one a one priority on the
list So when you start looking at, you
know, there is no money they talk about
economy They don't know anything about health to
talk about diseases So, you know, I mean
this is that's that's all stuff to keep
you busy and by time.
Well, you know I'm sorry about you know,
what's scary about day is Everything that they've
mentioned way back then has been put into
place and it's been going smoothly Very well,
I think I'm a little behind.
I think if you listen to the Areas,
yes about 20 years behind slow.
Mm-hmm Yeah, intentionally, I would think yeah,
but here's the ultimately the gods Yes, well
most 95% of the earth's population be
wiped out very violently.
Absolutely without a doubt positively Yes, take that
to the bank if you don't know that
You're stupid But who is it if you're
okay, so that's done Don't even think about
it because that's that's gonna come like the
Sun's gonna rise tomorrow The thing to think
about is this really is that mankind the
people that are behind the scenes that really
want this are Not going to get the
satisfaction The gods are gonna do it That's
all that's all that taught that that topic
is closed, you know, I mean, mm-hmm
Yeah, mm-hmm And
if the gods are gonna do it and
you have no control I don't think it's
a morbid or negative topic You know Right.
I mean remember these are these are the
guys that made the whales and the birds
and the cheetahs and the roaches and the
planet it's your Sentiment feeling emotion desires are
out of the are irrelevant So It's it's
not to be viewed as a bad thing
because there's at that point it's transcended good
and bad And if you really want to
get into the touchy-feely aspects of why
it's gonna happen Is it you know, like
it's not deserved possibly hell.
No, it's fully deserved.
It's completely deserved and that's obvious so And
if you don't think it's deserved, you're not
paying any attention All right, so dy I
got a bunch of emails here Starting early.
Okay.
Let's see.
I Just comments.
Yeah, okay much out just the basic stuff
that you learn about when you're on the
internet, but Yeah, I'm not gonna read some
of this pretty I thought I was lascivious
this pretty little serious but okay I wouldn't
say there's much there other than the stuff
I brought up.
Mm-hmm.
I See, okay Anything else?
Let me go back and chat.
I just answered to custodian Hey, I put
up a biggie mix that I did a
while back.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, great.
I call it So it's a beat thing.
I think it's better than the music that
they use Yeah, and I brought up, you
know the Christians, you know, they have this
fake morality You ever you ever been around
them and say hell?
Oh, you just said oh, that's a bad
word Yeah, I mean while you know, they're
involved in the most abominable stuff, you know
Spiritually you can imagine.
Mm-hmm.
Now.
Here's the thing that people don't realize They
haven't studied but I'll break it to you
Okay, when you read about headhunting societies or
you know The Canaanites or the Giants or
you know, anyway, they did these horrendous things,
you know Like sex with animals and then,
you know while they were killing the animal
or eating killing children You know with Moloch
or Murdoch or all these things, you know
when they were doing all these things Marduk,
you know In Babylonian societies you read about
all the you know, like don't do this
like they did, you know Like they eat
their children don't offer them in the fire,
you know all this stuff Do you think
that this was viewed as a horror film?
It was viewed as the most pleasant thing.
It was a wonderful thing You can do
You know, it's the same thing like you
go down the street and And you see
people Oh Christmas, isn't it beautiful when they
were offering children and doing cannibalism?
Isn't that beautiful?
You see great.
It was not a nightmarish scenario Now obviously
just like we were started off discussing certain
prejudicial Stereotypes that are accurate because of the
culture It did look if because you're let's
say coming from this century or this culture
what you are used to If you were
to see it, it would be probably nightmarish
to you Right, right, it would be very
unpleasant to most people today Right, but you
know, you know, but to the people there
it was very pleasant.
Now.
Here's the other aspect of it What what
makes it worse now is that it's all
been changed to be modified so it is
pleasant You're still doing it the intent of
those things the cannibalism the child sacrifice So
but it's it's you know, the birthday party
the Christmas the church all these things are
Modified to your cultural liking your cultural acceptance
It's the same stuff and it's done in
parody You may not go to church and
see that it has to do with an
offering to ball or whatever Because you don't
you're not aware of the fine points of
the birthday celebration or the dolls Or you
know Lord, you know all this other stuff.
They they yeah, so it's a parody Which
in many cases is much worse Because if
you ask the people that were doing the
real thing, oh openly, what are you doing?
They can give you a pretty succinct Accurate
clear description and explanation, but now if you
ask someone why do you do a birthday
party?
Why do you go to church?
They don't know everything that comes out of
the mouse is false.
It's just you know, the opposite of what
they think So that's why it's much easier
to continue it now because right now the
way the situation goes with what humans celebrate
You won't find a contrasting Culture to let's
say counter it or battle it or show
a contrast Because no matter what culture you
have on the earth and say, oh, look
how happy and pleasant it is Look, the
child is being taken care of.
Look how wonderful these things are Aesthetically see
even back then Even though within the Canaanite
culture certain cultures when they did human sacrifice
openly and it was pleasant to them You
see it was possible to have a contrasting
culture come in and say this is horrible
And they're not going to change this either
you change or you got to go and
they obviously chose the latter, right?
So but now because of the homogenous there
is very little Contrast to it, you know
Which is actually yeah.
Yeah global It's alright screw Mm-hmm Ain't
much a much here man.
You were chosen if you're born here.
Let's say you're alive on the earth right
now Just make the best of it every
day every minute or whatever, but don't get
involved in anything That's too altruistic because it's
just gonna fall flat on your face Altruism
means, you know make the world a better
place how to make things better and a
general sense, you know.
Mm-hmm Ain't gonna happen Now Of course
You're going to be given the visage of
it happening, you know the image or the
idea Which is part of the new order
in the Middle East, you know when that
starts coming together Oh, yeah, you'll be promised
all this stuff and it'll come to a
certain degree.
Yeah, you'll all you'll all buy it So
but that that doesn't mean that it's that
it's more than skin-deep other than When
it comes down to the application of law
Obviously if you study you will see that
There is a I would say a revival
but an application of biblical law throughout the
entire planet at that time So and it's
going to be used in a very harsh
way.
Yeah, that's just how the things are done
So it on the part of the side
of the world that matters, which is the
Northern Hemisphere The it's fall going into winter
so this is a breaking down time So
we finished a growing season see what's being
harvested One of the things that an email
I was going down a list last week
and sort of a tirade Before we got
cut off on the internet, right?
What's going on where it's quiet.
I think I remember what was one of
the questions Well, that's where the real stuff
is.
You've heard me say where it's really quiet
So, you know you can actually divide one's
perception So one's perception would be everything you
could see here in terms of this kind
of information Immediately you divide your perception.
Where is it noisy?
Okay, what's noisy?
Right.
Well here let's say Syria Iraq, you know,
Russia America.
That's okay But you put all the noisy
stuff aside now You see all the things
that you can perceive where there's no talk
about and that's where the real stuff is
happening you see So now there's more to
investigate right because usually the stuff that's noisy
is poignant and small and limited but the
stuff that is Quiet is much more vast
and open.
Okay, so then the efficiency aspect comes in.
What do you know about what's quiet?
And that's how you begin to study All
right, so let's say there's let's say take
grab something there's no discussion about pandemics and
the medical industry right now All right.
No one's really crying Obamacare.
No one's crying pandemic.
Really?
No one's correct Okay So now's a good
time to start assessing what is the medical
community up to?
Because they're do they're up to some bad
shit right now if there's nothing in the
news Right there what they're doing now, you'll
see later, you know the project Right.
Okay So, let's say you see the petrochemical
industry what's going and then is no no,
okay, that means that they're working on shit
They're up to some bad shit and you're
gonna see it later.
You see how it works.
Mm-hmm So, where is it really quiet,
you know Hmm It doesn't have to be
industry.
It could be cultural also, right?
Alright, you know like for example in America,
there's like the race thing that's been going
on for a past decade or less So
right now American blacks are you know, not
in the news, right?
Well, guess what?
They're getting ready to do something By springtime,
you'll see the American black issue again, right
or something Right.
Yeah, all these things in basically you divide
your perception It's very simple humans are not
that complicated they're quite stupid And they're and
whatever they involved in their institutions their culture
their society Their authoritative figures their their scientists
their leaders.
I mean, they're they're not from other planets
They come from themselves.
And then of course you have the background
leadership, right?
Right the owners the people have been pulling
the oligarchs Let's say people have been pulling
the course of events through the gods, by
the way for thousands of years, those are
the ones that are you know working the
the The human aspect of the power base,
but essentially the the main power base is
the residing presiding gods over each nation That's
the main power base and then you have
of course Interactions and things going on on
their side and those that they influence See
in order to get a military to do
something You don't have to go to each
soldier.
All you need to do is go to
the general and have him give the command
Yeah, so the oligarchs ruling that are the
owners of what you call the states and
all that of various governments and various countries
The gods influence them Then they influence their
puppets which are the president's Kings ministers and
all that.
Yeah, right And then they gets to you.
It's very simple and Of course, there was
a change thousands of years ago if not
less You could see anyone who studies history
Will see the Nepal Napoleonic Wars were profound
change in world The way things are done
in the world in terms of you know,
bureaucracy administrative government all that Napoleonic Wars changed
everything where no more If we want to
rule shit, we're not coming forward anymore.
We're gonna stay in the back Right now
we know who they're their financial people are
the Rothschild's the Morgans the Rockefellers the Zeeves
The Sipes, you know, we know the Habsburgs
we know those there we know who their
financial people are We don't know who their
spiritual people are You know one can say
this comes like before like Freemasons or Illuminati.
Yeah, I don't know if you know any
Freemasons They're not very smart You know, there
might be some smart people in Freemasonry.
But what do you see Freemasonry?
They're just as dumb as everyone else at
this point.
That's just what's put out for public consumption
Illuminati and Freemasons Yes, that is a gateway
Into that realm, but we don't know who
the priesthood is We know who again with
our economic brokers are the Rothschild's Rockefellers and
all that Morgans on and on and on
we know they're brought we we don't know
who their priesthood is We don't really know
their techno who their technology, you know implementers
are which should be you know, the technology
people We don't know them either and they're
we can kind of verse Yeah, you can
kind of guess military industrial complex, you know
DARPA No big military contractors, but yeah on
the surface again for public consumption You know,
it's easy to see the food people the
food who they put in front of measure
that the DuPont Monsanto, right?
Sure, Daniel Midlands is another one, right?
So those are names that people know in
the Midwest really well So Yeah, it's just
a conglomerate of each industry has its own
setting of Power base, but remember if it's
if it's visible, it's for public consumption You
know, it's not it's usually not true Just
like they call September 11th How many people
are like well, you know, here's the thing
at least it's on a Tuesday this year
It took about 17 years to make it
back to a Tuesday.
Yeah, what happened on a Tuesday before what
a bunch of morons Someone I saw a
comment one saying.
Oh, yeah All those comments about 9-11
is crass to the 3,000 people that
died.
I'm like what a moron It's kind of
like, you know the medical Establishment killed 3
,000 people yesterday and 3,000 the way
before and they killed 3,000 today and
they're gonna kill 3,000 tomorrow Get your
head out your ass Anyway It kind of
reminds me of the comments that I've seen.
Oh this Greek guy He makes comments about
older people wait till he gets older and
someone right he is older.
He's in his 50s, right?
Oh, you know and I was like, oh,
thanks for demonstrating that how worthless the older
people you just demonstrated it All you do
is cry and bitch and nothing to say
It's crazy.
Yeah, in other words, you're gonna see the
demonstration of stupidity You know someone needs to
get together that these sites do exist a
an atomic nuclear atomic nuclear whatever Website facts,
you know where you start out with Madame
Curie Madame Curie and you move all the
way down the line show Manhattan downtown Manhattan
show, you know the bombing in Beirut show,
you know as being nuclear, you know show
Bali bombing show You know all the bombings
all over the world that many notes show
the different sizes, you know You could sort
of the czar bomb which is what three
megaton in Russia and show all the nuclear
tests underground You know, here's a good example
for September 11 You know people look at
the spikes or squiffs or whatever.
They call them shooting out of the building
windows Okay, if you go to any underground
go to YouTube and put in underground atomic
bomb or underground nuclear explosion and they'll show
them to you and Once you get to
zero time at ground zero You see the
earth sink down and you see lots of
little puffs of clouds everywhere on the surface
Now if you weren't showing anyone that that
if you weren't telling anyone you just showed
someone a shot of that What do you
see I say, oh I see lots of
explosives going off on the surface wrong That's
one Explosion going on underground and it's showing
up as many little plumes and clouds on
the street You see you get the picture
looks like a head of Brock spread out
Great, right?
Yeah, it doesn't look like one mushroom got
so people don't it's all those scripts and
things that you see There's a couple of
good 9-11 videos on the sidewalk when
the buildings are coming down There's a manhole
cover that blasts up and a jet stream
goes up about 10-15 stories of like
just as incredibly super hot Super gaseous, you
know cesium gas whatever radioactive for molten stone
shoot up out of the ground in places
around You know the Federal Reserve building and
other buildings that are about a half a
mile south Let's see north or southeast the
World Trade Center their foundations cracked The stones
that they used in those buildings all prior
Prior to the buildings coming down there used
to be some articles on the internet about
that and how they had to repair the
downtown Wall Street area foundations that were cracked
and they all cracked before The buildings fell
down from the actual expansion of the granite
You know, which is deep underground, right?
And that's all been covered You know I
remember five six years ago before 2011 seeing
that the concern I forgot the name of
the construction company did the restoration on the
building They had to do what's called epoxy
consolidation You know where you actually, you know
put an epoxy in the crack but it
has to be you know able to expand
strong enough to hold the stone together like
stone would but also Expanding contract without separating.
So that was the article and it was
led me to oh Yeah on September 11
and it turns out that everything those buildings
that did have damaged it happened prior to
the buildings collapsing So, you know if you
only had a window of 10 seconds, but
right on the rice So anyway, who are
you gonna go to?
I mean, this is like basic stuff.
You know, this is nothing regarding theory or
opinion or Whatever.
Mm-hmm snap this planet Earth man.
I was out in public yesterday and some
guy was complaining I said chill man.
It's planet Earth.
He started laughing.
He says yeah, he kind of got it
But he went back to shit right away,
you know All right, I don't know if
there's anything else I don't see nothing here
Greek no Anything else we need to bring
up or I mean usually Sonic unless or
something, you know, right I but Personally at
this moment don't Yeah, that's fine.
Keep our personal stuff personal right either way.
Sure Yeah, I think these Sonics are just
I think it's good to do them every
week if possible You know repetition and wrote
There's lots of stuff to talk about I
mean there's stuff to get into and then
you know It has to do with perspective
mindset and you know, are you using your
faculties?
You know, are you blind is your mind
blinded or is it just your eyes that
are blinded?
Right, right?
so The getting over the mental paralysis, you
know the emotional paralysis You know So yeah,
that's simple.
You know that it's basically The Greek speak
stuff is like a form of therapy You
know to get you moving like someone who's
a paraplegic who hasn't moved their limbs.
They get sores, right?
So if you just you just got to
move even though you can't move them on
your own at least they're being moved, you
know mm-hmm, so It'll work out oh
Yeah, it's gonna be great later on post
-resurrection Unfortunately, most people you know, you're gonna
have to be killed first before you realize
it.
Mm-hmm You know, even those that are
for example considered the elect and are chosen
And nowhere does it say that their behavior
deems them to be so they're chosen to
be that Right, so it's not meritorious Right
in some cases it is meritorious.
There is something that still needs to be
looked at.
You know the 144,000 But it doesn't
seem itself.
It doesn't deem strictly meritorium They're chosen and
it says that they haven't defiled themselves with
women as their virgins that I don't think
that's an accurate translation I think when you're
chosen To be part of the elect it
doesn't seem to be meritorious because we remember
Nebuchadnezzar was chosen, you know, he's here's a
guy that you know, a piece, you know,
I'm presuming, you know Because this is what
their thing was so It's gonna be interesting.
But even if you're part of the elect
you still have to be killed first you'll
be experiencing the resurrection instantly, you know be
standing around picking your nose or whatever and
You'll be killed and resurrected instantly and you
know, so you still in other words, there's
no passage to Truth righteousness knowledge or what
they call the Christians call holiness or all
that in this life You have to be
snuffed out and brought back to achieve that
so It's quite interesting concept there.
So anyone who tries to achieve that on
that celestial or cosmic level?
I assure you you won't you know, the
New Agers or you know, they talk about
their ascended masters and all that crap You'll
as a demons, you know All right, the
Gnostics also, you know, it's a various old
demonology So, you know again, we brought up
the Freemasons if you look into demonology whether
it's you know, the public consumption stuff that's
put out by the Crowley's or the The
the more cloaked stuff that the Gnostics put
out or whatever, you know on and on
a lot of the Eastern demonology You know
that on the surface it could be branded
as such people say, oh, that's bad, right?
Oh, it is, you know, like a harsh,
but when you actually investigate it, it's try
it fills one's minds with pleasantries, right?
It goes on and on and on about
you know Those that partake are endowed with
special, you know purpose and power and it
goes on, you know So even the most
manipulative malevolent spirit will present works To its
victims or its its subjects that are pleasant
to the victims or the subjects, you know,
right?
I'm not talking It's beyond the calling card
the content Delivers, let's say the sentiment and
emotion and feeling to those involved that they're
doing the right thing Right, you know, for
example, you'll never find a religious cult Christianity
Judaism on and on and on Buddhism that
their followers don't think they're not doing the
right thing go run into like with these
you ever see The real furry Jews in
New York or in Jerusalem.
I'm furry Jews, you know, the Hasidim, right?
How ridiculous is that?
You know, I mean, but nonetheless if you
go deal with them on a personal level
I mean the personal meaning on it on
their faith base.
They really think they're doing the right thing,
right?
Right Freemasons in the Memphis rites of Mitzrayim,
which is probably one of the darkest deepest
They probably engage in more human sacrifice than
the other Freemasons.
They think they're doing the right thing, you
know Mm-hmm.
You see what I mean, right?
So if everyone thinks they're doing the right
thing and they're all contrasting who's doing the
right thing Oh, they all can't be doing
the right thing.
Yeah, you know all say so contrasting you
see so It so anyway, yeah, this is
this is part of the human again, I
have a Someone that I've known have moved
up to the Mount Shasta.
He's Runs a I don't want get into
what he does He's business quite successfully in
the New Age stuff and him and someone
else a few weeks ago similar New Agey
They all say the same thing.
Oh, well you do love will fix that
love is like oh shit You don't even
know what love is.
Oh boy that now we're talking snake oil
stuff, you know So don't buy into that
by the way They again you ever see
the Jack fresco love is bullshit the way
most people find love I think I've been
talking about it before I discovered fresco, but
What people call love is something that accommodates
them or something that fulfills their requirements or
needs Once that stops doing that they no
longer love it right like ask a wedding
couple on their night.
Are you in love?
Yes, ask them the same thing on their
divorce No, because they're no longer meeting each
other's needs that's not what love is at
all Love is doing the right thing even
if it inconveniences you See, they don't know
and they never will it's too late by
the way on a social cultural level for
people to acquire wholesome righteous things It doesn't
mean that they won't be made aware of
them in the near future So they admit
that this is right, but doesn't mean they're
gonna do it, right?
All right Because otherwise you can't take them
out lawfully, right?
Correct.
Yeah, the gods will cannot take out a
society without them being aware why they're taking
it Whether they agree with or not, they
have to acknowledge This is why they're being
you know, just like what they read the
rights to someone you're being arrested for this
or even on a firing Squad, they'll read
you again while they're shooting you, you know
all over again Mm-hmm.
So there you go and Again I want
to I don't want to stress this but
let me just bring this up in closing.
It's the seventh month folks right, I Don't
know should I say it again?
It's the seventh month.
Right?
Does that mean that what it means to
you?
Because that's irrelevant.
What does it really mean?
Can you objectify?
what harvest in gathering the end of The
year by the way, this past year is
marked now not when it started right?
It's marked the end.
Mm-hmm, right?
Just like when you're pumping gas You know
how much you don't know how much gas
you put it in until you put you
the pump shuts off and you retract the
Nozzle, right, right?
Otherwise, you'll just be flapping your lips at
five gallon six gallon seven gap Well, why
don't you just when you pull the nozzle
out, you know, there's no more pumping of
gas Now you could look at the meter
and say well I put in 16.2
gallons done So what the seventh month comes
you're done with the year, right?
So So, what does that mean not what
you think it means or whether you care
find out what Harvest time means what in
gathering means or the end of the year?
What does that really mean the pagans got
their own rituals, but it still ties in
they make resolutions, don't they?
Mm-hmm, you know stuff So, yes, they
do breaking down time And if nothing much
is breaking down, it just means that it's
it's not noisy So, we'll see Mm-hmm
still got and remember these periods are ongoing
So for example when the harvest comes the
seventh month in the breaking down the in
gathering seasonally It doesn't mean that it happens
within that season it that breaking down period
starts and it keeps going through winter, which
is like Typically a time period that's set
for doing things that you can't do during
the other seasons or what shouldn't do Right,
and it might even go into the springtime
and carry over so they constantly overlap like
fish scales You know or they you see
so even though this is a breaking down
period It still culminates with the building up
period that passed this spring Which culminates also,
you know at with the the previous years
breaking down period so these periods It's like
a sinusoidal, you know, it's still have that
zero the the line that goes through the
how do you determine frequency?
It doesn't matter how far down line you
go.
You still see how it's operating.
So right Yeah, there's a resonance Right and
it moves backwards too, right?
All right.
Yes, I don't see much else Got quite
about six or seven emails just basic questions.
I think I've brought up most of this
stuff before they're basically just comments So That'll
be it for now, okay, and Yeah so
until and if they make if they by
the way, if you look at the Mockumentaries
or whatever they're doing because it is September.
I'll just remember doctors killed 3,000 people
yesterday They killed 3,000 today and they're
gonna kill 3,000 tomorrow So that kind
of makes what they're they always by the
way memorialize it canonized their victims So you
want to fall for whatever?
National holiday you do what you find fit
What you've seen pleasing also, but to me
it's not pleasing at all.
No, the hypocrisy is yeah Okay, I mean
Okay, great.
Yeah.
Well, thank you very much.
Thanks.
Okay.
You take care now.
Bye.
Bye The
place I will