Here we go, I'm going to pop us
on in right now.
We had a little bit of that they're
going Hello folks and we're online with Greek.
Good evening, everyone.
Yeah, greetings.
We might have some interruptions, so I might
if I do I'll just let you know
I'll be right back so at least for
the next hour I'm not sure.
So, yeah, okay, well Sam's off tonight and
we're going to be doing a little bit
of a sonic semi solo because Bruce you're
just the producer right just the producer right
well I'm not a producer who doesn't mind
chiming in once in a great while.
Silly as that would be.
Yeah yeah yeah no so what I'm saying
is, you shouldn't have to do everything so
I don't mind.
That's good.
All good.
Why don't we.
Any questions anybody got anything to ask and
chat before I came out I'm outside right
now.
Greetings folk I'm currently in Tunisia.
Something about the moon.
Does Greek still suspect the 13th moon or
month, and interested in intercalation.
Yeah, it's possible, it looks that way only
because the moon has not been showing up
as it normally does it shows up more
now as it would when you're going to
have a 13th moon.
Now I've been kind of absent minded about
statements I've made about when the last one
was apparently it was last year, and then
it was not the one before but the
one before last.
So to have.
It doesn't say anywhere that there can't be
an ancient records two in a row.
I've never seen two in a row.
You know that that's 13 month moons.
So we'll just have to wait and see.
I remember.
Fortunately when I started getting into this around,
oh 203 or 405 that was pretty steady.
In terms of the way we're very predictable
and then things started getting a little shaky,
and then they stable stabilize and they got
really shaky.
Again, and now they're sort of stable.
In terms of the way appearances are what
I mean by that is if you photographed,
let's say, or recorded what the fourth moon
of a certain year was.
It's generally the, you know, the same just
like the pagans do they say they have
a wolf moon or a harvest moon or
whatever moon, you know the hunters moon you
know they have names for the.
It's by the way they appear, you know,
they don't know they don't know what they're
doing but they do have enough.
Let's say discernment to know that this looks
like this type of moon they don't know
what to do with it anymore.
So, yeah, so it's kind of something that's
basically, no matter what you think or do,
it's going to be observational anyway.
So we'll see.
Based on when the time comes.
So, still there Bruce?
Yes.
Now the the moon right now lined up
very neatly with the Sabbath.
Very neatly in the middle of the month.
So, I've got about the 16th day of
the 11th month.
Now is that still lining up with the
Sabbath.
Well, yeah, it always does.
Okay.
Because at one time, what was it last
Sabbath or maybe the one before was a
little off you mentioned and I thought so
also.
Well, it tightens up towards the end or
the beginning and or the middle.
Yeah.
But I haven't noticed, sometimes it would be
a day or two off a few years
ago and it's tightened up again, which is
to be expected.
By the way, this is a, it's been
written about the moon will, these astronomical bodies
are going to err in their ways.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
But overall, in terms of astronomical timekeeping, just
in a nutshell, the, the, well, let's just
call them the scientists and the astronomical community
does acknowledge astronomical time, where the day starts
at solar noon and the moon rules the
month.
But they don't know how to measure the
moon, because they're schizophrenic, meaning.
If you look at academic circles, they tell
you solar noon is when the day starts,
but when they start reckoning moon measurements, they
reckon it with, with civil midnight with the
clock.
That's why if you look up, still the
majority of people on the planet, when you
told them a lunar month, tell them a
lunar month, they think it's 28 days.
Or 28 and a half or 29 or
something, because it's 28.874, whatever.
Yeah.
You know, they, because they're schizophrenic.
It's very simple.
It's like, which, which one of them are
you talking to?
You know, which personality are you talking to
when you bring up a thing, you know,
like, bring up the sun and bring up
that thing, you know, so yeah.
For scientific and astronomical purposes, solar noon and
you bring up the month.
Yeah, that's the moon.
But the moon only got 28 days.
Well, how you just finished saying the day
starts at noon.
How can you have 28 days if, oh,
because you see, we measure the day with
midnight.
You just finished telling me.
You see my point?
They're completely.
Yeah.
So the purpose of these psychologists and psychiatrists
is to make sure you're crazy.
Right.
Keep you on your toes.
Yeah.
So it's just a pretty bizarre situation, a
bizarro world.
Anyone old enough to remember bizarro world, the
Marvel comics?
Oh, yeah.
Everything was backwards.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
That was very pathetic.
Is there a technical term for when the
moon is at its peak?
Epigee, I think, or it's at zenith.
Yeah, zenith sounds correct.
At peak, well, its peak is only.
Well, that could be taken a few ways,
yeah.
Yeah, nothing exists as it is or appears
if you're off the earth.
That's a very simple and true statement.
Okay.
So all of this has to do with
this terrarium that you're on, that the gods
have set up, known as the planet.
Speaking of which, with the terrarium, I posted
that in the uploads about the 40 years
with that one fella from England.
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Fascinating fella.
I've personally seen them back east back in
the day, some really large ones as well,
bigger than his.
Bigger than his, yeah.
Not necessarily in a leader gen, that type
of vessel.
It was more like an aquarium type deal.
Oh, my goodness.
And they were about, I would say, almost
as old.
And I was not as familiar with the
importance of a completely sealed system relative to
what we're being taught generally, you know.
Right, right.
Yeah, that, you know, something like that.
Now, here's the thing.
If you piece together the science that they
use regarding how that works, like this produces
acid, that produces this gas, it's not true.
There's more to it that they cannot acknowledge.
Like, for example, with water, I think we
had Ocelli on and actually went into his
chat just to see what was going on.
I'll admit that shamelessly.
And what was interesting is from all the
years of experience I had working with water
people in the industry, and not just the
regular schmoes at the whatever.
I'm talking about the people that design this
stuff and, you know, the top of the
water industry in the world.
And I've only had one or two people
not even admit, but they acknowledged that when
they put chemicals in water to get rid
of pathogens, right, it's to get rid of
known pathogens.
You know, your biggest waterborne ones are the
Giardia that they go after because that's the
smallest.
The eggs are like, you know, you need
less than one micron, but mechanically.
And then other things.
And they all admit, by the way, there's
no such thing as a virus, by the
way, once you push them to it.
You know, once they say they get rid
of viruses, they'll admit that no one knows
what it is.
I say, of course, you're not supposed to
know because once you find it's fiction.
But anyway, I even have people, you know,
surgeons admit that this whole thing is something
wrong with it.
But essentially, when they put chemicals in water
to eliminate or eradicate certain pathogens, what they
do not want to acknowledge, secretly and openly,
believe it or not, is that these chemicals
like chlorine and things similar to that, chloramines,
which is ammonia also, to eradicate these pathogens,
they eradicate the targeted pathogens, but give rise
to a new set of pathogens that would
have not have been in the water without
those chemicals.
I know it sounds kind of sci-fi.
It sounds like a sci-fi thing.
But it would make sense.
In private conversations, I do get into more
detail on my experiences with water projects.
And the reason I don't do it publicly
is I'd say 75 or 90 percent of
them were based on NDA type stuff, nondisclosure.
Right.
And usually when I stop working with someone,
I return everything to them.
So later on, they can't say, well, you
know, you had, you know, this stuff or
whatever, you know, even if it's trivial.
Just like I have no Skype recording equipment
or anything to record anyone.
Oh, right.
You're preserving your integrity as well as theirs.
Well, they have very little, believe it or
not.
Technically.
So, yeah.
They cannot acknowledge it, secretly or openly or
publicly, professionally or personally, because they're sick.
Generally, humans are in a sick condition right
now.
Yeah.
So when I say sick, I don't mean
sicker than anyone else, just the general condition.
Yeah, so the thing is, you know, water
is wet and that's about as much as
you're going to get out of these idiots.
And I'm not speaking now of, you know,
high school science teachers.
I'm talking about the head of the top
field researchers in the world.
Yeah, they're in very bad shape.
And where does that leave the common pedestrian
plebeian?
Actually, the world is wide open.
I've always said that the world for, meaning
the aspect of living here, the aspect of
learning and doing research, really good research that
is effective, is wide open.
It's completely wide open.
Most people tend to focus on their job
or their job or whatever.
And they trust in any field other than
what they're exposed to.
And even the ones they're exposed to, they
know very little about.
Others to tell them what's going on.
And I'm telling you, they're not giving you,
you know, what's true and correct in its
totality, or at least impartial.
Very little of it is true and correct.
That's why I say that the world of
discovery in terms of what's going on in
any field is wide open.
And I've always been saying this.
It doesn't matter how many reams of paper
you see in research documents or whatever.
You know, every field is still wide open.
And the main ones would be, you know,
water, weather, energy, food.
You know, all that stuff is completely wide
open.
There isn't, the level of research, you know,
even aerospace.
These jokers, man, they're still packing metal tubes
with high speed chemistry to send them up
into the sky.
We'll get into the future as an experiment.
There's nothing on the internet, as far as
I know, demonstrating what they call anti-gravity,
even though it's not really gravity.
That we call, you know, no one can
explain gravity, and I'm going to show you
what it is.
What you do, basically, is you take, let's
say, two objects, and you weigh them separately
on a good scale that goes down to
a tenth of an ounce or a tenth
of a gram.
It should be, because it doesn't even have
to be that.
It could just be even any scale, really.
That's a good quality scale.
So, you take two objects, and you weigh
them separately, but when you put them together,
they're ten to twenty percent lighter, less in
weight.
Right?
And it's not a trick.
It's not, and these are metals.
Right.
Yeah, and you can see the levitation.
You can see it's going opposite the direction
of gravity.
Or it's still moving towards gravity, but very,
very slowly.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, and some people say, well, that's
Lorentz's law.
No, it's not.
You know, the right hand rule.
Right, right.
That's not what's going on.
So, when you understand that gravity is a
push force, not a pull force, everything is
pushing against something else, right?
Even when you have a vacuum and you
have the illusion of it sucking, you're like,
well, it's a vacuum, so it's sucking.
Yeah, but really what's happening, the dynamic is
that the side that has more pressure is
pushing into the side that has less pressure.
So, once you understand that all materials are
unequal, right?
Like, for example, some iron filings are unequal
in property and weight to sawdust, even though
they look very similar granularly, right?
And even if you stain the wood to
be dark, you would see that if you
spun them in a centrifuge, the iron filings
will end up shooting to the peripheral perimeter
faster than the sawdust, right?
Right, right.
Okay.
So, when you design aircraft, what they want
is they're looking for thrust or rockets, right?
So, why are you brute force creating the
thrust through three or four stages of either
combustion or chemical reaction to ultimately get that
thrust?
Why don't you just rotate the ambient air
to a speed?
It doesn't matter what you use to rotate
it with.
So, you can have a low, you know,
the Tesla pumps, the flat discs that have
no distance to a medium.
Okay.
Why don't you take the air itself and
centrifuge it and you look at all the
various gases in the air.
They have different molecular weights, let's say, right?
Ranging from one to 17.
So, you have a gas and you have
another gas on the other end that's 17
times heavier, which is a good ratio, like
even cars, right?
Anyway, so cars use ratios like that, one
to 14.7, right?
So, when you centrifuge the air, what will
happen, the heavier gases will reach the periphery
of the device first.
But once they release and mix into the
atmosphere again, they're going to aggregate how they
were with polarity and other things, how they
are normally in the air, which is not
spaced apart but spaced evenly.
At that point, at that point, from centrifuge
to reaching, to going back to being in
equilibrium, there is a tremendous shockwave that's released.
That is the same thing that happens when
you have something designed to be called a
thrust generator.
When you design aircraft or rockets, they're looking
for thrust, right?
Right.
Where cars, they talk about horsepower and torque.
Correct.
So, there's your thrust element.
So, I sat down with some engineers a
while back and explained this.
I was fortunate enough to have doors open
so I can get to some people that
really were researching this very quickly.
And they said, well, I can't see why
that won't work, but we're not going to
do it because it runs totally silent.
Okay.
In other words, they have to have noise.
So, and then another guy, I told this
story a while back, a couple of years
ago, who is a patent engineer, a patent
reviewer, used to work for the Patent Office,
and an aircraft engineer.
And he says, yeah, there are some treaties,
I don't know if they're in effect, that
certain aircraft have to be noticeable.
And what does that do to the stealth
projects?
So, that's schizophrenia again, right?
Yes, it is.
The other side, they tell you they want
it to be stealth.
But anyway, if anybody knows John Arava, if
you've ever heard of him, there's very little
of him on the internet.
He developed a stealth paint.
You paint anything with it, and it's invisible
to radar.
And the formula is, and I'm not going
to say it.
And what's so cool about this is when
the stealth aircraft came out, he came up
with this in the 60s.
It's a very simple formula.
When he did this, when the Americans came
out with the stealth airplanes in the 90s,
the Israelis says, oh, we did that too.
We got some old F1s and A1s, really
like old 1960s planes.
And they're stealth too, with this paint.
Hmm.
And, well, I can tell you how it's
done.
It's basically a mixture of magnesium oxide, predominantly.
70% magnesium oxide with tantalum and barium
and a form of carbon powder.
And it's not a graphene.
Someone said, is that graphene?
I said, no, it's not graphene, because it
has like a rainbow color to it.
It's not black.
And then you have to put it together
in an attritor, which is, I had someone
look up a sonic attritor recently.
He said, I can't find anything on the
internet.
So, yeah, attrition is when you break something
down into a powder or a fine.
And sonic is when you do it using
sound.
So, anyway, there you go.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, my.
Okay.
So, I noticed, was it Seth or Dreadshoes
wanted to come?
Oh, this walked into the office there.
So, okay.
Anybody else?
Anything else going on?
Let's see.
I've always got a lot to talk about.
Looking at an engine tech from the German
aircraft research programs in the 20s and 30s.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Yeah, his stuff was actually being used by
the Schustafel.
He was, if you look into the story,
one of my mentors that passed away is
a guy named Joseph Blankenship.
Joe Blankenship.
There's a couple of four-hour videos on
him.
Blankenship with a K or Joe Blankenship.
He's pretty much met or known anyone and
everyone, believe it or not, from Tesla to
Howard Hughes to Victor Schauberger.
When they brought Schauberger over to Texas, he
knew someone and he went out there at
the steel factory where they kept Schauberger for
a few months.
And he spent every day of a month
with him, communicating and looking at stuff.
And Schauberger did not speak one word of
English.
He refused to.
You know how you spend time in a
country and you want to learn something.
He just said hello and goodbye and that's
it.
He had no interest in the English language
whatsoever.
So there was that barrier, but there is
no barrier.
When someone opens up a set of blueprints
and rolls them out and you're looking at
them, it doesn't matter what language that is.
You see what you see, you know what
I mean?
Yeah, yeah.
So his stuff, but he worked with the
Schustoffel or the SS predominantly.
He gained favor of Schauberger with the SS
by providing them the administrative side with really
good quality water.
He brought some water machines over there.
They drank up real good.
They got high from drinking this spring water,
came out of a ditch, basically processed.
Wow.
Right.
Very interesting, yes.
Oh yeah, there's lots of stuff.
But the thing is, you know, there's a
lot of talk around.
The thing is, can you talk about stuff
people can actually use?
Let's see.
Oh, you know, I could add.
Let's see, I should be able to.
Let's do it this way.
Let's see if he comes on.
An extra party there, right?
So.
Oh yeah, that's right.
You switch back to the old one.
Yeah, yeah.
Back to the old Skype.
Greetings, Seth, we have Seth.
Salutations.
Greetings, Seth.
Greetings.
I'm not causing an echo, am I?
No, you're very, very, very nice and clear.
And the honor is mine.
Oh, thank you.
Are you spinning metal?
I'm just out of curiosity right now as
we speak.
Or are you not spinning metal?
I am not spinning metal.
No, I am in the comforts of the
home.
Sure.
I'm still doing that for the job, as
you say.
But the hours that I do it have
changed.
So my local time that I get off
is 8.30 instead of midnight or 2
in the morning.
Right, right.
Okay, cool.
So you get to act more normal now.
Yeah.
Honestly, it's kind of a pleasant middle ground.
I'm not and never have been one who
enjoys waking up early, I guess.
It's probably just a personal bias more than
anything else.
It's easier for me to stay awake than
it is to wake up.
Sometimes it's best to never have woken up.
Indeed.
On many levels that goes from just knowing
what's going on as well.
So anything you want to bring us up
to speed with in terms of stuff we've
spoken about in the past?
We haven't heard from you in a long
time.
Anything come up interesting that you want to
share with everyone?
It's been maybe a year plus, so go
ahead.
Oh, I'd say it's more of the same,
but that wouldn't be accurate.
It's always improving just on the personal level.
But beyond that, the world and by that
I mean the society of man is as
skewed as ever.
But it's interesting.
I observed that the date that they go
by has lined up with the moon for
the last few weeks.
I don't know if it's interesting or not,
but I'm always amused to see that.
Yeah, it does so logarithmically.
I've done this by looking at trying to
find the lawful day that people were born.
So sometimes you'll see it's off by a
week or two.
Once it goes past two weeks, then it
gets closer to the front again.
So it's still off by two weeks, right?
And then it tightens up.
I noticed that the logarithmic flux on that
is four to six years.
So every four to six years, it tightens
up real close and almost like spot on,
except for whatever arbitrary number they want to
put on their calendar, we'll throw it off,
right?
Because the number, yeah.
So yeah, this year it will be, well,
this year, I mean, well, yeah.
Seemingly so far this month, it seems, yeah.
So it'll be like that for a little
while, then it'll drift off again by fall.
By fall it'll drift off and then it'll
get really off in about a year or
two or three.
And it'll probably suck itself back in to
being somewhat lawful.
But it never will be lawful the way
they're using it, you see.
Yeah, well, they've changed.
They've arbitrarily changed the times and the days,
right?
And the day into night.
Well, actually, what they've done is, that's an
interesting thing.
We'll get into certain writs in the future.
I think more time needs to be given
just a little bit to see how they
really apply.
But what I've garnered so far from that
is, where man is right now with their
time is that they're completely ignoring the ways
of the gods, completely.
The change in the times is going to
come when they acknowledge the gods again.
And what's unusual is, you know, when you
speak of anything out of scripture, it is
such a strong narrative with a narrow focus.
There's very little peripheral detail when you read
scripture.
And sometimes there is, but usually there isn't.
And what you'll eventually get out of it,
well, I should say what I got out
of it, when they're speaking on things, they're
speaking on things from their perspective, meaning the
gods' perspective.
And that hit me like a ton of
bricks a few years ago when I noticed,
it's like, well, how come there isn't anything
as important as grid living, you know, electrification,
and jet airplanes, and cars, and this crazy
medical system, and all this stuff directly.
How come there's no detail on that?
And I said, well, how can you just
write something about the future, or an all
-encompassing narrative like the scripture, and omit some
of man's big advancements outright?
And I'm like, oh, it seems like no
matter how advanced humans think they are, or
really do get, there's no mention of it
by the gods, because guess what?
It's not about us.
It's about them.
You see?
So on the peripheral, you read scripture and
you think it's about you, meaning mankind, but
it's not.
It's about them.
Yeah, that sort of seems to be a
relatively common, I don't know, trait among people.
I know I myself have certainly done that,
read passages and thought that it's speaking directly
to me.
And on further inspection, that's relatively absurd, unless
you're reading something that is written to all,
then it's pretty safe to assume that.
Oh, you mean like the ones that they
single out as being quote-unquote special in
a good way?
You mean that way, or just in general
in other ways?
There's not a whole lot of singling out
that seems to be good.
Yeah, I know, I said that sarcastically.
They don't speak good about anyone in there.
And even when people are held in high
regard, it's because they're being used to do
something for the rest of humanity and themselves,
you know?
Right.
So, still not wanting to get into specifics
publicly, it seems, I know things are not
always as they seem, and you know, my
curiosity and what I'm trying to attain as
far as information goes, all kind of ties
into Scripture being the one thing that has
been relatively constant, even through its flaws and
whatnot, or not its flaws, but the flaws
of those involved in disseminating what we have
available to us currently.
Right, that's on many levels.
Yeah.
We don't have any New Testament writ, you
know, anything that we could say has fingerprints
on it.
We have Greek, and that's why I rarely
discuss the New Testament, because you're just going
to get a couple of books, probably the
closest you can get is 1st century, really
2nd or 3rd century Aramaic, and that's it.
And the rest you're beholden to whatever they've
put forward after that time.
And as time furthers and goes on and
passes, you know, the inconsistencies and errors in
the translations become more obvious.
Well, they're not even really translations.
Well, they were intended to be.
Right.
Well, there's some of it.
There's some of it that has been translated,
but it's even what it's just fraught with
errors.
Now, just to throw something in here, like
I did in the chat a couple of
days ago in a forceful way, is when
anything is brought up in Scripture, I always
suggest, well, it's actually the right thing to
do.
If you know something is erroneous, don't bring
out the erroneous stuff.
Like if you're going to buy a turkey,
you know how white people do at the
supermarket, you don't bring it home and throw
the whole thing in the oven.
You have to take it out of the
plastic first and clean it, marinate it.
If you cook it with the plastic, I've
seen, I've heard stories of people, they go
to what they call the Thursday Thanksgiving celebration,
and in horror, they forgot to take out
the giblets, and it's in the package still
baked, the organ meat's disgusting.
Okay, that's when people are discussing Scripture, that's
what's going on.
So I found that I've been giving this
advice for over a decade, well, a decade
and a half now.
If you're going to bring up a point
in Scripture, or even consider Scripture at its
whole, then it's very difficult to do this.
But if you're going to bring up a
point, a book, or a verse, or whatever,
and it's something in your mind, and it's
finite, like let's say a particular situation, like,
you know, whatever, let's just say Exodus, you
know, crossing of the Sea of Reeds, or
they call it Ditsy Crossing, right?
Don't start kicking, you know, it doesn't matter
what version, King James, some people say Geneva
Bible was better, I've looked at it, it's
the same crap.
Go into the interlinear and inspect it, and
then your conversation will change greatly, and then
you'll be like, well, let's talk about the
Exodus of the Sea of Reeds.
And when you look at it, and what's
been preserved, you know, before the attempted translation
was made, it really has a very different
story, a very different meaning to what everyone
is pushing around.
And I feel that is, I think it's
the least toxic way, I'm not even going
to say holistic, or healthier, or wholehearted way,
but least toxic way to approach the subject.
So, when you said I don't like to
get earlier into a lot of specifics, I
don't because, well, for several reasons, I know,
number one, we're coming on a time period
where more understanding will come forward, but the
other reason I don't like giving more specifics
is because you have to assess the audience,
you have to assess the society at large,
and then the group that you're speaking to,
and then imagine what the individuals are like,
what level of study they have, let's say,
or whatever.
So, I think it's more, the mindset is
more important, it goes back to the, let's
talk about fishing instead of fish, because once
you become really good at fishing, when we
get to discuss the fish, well, you will
have a whole hell of a lot of
experience with fish by that point, you see.
Right.
But if we talk about fish and you
don't know about fishing, you probably have very
little experience with fish in the wild, unless
you're a scuba diver, or a diver, or
whatever.
So, I would rather talk about how to
get the stuff if that makes any sense.
No, it does, absolutely.
And even before you talk about how to
get the stuff, talking about the condition of
the stuff, so then you have a more
educated and a better way to approach the
stuff, right?
Right.
I've heard it prefaced many times in the
past, where, paraphrasing you, that we're dealing with
incomplete and erroneous translations to the point where
they are versions, and that's why it's stated
as such that they are versions, because we're
not dealing with translations, although the term is
thrown about in academia quite a bit.
But you're also dealing with crazy people.
Now, I keep saying this.
Now, recently I heard a conversation between someone
who's part of this black Israelite thing, which,
by the way, if you want to go
be part of a cult group or something
that makes you feel special, because you know
everything is full of deceit, so these guys
are telling you the truth, show me one
mummy with an afro, and I dare you
to show me one mummy with an afro
and a pic in it, but anyway, I'm
just joking.
So, what I mean is, let's get real,
you know, but I was listening to this
conversation, where this is a typical born-again
Christian moron, and he gave the guy the
floor for like 20 minutes, and he was
like, oh, and he was asking these dumb
questions and of course getting dumb answers.
Now, the guy who was part of the
black Israelite nation obviously was referring more to
scripture, where the born-again guy knows no
scripture at all, he can't, there's no way,
he would know anything in scripture, new or
old testament in context, it's impossible, unless he's
totally wicked, and doing it to just harvest
morons, but the interesting thing was going back
and forth, the born-again Christian guy is
like, you have a very interesting interpretation of
the Bible, and I forgot the answer that
the other guy was giving, so here you
have two people speaking on, this is an
interesting thing, you have two people that are
completely devoid of the truth, most likely in
any other subject, not even just this one,
and they're discussing something as if they both
know what they're talking about, and it's totally
accepted.
That's the society of man in a nutshell
right there.
Because they're crazy.
Easily.
Because they're insane.
You can apply that not just to the
study of scripture, regardless of what religious association
anyone claims.
Oh, it's the medical, it's everything.
Medical, government, economic.
But my point is, that's what I'm saying,
you're dealing with crazy people at large.
I'll be back, I've got to say something
for about 10 seconds.
All right.
To tell you just how goofy things are,
recently Seth I had busted a rib, and
of course I had to go hop through
different things.
A rib?
Is that what you said?
Yeah, a rib.
Yeah, that's what I said.
Not like Adam, but...
Yeah, exactly.
But anyway, the second visit that I had,
which was mandatory to go to, the kind
physician added the two words hopping and jumping
to my restrictions.
And I thought to myself...
Do you do a lot of hopping and
jumping?
Does that work?
No.
And I'm thinking to myself, boy, that would
have been a $20,000 diagnostic and treatment
plan there.
And I was set back, Seth, I was
just absolutely set back when I looked at
the paper and I seen that and I
was like, oh, for God's sakes, we've really
sunk to an all-time low.
Did they try to put the magic cuff
on you?
No, not the second...
Oh, yes, as a comforting and warm-up
for sitting on the thumbtack.
Yes, I do remember that.
The stichometer.
I recently, just as an anecdote, I've never
figured out the pronunciation of that word.
I had to take...
We got a puppy and to be a
friend of our other dog, my wife and
I are relatively fond of four-legged friends.
And through an unfortunate set of circumstance, the
front door of the house got blown open
by the wind, actually, and the new puppy
that we'd had for a month got out
and was hit.
And through the magic of the internet, I
was able to figure all of this out
while I was at work.
So, long story short, we ended up going
to two different veterinary places.
And looking at the bill for one of
those is just as infuriating.
Infuri...
I cannot speak this evening.
Infuriating.
It causes anger.
Maddening?
Maddening is okay as well.
I paid $80 for saltwater.
Oh!
I know that I didn't actually pay for
anything.
It's all just numbers in a computer.
Or what do they call it?
Saline.
Saline injection.
They had the chemical terms written out there.
I'm going, that's saltwater.
That's like one of the most prevalent substances
on the face of the planet.
And for like three ounces of it, I
paid...
yeah.
So, but what do you do?
Well, you train the dog not to run
to the street.
Right.
Yeah, that was...
That was...
he was...
The older dog is an escape artist.
Like I said, when it happened, there was
no one here.
There's generally, you know, we take preventative measures
to prevent there being...
to get out.
But the door blew open.
It was incredibly windy.
I'm in the middle of the continent.
No mounts to prevent the wind.
So, but that...
And that's just, you know, one example, $80
for saltwater.
People will buy anything.
Well, it's their overhead that...
And they end up paying more than it
should be from the beginning.
And they step on it and yeah.
But yeah.
Well, the basic thing is if these are
basic things, you know, how to treat injury
or harm to a physical living thing.
Why don't they spend more time teaching everyone
on how to do that?
Why do they keep it specialized?
Because it's their interest that they're looking for,
not yours.
They don't have your interest.
Like I had a discussion.
One of these morons who thinks that we
should restore the Republic.
I'm like, why?
So you can start it all over again,
you know?
I'm kidding.
Yeah, there's no interest unless...
If a government is a leader of a
people, if he's really interested in his people,
what he will promote or she or the
body politic is self-sustainability, right?
Not centralization of things, right?
None of this should come to us.
Also, it'll promote arming the citizens that you
should all have arms, from light to heavy
arms, right?
So in case there is an invasion, there
is no army to mobilize as a front
because no matter where the invaders go, they're
going to be met with fierce resistance, right?
All of these things in terms of teaching
people law, at least if you were to
set up, let's say, a kindergarten through 12th
grade, a third of that minimum, four years,
should be completely dedicated to law, health, and
protection, military-type protection because the rest of
the world is crazy and violent.
And clean water.
Right, right.
Well, the thing is, then the other third,
the other four years would be basically how
to live, how to cook, water, animal husbandry,
building vocational stuff, building not only, knitting a
sweater, building something out of yarn, right?
The use of all things.
Yeah, the use of all things.
And the other third then would be the
three R's, which would be the natural world,
or the creation.
Yeah, or the creation.
I'd like to get away from that word
nature eventually because there's some strong Egyptian, I
know that sounds like Greek, you've got hang
-ups on words now, but the word for
these low-level gods in Egypt were Neters
or Naters, that's where you get nature from.
So, when you say nature, you're actually saying
gods in ancient Kemetic.
Nurture?
Not sure.
Could be.
Yeah, that would be nurture or net.
No, it would be Nater.
NTR, there's no vowels, so it would be
the word would be spelled N-T-R.
So, yeah.
But the society that we find ourselves in
would have to be incredibly different than it
is currently for these things to...
Oh yeah, it'll be like that later.
I assure you later there'll be a real
education on all of those things.
There has to be.
And that's why I assure you there would
be because it's, you know, for example, if
there is such a thing as an animal
without a download and it has to be
shown and trained by the mature animals around
it, the mature animals around it would train
it about what?
The things that they need to do to
not only survive but to thrive and live
well in the environment as that animal.
So a bird would have a different training
to other birds than a fish would to
other fish.
And when you look at what people are
being told, they're bait like fish out of
water.
There's no law.
What's being done, of course, it's a cosmic
setup, is that you have the great masses
and then you have the entitled classes which
take on parasitical and predatory positions.
You know, the attorneys, the economic people, the
doctors, the religious people, the government people are
parasitical and predacious with almost no exception.
There is almost no exception on that.
Even if you look at the extreme separatists
who want to form their own cults or
groups, they become that way and so this
is a cosmic problem.
And in the future, when you have things
being entropy and death and things that we
consider to be the limits on humankind and
nature being reversed, well, you can't just reverse
those energies without getting people to thrive in
it.
And they're not going to be sitting back
with some entitled class that's going to be
predacious and predatory and parasitical on them.
Predacious and parasitical.
This goes back to the very beginning almost.
This is not a recent or western or
eastern thing.
It's a cosmic thing for the whole planet.
Certainly.
I mentioned in chat a few days ago
a book that I was reading that I
just come across.
You know, I work in the machine shop
and I thankfully don't have to deal with
many people so I am able to, you
know, they give me the jobs that they
want done and I do them and while
I'm doing them I can listen to anything
that I like.
I like to listen to books which I
suppose is sort of strange being that I'm
a musician and I enjoy making music but
I suppose I enjoy making it more than
I enjoy listening to it.
Especially while I'm working for whatever reason.
But I listen to like LibriVox is very,
very...
Public domain people.
Uh-huh, yeah.
It's free audiobooks is what it is.
Yeah.
So I came across this book and in
this book within the reason I actually made
it through most of it, I was in
a hurry and it was kind of a
random download but within the first three chapters
is...
I'm just paraphrasing kind of glancing over it
but this guy...
Tolstoy guy?
Uh-huh, it was Tolstoy, yeah.
Okay, I remember you chatted to him.
I should point out that I don't...
The guy's character doesn't come into question with
this because I don't know anything about him.
I know that he wrote War and Peace
and the book that I've read which is
what I believe but what he was saying
in there, what caught me was that he
had a point of contention with a piece
of scripture and he did a little bit
of research and found that the point of
contention wasn't actually a point of contention because
the wording that he had an issue with
didn't exist.
It was something that was added around the
5th century and it was just that struck
me because our conversations that we've had public
and private in the past we've talked a
lot about some of the misconceptions on what
is actually there is the direct results of
errors in the translation or the version itself
and the adding and subtracting of words.
You know, there's the 8th that is in
you know, occurs 6,000 times in what
they refer to as the Old Testament more
than 6,000 times.
It's between 6,000 and 7,000 times
in this particular...
The aleph tav where you'll see in Hebrew
but not in the Greek.
Right.
And I always go to the Hebrew interlinear
because it's available in the old what they
call the Old Testament.
But even in the New Testament what is
there in Greek is different than what is
there in Latin and a lot of or
at least a lot of what I've seen
translated from the Latin and the Vulgate just
referencing a Greek interlinear has been beneficial because
again there are words that are just not
there that change the meaning of a sentence
quite significantly.
Or let's say if the Greek is the
commanded text to translate out of to create
the version why do you have let's say
a particular Greek word showing up the same
Greek word let's say 10 times in various
books and let's say the whole text but
they use three or four sometimes I've seen
as many as three or four different words
for the same word like spirit will sometimes
be soul sometimes soul sometimes be spirit sometimes
that's one of the most aggravating things yeah
yeah and various words are being used and
translated in other words you'll see sometimes in
you see this often in actually Hebrew and
Greek you'll have one word and I can't
bring this is so common I'm surprised I
can't just bring anything to mind right now
but let's not just say bring the specifics
to mind but just the concept here you'll
have one verse for example and the word
will be used twice the same word but
in the version they will not use the
the same word twice they'll have two different
words as if the meaning now changed you
see so it's like imagine you have a
string of numbers and the number two is
used in the beginning and the number two
is being used in the end well in
the in the translation they use a number
two on one side but a number three
on the other right which is a totally
different number or a totally different word so
what they're doing is even though a particular
verse just to recap here might have the
same word being used twice in the version
they use two different words and it changes
the meaning regardless of what you think the
intent is or it was a better choice
to use that word or not they should
have just kept that word they should have
just stayed with it and used it twice
in the version as well so if people
want to study what the Aleph Tav is
there's not much discussion and I have not
done public discussion I do rant and rave
in the past about when you do look
at especially the Hebrew you'll see how they
don't translate the Aleph Tav and the Christ
identified himself with that phrase let's say and
the significance of that and I stop there
and I've never really gotten into what the
significance of the Aleph Tav is in Hebrew
alone it is always just dismissed as a
grammatical function and I could just do a
short thing here and I'll go into it
more in the future what the significance of
that really is in terms of the underlying
meaning of the text but on the superficial
meaning let's say on the overall just at
a glance meaning of the text for example
if you look at the first verse of
Genesis you know you have seven words and
the fourth word is the Aleph Tav and
it's not being translated you'll have ten words
in the English and by the way if
you I had someone recently say well I
can't find an interlinear that's got the Alpha
and the Omega in the first verse of
Genesis and it's like I'm not even going
to address that it's just dumb but you
know and I've used that as an example
it's a miscomprehension yeah so I'm meaning that
just turn off Greek speak because you can't
follow so but here's the other thing when
you look at this will help with that
let's say add more meaning to it without
getting into too much when you see the
Aleph Tav like for example in the beginning
God created the heavens and the earth is
what you see in English but in Hebrew
it'll be something like Bereshith bara Elohim at
ha-shamayim v'het ha-aretz Bereshith bara
Elohim et ha-shamayim v'het ha-aretz
et ha-aretz okay right now Bereshith bara
Elohim is in the beginnings the Elohim created
and then you see the Aleph Tav and
then you see ha-shamayim v'het ha
-aretz which is created in the heavens and
the earth now what the at does usually
when you see it in Hebrew it means
towards something so when you see the beginnings
Elohim created what is it towards the Aleph
Tav means towards created towards the heavens and
the earth you see that's the grammatical purpose
of that in Hebrew and other places you'll
see like in Book of Jeremiah there's one
chapter I think it's 17 it's a medium
length or I would say short chapter and
the Aleph Tav within those 50 words is
used almost 10 times right because there's a
lot of action there so you'll see a
verb or an adjective something that's going to
happen to either Israel or to something and
evil will go and then it says where
then you'll see towards what so you'll see
the Aleph Tav when you see an action
or a verb being brought into the text
and with that action and verb being actionable
towards something you'll see the Aleph Tav in
between you see so it's sort of I
got a question so what what's your take
on why it's been removed or not I
mean now it would seem like it would
be an easy thing I'm giving you in
other words yeah let's just recap for a
moment if you were to do the first
verse in Genesis you could say in the
beginning the God's created towards the heaven and
the earth that would be fairly accurate even
just purposefully accurate from the grammar that's held
within the text right I also yeah I
also have a a question and I suppose
it's it's a form of clarification as well
because as I've read it and it's instances
that I've found and those few that I
have you know looked at not only that
but it also seems in English there's a
lot of it's not replacement it's addition of
the word z because ok we have which
is it's a single word but the at
the beginning of it intonates another word in
English which would be so it's in the
beginnings or in beginnings created which a would
reformed would almost be a better translation of
the word which is at the sholoyim well
hold on that yeah you could say but
performed is another word ashay also which is
another form which is more like form than
bada I think I have to go and
look at it there's a word in Genesis
that's by the way I just interupt they
do
interchanged,
created, and formed very differently.
So it's not just an at or a
towards, but it's almost adding specificity.
It's not saying, it's speaking to this earth
and these heavens.
It's almost like a Z, but in a
context that we don't have in English, where
it would be like a, you know how
they will, this is just an example, but
they will capitalize the beginning of a pronoun
like him, like they will capitalize that to
denote something separate from a regular pronoun, someone
specific.
It's almost as if the aleph and the
tav as a word put in there, the
et or eta, is set in there to
denote specific things.
And that could be simply a result of
me, you know, going through the inner linears
and specifically seeing it constantly and giving a
new light or a new significance to the
sentence or the phrase or the words that
it is joined with.
And so that's just kind of something that
I've noticed.
There's much to be considered also.
It forms the, I wouldn't say a pointer,
because the aleph and the tav also symbolize
the written word in its entirety.
Do you know how people say, well, you
know, soup to nuts or A to Z,
you know, it means it's all encompassing?
Alpha and omega, yeah, certainly.
Or alpha and omega, from the beginning to
the end.
So it has this definitive thing where usually
you will see it when something will be
brought up and the context that you're looking
for in what is being written is complete
when you see the aleph and tav.
In other words, you're not really looking for
more outside of that passage.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
But then again, all of the passages together,
just like a carpet or anything that's woven
together is what gives the article its definition.
That's why, for example, yeah, it's a binder.
You can also look at aleph, tav as
a binder.
And I would suggest that it would, that
technique or that tool would have been used
literary to, from a literary standpoint, also in
what was written in the New Testament, if
it was transcribed in Hebrew, which would have
been considered a hieroglyph.
And like hiero means holy or literally it
means altar, and glyph means to write, right?
So it would have been the higher form
of memorialization.
You know, like years ago, they hired calligraphers
to pen, yeah, to illuminate or calligraphers to
write a final text.
Like you'll have a first or second draft,
and the final draft, let's say a U
.S. Constitution, you know, it'll be done with
a calligraphy for final presentation.
So there'll be a lot of dress rehearsals,
but when it's time for the show to
go on, not only will you have calligraphy,
you know, it'll be written so it looks
good, but you will also start implementing various
literary tools like the aleph, tav in Hebrew.
But, yeah, there's, but here's the thing, there's
so much discussion through the years on these
fine points, but yet very few people get
the whole picture of Scripture.
What's the purpose?
What does it mean?
For many years, and this is just a
side note here to anyone listening to remember,
I've spent, well, fortunately not too much time,
but when I figured out that the Scripture
was what they called the Bible at the
time, what I thought it was called just
the Bible, was important.
I figured, oh, that's easy.
I just need to seek out some Bible
experts and hang out with them for a
little while and I'll figure out, you know,
just like they figured it out.
And I found out they didn't know what
the hell it was about.
So I was going to ask how that
went.
Didn't go well at all.
So I said, okay, it's something you got
to do on your own.
And then I figured out, you know, wait
a second, you know, what's going on?
Why are my fingers and toes shriveling when
I put them in water and I got
one of those vacuum pack machines and every
time I fired it up, I noticed when
I drew a vacuum on a soft membrane,
it shriveled up around whatever was in the
container.
I said, okay, guys, there is a vacuum
in the body.
I would have a point on that.
It would, and that is that if you
have nerve damage in your hands, that won't
happen.
Hmm.
Interesting.
It's something that I've, because that's something that's
stuck out, you know, the vacuum in the
body is something that is, you know, relatively
obvious once you're looking at it as such.
What holds it all together.
Right.
Because structurally it's an impossibility.
The mechanism for the, yeah, exactly, yeah.
The mechanism for that, you know, the hand
shriveling when you're in water is certainly the
vacuum.
Without the vacuum, that would be quite an
engineering feat actually.
But the, I've also read articles talking about
it being, you know, nerves that your hands,
there has been documented cases of that not
happening to people and it being attributed to
nerve damage.
That's just.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll keep that.
But we have, we, you don't have firsthand
experience with that.
No.
Thankfully.
Yeah.
I don't.
Okay.
So we'll keep, we'll have to keep an
eye on that and anyone who has any
nerve damage, please report back.
Like if anyone poops charcoal briquettes, let us
know because then we can apply calories to
food.
Exactly.
Yes.
I mean.
Now the nerves, the nerves are interesting too
because they're the backup system.
They have to be there if you're going
to set up something as elaborate, you know,
that's going to be reactionary, right?
You're going to have structural evidence of it,
right?
But at the same time, you got to
look at this also.
It's coming from the quackademic.
Oh yeah.
Cannot be trusted.
You just got to take that with a
grain of salt, you know?
Oh yeah.
I'm not, I didn't mean to make it
sound like I was making the assumption that
I have, you know, that I know what
nerves actually are.
No, but the thing is, hold on a
second.
The actual experience that people feel goes beyond
the nerves themselves.
The element is there and you see.
So in other words.
And there's a reactionary thing going on and
you know, maybe that one thing causes another.
Yeah.
You just think of it from a rational
perspective.
You're going to create a being that's going
to feel, move, repair itself and all this.
You're going to always have some physical evidence
of all of those factors, you know, in
the structure.
Right.
But most of those structures are operating outside
just the physicality that's being probed and we're
being told about exists.
Because it's still, I have not found anyone
in, whether it was scientific, medical or what
have you, even psychological community that can tell
me what life is, what, how can, what
allows, and not even a big open question
like that, but just what allows someone or
permits or instigates the mobility from you to
get up on your chair and walk across
the room?
Exactly.
What allows you to do that?
They cannot explain it.
You know, let's say, well, the muscles contract
and the nerve tells it, well, okay, that's
a description.
Right.
Yeah.
How does it all work together and how
is it, how do you have all this
soft stuff hanging on a skeleton and it's
not drooping?
I mean, everything starts to droop when you
get over 60 or so, right?
Or 70.
Yeah.
You know, you start to, your skin keeps
growing and the skeleton doesn't, right?
It's very simple why wrinkles and things.
The skin grows, the earlobes grow, the nose
grows, the brow bone on the skull keeps
growing and the skull keeps growing.
So anyway, so and.
Yeah, it becomes very apparent as you, I
don't know, looking at things with, through a
different perspective that any, why is a question
that we'll lump them all together and call
them academia has a huge problem with.
Because when you get into, as you were
saying, you know, what makes this possible?
They can describe the mechanism that is doing
it, but not, not the spark, not the.
Well, partially, they can partially describe it and
also they don't see it as a problem
because if you don't acknowledge it, it's not
a problem.
Like what problem, right?
They don't acknowledge it at all.
But there's a, you know, we, one day
we'll do a discussion from beginning to end
on the vacuum, the biological vacuums at large
and anything that's living from the cell to
a plant to a fish to a bird
to the human and just all the various
ways that it can be evidenced, right?
In short, I always give the shriveling up
of the membrane, right, and all of that
as the easiest, but essentially also you have
the fluids in the body, right?
You also have the, you know, besides just
the fluids, you have the gases, the fluids,
the tension that's required to keep everything together,
right?
When you start factoring structures that are, that
have a rigid structure with a lot of
flexible membranes, you know, whether it's a building
or a robot or anything, you start to
notice a lot of problems, right?
And, you know, let's say in buildings, let's
say you put a tarp over a metal
frame, right?
You have a lot of problems unless that
tarp is under a lot of tension, mechanical
tension, it's stretched, the wind will shake it
and all that.
When you look at the human body or
anything that's alive, there's very little mechanical tension
holding it all together.
So then it can't be mechanical in that
sense, you know, within the structure itself.
It has to be a pressure, a batho,
what would be the various terms that they
use for pressure, right?
So, or barometric issue.
Once you figure out that it's barometric, let's
say, then everything works very neatly together as
it does.
I'm curious, and this is kind of going
back to what we were talking about a
few minutes ago, about what would you say
about the word, the Hebrew word, Badrach?
And the reason I ask is because, as
you know, you know, I'm learning to speak
and comprehend Hebrew.
And my- Modern Hebrew is very different,
but that's okay.
Certainly.
Absolutely.
And I believe that that's probably a factor
coming into this and, you know, causing this
question.
But my question is, Badrach, you know, Rach
is bad, evil, Rach, right?
And B is in or at, depending upon
its inflection, essentially, how it's pronounced.
The B or the B, you know, there
are subtleties in it.
So in just reading Bereshit Badrach, you know,
Badrach, and admittedly, this is, you know, the
type of Hebrew that a college student would
be speaking over there, is my comprehension of
it.
And it is spoken.
I cannot read Hebrew.
I don't mean to misrepresent that.
But the Badrach would be, you know, in
bad.
So I'm just curious as to, and I've
read, you know, the Interlinear and the Strongsteins
and what is readily available.
But I'm just curious as to, just on
that one word, what is that one word?
Well, and an easy way to look at
it, as I always suggest, get a handle
on letters, right?
Because the reason you have a finite, you
always know which culture promoted literacy because they
had a finite alphabet versus, you know, 2
,700 pictographic characters.
So the Greeks and the Hebrew, you know,
I think cuneiform also had 22 characters.
The reason why you reduce it to those
characters is so it's compact and easy to
apply and anyone can learn it.
So when you look at what the letters
represent, because, again, you don't have to use
letters.
You could use pictographic symbols to do it,
but what's, there's a more, when you reduce
something down to a letter, right, and you,
let's say you're creating the alphabet versus just
doing pictures, you still have, that letter still
has to retain and have a meaning.
You know, they're not arbitrary, right?
It's not like the Pope's work schedule, Gorian
calendar.
When you- Tie that in, tie that
in not only for me, but for anyone
else who's listening, because I assume, and assumptions
are horrible, but that most of the people
that are listening are at least English speakers,
if that's not their native language.
And this is kind of a foreign concept
to English speakers, because A could have the,
you know, a meaning, but what does B
mean other than, you know, the flying insect,
like?
Well, the house.
A house, or it could mean the house
in a sense of something that is intentionally
a house.
You know, it is made where things of
authority or things come out of.
B?
Uh-huh.
In English, how, like, where, like, how does
- Well, what's, English is interesting, because is
it really, is the English alphabet really English?
Well, no.
Is it the alphabet, or is it the
alephbet?
Yeah.
If it was English, we probably wouldn't call
it, you know, the alphabet.
Well, what's the seventh letter in the English
language?
What is it?
G, isn't it?
Well, let's see.
A, B, C, G.
No, you're right.
G.
Right.
I was off by- Yeah.
That's why you ever notice the Masonic symbols,
they have a G on the ring, typically.
Not always, but- Uh-huh.
When you show the G to, you know,
that's like the big, you know, the big
honcho, el jefe, right?
So, they play around with certain things in
the English language that is a road that
you don't want to go down without frequent
showers, I should say, if you know what
that means.
It's dirty.
But, nonetheless, let's just look back to what
things, well, okay.
When you ask, let's say, a word, bada,
what does it mean?
Okay, well, how do we know what it
is?
Well, it's a word, and it's made up
of what?
It's made up of letters.
And why are we using letters?
Why don't we have a picture?
Why don't we have a different, well, because
there was a decision or a standardization or
form that was used, and when you make
a word, because words can be made still
today, you choose them basically on what other
words that sound similar or mean, and with
changing the prefix and suffix to be for,
against, or with, right?
Or, when you're looking at times of antiquity,
these words or these letters that made up
these words themselves had a meaning.
So let's, if you want to just take
bada apart really simply, it would be something
coming out of a house or a central
place, right?
And it would be the head of it,
the R, right, rosh, you see?
You see how it works on that aspect
of the letter signifying the meaning of the
word as well as the word being placed
to have a meaning within the context of
the sentence?
Yeah.
Now, what's very interesting, like, I was recently
listening just to give just more of a
roundabout thing.
When you're learning Hebrew today, it's very different,
because recently I was listening to a conversation,
someone speaking Hebrew, and he was basically asking
the person, you know, did you do this
for yourself or did you do it for
everyone?
And he says, oh, well, you know, olam,
you know, basically he says he did it
for everyone and he used the word olam.
Now when you look at scripture, olam is
typically being used to mean the age, meaning
this time period, or it could also mean
the world, the world at large, right?
But what's interesting about that is when you
look at the meaning of it meaning the
age, right, it's finite, number one.
Number two, when you look at the world
at a certain age, well, it's discerned at
the world of that age, and then at
a different age, the world is very different
again.
But in modern Hebrew, they use the word
olam to mean everyone, like, you know, not
only did I, you know, have a piece
of chewing gum myself, but I gave the
rest of the chewing gum to olam.
In modern Hebrew, they would say that, you
know, to everyone around me, right?
Okay.
You see what I mean by this?
I'm unfamiliar with the word olam in that
context.
I would say a ten.
Okay.
But that's not necessarily everyone.
That's more like many.
So the interesting thing here is, how much
can we read out of what's there, and
how much do we want to read into
what's there in scripture?
Right.
Well, we don't want to read anything into
it if we could avoid it.
Sometimes you have to, and the only time
that it's viable, and I've said this before,
I've said it more lately than before because
there's more of this topic going to be
coming up, it's safe to read into scripture
when it comes to archaeology, right?
Because you have a finite, provable, you know,
what are they going to say?
Can you provide an example?
Sure.
Like the Mesha Stele, for example.
The Mesha Stele, which is a stone that
was, I think it was a Canaanite stone,
it dates back to around 1000 BC, a
little after that, probably.
And actually before that, and it uses the,
it has the name of Yahweh in there.
Like the king went and raided the temple,
and it was actually after that, it was
maybe 700 or 800 BC, and he got
the utensils from the house of Yahweh, right?
So if you have, like there's a bunch
of German scholars in the 1800s and 1700s
that wrote, oh, all that stuff in the
Bible, that was all written around 1000 AD
by a bunch of mystics, you know, that
were in mythology.
So here they find like a, I think
it's the Mesha, M-E-S-H-A,
Stele, S-T-E-L-E, it's in
a museum somewhere, in London or in France,
I think it's in the Louvre.
And you will find that.
There's also other artifacts that are found from
that part of the world that have...
Mesha.
M-E-S-H-A.
You found it?
Okay.
I'm just going from memory.
So, archaeology is a bitch when it starts
to prove out things that people say did
not exist.
You know what I mean?
So in that case, like for example, right
now there's, for the past 10 years, there's
a fellow Collins, he's been digging up the
Sodom and Gomorrah, and anyone who knows scripture
knows that Sodom and Gomorrah was never at
the location where they tell you on the
southwest east end of the Dead Sea.
It's not possible, because that was the land
of the...
South of that was the land of the
Edomites, let's say, and it was nowhere near
there, especially if you look at the story
between Abraham and Lot, and also Abraham's experience
with it, it had to be seen almost
from the hills of Jerusalem.
So there's no way you could see that
far down the Dead Sea.
So they're uncovering Sodom right now, and they're
finding artifacts, and what's interesting is they're finding
artifacts that are directly connected to the Minoan
civilization, right?
Or the Minoans actually, they were not called
the Minoans by that part of the world,
they were called by something else, but I
have to go through my notes for that,
because there's like three levels, or actually almost
four names, almost for every society that we
can refer to, right?
They were not called Minoans.
So the interesting thing about archaeology is that,
well, you know what the prime artifact of
any archaeologist is?
Well, this is not really even discussed anymore,
because they make these things fit how they
want them.
But the most significant artifact an archaeologist can
find is what?
Is an artifact that has what on it?
Writing, right?
So, in order for these archaeological finds that
have been found, and the ones that will
be found, to bear significance on turning the
archaeological evidence into something that can back up
what the scripture says, even though there is
no direct reference in scripture to it, is
an allowance that can easily be said, can
be read into scripture.
Okay.
But in other words, taking a book that
someone wrote about commentary, or whatever they think,
and reading that into scripture, especially religious doctrine,
I recently wrote in chat on how to
do study, how to research things, whenever you
want to study scripture, if you go online,
let's say, or in a library, and there's
a scriptural commentary or information about quote-unquote
the Bible, and it's in a religious context,
it's generally wrong.
Or, generally, they're wrong, because it's
propaganda.
So the allowance that I like to, I
actually enjoy reading into scripture when it comes
to archaeology, you see.
Yeah, okay.
So, an easy thing for that, an easy
way to look at that, let's say, put
scripture aside, look at written history, look at
the archaeology that has been found and can
be shown to match up with, let's say,
Greek writings, or other parts of the world.
For example, Troy, Troy has been taught as
a mythological, the whole Trojan War, and the
city of Troy, and all the things around
it was mythical, because much of the story
of Troy was intertwined with the Greek pantheon.
So I said, well, the Greek pantheon is
mythology, so anything within that, it comes even
proximity is mythology.
Well, Schliemann, there's a lot of those guys
from that part of the world, Germany and
such that were very interested in antiquities, he
uncovered Troy, and when they uncovered it, they
uncovered Troy by basically reading the writings of
Homer and others on where they said it
was, you know, mythological documents, right?
And he just followed, just like this guy
Collins, he just followed what the Bible said
to find Sodom.
So anyway, Schliemann finds that, you know, the
best geographical markers or points of interest that
we have to find it on the map
is here, and he went and dug, and
guess what they found?
Troy.
So now, do we take that archaeology and
say, well, that Troy that they found has
nothing to do with the mythological Troy that
the Greeks spoke about in Homer and all
these others?
Or is it okay to take the evidence
that Troy has been found and now put
it together with the writings, and now what
have you got?
Even though, you see, now it comes together
and it confirms.
And this works with pretty much anything.
For example, I hate to use anything in
legal society as an example, but the creme
de la creme of a quote-unquote investigation
in the legal world, or supposedly law, is
when a case is being argued or needs
to be solved, and they find evidence that
supports the outcome of the case.
And I mean in truth, not with the
way they're doing it.
So you go to the scene that's described,
and you look at the evidence to see
what's going on.
And it's physical evidence.
So the same thing goes back, if you're
going to look at, like, what does bara
mean?
Well, at that point, we're looking at, I
would say, a semi-formalized, if not a
formalized form of text from the time of
Ezra and Nehemiah all the way to, let's
say, 1000 AD, where they kind of left
it alone by that point, you know, to
what we have today, right?
That was the Masoretic text, was pretty much
left alone around then.
With minimal transition in and out, you know,
some things added, some things taken away minimally,
you can see that the architecture of the
letters forming, you know, the word still hold,
the meaning of each letter still holds a
significance within the word itself.
Just like when we were speaking of the
aleph and tav earlier, if you're going to
look at a case in point, well, what
is aleph, what is tav?
It's the first and the last.
It's an all-encompassing thing, right?
So when you go back to bara, what
is be, what is bet, what is rush,
right?
Right.
These things come together.
I mean, this is an interesting thing that
I've always looked at, modern, like with edeb,
right?
It needs to emanate from the top of
the house, literally, right?
The ERB.
But in Hebrew, modern Hebrew, any time after
noon, it's edeb tav, right?
But they have a different name for noon,
and they have a different, and it's edeb
tav all the way to the time you're
ready to go to sleep, then it's lilatav,
right?
Edeb, lilah, boker.
Right.
And what's interesting in scripture, it doesn't get
into the breakdown of edeb, but we know
there's a boundary layer between morning and edeb,
and that boundary layer has to be noon,
you know, even though it doesn't mention noon,
right?
Zowain.
I remember it was a word with a
Z.
Yeah.
So, you see how it's easy to see
that transition, that, well, what comes between morning
and afternoon, if you're a day count, well,
what comes there, you know?
And the thing is that when you understand
human justification of human actions, it's not, when
you look at things like, for example, the
day starting at noon, to justify human action,
people don't operate like you're on a, everyone's
on a starting line at a racetrack, you
know?
It's like, go!
You know, like you're on, you can't, you
know, as soon as you go over the
line, the race starts.
It's not, see, human behavior, if you know
the day, let's say, ends at noon, you
start acting as if the day has ended
an hour before, you see?
And also, even an hour into the day,
you see, it's not exactly at, even though
the marker and the measurement and the time,
it starts exactly at noon, we don't live
our lives like we're on a racetrack, you
know, for the day, let's say, and I'm
referring, let's say, to the Sabbath, right?
Uh-huh.
That's why you heard of preparation before that.
So, let's go back to the word bara,
when you consider all those things, you know,
what is the head of the house, something,
you know, the top, yes, basically bara would
be the top authority in the house, would
mean to, basically, a loose examination of that
word.
The house, the top of the house authority.
What does that have to do with create,
you know?
How do we define it?
Is it like a line that we start
and stop, like, what is creation, why did
we use the word bara?
It gets philosophical very quickly, doesn't it?
Most of it does in, I would say,
not in the way that the term is
used colloquially currently, but in the actual, in
the philosophia, certainly.
So, the thing about the literacy and promoting
literacy is when we see the word being
used and it means a certain thing, does
it mean that because we've been told it
means that?
Or does it mean that because of the
words around it?
Right?
And I think it's a combination of both.
And also the architecture of the word, which
are the letters.
Right.
Well, there are those that would say that
it's not what you say, but how you
say it.
And there are those that would say that
it's not how you say it, but what
you say.
And if we're talking in absolutes, they'd both
be wrong.
Sure.
Yeah, no, of course, because it's human.
That's why, you know, like, let's say the
beginning of one day to the next, there's
a transition period, there's a threshold moment.
So all of these words that we've been
told what they mean, for example, an interlinear,
they work that way.
It works very well.
But if to go back and look at
the architecture of the word, and study what
each letter means and putting it together, I
think gives you more of a deeper meaning.
And does this open us up to really
getting even more meaning out of what's been
said and really not accepting what we're being
told that it means?
Yeah, it does.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
It's almost 11 here locally, and I still
have to take care of two physical bodies
here.
We got to we're going to eat dinner
here in a little bit.
So I'm probably going to leave you here
in just a moment.
But one other word, significantly off topic, but
maybe not at all, would be mime, which
is water in Hebrew.
Yeah, isn't that interesting?
It is interesting.
Because it's motherly, and there are a lot
of mother stuff in there.
And bringing the modern Hebrew in as well,
mime, literally taking it apart, the ma is
how you say what.
It's like, what?
Like matadrodze would be what do you want,
matadrodze.
I say the m letter is one of
the most frequently used letters in Hebrew.
And the e is the plural.
So an interesting way of looking at that.
It's probably relatively inaccurate.
But water is something that you've spoken about
that modern, we'll call them academia, is they
don't know what it is.
They're going off of what they've been told,
you know, hydrogen and oxygen.
And in Hebrew, mime, water, would be the
many whats, or the plural.
And when you ask what, you need to
see or discern or comprehend.
That's why you're asking what, right?
And that's what the middle of the word
means, basically.
It's interesting.
There is still information there, but it takes
some doing to get at it.
Well, this is what the mystics were chasing
down, and it's interesting in itself.
But there's nothing wrong with the, like you
said earlier, is it how you say it
or what you say or both?
There's nothing wrong with studying.
Are we deriving the meaning that we should
be getting out of the word?
And the answer to that is a wholesale
no when we start looking at the words
deeply.
But when we put everything together and see
the purpose of why it's put together, does
it change the meaning?
It shouldn't.
But we should have an understanding of how
everything is strung together.
Like just, like you said, bara and mime,
right, looking at those two words together, you
see there's more going on within the word
that we use as mime or bara, right,
or even aet, right?
And believe it or not, there's, you know,
the mystics, what were they called, the Hebrew
mystics, the, not the Tamurists, the...
The Mejai?
Yeah, well, not even, yeah, they're just...
I mean, that's, it's a horribly, it's inappropriate.
No, the Kabbalistics, yeah.
They get into this stuff and they could
sit there and tell you what each letter
means for hours.
But if you ask them what, tell me
about the gods and what are we in
for, they don't know.
You see?
It's that, it's that censorship.
Well also...
That, going back to that book that I
was talking about, the censorship is evident because
you have this guy, regardless of whoever he
is, who finds that, a point of contention,
and he does a little bit of research
and finds that the words aren't even actually
in the text, but he doesn't apply that
to his own perception of the text or
existence as a whole.
And it's something that he obviously saw as
important enough to write his own book upon,
but at the same time, he stumbles across
something that should be monumental and should be
like what's wrong with us?
It says this, but we're doing this.
And instead of that, he just, it just
digresses into...
He's living in the residue of the torturous
society that the Christians set up.
Because you know, Christianity was used as a
political tool, you know, they burned people that
inquired into the scriptures.
Which is absurd.
It's absurd.
You look at the scripture and the society,
the way that the society of man is
structured right now, what we would call, or
what I would refer to as the world,
separate from the earth, not the earth.
The earth is doing great.
If it doesn't want us here, it's going
to shake us off.
But the society of man, the world is
so very...
It's skewed, but at the same time, we
have all of these religious organizations adding their
justification to things, and it's very simple.
Most of these organizations couldn't exist without oaths
being taken.
Right?
With military orders, when you join a military
order of anything, you know, you take an
oath.
The pledge of allegiance, like they do here
in the States, you know, there are oaths
involved.
You go into, you know, Eustacius' court, there
are oaths involved.
And all of that is strictly verboten, very,
very plainly, even in the rough translations and
erroneous texts that we have readily available to
us.
The president takes an oath and he swears
on the Bible, which is an oxymoron.
Absolutely absurd.
Because in doing this, you're making that book,
that physical item, something other than what it
is.
Well, the book condemns you to do that,
if you do that.
There's a condemnation in doing that.
So yeah, that just shows you...
It's just like the doctor, you know, people
will say, Greek, I want to tell you
what the doctor said.
Hold on a second.
I know you want to tell me how,
you know, you ended up with that particular
moron.
But let me ask you, did he put
a cuff on your arm and tell you
you have blood pressure?
So if he started off with such a
farce, what makes you think that the rest
of it's not a farce?
So when you have a president swearing on
a Bible, if you're starting out with a
farce, what makes you think the rest of
it is not a farce?
And also...
They've made it painfully obvious that it's a
farce.
Yes.
And the other thing is this.
If they're telling you that your sacred right
to vote is secret, well, you all got
together to put us in power in secret,
and when we're in power, guess what we're
going to keep from you?
Secrets.
Show me where in history, when Scripture or
otherwise, when someone was elected, it was done
openly.
They had the crowds, all for, yes, say
yay, and people wanted to say, yelled yay,
and then nay, nay.
And the one that was louder was the
vote of that general group, and then they
went to the next town.
It was no secret.
So people were like, oh yeah, they've all
accepted the secrecy in government.
Show me where you had secrecy in government
in ancient, openly like that.
Show me any ancient Stele or tablet or
writ or Scripture that says, oh yeah, we're
rulers of this, but we keep these secrets
from the people and all this.
Show me where that's ever in there, or
were they open with the people?
Yeah.
Now, whether they were or not is not
the point, because we know they were hypocrites
also.
What I'm saying is that it was not
memorialized.
Now they're memorializing that you vote in secret
and the government has secrets and everybody's okay
with it, but then they complain about the
secret government.
That's why I keep saying this is unreal.
You cannot fix the situation.
They have plenty to complain about.
It accomplishes little, but there's plenty of it
there.
If anything they do can be justified, the
complaining, I suppose, would be up there.
It boils down to the very simple deduction.
It's an Occam razor type thing, even though
I don't endorse Occam's razor thing.
The only obvious reason why things are the
way they are is because the gods have
somehow figured out a certain number of humans
over a certain amount of time has to
pass before you go to the next level.
There's no reason to have 200 years of
whatever they're calling in history right now the
way it is.
There's absolutely no reason for it.
It yields nothing.
It changes what countries mean and go kill
a bunch of people here and there.
That's been done before.
It's because a certain number of people have
to come and pass through this existence, you
see.
That's all.
The rest of it doesn't make any sense,
you know.
Yeah, the next 10 years are going to
be very interesting to observe.
Yeah, seven essentially starting this spring, and the
middle of that seven is three and a
half, so we're going to look around when
they call the next decade.
By then for sure you'll see the changes
in place that leads to the next thing.
If you know what's coming, it's going to
be superb, because even though no matter how
drastic the changes are, the people are going
to accept it.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, with the absurdity that has been prevalent
in just the news cycle, it's become more
...
Sidiocracy.
Yeah.
Yeah, it is absolutely the fictional movie that
is quickly becoming a documentary film.
Yeah.
Future documentary.
They're going to have to create a whole
new genre.
Here's a general statement that holds true, even
though it's not specific, which is general general,
right?
Not specific, not specific.
There's still a lot of people out in
the world, whether it's on the rectangle or
not, that have certain attributes, talents, skills that
you can glean something off of, you know,
get edible corn out of poop, right?
There's still discoveries being made that are communicated.
I think that's how I described reading that
Tolstoy book, was picking peanuts out of refuse.
Right, but it doesn't mean that what they
do, the rest of what they do is
not just reprehensible and repugnant.
So when I say that there's no one
out there discussing anything noteworthy, I mean it
in a wholesale, qualitative way.
Oh yeah, no, absolutely.
There's been a number of programs I've at
least read about, seen a couple of them,
having to do with subject matter that I'm
interested in.
That subject matter being not simply scripture, but
the gods, as in plural, like across all
nations.
As in the truth, yeah.
And the subject matter is there, but the
accuracy is nowhere to be found in several
books, at least a couple of television broadcasts
having to do with the subject.
I'm watching these things going, I know that
the interest is going to grow, but what
is being presented is still the academic mythos
garbage that is, with the tools that we
have at our hands, is easily refuted.
The tools being just the access to information.
So I still have yet to see anything
mainstream being broadcast about any of these things,
be it Nordic gods or Indian gods, Indian
as in India, like Hindi, none of it
is dealing with any of it accurately.
In other words, referencing something without making stuff
up, yeah.
Yeah, and it's not even, they're not being
original with the making stuff up, they're just
following the preconceived mythos as opposed to what
is actually there in the archaeological and literature
references.
Like instead of treating these people like actual
things, they're treating these things as just subjects
that only exist because people think they exist.
It's absurd.
Well that subject, just like all other subjects,
is people will, the access to the truth
is not difficult, but it's the censorship, the
fog.
Like if you're in a dense fog, you
could be a ship just meters or yards
away from a rock outcropping in the water
and you don't see it, right?
So it could be just passing right by
you in pitch black, you have no idea
of your surroundings.
So when the subject matter of the gods,
like you said, whether it's mainstream or cable
or even YouTube or whatever, they're in pitch
black.
It's whatever they're just immediately grasping and the
truth or a bigger matter that could be
more significant to help the program along could
be right there and anyone can access it.
And they don't even access it and they've
taken the position to be in the media.
There's a difference between the common plebeian on
the street mouthing off the crap and there's
a difference between someone in the media broadcasting
it.
They have a different responsibility, you see.
When they go, when you see the media,
whether it's alternative or mainstream broadcasting the same
crap that the plebeian knows, you know, whatever
myth about it, that is really, you know,
I should say a sad state of affairs
because it's not edifying at all.
How long do you think until there will
be a realization of the inadequacy, a realization
of the responsibility that these people have been
abused?
And not just the media, but like the
leaders of any organization.
Well, look, there's two examples I'll give.
The first example is the real history and
the real matter of things is not, it's
simple and really, I shouldn't say simple and
not easy, but simple and not difficult to
discover, okay?
I'll give one example regarding World War II.
You know, like everyone says the Nazis, right,
and Hitler were so bad.
Well, if you go back and just spend
a few hours researching periodicals, you know, which
would be real time in their time, you
know, like dated because let's say you see
the New York Times, you know, they'll put
a date up top, you know, like January
6, 1939, for example, right?
And you read the news there and what
you will find if you look at the
New York Times and other big newspapers prior
to Hitler and the Nazis being the bad
guys in Germany, what you will find is
headlines in the New York Times in the
late 30s and you'll find one headline, you
know, it's a surprise attacks as France attacks
Germany.
This is before, you know, the Socialist Party
armies were mobilized, right?
Then you see another headline, this is again
prior to historically when the Blitzkrieg was started
again, Poland attacks Germany this weekend.
And then, you know, you look at the
newspapers and then a year later, Hitler has
a Blitzkrieg.
But you don't hear that France attacked Germany
and Poland attacked Germany and England shredded all
these treaties years before.
You only right now remember, oh, Hitler was
so bad because he did the Blitzkrieg across
Europe.
Do you see my point?
Certainly.
Okay.
The other thing to remember, that's about getting
any information, the other thing to remember for
anyone is whatever humankind from now on discovers,
not because I'm saying this, it's because you'll
see again in the strong narrative with very
little detail in scripture.
The only reason, if they're unrehabilitatable and there's
really nothing to fix humanity other than what
happens at the resurrection, the only lawfulness that
mankind will gain knowledge of and admit is
what?
The amount of lawfulness or knowledge for them
to gain so when the kill shots come,
they're lawful.
Because it's not lawful to put on global
kill shots on a group of people that
don't know why they're receiving those kill shots.
Right?
Uh-huh.
You know, they tell you what they're going
to do before you do it.
So if the people have no concept of
the gods, how can the gods come and
wipe out their society?
Then at the resurrection, all these people are
going to be sniveling, well, we didn't know.
Why did you do it?
We just needed a little more time to
figure it out, you see.
So keep in mind what you'll see in
the near future and the next seven years
and decade, what will be coming on the
scene in terms of knowledge of the gods
will be just enough where people acknowledge it
just enough so when the kill shots do
come, it'll be lawful so then later at
the resurrection, they can't say, well, we didn't
know, you know.
Right.
They will.
So then you have to rationalize, which I
don't know how much knowledge it'll be, really.
We'll have to see it, but the people
will gain enough knowledge that how much knowledge
does a society have to have of the
gods before the gods then can say, now
we can take them out lawfully because they
acknowledge us?
And that's the amount of, that would be
the answer to the question, how much more
people of the truth are they going to
get?
Absolutely.
It could be a lot or it could
be a little, right?
It just has to be enough.
Just has to be enough.
So then the question is, how much knowledge
of the gods does society have to have
for then the gods to lawfully proceed on
their mopping up their society?
That's the question.
So before this happens, will there be, there
would have to be widespread comprehension of the
text.
Yes.
Well, no, not necessarily widespread comprehension of the
text, but widespread comprehension of the significance of
the text.
The text as itself is a lawful reminder
and a lawful notice of all of these
things.
Well, I'm someone who is personally invested in
the comprehension of what would be called the
New Testament.
Well, not only the New Testament, but it
does say in the end, the wise will
understand.
It doesn't say everyone will understand.
And comprehension of the New Testament is very
simple.
And I've always said this, and I've stuck
by this for a very long time, and
that is, that should have never been made
public, as we know, because that is a
series of testimonials to those that were waiting
for the proof of what happens after you
die, period.
There's no, recently someone challenged me, how few
words can you describe scripture?
And I put it in chat and I
came up with it.
I thought about it for a few days
and I put it in chat.
Because I used to say, well, I could
explain scripture in 30 seconds or less, or
I could explain it in 20 words or
less or 30 words or less.
Now I've got it down to three words,
Adam, Christ, resurrection.
That covers everything.
The Christ, because the Christ is the Godhead.
If you said just the gods, well, then
some moron might come say, well, are you
denying the Christ?
You deny Christ, you deny the Father.
Like, well, so you just put the Christ
as the head of the Godhead.
Because he says he's equal to the Father
anyway.
And Adam is this, the descendants of Adam
are the pivot of all the actions of,
you know, all the battles, all the births,
let's say, all the thing, right?
Those are descendants of Adam, right?
And there are others, but the pivot is
Adam.
The invasive man.
Right.
And then you have resurrection for two reasons.
Well, resurrection for two reasons.
The main reason is that it's the end
of this process.
And also after the resurrection, all the things
that have ever been questioned up until this
point will no longer be questioned.
There'll be full knowledge of all the things.
Any question anyone can ask now, like the
meaning of life or what happens after you
die or, you know, how is the earth
made or this, that and the other, all
of that will be satisfied at the resurrection.
So just saying Adam, Christ and resurrection encompasses
the entire scripture.
What of judgment and mercy?
Resurrection.
Because when Israel, even just like anything, when
you look into the resurrection, well, that has
many, many details.
But when you say resurrection, it's the end
of this process that we see in scripture.
And also, it's the answering of all the
questions that man can possibly have.
In other words, you're coming into full knowledge.
I mean, in other words, by the second
resurrection, everyone will be in full knowledge of
the gods.
That's pretty obvious.
And there's many processes in between there.
Remember, there's a thousand years before everyone is
resurrected after that.
You know, that's a study within itself.
Each one of those things is a study
within itself.
But that is the simplest way to categorize
the entirety of scripture.
And that's the reason why that was, and
I focused on doing that recently also, was
because of the thing that I just said
also.
What does man need to know about or
acknowledge?
What is not, you know, what is, what,
you know, and so how many times have
you run into someone that was so excited
about learning something, and then a year later,
they're not so, they don't care about it
anymore.
You see, this is, I have a feeling
it's going to be very much like that,
because you have something spoken of as the
great falling away, right?
So they're there at one point, and then
they fall away from it, and they get
worse than they've ever been.
So.
Well, humanity has historically been relatively stubborn.
Stubborn, evil, self-centered, rebellious.
You want to go on?
Well, yes.
But all of these things, I mean, that's.
Descendants of Adam.
Like that gets back into the, well, yes,
good and evil, but where does evil come
from?
And it comes from the same place that
good does.
What gets into Adam?
All of these things, all of this, it
all is going to happen, whether we want
it or not.
But we were dealing with a society of
men currently where there is a portion of
it who is at least nominally dedicated to
bringing what they see as prophecy to fruition,
which is completely and totally absurd.
If you have any sort of comprehension of
what you're actually dealing with, those that are
basing it upon scripture or, as I said,
nominally basing it on scripture, you know, saying
whether or not.
But they've been, you know, that's an interesting
thing, and I think that's more of an
urban myth because I seriously doubt they understand
anything in prophecy.
Well, yeah, no, no, no.
That's what I mean by nominally.
They're naming it as a belief or a
faith in prophecy, but in reality, literally, it's
garbage because if there was a comprehension of
these prophecies of which they claim, they would
realize that no matter what they do, these
things are going to happen.
It's not up to
Well, and they won't realize that it happened
until after they happen.
They won't see it coming.
It'll be like a baseball bat to the
back of the head in a dark alleyway
to them.
Waking up going, what happened?
My head hurts.
And even though they know one prophecy just
took place, they didn't see it coming.
They won't be
They have so little rationale, they won't be
able to piece it together to the next
one.
That's because they're in terminal order, right?
One thing happens, and the next thing happens,
and the next, right?
Right.
Mm-hmm.
But there is no understanding.
The reason they have no prophecy is very
simple.
They don't have the right information.
They don't know what day it is, right?
They don't know
They cannot define any of the biblical characters.
It seems relatively important to know what day
it is if you're dealing with prophecy.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
If you read the
One of the reasons I got into day
Figure into what the days are in Scripture
is because I started reading Scripture, and it
said, well, it was the 15th day of
the second month.
And I'm like, okay, does that mean February
15th?
And I looked at the Jewish calendar that
they were putting in front of me, and
I was looking at all these names.
I'm like, wait, they're not even in Babylon
yet.
This is Exodus.
What are you talking about?
You know?
And even the Jewish calendar goes off of
There was no
It's flipped.
It's all the day is night and the
night is day.
Not as in it's bright outside, and we're
going to say it's dark, but as in
the dark moon versus the full moon.
Something that can be observed versus something that
can only be observed by its absence.
Right.
They left in the beginning.
It was very important to let them know
in Exodus when it was the beginning of
the month.
Do you remember that?
There was two or three verses dedicated to
that.
This is this.
This is the beginning of your months.
Well, okay, if that was something new to
them because they're in Egypt, that's like saying,
okay, you see, when you wake up in
the morning, the sky is blue.
I want you to remember the sky is
blue.
Why would you say that with a narrative
that has no detail in it?
So it's very important because when they left
Egypt, it was the beginning of the Egyptian
month and the middle of their month, the
lawful month.
Anyway, that's another discussion.
In the future, I'll get into Egyptian timekeeping.
Here's a little tidbit on timekeeping.
You know how you mentioned the Hindu earlier?
You know the incense sticks that you buy
still at smoke shops or places?
You know they're like a stick?
Nakshampa.
Yeah, Nakshampa.
Uh-huh.
You know the incense holder that they go
on?
It's usually some kind of teak wood or
something.
If you'll notice that the ones that are
more traditional, they have embellishments or markings on
them, like little triangles that go on the
end, across the length.
I would say the embellished ones that are
most common are the ones that have the
cover.
They're generally a trapezoidal wooden box that has
a cover that folds down.
Maybe they're engraved with faux gold.
It'd be like a bas-relief kind of
thing.
But I mean the horizontal holders that the
common people use, you stick the incense stick
in horizontally.
It's meant to hold the stick horizontally, not
at an angle.
That's exactly what I'm talking about, actually.
If you look at the bottom of it,
there's cross-hatchings or triangle.
The reason they're sticks is because they were
to keep time, like an hourglass with sand
or a lamp that burned a certain amount
of oil.
That was their timekeeping.
So that the incense stick had to have
a certain length and a certain thickness, and
that was just a way to measure time.
So in other words, that's another thing to
bring up.
There are so many mechanical ways to measure
time within a culture, right?
So even when you go into the astral
bodies, there are so many ways to use
the astral bodies.
In Exodus, it stresses the beginning of the
month at a certain time.
So anyway, and that was more of a
universal timekeeping that you see in scripture, that
you still see carried out scientifically, quote-unquote
scientifically, nationally today.
But each culture has their own variation of
it.
So anyway, it's good to understand what is
lawful and then the variations of it, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
So what is lawful seems to have been
provided not just to one culture, but to
many in different forms.
But at the same time, that lawfulness is
being deliberately avoided, it seems, regardless of the
culture.
What's lawful is what are you using as
a reference, you know?
And you use a reference based on that.
That reference seems to have been provided to
different cultures at different times in different ways.
Because how do you keep a group of
people that keep procreating over 6,000 years
busy?
Just make busy time.
Do you ever think about how simple this
stuff is?
Well, I mean, if they're procreating, they are
busy.
Yeah, they can be, yeah.
They're doing it correctly.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
It's been, thank you very much for the
conversation.
Thanks for calling in.
I appreciate it.
I hope to do it again in the
near future, but I've got to go.
Thanks for coming, man.
Yes.
Thank you, Seth.
Enjoy your meal.
See you again.
Thanks, Seth.
Likewise.
Bruce, and thank you.
I put it in the text, but thank
you very much for all you do, man.
I greatly appreciate it.
You're most welcome.
Go get your food while it's still warm.
All right.
I'll talk to you all later.
Be well.
See you, Seth.
Well, we had a blast from the past,
isn't it?
Yeah.
Ironically, we had two in a row there.
May not be enough suffering backwards in time.
That's good.
You know, it always made me curious how
they're doing, how their minds changed, what's new.
And it was certainly a welcome to hear
him again.
Certainly.
Yeah.
Quite the fellow.
It's always good to, like you said, bring
people around that you've spoken to in the
past and just go over things again because,
you know, much, you know, there's change every
day, of course.
You know, when I say, of course, and
I don't mean it facetiously, I mean, really,
there's a lot of change going on.
But at this time, how much is really
changing?
Well, if you understand there's a playbook and
the way things are going to go, I
think the change needs to be measured that
way, you know?
Exactly.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
So anything else going on in chat?
I'm just wondering.
Not so much.
No.
We had, let's see.
What do we have here?
We got, we had a total of 15
listeners at its peak, which is good.
Okay.
Three or four is fine.
Yes, exactly.
Exactly.
I always say, why, you know, why go
any further when you only have three or
four people listening?
Well, 15 means that we got five times
as much, so, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And here's the interesting thing, just so everyone
knows, you know, people that do go into
chat, I've gotten over 50, almost midpoint between
50 and 60 emails in the past week
regarding the chat, you know, where the new
chat is, right?
So that, what that does is when you
go into chat and you see, what, five,
six, seven people usually, you know, at the
chat, you know, maybe a few putting things
in here or there, a few, a couple,
a couple, four, five, maybe a few, five,
six sometimes, there's 50 people that come through
at least, minimum of 60, maybe even 70,
right?
Yeah.
That come through in and out just to
give everyone an idea of how many minds
read what's going on.
So for everyone, I thank everyone who does
contribute.
And not to mention that, but when they
do come, they're hitting the server at the
same time, picking up some past Sonic events.
It's all over the map as far as
what they're grabbing, and it's all good.
Yeah, I mean, if you ever told me
there'd be 50 or 60 people coming on
a chat coming through, I'd say, no way.
There can't be more than four or five
people that are able to listen to this
type of stuff or this, the subject matter
this way.
There's no way.
So that's 10 times over expectation.
Right, right.
You know, and what's funny, you know, you
know, people are looking for thousands, you know,
and I'm actually not looking for anyone, but
I'm just saying that I'm pretty surprised that
there's a consistent half a hundred or so
that come around and find what's being said
interestingly enough to be present.
I mean, that's pretty, that's pretty astounding amount
of people because what's being spoken of is
usually that, you know, hey, did you ever
think of this?
And it's not something that's on the other
side of the world or something esoteric that
you have to rely on someone to tell
you about it, but it's, hey, have you
ever thought of this or looked at this
this way?
And it's stuff that's in your immediacy right
around you immediately.
I think it was nothing like farmers, you
know, in a lot of ways, just throwing
out the seed, you know?
Yeah, but it's really the human crop is
a very bad shape.
It is.
But the seed is a manifestation to change,
maybe open eyes, spark a question in their
mind at some point and question.
Just stop and look or just hear.
And you have to remember, it's not for
changing anything.
No, no.
But it's for appreciating the reality that you're
in.
Exactly.
There's a big, yes, that's right.
There's a big difference between those people that
say they want better information to make the
world better.
And there's a bit and there's another mindset
where you want to know the truth because
that's a true appreciation of why you're here,
whether it changes anything or not.
Right.
And that's a change comes all the better.
Yes.
But yeah.
Yeah.
You know what it's akin to?
You buy an exotic race car that couldn't
go 200 miles per hour or 300 kilometers
per hour.
And you know, according to what they call
the rules of the road, you can't go
fast, you know, speed limits, 65, 75, whatever.
Right.
Yeah.
So, but at least you can take it
out to the track and go 200.
And let it roll.
Right.
And take it to what it was made
for.
And that is home, by the way.
It is.
Yeah.
Well, I'll tell you, I have lots of
stories about that.
I kind of figured you did.
But you know, in the real world, if
you have one of these super cars, guess
what?
What are you constantly reminded of?
Speed limit, 75, you know, one over a
third of basically what it can do.
Yeah.
And all that.
But you know, at least you can take
it out to the track once in a
while and bring it to a realization of
what it was really made to do.
Not consistently either.
Mm-hmm.
You know, certain cars that are made that
way because of safety concerns, when you do
reach a top speed, they design the gas
tank size that you run out of fuel
after a certain amount of time, a short
period of time.
Yep.
Designed that way because it's too much of
a liability to run at that speed.
And also, you know, just to give a
short story, I remember once getting in one
of these super cars, I'm like, oh, great.
So we get on the highway and we
start, you know, going over the 150 limit,
not the limit, the limit 75, going over
the 150 speed on the car.
And once we hit over like the one
between 160, 170, you felt like the doors
were going to rattle off and the windshield
was going to pop off.
And I was like, what a piece of
junk, you know.
It doesn't tell you, just because the car
is a super car and goes fast doesn't
mean that it's going to do it well.
Or for long.
Yeah.
So I just want to throw that in
there.
And you don't want to be a quote
unquote passenger in one of those things when
you're going fast.
No.
There's a reason why these cars have 400
watt stereo amplifiers because it's so loud that
you need that.
You can't hear the music otherwise, you see.
But they're not made to be comfortable.
So hopefully when you do hear some Greek
speak and whatever else, that you are comfortable
and you do get the realization of what
the mind is, either should have been or
can't do or will do.
Exactly.
So much things to ponder on and so
many topics that we want to address later
on, as you said.
When the time is right.
Mm-hmm.
Well, the time, here's another way to address
that, is the time to have done all
these things is way past and gone.
Oh, God, yeah.
Yeah.
It's too far gone.
It's like the horse is not only out
of the barn, but it's broken its leg,
it's shot, and it's at the glue factory.
You're not going to get it back.
He's out redistribution.
Get another horse.
Yeah.
The horse out of the barn with the
horse.
Well, I got news that it's at the
glue factory.
That's society and most people.
But it doesn't mean that just because the
time is over that you can't make best
use of the time that's left.
Exactly.
That's the purpose in all this.
Yeah, it's about best, the highest and best
use.
I always use that terminology, whether it's in
projects or it's public.
What's the highest and best use of something,
you know?
Right, right.
Yeah.
That's why, for example, I don't know if
you remember the days of the Carter administration.
They had made it very easy for people
to go to college, and there was a
flood of the market of PhDs, and people
had a lie.
I mean, they couldn't hire.
They were overqualified for most jobs.
So there were people with graduate degrees and
PhDs that had a lie about their qualifications
just to get a regular job to work.
Even a stockbroker or something, yeah.
Yep.
That was a pretty big mess.
Do you remember that time?
Oh, yeah.
Distinctly.
Yeah, the 70s?
Yeah.
People with PhDs, they were starving, right?
Right.
So for example, imagine you go to get
a job flipping burgers and you put on
the resume to PhD.
They're not going to hire you.
No.
Period.
Right?
But if you just basically finished high school,
they'll say, yeah, we'll hire you.
You see?
And you got what you got, you know?
But at least you had something, you know?
What I mean there is that that's the
disposable, the equity and the value that people
have set in the society is disposable.
What I mean by that is- And
they placed it upon you, especially if you're
accredited in any way.
Sure.
What I mean is what people hold to
be valuable and being the equity is really
not so.
No, no.
Yeah.
So one of the discussions, a lot of
the discussions is how it's not so.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, what do you think we wrapped up?
You can pick any topic.
Oh, yeah, any topic.
And you don't have to listen to anyone
else what they have to say about it.
Just go and see what they've memorialized about
that topic.
Yeah.
And pick it apart a little.
In their own stuff.
Yeah.
It was in their own stuff.
Well, we certainly have chewed the fat tonight.
Good.
Busting on two hours easy.
Okay, great.
So we have another one in the can
for this week.
Exactly.
Maybe next week we'll get Sam.
Maybe we'll get Seth again or we'll see
how it goes.
That would be something, huh?
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Thanks for everyone who's contributed and all the
work that you do as well.
And we'll catch you guys again soon.
You're most welcome.
All right, see you all.
See you.
Bye.