And greetings folks, we're here with the Greek,
and how's it going tonight, Greek?
It's going.
It's about the first, over a week into
the ninth month, in case people aren't aware
of it.
Just past the Sabbath.
And I'd say, yeah, it's the rainy season
in the Middle East, by the way.
Ninth month, you should remember, also for historic
events, the ninth and the tenth month biblically
are going to be, let's say, noted for
future events.
And if you don't know what I mean,
or don't ask what, because all you've got
to do is get on the rectangle and
just put in Bible verses ninth month, or
Bible verses tenth month, and just do a
search on some Bible software, and you'll see
what I mean.
Easy, right?
Yeah, so we don't have any questions or
anything, I figured you wanted to tell us
about coffee maybe?
Oh no, I was opting for my coffee,
and then I instead seen the container of
large water there, and I figured, oh, a
nice tall glass of water, and that'll be
much more refreshing anyway.
Yeah, subject matter.
What is it, these morons that do podcasts,
the internet, YouTube, all that, that's called content,
right?
Yes.
Instead of subject matter, that's what they do,
yeah, content, I guess it came from table
of contents.
So any questions out and about?
I'm going to be going into the office
shortly.
I did have, this past week we had
some stuff given to us by, what's your
handle here, 618 of, 618 the 7th-ish
of, yeah, and it had one in there
about the rangatangs being strapped down for sex,
and I immediately went back to one of
your old Sonics, and it was remembering you
taking the windy walk down the street in
the tent with the animals tied down, and
I thought, my goodness, how much things just
repeat, and keep on going on, and...
Well, it's always been going on, just like
it was back then, they were doing it
for over a thousand years, but even back
then, it's just that it's being put on
the rectangle, which is a psyop, until, you
know, the rectangle's being used by the gods
also, to set man up.
It's not a good thing at all.
No.
Yeah, when I say the gods, you know,
I'm talking about the ones that are, the
ones that when people say God, or they
think spirituality or religion, those are the ones
I'm talking about usually.
I never really discuss much about the Creator,
because no one knows anything about Him or
cares to, right?
It's very, I mean, let me just take
that, the last part, the latter part back.
Some people do care, but when people bring
up the topic of spirituality wholesale, they don't
know that they're talking about the earthbound ones,
you know, like the sons of gods or
the ones that were, I call it the
patron and matron deities, right?
Those are the gods that we're talking about,
right?
Usually when I bring them up, yeah, I
tend to, you know, this is the dogma
that I entail in anything that I do,
which is I try to parallel it to
something.
If I notice I have a dogma, I
try to find, is there a parallel to
what I do?
You know, a dogma means like rigid and
single way, means my way or the highway,
and in one way I'm kind of like
the conservative, rabbinical aspect of it, where you
don't share certain discoveries and certain things about
the Most High in public or with people,
unless they're already initiated, and there's nothing to
be initiated in, but other than you know
that it means something high, you know, high
order.
To be initiated really means to start, to
begin.
So maybe those that are initiated in the
concept of what the Most High is about,
you discuss with, you know, that's why I
think I bring up sometimes what the old
rabbinical sages wrote about Genesis, and they said,
well, there's a lot there, and if you're
a commoner, be happy with what you know,
but if you do know what Genesis really
holds, you don't tell people.
You know, I mean, you know, you don't,
you don't do it, and yeah, you discuss
it still, but not in public, right, right.
Another thing is what they call the, you
know, the father's name, the tetragamma tone or
written any other way, a very conservative person
wouldn't want it written or spoken, you know,
like, you know, because it's, it could, it
could easily be used disrespectfully.
So what I mean, when I say the
gods, I'm talking about the ones that are
not doing their jobs that are doing their
job as, as gods only, but they're not
doing their jobs from the beginning, obviously, and
those are the, that's the, you know, the
human mindset is based on what these gods
are projecting.
So, which is a very interesting subject in
itself, but you don't need me to tell
you because, you know, people say, let's not
go there, you ever heard that term when
people are in discussion, let's not go there,
Ocelli's does that a lot, you know, what
that the place where you don't want to
go is where it's obvious, the obvious stuff,
you don't want to, right, let's not go
there, right, means it means let's not discuss
what we should be discussing or what we
should know, but because it's right in front
of us, but we don't, right.
So yeah, it's interesting.
There is going to come a time where,
I don't know what, you know, I don't
know how to say this, but even if
you, let me just give it by example,
if you read in scripture, let's say the
book of Johan or John, the Christ even
says, look, I've shared a lot with you
in secret, right, right, right, he didn't say
go start a religion or he didn't share
anything with the people in public, he was
just making general proclamations based on what they
already knew about him.
Let me say that again.
When you read what they call the New
Testament, whenever the Christ speaks to people in
groups, public groups, or he just supports and
goes roundabout and within the conversation or what
he says regarding what they already know of
him, he doesn't disclose anything to them very
rarely.
And when he does, it's a parable.
Yeah, you see, you see, there's not, and
the stuff that you're reading in the New
Testament are the logs and the accounts and
the witnessing to this man, the Elohim in
the form of a man.
And it's not for anyone or everyone.
Like, for example, the New Testament doesn't really
apply to very few, so few people today
that it's not for you.
You know, many times have I said this,
these biblical writings are not for you.
It's about you and it's about what the
gods want, but they're not for you, that's
for sure.
But if you're curious and you want to
know what's going on, you know, like, for
example, when a building goes up, what's for
you is the door, the window, you know,
the, the directory, you know, what, yeah, the
space, the stairs and all that, going into
the blueprints of the building.
That is not for you.
No, right.
No, it's not.
Looking at the technical schematics and the specifications
on that is not for you.
Yes, you, whoever's listening, that is for a
very specific group of people, the architects, engineers,
the builders.
Right now at this time.
So and to prove myself right now, Bill,
facetious sarcasm, I've come out and given more
hints than anyone else has in the history
since any kind of whatever has been put
together in one place.
And no one at all other than you,
Bruce, you know, you've basically collected sonic events,
but no one has taken anything and developed
it.
You know why?
Because they can't.
Sorry, guys.
But anyway.
All right.
So let's continue.
Anything else going on?
You know, I think this comes back to
how do you be general enough to create
mindset?
Utilizing everything that's been given, you know, generously
from you.
And trying to relish that into a because
we live in a sitcom kind of society,
like you mentioned.
You are in what the attention span is,
what that of a cat?
Right.
It's very short or goldfish or goldfish.
They tap on the glass and they look
and then they run away in a nice
little way.
And, you know, so, you know, I've said
and I contemplated this many, many, many, many
times.
Even my my my tries of having conversations
with different people, very general, very small.
In passing, I'll forget.
Yeah, yeah, that's going to be very.
Yeah.
And I think that it's I see where
you come with the why bother?
Oh, yeah, that's but that's the that you
see, you talk about mastership when you get
to a mastership level, you do that.
Why bother anymore?
I'll tell you why.
It's very simple, because you have to consider
the setting.
You know, like let's say you're the king's
roaster, you know, the king's head, you know,
the king's tail or the king's roaster.
OK.
And you the king is no more.
It becomes a parliamentary whatever.
And you get thrown in with everybody else.
You're not going to roast things like you
did for the king.
Why bother?
These are like total, you know, these are
these are common oafs.
You know, you just get a feeding trough,
whatever you put in and it's not easy
peasy.
Yeah.
Why bother?
Look at the the Star Wars characters.
I don't like to use that, but it's
very universal in the in the cultural meme.
Where did you find the Jedi?
You find what Jedi?
Where are they?
You know what?
And when you found them, what were they
doing?
Right.
Nothing.
Pretty much kicking.
Yeah, because not because they shouldn't do something
you shouldn't because why bother?
Because look what's going on around you, you
know.
At some point, these people will come up
with something that maybe is five minutes long.
Hopefully, you know, we'll have a rarefied cat
or something or a goldfish.
OK, well, look, here's the thing.
There's something about authentic, you know, there's a
guy, Daniel Estulin.
He's kind of funny.
He's he's our age.
He's a little younger, but he's written the
books on the Bilderbergers and all this stuff.
Estulin, S-E-S-T-U-L-I
-N.
And he did I listen to him.
I had found some notes on the Bilderberg
stuff that's not public, by the way, because
it's a long story.
I know someone who's involved with that, but
not in the group itself, but their organization,
like someone who does organizational work, you know,
for whatever.
So anyway, let me just cut to the
chase here.
So Daniel Estulin, he's getting interviewed.
It came up.
I said, OK, this guy's talking about, you
know, the reality is not how people think,
but he still doesn't know how the money
system works or anything like that.
It sounds to the uneducated that he does.
He doesn't.
He's pretty censored himself.
But he does.
He talks about the Internet and he talks
about the people on the Internet, you know,
how they just put out all their information
on Facebook, social media.
And even if they didn't, they don't have
one authentic creative thought in their whole lives.
And they're pretty, you know, useless lives, mediocrity,
you know.
And I'm like, oh, wow.
OK, good.
You know, I was very pleased to hear
that there's, you know, someone else being vocal
about the real reality of humanity.
Right.
Then you go to the new age assholes
and or whatever people that want the, you
know, the following.
They're like, oh, we got to do something.
Say a few people are good.
Look at all these evil people.
No, people are not good.
Sorry.
Right.
They're not good.
At all, this is all very well deserved,
as a matter of fact, their humanity is
going to get to see what they deserve
later in about a decade plus, you're going
to you're going to get what you deserve,
which is population reduction by about 95 percent.
Is what you deserve of written thousands of
years ago, and if you don't know humanity,
you don't see it, if you know humanity,
you're like, oh, yeah.
This is totally in line, this is no
big deal.
Right.
So anyway, and it has nothing to do
with the numbers, because here's the thing, the
group that's going to be left over is
still going to be majority of shitsters or
scumbags, whatever you want to call people, you
know, it's still going to be but but
they're going to be that's a very controllable,
manageable group.
And even the group now could be manageable.
But the thing is, they're not going to
want to be they're going to just kill
each other off.
And they're going to get a little bit
of that before it happens.
So.
And the reason why I sound so rank
on humanity is because there's something called free
will, and it's pretty, you know, there's a
lot of arguments about it, I've given I've
given examples of how it works, not that
I know exactly how it works, but I
know more than anybody else, but excuse me,
or I've given enough on it that anyone
who does a study, what free will is,
you'll say when I say more than anybody
else, I mean, that's speaking, right?
I mean, they're sure somebody died a long
time ago, they did too.
And it's, it's just astonishing.
It's actually pretty embarrassing, even so you've heard
me say it's I'm embarrassed to say I'm
human, right?
Right.
At this.
Yeah, you couldn't imagine see, if you went
to find a species or a group, and
I said, this group will degrade to this
point, you'd say no way.
But you can see it around you, but
you don't notice it because you're in it.
And you were raised in it.
So again, that just to back to Daniel
Estelian, he's pretty rank on humanity also, in
a sense, but he's altruistic, you know, thinks
we got to do something.
No, you don't got to do anything, you
know, but you do you do.
Because you know, your your spirit, your soul
and your body and your body needs to
move to stay healthful, needs to do exercise
and all these other things.
So you do have to do stuff.
So when I say why bother, it's not
a it's within the the concept that we're
all communicating on the Internet, you know, very
rarely do I still write letters or speak
to people on the phone.
It's either a Skype thing or, you know,
or in person or on the rectangle.
So when I say why bother, it's it's
in contrast to what else you see on
the rect on the rectangle.
Right, right.
Because you're going to bother about certain things,
you're going to be doing stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, like I'm sorting out various types
of wire and I have about 17 types
of wire and about 20 different forms and
I have to sort them out because you
can't just start putting wire together, this wire
gauge or whatever, because you have litz wire,
you have solid wire, you've got Teflon coated
litz wire, you know, litz wire is all
little strands are coated individually.
Right.
Have you seen that?
Yeah.
Yeah, silver wire, this is something like after
a while.
Yeah, if I say why bother, I got
a couple of boxes full of wire, you
know, it happens when you tug on it,
it's like spaghetti, get a big thing of
spaghetti, tug on one piece, you're not going
to take just one piece, it'll take a
little while, you'll have a good amount.
So I'm like, why bother?
Well, you have to bother, you know, there
are lots of things you have to do,
you know, brush your teeth.
I always give people recommendations.
If you're going to use a toothbrush, get
a baby toothbrush, because when you get these
adult toothbrushes, there are these long rectangles with
thick bodies and they keep knocking your gums
and other teeth.
But a little baby toothbrush or an infant
toothbrush is pretty square.
It's real small and it's usually soft and
you could get all the way into the
back with even pressure.
And also, you know, force, you know, pounds
per square inch.
This if you put the same amount of
pressure on a smaller surface, the same amount
of force on a small as a surface
decreases, the pressure goes up.
Right, right.
So, you know, if that's why you could
take a little 90 pound woman or 110
pound woman, 120 pound woman, put her in
high heel shoes.
That back heel has got a thousand pounds
per square inch.
Yeah, right.
Because it's about a tenth of a square
inch in area.
So you see, you're getting more.
So the baby.
Right.
So a baby toothbrush, the little tiny ones
that you get around, you can contour between
the teeth up and around the teeth, you
know, you get all the way in the
back.
You might take you a sleep.
It'll give you the illusion that you're taking
longer to brush the teeth.
And here's another example.
If you look at a lot of the
machine power toothbrushes, you know, the Sonicare or
whatever, they have very small heads on them.
You ever notice that?
And the more sophisticated the toothbrush, the smaller
the head.
No.
So why bother?
All right.
I've had some positive feedback.
People say, yeah, man, I switched to a
child's toothbrush or a baby, you know, an
infant toothbrush.
And my mouth feels cleaner.
I get a better job brushing.
Yeah.
I was like, OK, good.
Great.
I know somebody posted.
Haven't you noticed or something post someone posted
the thing about pedophilia on a TED talk.
It's funny.
Yes.
Yeah, I didn't watch it.
I just clicked on it.
But the lady giving the demonstration looked like
she was a victim of it or under
some kind of NK Ultra, which is a
form of torture.
Yeah, right.
There's just something off about that one.
And in the week before I was knocking
and the week before I was knocking, TED
talk is at a front for these organizations
that want to change you.
Yeah, it's interesting.
Right.
So, oh, someone once said, don't hope the
Greek doesn't say it because it usually comes
true.
Well, you have a try.
Any questions, anything venting about or see, maybe
one day post about how you had two
serious injuries at work.
Did the towel and wrapped it and very
positive feedback.
A week later, I was amazed because it
was serious cut down to the blood vessel
after a week.
Looked like nothing.
Right.
More shorter.
Three days.
Yeah, it looked like it looked like a
paper cut.
It'll be completely healed in a week.
Yeah.
Yep.
All right.
The TED talk was an interesting one.
Oh, yeah, it's just rubbish.
It's all rubbish, but they are putting it
out in the in the face more than
that.
You know, it's kind of something you notice
with the over the period of time is
how they control the masses, how they just
keep easily bringing it up, bringing it up.
And after a while, they're almost in a
hypnotic state to it or some crap, you
know, and the stuff on the Internet is
like what cattle probably have in their minds.
It's like very few cattle complain about this
being slaughtered.
Right, right.
They don't know what's going on, but I'm
sure they have some kind of a dialogue,
communal or internal as cattle, because, you know,
here's the thing.
If people, you know, one time in the
mid after the medieval ages, they taught they're
trying to tease aside, quote unquote, natural philosophers
or the ones that worked for the state
or the monarchy or the church, try to
convince people animals have no emotion, which is
not true at all.
Right.
And they're just dumb beasts.
And they're not.
I mean, they like if anyone's been around
cattle or cows, let's say they're very distinct
in their personality.
Well, they also have face recognition.
They recognize faces and they will.
You once you get to know that, you'll
see that they need to see your face
to right to figure out who you are
and don't actually move around.
Yeah.
And also for most animals do face recognition,
by the way.
Yeah.
And so.
In essence, if you look at the human
livestock, they do face recognition.
And if you want to know what that
cattle group is thinking, go on the you
know, go to church, go to where they
work.
Listen to them.
Look at their newspapers.
Look at their universities.
Look at the rectangle.
I mean, it's garbage, really.
You know, slop straight up.
So but, you know, that's OK.
Why bother?
You don't have to be a part of
it.
You might pass through it and mingle with
it, but you don't have to be of
it.
Yeah.
You can always clean your shoes.
So I don't think there's much going on.
A lot of the e-mails I get,
believe it or not, lately, you can keep
sending them.
It's fine.
Some of them are extremely personal, as if,
you know, I need to what I used
to do.
I used to get on Skype calls and
people used to just come up with any
do they need advice.
Right.
And I'm talking about serious stuff.
And I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Listen, you got to send me your contact
information so I know where to send the
bill, because this kind of therapy, you know,
usually, you know, you go to, you know,
these people that charge thousands.
Yeah.
So I'm not going to I don't I'm
not anyone's psychiatrist or priest or therapist.
I don't mind getting them.
Actually, I do.
But but in other words, if you need
if you're compelled to send me a very
personal help thing or something very personal, you
may.
I don't I don't I don't really need
to know because I'm not in that position.
You see, I'm not your friend also.
Right.
I'm friendly.
You're acquainted with Greek speak.
Right.
I'm not apathetic to it, but I just
don't want to I'm not a part of
it and I don't want to be a
part of it because the amount of work
it takes to get in to get involved
with people personally is just that amount, a
good amount of work.
You can't just give an answer.
The best way to do it is to
form a working relationship on an issue, whatever
it is.
Right.
So you'd hate to be responsible.
And I'm not going to do it.
I mean, the minimum for that is one
hundred and fifty an hour.
So, you know, the minimum.
So I'm not going to, you know, and
it's sadly to say I'm far more effective
than these other professionals that exist.
But you're not going to you know, you're
not going to succeed in the with the
entitled classes.
If you go to an attorney, a shrink
or a doctor, they're not going to they
don't know what they're doing.
How do I know?
Because I know enough if you're going to
a shrink.
Yeah.
So anyway, nothing on the emails I see.
So maybe we'll just cut it short.
All right.
Stuff to do.
So, yeah, nice talking with you again.
It was good.
Yeah.
We'll do it again next week then.
All right, everyone.
You take care.
Good night.
Take care.
Bye.
Thanks.