There we go.
Good evening, Greg.
How are you doing?
Good evening.
Yeah, okay, we'll do this for another week.
People are getting used to it, I guess.
I certainly am in a way.
Regularity, if you know what I mean, but without the poop.
Yeah, and the corn is always fresh and clean.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, I only have got less than an hour, so I might as well just touch base with whoever, you know, it's a unilateral, meaning there's only one, I guess.
Got a bunch of emails.
Actually, I'm making a little bit of coffee now.
I might be out for a second to grind those beans.
Certainly.
And I would just want to address, I've been getting quite a few emails, and most of the questions are pertinent.
Rehashing stuff, but, you know, at least it shows that people have heard and are listening slightly, so.
Right.
Anything on your end?
Anything you want to bring up?
I was just noticing the uptick in Turkey, and as I venture around, you know, during the week when I get a little bit of time, I'll pop in on different radio stations to see what's going on, and maybe pick through some media quickly.
I noticed a little Israel bashing starting to go on in Turkey.
The fall would be.
Turkey as in, not the bird, but the country.
The country, yes.
Yeah, I like to say it like they do there.
Yeah, okay.
The tariffs, and the Daher war against everything in the bank.
And you noticed a subtle little hint of the bankers in the background in what they're playing.
It's rather interesting, yeah.
Well, the banking is interesting.
Let's just cover that.
Sure.
For a very long time, over 500 years, the conquering and the conquest modalities have changed.
Okay, it wasn't, it wasn't, well, let's just say it wasn't popular to do conquest the way conquest was done up until, oh, 12, 13, 14, 1500s, and they settled into the new modality by the 1700s, which kind of went a little askew, which it always does, and then it settled really well by the 19th century.
And, you know, that's where you had the American Revolution, French Revolution, Napoleonic Wars towards the end of the 18th century, and all that.
All that's backwards, by the way, it's not what you think.
You almost have to go back and look at contemporary writings.
Don't look at, don't look at what is written later about it.
Try to pick up, you know, stuff that was contemporary, written at the time while it was going on, right?
Very different.
The other thing is, the money system is tied into that, because that's what commerce is.
And unless you're dealing in an isolated commune, you're going to need means of exchange.
What happened with the new modality of conquest is they developed forms of monarchy and forms of parliamentarianism and forms of governance that incorporated constitutionalism and various isms, you know, socialism, communism, various modalities.
All of those were basically set up to be a good curtain or a hiding place for those that really were in control, publicly, where prior to that, those who were really in control were more public.
Now, this
new system of constitutional government or socialist government or the new monarchy, ministerial
government, and all the various modalities that came out were so successful, and it got the people
so enthralled into what you might call in a chattel state, or a slavery state, or just in a
worthlessness state, that it was time now to pull money and to pull knowledge, to pull science, to
pull all kinds of things that most people would say are integral aspects of the human community.
Now, when you look at the money system, it's very, very simple.
I've tried to give some information that's not out there, because that's all.
Otherwise, I just sound like everybody else.
A bunch of morons repeating what, you know, what moron said, you know, to the other moron.
In essence, imagine you are in prison, and with no chance of ever getting out.
And the way you engage in exchange is by playing a board game called Monopoly.
And you have a player, a thimble, a house, whatever, and you have this monopoly money.
And you use this monopoly money to get drugs or pay for sex or whatever in the prison.
That is the money system.
It does not exist anymore as it is.
I've even, I remember a decade ago, even asking an assembly-type politician, you know, I set them up.
And I'm sure other people have done it, and I've discussed it with other people who have.
When they get on an economic discussion, you just say, well, money's Federal Reserve.
And they answer, yes.
You know, you do the old car salesman stuff.
You get them to say yes enough times, and you close the deal.
And they say, well, Federal Reserve is a fiat currency.
You're like, well, not exactly.
Well, is it a fiat currency or is not?
Well, yes, it is a fiat currency.
Okay, then they say yes.
And then you say, well, the government can pretty much, with the Federal Reserve, print as much money as they like.
And they say yes.
So then why do you need to collect taxes?
Oops.
Right.
Big problem.
Subject to insert.
Yeah, it's because in prison and lockdown, they do whatever they want to do.
It's because actually, that's what gives the money the value.
When they, when you, when you engage, when they say you have to pay taxes or you get in trouble, well, now it's worth something.
Right.
Because through penalty, not because the taxes are, I assure anyone that not one penny, not, not one iota of any tax money anywhere has ever paid for anything in the past, let's say, minimum 40 years, maybe realistically 80 years.
Not one, even a button in a, in a government or a line painted on the street, one line, nothing, not one penny ever at all.
They even tell you that when you're driving down the street, it says, thank you for the roads, all you idiots.
It's the bonds that paid for it.
What is a bond?
A bond is an indenture agreement.
Right.
If I mow the lawn for you and you can't pay me, let's say you write me an IOU for 10 bucks, if we agreed on it now and you can't pay me for another month, but I could take, I need something right now.
I could take that IOU that you wrote and give it to, let's say somebody else for five bucks.
And I'll be, I'll be happy with five.
Now they, now they can either try to get the 10 bucks from you later, or they might sell it for six or bundle.
They might have so many of them.
They could leverage that for something.
You see, that's, what's paying for or not paying, but it's an exchange.
You know what a helicopter is like a money scheme.
It needs to keep moving.
Right.
You know how immigrants do that?
They put a pool.
So you put in a hundred, everybody puts in a hundred dollars and once a week, someone gets a thousand.
Right.
Sounds good.
You get enough people.
It's bigger.
That, that has to keep going.
And it can't stop.
It's a Ponzi scheme or whatever.
Right.
It's a helicopter thing or whatever.
So the money system, there is going to be no collapse.
There isn't going to, because no one knows how it works and it's going to keep going as long as whatever, as long as there are roofs on buildings.
Right.
And there's going to be a time period before that, when the roofs are
removed from all the buildings, even the chicken coops, where the people will say, Hey, we're no
longer going to use this money system, but that's going to be, you know, irrelevant at that point,
because even if there's less than three days food in the store, it doesn't matter because
you don't have more than three days after that point anyway.
You see?
So, okay.
So out of memory, I'm not in front of the computer now, but I've got a, like I mentioned earlier, there's a bunch of emails and not much talk like what you brought in looking at the news about the Middle East and all that, because it's a growing period.
And if it's for real, you're not hearing about it.
You see, other than little hints.
So you're going to, right.
Because what they put out there is, is for the more on public consumption, whether it's mainstream or alternative media.
And the alternative media is more of a joke because they have an inferiority complex.
So they have to scream louder.
You know what I mean?
They're like Fox news doesn't have to scream as loud as, I don't know.
You could pick any of the alternative idiots of choice, right?
They have to try harder, you know, because they're in Fox news and CNN and me, MSNBC or the government websites.
They don't have an inferiority complex, right?
They're well-endowed where all of the other idiots with a website, I have an inferiority complex, obviously.
I mean, the thing that kind of took me notice was how many of them went to the Turkey story.
Um, and, and they really pumped it.
They pumped it up as much as they could, which.
Yeah.
Turkey is the Australia.
Turkey is the Australia or the New Zealand of that part of the world.
You know what I mean by that?
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
They experiment.
Like if you, if you're a New Zealander or an Australian, you're being experimented on your, your only, only reason you have a society is to be experimented on.
It's like when you go into a building and there's rats on cages, you're like, well, what's this for?
It seems like he's standing up against the, uh, um, no, he's not.
He was one of the Turkey was one of the few nations to turn into this new system with using, they didn't use the Pope's work schedule and they didn't have surnames and they didn't have fiat currency.
They didn't have a constitutions and they didn't have all that stuff and they were given an ultimatum.
You either turn over to this system or we destroy all of you.
And when they did turn in, they turned in more than anyone else ever could have.
So that seems like he's backstepping now and that's given him some, some real trouble.
He's just, he's being like the alternative media.
He has an inferior, you know, they're, they're poised there because they're the gateway from the east to the west, um, without going through that dark continent.
And I mean, dark, literally it is a dark place to go through there, uh, to go through what they call the continent of Africa.
Um, dark spiritually.
Right.
So, uh, yeah, that's another discussion now.
Um, so Turkey is interesting.
Yeah.
They experiment on them.
Uh, and like I mentioned down under they're quiet, um, right now, but what's really going on is the time period.
I would suggest, uh, when I say really, if, if this time period is accurate, usually by the midpoint in the three and a half year period.
So 2021, the fall, the summer, there'll be no doubt that there, that there's a, uh, a, um, an assembly or an effort to create a middle east union and more of the effort will be done.
And of course, 2026, it'll be in with many other things that correspond to that spiritual ones, scientific ones, social ones.
Right now, uh, the, the agenda that's in place, uh, like give you an example.
I just looked at a bridge, the big bridge that fell in Italy, you know, people say it's a tragedy, but from those that own Italy, that as a company, they're like, fine, these idiots will never figure out.
They're letting everything crumble.
There isn't going to be any, uh, and even the new stuff that's being built, it's because, you know, it was a previous promise, you know?
Right.
Uh, so yeah, but nonetheless, okay.
To some of the emails, um, I just want to, before I get in front of the computer here, uh, mentioned the last one I got just maybe about 20 minutes ago was a talk about a lawful, what makes a lawful society?
Well, that's easy.
Law, right?
Not policy, not opinion, not politics, right?
If you actually look up the definition of a politician, do you want to look it up?
It's not good.
It's very bad, actually.
If you want to look it up, etymology or definition.
Yeah.
If you want to get it and, and just get to the juicy parts, if you want to read it, because some of the definitions are paragraphs long, but essentially it's someone who has a career of lying, deceiving for their own personal gain.
That's the definition of a politician, right?
So yeah, all of them, you know, doesn't matter.
Even you can go back 500 years, they're jokers, you know?
Uh, so they're not the leaders that are spoken of in scripture.
They, they do speak for the leaders on occasion, which is interesting because you'll have, let's say the current Trump, you'll say, I'm going to do this.
And then they, I don't.
And then he says, I'm not going to do it.
Well, he's not, he's speaking for his boss, you know, his boss is telling him, this is what I want you to say and do.
Don't worry.
We'll take care of you.
See?
So yeah, he is the mouthpiece, but he's not an agent.
That's another thing I want to bring up.
They're just jokers, but you, even though they're just agents, I mean, they're not agents.
They, that's the best you're going to get.
You see until you have someone until you know how to discern someone who really is.
Right.
And that's a, it's not going to be found in a constitutional Republic.
I'll tell you that for sure.
Right.
Constitutional Republic is a joke, you know, cause they, their God is justice.
So, yeah.
So the lawful society basically, and also the other part of the email is, I'll read it here in a second.
Okay.
I get back in there, but let me know what you're doing on the politician.
You're going to find anything there, or does it look possible?
I'm getting there.
My computer was running a little slow.
So bear with me.
Okay.
Let's see.
All right.
Okay.
Let's see.
This one was hi, Greek.
I had an idea for a Sonic.
What is a lawful society based on question mark, perhaps approaching from the bottom up elevates thinking and set it from the top down.
Just a thought.
Well, it's all from the top down, meaning that we have external input, right?
Your actual thinking process is happening on a cloud, you know, using the computer analogy and the thinking, you know, it depends on what the gods want to do.
Like, well, first of all, you know, your law comes from your God, your God, or the God that society is based on.
Right.
And in this case, it's the goddess and she's based on destruction of all things living.
That's why seeds are made now not to sprout.
You know, I mean, plants are fertile, you know, male with male in female, female union, children are basically worthless.
You know, their value in terms of the position in life, you know, all the various chemicals, drugs, science that you taught, right?
It's anti life.
So, well, the thinking you see, when I hear I see a question like that, that lends me to think of good things being better, or whatever.
And it's not necessarily true, because top thinking, it's all top thinking from top thing from the top down, or the bottom up, it's because it's external.
So let's say it's time for the gods to put evil on a society.
Right?
Right.
What they'll do is they'll get the people or the leadership or whoever to guide them into doing evil.
That's still from the top.
You know, not this email doesn't say good or evil, but I'm presuming.
So, for example, the situation that the world is in right now goes all the way back to Genesis, right?
That's a really long time that you really didn't miss anything.
You know, a little bit, maybe at a certain time period.
And if you missed anything, it was something you would have done different in your life yet, if you had believed it, or had information.
That's the only thing you really missed in your own personal life.
And if you do get the information and the opportunity later, then, you know, be seize the day, seize the moment, seize the opportunity.
Carpe diem, like, I don't like to use Latin terms, because that's, you know, the adversary's language, believe it or not, so is English.
So most people, and I'm bringing in the good and evil part, they think that when it's due for a society to go down and evil brought upon it, people think that's bad.
Yes, it is.
But it's actually an accomplishment that has to be done from the other side.
So in a sense, their will is being done.
So it's good.
You see what I mean?
It sounds kind of crazy.
But essentially, let's say, for example, many times I've spoken of how this society is unrehabilitatable, that means you can't fix it.
So then it has to be destroyed, or cleared out, clear the board, whatever, you know, like, when there's a bunch of gibberish on the blackboard, the teacher or somebody comes clean the backboard, you don't save it, you just wipe it off, you know, it's done, right?
Clean the site, right?
So right now, you're at the clean the site point.
So would the end of the society be a good thing?
Absolutely, without a doubt, definitely, no option, of course.
How else can you say it positively?
Yes, has to be done.
What does that mean?
Well, cleaning out the physical presence of the majority of the humans and most of the wildlife and all that, because wildlife is corrupted, and a lot of the natural features, and really cleaning it up.
And then the universal representative sample that's left over is then tuned up and then given an upgrade, you see?
Marine.
And that's how it's done.
Now, is that going to be pleasant?
No, it's not.
Well, if you're a corporeal being, no, it's not going to be pleasant, right?
But if you're a non-material being, of course, it's a will that was written about thousands of years ago, it should be done.
So, you know, the other thing is, is an unlawful society really unlawful?
Yes, it is.
But it's also by design.
And then you have the free will within that unlawful society.
Many years ago, it was correct to move if it was, you know, if you wanted to be lawful, and you lived amongst the Canaanites or the Philistines, right?
Or the Hittites, you would want to leave.
You wouldn't want to be there with them unless you're into the child sacrifice and all that other crap that they did on a daily basis.
Right?
Yeah.
So but now it's everywhere.
Now there's nowhere to go.
I can't suggest, even now, even if you go back 20 years ago, 30 years ago, I can't say, well, go to Australia, I mean, or New Zealand or some part of the Dark Continent or Asia or an island by yourself.
You're not gonna know it's not gonna, right?
It's not gonna help.
They'll just, you know, now if you get, you'll, if you try to live on a deserted island, you'll get in trouble.
Well, years ago, they said, Well, I was a madman, leave him alone, right?
Right.
So now it's a spiritual thing, meaning of the mind.
And how much can the mind take before you check out?
Right?
Another email was going from memory here, regarding the gods.
And I had mentioned divination to a certain degree regarding casting lots.
Right.
And the person also made a list about, yeah, the person also made a list of like, what about tarot cards, this, this, that, and the other things we, and that's bad, you know, the Bible Scripture says it's bad, don't do it.
Well, here's the interesting part.
And this I have to tie in with many other aspects of things that I've said in the holistic concept of what Greek speak is about.
It's anything that you can think of or do, regardless if you think is morally moral, good or bad, it's who are you doing it for?
And are you doing their will, meaning your spiritual father, you know, your God?
So here's an example.
People find a total offense and a gas to go for a morning jog in the local city park and find a headless goat or a chicken head.
Right?
And then they find a bunch of candles in a circle and some maybe red scarves and some herbs and oil and a campfire from the night before.
Totally.
All right.
So what am I saying?
They did a animal sacrifice for their deity, right?
Right.
Well, if you read the scripture, you were to bring an animal sacrifice for the head deity, right?
What's the difference?
You're killing an animal for a deity, aren't you?
It's which deity are you doing it for?
Right?
Then you can get into the history and look at, you know, for example, the priests were given the umbremum thermum, which are like basically like dice, right?
A stone, one side, yes, one side, no, let's say, and then they were, they had the vestments, right?
Right.
Very thick linen with stones on it.
Things like that.
Now, things like, for example, that were mentioned in the email regarding like tarot, that the history of tarot is something that came out a few hundred years ago.
And that was basically like the wealthy people needed a new card game to bring in a lot of the cultural influence that they got from the East, like Turkey or whatever, right?
You know how you hear when I say, oh, man, I'm going to the bridge club.
Are you thinking about a bunch of bus drivers and people on section eight?
Or are you thinking about wealthy people, the bridge club, right?
Yeah, right.
Okay.
So the bridge club of those days were the tarot readers, because that seemed a lot neater than the palm reader, gypsy, right?
And that goes back to the days of table turning and all that other kind of stuff and more mystics kind of behavior, right?
Yeah.
And also they all have specific gods.
I mean, you can get this long list, like the Ouija board is for one particular deity.
And actually, that deity, his name is on the Led Zeppelin album cover.
They use it a lot.
If you're familiar with the Led Zeppelin album covers, you'll see as part of their logo, that deity, I'm not going to say it.
That's the deity from the Ouija board.
And they all, I mean, all they all have their ways.
Now, the most high was like, for example, if you're in the book of Kings and Chronicles, whatever, people were told not to do that.
And they were told not to do it in the law is because they didn't have to.
He was, let's say, use the term, the Elohim or the God of openness.
He sent prophets.
If he wanted you to know something, he sent you a prophet.
He sent you someone who, a message and he, and it was signed and, you know, you knew who, you know, right.
It was none of this stuff going on.
Right.
So right now we've got so much information about what his will is and his law and what he's going to do.
Do we really need to do like big evocations and, you know, all that stuff?
No, not necessarily at all.
Because if you've got half a brain and you have at least the Old Testament and a good interlinear and good discussion about it, you get a really good sense of what's going on and how to act accordingly.
Now, the New Testament is a whole other mess.
I don't bring any of that up often unless I choose to my own volition, because there's no access to the original text or anything that resembles it unless you're going to start digging so deep and working on it so hard that you're going to go back to the Syriac, Aramaic, Peshetto, which is Eastern Western, which means simple, and have a firm understanding of the law.
Recently, I had someone who was a Christian say, you know, do you want to come to a Bible study and talk to people about that?
And I told him that would be like an alcoholic telling me he's drunk and he wants to borrow my car.
But that doesn't mean the answer is no.
Right.
But it's that bad.
There's no, you can't.
No, forget it.
No, that's not going to happen.
You are so far, so many layers removed from anything real that you might as well just stay in your fairytale complex for another decade or so, and you'll be fine.
It's not, you know, that's the kind of thing if someone professes that kind of religion, it's like you either have to run with your hair on fire and renounce it, or before you even get anything going in a positive direction.
Otherwise, that's secular.
Secular just means dumbed down, stupid stuff.
You know, stay there, you know.
There's no way I could talk to them if they're Christian.
Getting back to what you're just saying, though, about all these different rituals and things, you know, this goes back to the communication aspect.
You're using a technology, prayer.
Right.
Yeah.
But they recognize it as direct, yeah.
And they have no clue in what the power in all the manifestation crap that goes along with that.
My god.
No, there is a lot of power in all of it, historically and through urban legend or whatever, because once you establish that the gods exist, then of course there's power in it.
That's what I mean by that.
But on the other hand, gods have been so hands-off that enough time of their hands-offishness has passed that there are some species called atheists, right?
Right.
And that they're just a product of the show-me, you know, I'm from Missouri kind of thing.
That's all the atheists is.
They have no knowledge base.
They work on the show-me thing.
And then when you try to show them things that are memorialized, they can't see it because they're looking for it right now.
So that's how long the gods have been hands-off overtly.
Right.
I mean, you know, overt.
That's why the wisdom thing is very different than the knowledge thing, but it ties in together because you need wisdom to know what to do with what knowledge.
Right.
All right.
So yeah.
So the idea of divination and all that, again, one of the earliest things that I'd say in public was the animal sacrifice, all these things, blood and gore and temple procedures and all that.
Yeah, it's all lawful depending on which god you're doing it for.
Now, if you're stupid enough to want to do it for a lesser god, well, that's your prerogative.
You know, and also on the...
Well, yeah, you're kind of lucky.
Yeah.
But the thing is, if you understand the highest god, he's eliminated the venue for that, so there's no need for that because there's no venue for it, unless you have a personal message from him.
And to do that, and most likely these days, meaning past couple thousand years, if you were to get a personal message from the most high, you probably won't survive it.
So it wouldn't matter anyway.
You get it?
Right.
Not in this society.
No, no.
So the lives are too short to understand these things, but it's very simple, meaning the lives are too short, meaning 70, 80, 100 years, because, you know, doing the same thing over and over again long enough, you see a pattern.
And I don't think 70 or 80 or 100 years is a long enough time to develop the pattern as a fact or say things are this way with knowledge based behind it.
And also people are encouraged that knowledge is unpopular and being stupid is popular.
So that right away, that tradition is, you know...
Now, no one will say that stupid is popular, but everything they do sure shows it.
So that's what I'm looking at, not what they say, what they do.
Right.
Yeah.
So those are basically the two messages.
I'm still...
I'm just going verbatim.
I'm not verbatim, but from memory.
And then I got a couple of other messages regarding water and whatever aspects of early on Bereshith or Genesis, you know, talking about the name, use the name of the adversary and man and sons of gods and all that.
And that's a very big open subject because, you know, do you want to discuss the details of that alone?
Do you want to discuss the historicity of Genesis and the rest of it?
You know, you can't just look at Genesis by itself.
Genesis has three parts, by the way, actually five parts, but...
And then you go back to the other texts that support it and get the mindset together.
If you get an idea, you know, the two major parts in Genesis are very simple.
It's before flood, after flood.
That's like a central division.
Now, regarding that, there's a beginning that we are to know about, you know, which is the remodeling.
Basically, the centering of Genesis is the flood, essentially, because before that you have the various aspects of man, man society, and after that you get into the patriarchs, right?
Right.
So, and then there's parts, the patriarchs have divisions and so do the historicity of Genesis has divisions as well, but in essence you have the two parts before the flood and the three parts after the flood, which is the flood and the two sections of patriarchs, right?
Because you have the establishment of promises to Abraham and the promises to Israel, you know, and as that develops, right?
So those are the three parts.
And the first two parts, obviously, are the two men, the two types of men, the two various times of creation of the two types of men, and all the other infiltrations, right?
So...
Does this lead into the possibility about the fourth species?
The rest are hybrids.
Well, the other species, what do you mean by the fourth species?
You made mention, I believe, a sonic event or goal about a possible fourth human.
That's right, right.
And that would be a hybrid type, yeah.
Okay, that's...
I just wanted to clear that up, yeah.
Because, you know, when you look at types of people, like when he talks about the nations, look at, for example, South America, you know, where the indigenous people really no longer exist as a majority, or I don't even like to use the word majority minority, because it actually means things very different than what people think.
But by number, you know, like there was no Puerto Rico.
What do you do with a Puerto Rican at the resurrection?
Where do you send them?
Right.
I mean, there was, you know what I mean, the Puerto Rican Indians, you know, that got...
Or Brazilians, you know, I mean, or, you know, the mixture of the various people.
What do you do with the Mexican?
You know, that's one third Mestizo, Indian, Aztec, or, you know, and one third, you know, Ashkenaz, and one third from Spain.
What do you do with the mixed groups?
You know, because there is an aspect of returning people back.
So maybe these are new establishments, we don't know.
We're not given the small little things.
It's very easy.
What do you do with an Israelite?
What do you do with a Philistine?
What do you do with a Greek?
I mean, you go back to, you know, where time immemorial.
So there's many, in other words, the fine point about the other species of man gets down to that.
When and how, you know, did they come into history?
And why that little aspect is the optional appearance in historicity is not addressed.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
And but also, you could look at that as a mirror image back to when, in very early man, how they developed into various mixes like Brazilians, Mexicans, Puerto Ricans, and so on.
And I think Australians and New Zealanders are now a new species on the map because, you know, the Aussies say g'day, and the Kiwis say mate, oh bro.
And so they're another species now, right?
That's another thing, how different styles infiltrate into a whole society.
And I've been noticing that quite a lot lately.
You know, there are some that walk around.
Go ahead.
No, go ahead.
What do you mean by that?
Well, there are just some that walk around like, the walk, the different styles, I guess.
Some are more harsh.
Even the music, which always astounds me, you know, who could be the loudest?
Oh, that's just a...
Very intrusive stuff, you know.
Whose dick is bigger.
Correct.
Whose tits are bigger.
But, you know, the overall fashion sense is the poor.
Like, the pants hanging down and the hat to the side.
That's the poverty mentality.
No one is aspiring.
And well, the thing is, I mean, the upper classes, which are still slaves, they're now aspiring to that poverty class fashion.
You know, I recently saw a photo of a black billionaire, and he's wearing like one of those wrappers as a clothing company.
Looks oversized t-shirt with a big stupid logo on it.
I mean, it's really stupid.
So, you know, so even the wealthy are aspiring to the poor fashion.
It's just amazing how that's infiltrated into the whole gamut of things.
Well, that requires meditation, you know, a history of it, you know.
And you're really breaking up there, Bruce.
So those are just...
Yeah, it sounds like you're underwater.
I don't know.
I just went, I just got rid of the wireless.
So I'm wired in, plugged into the internet.
So I should be fine.
I don't know if it was on my end.
So if there isn't anything else, I don't, is there anything in the new Greek speak chat?
Let's turn that on and see.
It was on there before now.
And I just got an email.
Let's see what it's about.
Okay, well, the emails get into it all.
Well, yeah.
Actually, if you've been, quote unquote, following or listening to Greek speak for a while, you have plenty to chew on.
Always studying and learning about how piss poor the internet is and information, especially when you go back more than 50 years.
And I'm still wondering what's going to happen with what's quote unquote, the New Testament.
I still don't see any movement.
There's a bunch of stuff regarding Aramaic primacy, back and forth.
There is a lot that's been done, but not enough.
So we're going to have to look and see because that's one of the promises, right?
Whether you know the New Testament or not.
Well, you cannot know, let me just say it this way.
There is no New Testament, right?
It's all one continuous document.
So, and again, everyone in any character or event in the biblical text has been subject to identity theft and misrepresentation.
So, and I don't mean Gnosticism, which is bunk, or all this new age philosophy or astro theology, which is garbage.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about just the story has not been told yet.
Whether it's what you call Old or New Testament, it just has not been told, just corruption and distraction of it.
So, you know, what's interesting is when you, if you in the past had spoken to anyone, if you discovered that the New Testament had nothing to do with Greek until later, right, much later, when you start researching it and you start telling people what's really in the New Testament, most people that are familiar with the contemporary lie will say that can't be because it sounds too Jewish, right?
So, and they don't even know that Jewish is not Jewish.
So it's not biblical, let's say.
So there's still a long way to go, but I think a lot of stuff can be put together very, very quickly.
And one day, maybe when more things are out, there could be some more viable discussion.
But again, the discussion cannot proceed or even start if the mentality or the imagery in the story is wrong.
You know, if you bring up Adam and Eve or the Satan or what they call God or the gods or anything in the Bible, Abraham, Moses, Noah, all the way down, the people's concept of it is incorrect.
It's not scriptural.
And it's not that you have to make something up.
It's just that it has, the original stuff has not been examined as it should be.
So, all right, with that said, I think I'm going to just kick off a little bit early, less than an hour, if so.
I made some adjustments.
Okay, you're really low.
Yes.
Anything else you got?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, we'll do it again next week then.
Okay.
You take care, Greg.
Thanks, Bruce.
See ya.
Okay.
Bye, everyone.