Good evening folks, we're live with the Greek,
and good evening Greek, and how are you
doing tonight sir?
All right, good evening, it's another week, Teriyaki
Tuesdays, right?
Teriyaki Tuesdays, yeah.
What they call the Pope's work schedule.
You know, it's funny because I have, I've
got all kinds of animals, and the meat
eaters, on the meat eaters I do what
I call Teriyaki Tuesdays, it's literally, I just
go to Walmart and get a big 10
pound bag of chicken, and lightly cook it
with honey, garlic, ginger, and tamari, or soy
sauce, and just lightly cook it, slightly, and
feed it to the meat eaters, right?
So, it's kind of like a joke, yeah,
and they know it, when you say Teriyaki
Tuesdays, they're like, oh yeah, where?
It's not Tuesday, you know?
We don't use that crap, you know, that
time schedule anyway, so.
So you know, whenever I'm doing the sonic
event, it's somewhere in the background I'm preparing
Teriyaki meat, animal meat, for the animal eaters.
That's a hard thing, by the way, for
those that want to just be totally clean
all the time, scripturally speaking, if you have
a carnivorous animal pet, you're going to be
touching, you know, meat to feed them, on
a daily basis, so, unless you have someone
else feed them, and then you sound like
the orthodox Jews that try to get around
their days off by getting someone else to
do what they have to do, right?
But I usually, like the bird feeders, I
call them cat feeders, because you load the
bird feeder and the cats get fed, and
you don't put the bird feeder really high,
you put it like two feet from the
ground, right?
Sure.
Because it's not a bird feeder, it's a
cat feeder.
Correct.
And I've counted a couple of birds a
day, you know, and they eat the whole
bird, the entire thing, feathers, everything, you know?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, the beak, the bones, everything, completely.
Not very different energetically than when you eat
an egg, you're pretty much eating the entire
bird, yeah, energetically.
So let's see, another week, what's going on,
we could make it a really short one,
I went back here, I posted something on
the tribal people, I think Apollo posted something
regarding a Christian missionary being shot up with
arrows by a protected island, a tribal island,
isolated.
Yeah, that happens all the time.
By the way, I think I've discussed publicly,
or on Skype enough, a lot of the
African quote unquote continent, because Africa is not
a country, it's a continent, and a lot
of the brutal dictators were into that, okay,
a lot of the brutality, Sam's the ones
that were put on brutality by the Europeans,
the Dutch, the Belgian, French, and English, you
know, like, you've heard of the country Rhodesia,
that's named after Cecil Rhodes, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Rhodesia is from Cecil Rhodes, so you actually
have a private guy, wealthy guy, that actually
owns a country, you know, no big deal,
right?
Right.
But a lot of the other guys were
highly educated in the spiritual realm, and when
they saw Christian missionaries come to their country,
they knew what Christianity was, not what everyone
thinks it is, it's a form of demonology,
and they would just hack these missionaries to
pieces, right?
Wouldn't you, if you had a demonologist come
into your country, and you were allowed to
do so?
Yeah, so it's no big deal.
All the religions are based on demonology, and
people don't know that, that's why it's best
to set yourself apart, but I posted something
about the Rook tribe, because I was familiar
with...
Fascinating little subject there, wow.
Yeah, I knew those guys, well, from being
around Vietnamese people for years, and partaking in
some business with them, they're quite interesting.
By the way, Vietnamese people are quite interesting,
they're like, you know how you have that
superficial politeness, whenever they meet an American, they're
like, oh yeah, my father and grandfather helped
the Americans in the war, that's what they
tell everyone, but when you get to know
them, and you have, they love to drink
by the way, well, who doesn't, but you
know, you bring like expensive whiskey, and it's
like, oh yeah, we're having a party, well,
when you get a couple of drinks, and
they're like, oh no, we used to hunt
Americans using the same tools we hunt pigs
with, we made bamboo spears, and traps, and
snares, and you catch them just like you
catch the pig in the forest.
Sure.
So anyway, so I knew, because I knew
something was fishy, but you know, a little
bit of honesty goes a long way, and
it's like, okay, great, that presumption is now
a fact, at least from them, you know,
so yeah, so there you go guys, with
that, so the Rook people are very interesting,
that article touches on a little bit, they
also do dream spells and all that, now,
here's the interesting part, when you read scripture,
you're supposed to avoid that, because you're protected
by Yahweh, and he's addressing the people that
he became a god for, where all the
other, well, he has no allegiance to protect
us in where we are now, because we're
not in that time, so you draw a
conclusion by, well, how much faith do I
have in him, or do I see that
technically he's not protecting me, and I need
to get witchcraft as a weapon, in a
modern day society, you see what I mean,
it's very tempting to think that, that's the
truth, by the way, you have to make
that choice, but what you're going to find
out is, if you do make the choice
for witchcraft as a weapon, in the modern
society, wherever you live, in Dakota, California, New
York, Arizona, it doesn't matter, Iraq, right now,
it will give you a tremendous amount of
power here, but you're going to be called
on it later, right now, you'll probably be
left powerless, literally, the creator has thrown pretty
much everyone to the wolves, you dog me,
but later, you'll be rewarded for it, so
I know, don't take my word for it,
I'm just saying it because that's the truth,
no one speaks about it that way, so
you have to make that choice, and it's
like Mishraq Shabnack and Abedinigo in the Book
of Daniel, when they didn't bow down to
the statue and they were threatened to be
thrown into the fire, they were like, yeah,
our god can save us from your fire,
but if he chooses not to, that's still
okay with us, right?
So, you know, that's the real reality, but,
you know, I've seen there are levels of
protection, but not directly like you do with
the magic, right?
And I'm not saying you should do it,
but hey, if you want to do it
and give a demonstration, by all means, I'm
not promoting it myself, or I don't think
anyone should really do it for the reason
I gave, but if you want to promote
it and put a YouTube video up instead
of all the crap that's on there, go
for it, you know, if you're already compromised,
you know?
Oh, that other video that you put up
a while back, there, Raka.
Oh, that you, I think you posted it,
I think I mentioned it, yeah, well that's
what's going on right now in reality, spiritually,
not physically, you're being destroyed spiritually by an
entities, entities, by the way, that have been
unleashed, but you don't notice it, you see
the results of it, I'll give you an
example, since we're on magic and all that
stuff, even on a pop level, a superficial
level, what they call Satanism, you know, it's
magic and human sacrifice, especially children and all
that, you go do the slightest amount of
research, when they do their rituals and child
abuse and all that, the assailants do gender
bending, gender switching, so if you're a male,
you dress like a woman, and if you're
a woman, you dress like a man, actually,
if you look up the Aquino and the
Anton LaVey, you know, the OTO, you'll see
photographs of them doing that, the man dresses
like a woman, okay, so when you see
these transgenders running around, guess what they're doing?
They're reviving that occult ritual, they don't know
it, but the occultists know it, you know,
the people that sacrifice children, the males dress
like women and the women dress like males
during the ritual, and when they turn on
the TV and they see the political system,
the administration giving permission for people to do
it and they'll protect them to do it,
they're clapping their hands, they're like, yeah, great,
finally, this occult, you know, quote unquote, which
is not Satanic magic, it's a form of
Baal worship, is now unleashed on society, it's
in your face, it's just no one sees
it that way because they don't, they're stupid,
you see what I mean?
It's very simple, I just said, you could
look it up, so the gays, the homos,
the sodomites, whatever you want to call them,
the transgenders are actually part of what you
call a modern Satanic cult, but it's not
really Satanic, Satan doesn't screw around like that,
it's various revived God and goddess religions that
are from various parts of the world, the
real Satanism, like the big governments, your institutions,
your medical industry, Christianity, Judaism, Islam, that's the
heavy-duty Satanism, the mainstream religions, you know,
the big juggernaut, the Titanic's class is Satanism,
you know, all your main things that you
subscribe to, the banking system is Satanic, right?
But the stuff that people call Satanic is
not Satanic, it's actually revived lower demons and
gods, right?
So anyway, right away you lose everybody with
that fact or truth of the matter, so
there's no escaping it, but there is a
way to exist, not even coexist, but you
exist by setting yourself apart from it, as
best you can, even though knowingly in the
back of your mind, just because let's say
hypothetically someone says, well, I study scripture and
I want to lead you to the Creator,
it doesn't mean you're still not dog meat
here, right?
99% of you will be dog meat,
I can almost assure you of that, but
by pure statistics, so if you want that
kind of power, it's all now, the greed,
need, fear and loss.
Greed, need, fear and loss is what you,
when you make an advertisement, you see the
old late night TV ads with the non
-stick pans, oh, don't you hate when you,
egg sticks to the pan, oh, no, don't
you want to always have a perfect egg,
yeah, you know, aren't you afraid of this
happening, no, so buy this right now, wait,
order now, and for the price of it
we'll give you two, right, greed, right?
Greed, need, fear and loss.
Yeah, and for five dollars, five bucks, I'll
give you yesterday's lottery numbers.
Exactly.
All right, we're going off the chat, which
is the new Greek-speak chatango, Nathan Brisk
podcast feed updated, okay, I see Nathan had
put up something regarding, oh, he's doing what
you're doing, but on a RSS or something,
is that what it is?
Podcast.
I'll just click on it, yeah, okay, it's
a question everything, yeah, okay, would like to
get some new audio monitors, and you say
design some that will hit the market soon,
no, not really, yes, but no, it's really
the way of dealing with sound, what I
do is I do build loudspeakers, but loudspeakers
are like buying tires for a car, so
if you have like a Yugo or a
Ford Pinto, you get a different set of
tires than if you have a Ferrari or
a high-powered, right, so when someone says
they want audio monitors or loudspeakers, I'm like,
well, that's like buying tires for a car,
you have to tell me what the rest
of it is, right, what you need, what
you want, yeah, but what I do for
people, you put 500 bucks in notes in
an envelope, and you ship me the speakers,
and if they're really large, you got to
drop like five or six, 50 bucks more
for shipping them back to you, give me
about two weeks with them, and you get
them back, and you plug them in, and
you'll be like, holy shit, how come this
doesn't sound like anything I've ever heard before,
so yeah, that's what I do.
Yeah, you did mention that on one sonic,
what you were attempting to do, and it
was quite fast.
Yeah, yeah, basically, because it's not, sound is
not understood, it's not a wave, it's what
it, you know, and also it has an
inertial point, so it's like a magnet, basically,
you set up a field inside of the,
inside of the loudspeaker that makes everything completely
coherent, so you don't get that combing effect,
like, you know, like, you know how cheap
speakers sound like this, you know, they kind
of have a sub, right, and then they,
and then you, the real high-end ones
sound artificial, I mean, all here in mono,
and you only hear in mono, right, all,
well, all audio sources are in mono, you
don't have a left-right flute, right, like,
when you look at an orchestra, all the
sections are segregated, are all on one side,
you have all the strings together, right, you,
so ultimately, even with two loudspeakers left and
right channel, you're trying to make a single
image, right, but you have a lot of
problems when you have all this energy going
out into the space, the subsequent out-of
-phase is behind in the box contained, so
the louder you make it, the more distortion.
I've approached certain companies like Magico and Wilson,
they have some interest, and so that would
be on the market, but the cheapest little
tiny monitor Magico makes is 10 grand for
a little, like, computer-sized speaker, and their
speakers go, their average speaker is $80,000
for the house, and Wilson, their smallest speaker
is also 10 grand, about $8,000 for
a little speaker, and the floor standards are
$40,000 and $50,000, so that's what
would be hitting the market from that perspective,
so I don't know if you have that
kind of, you want to, and then even
then, if you were to buy a loudspeaker
like that, that's so secondary compared to the
electric, the amplification and the other equipment, so,
like, Futterman, and it doesn't mean a lot
of power, like, if you ever heard of
Futterman's, they were seven, when he came out,
there were seven or ten grand per amp,
it was a mono, so if you wanted
a stereo, you needed two amplifiers, and they're
only rated at one watt, they were huge,
though, because if you can't get the first
watt right, the rest don't matter, right?
Yeah, right, right.
In terms of distortion.
Correct.
To get one watt of, let's say, audio
signal at no distortion at all is very
difficult, right?
Right.
The other way to do that is with
Class A amplification, so, but Class A is
running full power all the time, right?
Correct.
It's a push-pull.
Right.
And that sounds really good, and usually good
Class A's don't have an off switch, and
when you play loud music, you'll notice the
lights in the house flicker.
Yeah.
So, I have a lot of experience with
Class A's.
A Class AB, if you can design it
to be super linear, so you don't, you
know, so the switching, you know, is very
good, and it's linear, symmetrically linear, on both
sides of the circuit topography.
I'm not going to start explaining what that
means.
Then, then it starts approaching the power of,
approaching a true Class A, but the benefits
of an AB.
Right.
Which is just more efficiency.
And then you have a MOSFET amp, which
is an AB style amp, but it sounds,
some people prefer the sound.
I don't, for most of them.
Hafler made some good ones.
MOSFETs are, have a unique sound because they're
very high voltage, or higher voltage, just like
tubes or vacuums are.
Right.
Like, people like tube or vacuum amps, and
the reason why, well, because they're not solid,
you know, they're just vacuum tubes, you watch
the glow and all that, and you know,
if you listen to them all the time,
every year, you're gonna have to figure out,
you know, some kind of tube inventory, right?
Right.
And it's great when you walk in and
you start to see the tube starting to
get really bright, you're like, oh shit, that's
got to be changed, right?
But, but also see with a tube amp,
when it goes into clipping, it doesn't have
that harsh sound.
It almost has like this euphoric, like a
scream, you know?
It screams, but politely.
MOSFETs are the closest.
I'm a big fan of the old tube
amps.
Oh yeah, they're so smooth, sound warm.
They don't have to be, depends on how
you design them.
Like, I had a, who was the, oh,
the real basic one that they sold a
million, more than a million of them.
I recapped it and rewired it with silver
wire, and it actually sounded like a, like
a transistor amp.
It got very bright sounding.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, but the MOSFETs are like tubes because
they run on high voltage, high rail, high
voltage rails, right?
The tube amps, they're like 70, 80 volts,
90 volts.
The regular transistors run on anywhere between 14
and 30 volt, right?
And the MOSFETs can go up to the
high voltage.
So there, anyway, there's your brief scenario amplification.
Then you got wire, your signal path, and
then you get to the loudspeaker in the
end, which the trends do.
There's also, I'm working on a voice coil
design, which is how a true inductor should
be.
So, actually, I'm looking at one right now
on the desk.
I'll put it on the camera and show
you.
Should I start taking photographs?
But nonetheless, yeah, it's fun.
I mean, I grew up at the tail
end of the Radio Shack era.
Now, when I say Radio Shack, most people
think the store.
No, well, 1920s, if you said you're going
out to the Radio Shack, it was literally
a converted outhouse that had lots of wires
and crystal sets hanging out of it, right?
Or, and you didn't, you know, you probably
came in on the tail end of it
also.
It was really big in the 30s, 40s,
and 50s and 60s.
It got really commercial with Lafayette, Stereo.
They supplied the catalog.
I remember a bunch of those.
So, anyway, I mean, when I was nine
years old, the parents went on vacation.
I was about eight or nine, and they
left us with the grandmother, and they had
a big stereo council, a tube turntable, lots
of built-in.
And when they came back, said, how'd it
go?
And the grandmother says, well, he took apart
the whole stereo council, which I literally did,
and put it all back together.
And they're like, no, no way, because when
that thing breaks, we have to call a
technician.
There's no way he did it, right?
Well, she's like, seriously, he did it.
So, they pulled me aside and slapped the
crap out of me.
Don't ever do that again.
Even though it worked, even though it really
worked well, I took the whole thing apart,
looked at everything.
I tried to get eight or nine years
old, go to the library looking for vacuum
tube set topography.
Aren't you a little young for that?
Don't you want to go over here where
the children's books are?
Anyway, yeah.
So, okay.
So, basically, yeah, 500 bucks in the mail.
Send me the speakers.
Let me know.
Give me an email.
If they're really big speakers, it's anywhere between
500 to 1,000 each to modify.
And the shipping will probably be whatever.
But if you have like a tabletop or
a bookshelf or what they call a studio
monitor, ship it over to me.
Drop, put 500 bucks in notes in there.
If they're heavy, put another 50 for sending
it back.
And give me a couple of weeks, and
I'll modify them for you.
And I might even do some, if it
has crossovers or filtering, I'll upgrade it.
I'll properly wire it and install a periodic
acoustic inertial plane internally.
And you'll get it back, and you'll be
like, wow, what the hell's going on here?
The further away I go, the louder it
gets.
It's not supposed to be like that.
It's supposed to be like a campfire.
The closer you are, the louder it is,
right?
Yeah, it's really strange.
So, I remember once playing music, a modest
system, and the neighbor across the street says,
your music's too loud.
And I said, really?
He says, well, actually, I'm not saying it.
It's the neighbor behind me that said it
was too loud.
And it was the other side of the
street behind him.
So, it went through the street across, it
went the street across through his house, his
backyard, and the other neighbor's back.
So, he's telling me, I said, well, why
is it so loud?
He says, well, I'm coming to tell you
that the guy behind me thought it was
too loud.
I was like, whoa, and it wasn't that
loud at all.
So, what the hell's going on here, right?
I mean, I was playing a live, live
level, not, right?
So, yeah, I've got lots of sound stories.
Okay.
So, that's the thing about speakers.
It's like buying tires.
It's not.
Now, most audio, by the way, again, just
to finish up on the subject, there's a
big boom for a couple of years now
that you have self-powered speakers.
So, if you're not that picky and you
just need something to go and you can
get a pretty decent set of self-powered
speakers, albeit, you know, they're okay for studio
monitoring for 200 to, about 300 to 500
bucks.
They have the amplifier, everything built in.
Now, the NS10, the Yamaha NS10, do you
remember that?
It's a little bookshelf speaker with a white
cone, Yamaha.
Okay.
When they released that, it was a big
flop.
Nobody wanted to buy it because it sounded
terrible.
It was tinny and flat sounding, but it
became a studio standard because when they mixed
in the studio, if it sounded okay on
that, it means it would sound better on
anything else, right?
So, they balanced their...
Because most of the recordings didn't sound that
bad.
And by the way, when you get into
audiophile level stuff, you'll notice that it's really
hard to find...
It's no longer whether your system is good
or not, can you get good program material?
Is it well recorded?
That's why you end up sticking with older
records that didn't have a lot of equipment
to screw up the signal.
Or you go for labels like Deutsch Grammophon
or the CBS Digital or this other stuff,
right?
Right.
So, anyway, do you know about Deutsch Grammophon?
You know, I briefly remembered it, yeah.
It's a German...
Well, when you get their CDs, it has
a warning label on it.
It says, we do not use any dynamic
compression.
So, play at a low volume because you
play at normal volume and there's a high
crescendo, it could damage your system, right?
They don't compress anything.
Wow.
Yeah, there's always a little label on the
Deutsch...
That's why I like...
So, you know, you're going to get it...
Basically, it goes from the microphone to the
board to the master.
There's no buffering and no compression, signal compression,
uncompressed signal.
But basically, studios use like the NS-10
Yamaha, which is a crappy speaker, or the
Oritone, which is another crappy speaker, to make
music because that's what most people are going
to listen to in their car.
A lot of the early pop, especially the
hip-hop recording studios, when they would record,
they made a tape and they went downstairs
or outside.
It didn't sound good in the car, they
remixed it, right?
It had to sound good in the car,
right?
So, there you go.
There's the 10 minutes recitation on sound and
how the state of sound right now.
Okay.
White fellow tripping, all right.
Yeah, white people do trip all the time.
My country may look good on the outside,
but for a number of years and a
large growing number of pedophiles and incest, I
got to the point where they stopped reporting
the news.
Yeah, that's normal.
It's been going on for a long, long
time.
It's just coming out because we're at that
time where all things will come out.
It will increase also because, like I said
earlier, the revival of these ancient gods, you
know, when you see a tranny, that's not
a lifestyle or fashion thing, that is a
religious thing.
But they don't know it.
You know what I mean?
They don't know it.
It doesn't matter.
That's the fact as it is.
So, that part of that is a religion.
Hi, guys.
It was shocking to us last week, the
Greek mentioned the purpose of sleep.
Spent many years researching this with many dead
ends.
Yeah, of course.
I think even now, if you research, they
don't know why you sleep.
They don't know why your hands and feet
shrink when you're in water.
Okay, the answer is, I've answered it, but
I'd never gone directly into it and how
to improve that.
It'd be great if the, anyway, it'd be
great if the Greek could shed some light
on this subject someday.
Yeah, good.
I'm not going to do it now, but
I'll throw a hint.
The vacuum is, the body is under a
vacuum, right?
So, you know what pressure mediation is?
Like, when you move around, it's no different
than, let's say you have a bladder full
of water.
When you push on one end, it displaces
the fluid and creates a pressure on the
other.
You know, like imagine, you know, whether it's
air or an air mattress or a beach
ball or a water balloon or a condom
filled with water you're about to throw at
someone for saying something stupid.
Right.
But whatever, pressure mediation is constantly happening.
So, if the body needs to maintain a
vacuum and you're walking around and moving and
you have shock load on the bottom of
your feet and shock load, you know, you
don't notice the shock load of walking until
you break or hurt a bone.
Right.
If you had a broken clavicle, which is
a collarbone, you walk and it just, just
walking, it just tears you apart, right?
Why?
It's not, you're not walking on your collarbone,
it's the vibration that goes through the entire
skeleton, right?
Yeah.
You become sensitive to it.
So, all these shock loads that the body
is under every day and pressure differential, you
know, when you walk and you press the
bottom of your foot, which is soft and
gooey, not as much as your inner thigh
or your armpit.
Right.
But you're, you're creating pressure mediation, you're compressing
the bottom of the foot and then releasing
it.
So, you have all this super activity.
So, when you sleep, the body's vacuum, you're
not moving and what happens, that's why it's
very important to, to be on a bed
that is comfortable to you.
Right.
For your body, right?
Or what you like.
Like if I once had a Japanese roommate
and, and I would always trip on her
because I'd walk in at night late and
I'd turn, you know, look in, I said,
oh, nobody's home because the bed is empty.
And I walk in and I trip on
her because she never slept in the bed.
She slept on the floor always because they
sleep on what's called tatami mats traditionally on
the floor.
So, that would be comfortable for a Westerner,
that would be very uncomfortable, but I'm used
to, I could sleep on a picket fence.
It's no big deal.
So, but other people, you have to discover
what's comfortable.
So, once you get comfortable, you have a
sense of, there is no sensory displacement.
Right?
What I mean by sensory displacement is you
ever sit in a, on the edge or
side of a chair hastily and you're uncomfortable
and say, let me rearrange myself.
And you kind of rearrange yourself in the
chair.
Now you're sitting more comfortably because you display,
you know, you have a sensory displacement, right?
Right.
A lot of displacement just means to move
from one thing to another or one place
to another.
Right.
So, you have all these displacements that are
happening and how is the body going to
go into vacuum?
Now, it's in stable vacuum while you have
to sleep because in sleep you're not moving.
That's why people who sleep very lightly or
move around are not well healed.
Right?
What happens when you're sick or not feeling
well?
The first rule of therapy should be try
some sleep therapy, try napping, try resting more.
They know that.
That's about all they can tell you is
like, well, get some rest.
Right?
Isn't that what they say?
Get some rest.
Because there's, you've eliminated displacement.
So, what happens is you have built-in
system.
It's a download where you have to stop
and maintain that vacuum.
Now, I haven't, I don't know if I've
stressed the importance of the biological vacuum in
the body as much as I should have,
but I think enough people that have gotten
it and utilized it see that it is
the be-all end-all of all things
regarding the body.
Right.
Anybody who's ever, like I mentioned last week,
I got a pretty good burn and three
days later it was, there was no evidence
of it at all.
Right.
Where if I would have just, oh, I
got a burn.
Put some ice on it and some ointment.
Right.
I would still have a scar.
Right now, a week later.
Yeah.
There is no evidence of it at all.
So, and there are people you could tell
who's censored.
They don't understand a lot of these things
and you just, you know, you still, it
doesn't mean you can't explain it or still
re-explain it, but you have to be
kind of tentative, you know, and it's better
to work with people that understand it because
this is not about making the world a
better place.
It's about helping out those who want to
be helped.
And the creator or the spiritual realm will
let you know who want to be helped.
They'll give them understanding.
Right.
And there are a lot of...
Good.
Because there are people with good intent that
don't understand, but sorry, you still can't help
them.
If they're censored, you can't help them.
You gotta, it doesn't mean walk away and
leave them behind, but walk away and leave
them five steps behind or two steps behind
and try to find the ones that you
can develop.
Because the reason why I say that, because
if you need some help or assistance, you're
not going to go to the guy who
wants to learn, but is censored and hasn't.
You want to go to the guy who
is not censored and is working with it.
You see what I mean?
Right, right.
Sure knows.
That's the real reality.
It's not the bullshit reality that, you know,
the made-up reality or made-up perception
hearsay that people are told.
So, basically with sleep, the only thing I
could say about sleep in short, I should
do an entire sonic on it because I
could pull up notes that I have and
also I could give more direction on what
to look on the internet, but there's very
little done on it.
And don't believe in sleep studies.
Sleep studies are there to experiment on you,
capture your brainwaves and put a chip in
you.
Yep.
I know that sounds kind of crazy, but
the chips right now, you know, RFID chips
are so small that you could fit a
hundred of them on a grain of rice.
Yeah, yeah, nanotechnology and all that.
Yeah, it's above nano.
It's still above nano, but within it, nano
is overrated.
Right.
But they're small.
Like in the audio industry about nano pulp
paper and they sent me the article, they
made it seem so fantastic.
I said, oh, it's just a pulp hydroxide.
What you do is you dissolve something in
an alkaline, which is like Drano.
And of course it'll dissolve it and you'll
have sediment going to the bottom and stuff
foaming and going to the top.
What you do is you skim off all
the stuff on the top and you then
start lowering the pH down to seven and
you'll see more separation and the stuff that's
left on the very bottom is your nano
material.
Oh, that's so high tech, isn't it?
Right?
Yeah.
That's all.
So, it's basically the gluten part of the
fiber.
So, all the starch has been eliminated using
chemistry and you basically, you've left the skeleton
of the fiber with none of the starch
in between.
So, it still has the same strength, but
it has very little of the weight, right?
Right.
Just like your body.
If you took out all the bones in
your body, you have no strength.
The strength of what you can lift depends
on your skeletal structure.
Correct.
That's why the people that were on the
PCP, they got amazing strength, but they would
snap bones.
You told someone on PCP to try to
lift the car, he'd keep going and the
muscles kept contracting until he snapped the ligament.
He would actually start lifting the car.
I'm talking about like a 110 pound skinny
guy would do it.
Yeah.
So, it's this bone structure that gives you
the strength ultimately.
The actual movement and displacement is done by
the muscles.
So, anyway, yeah, that's about it on sleep.
Again, it has to do with the body
vacuum and all that and there's sleep therapy
and then the importance of sleep and we're
inherently, you know, have to submit to it
inherently.
Because three days without sleep is about the
usual limit that one can go safely.
Between three and five days, you can get
damage to your body the same that would
be like as if you passed out and
drowned for a few minutes.
And anywhere between six and ten days, you
can die.
No sleep.
That's like the main torture is sleep deprivation.
People are like, oh, sleep deprivation.
I get that because my neighbor's dog is
noisy.
No, it means that every ten minutes they
have a loud sound to wake you up
and or physically jar you to get up.
And you just keep doing it.
Because once you have more than ten minutes,
like 20 minutes is considered a power nap.
So, you can't let the victim go beyond
eight minutes or ten minutes.
Because it takes eight minutes or ten minutes
before the recovery starts.
So, even though it looks like someone's sleeping
for five or six minutes and you wake
them up, you know, to do the sleep
deprivation torture, it's like as if they fell
asleep.
And a lot of people have been killed
that way in prisons and government labs and
medical experiments and whatever.
Want to see how long you can go
without sleep.
So, after seven days, you get irreparable brain
damage.
Anyway, all right.
So, then the reason why is, again, it's
body vacuum, displacement.
And we've discussed, yeah, we get more into
the vacuum of the body because we maybe
discuss how it has to do more with
sleep and how eating seasonally has a lot
to do with it.
But when you talk about the body vacuum
and eating seasonally, then we have to also
discuss plants, plant life, seasonal plant life.
And plants are different during two parts of
the world and all that.
The one thing connects to the other.
And I'm not going to be like a
university for free.
Sorry.
It takes a lot for me to organize
that and for you and for me to
do it.
I'm not going to do it.
It's just these casual calls and stuff we
do are fine.
But I'm not serious about that.
You don't have enough time left to use
it anyway, unless you're just going to use
it day to day.
And if you're going to use it day
to day, what I mentioned on a clue
or hint level is enough for you to
take the ball and run with it if
you're the capable ones.
If you're one of the ones that might
be capable, then you should get together with
those who are more capable, which is why
the chat is there.
And if you're censored and not capable and
need a lot more training, tough shit.
Wait for the resurrection.
That's my view on this existence.
In other words, you're too fucked up as
a society to deserve good information as a
group, as a rule.
It doesn't mean that the exceptions don't exist.
But sorry, for the exceptions that do want
to learn more or whatever, tough also because
you're getting hints and clues that no one
ever gave me and I'm just handing it
over to you also.
So I don't want to sound like a
dick or be like this guy's a real
asshole.
What's his problem?
My problem is everything and everyone around me.
Just look at it.
What do you mean what's my problem?
It is a problem.
So anyway, you're here to die.
You're here to have X amount of heartbeats
and then die and then be resurrected.
So get over it.
In the meantime, clothing and shelter.
If you want real knowledge on how to
mitigate things and make life better, hey, you're
getting hints and clues here all the time.
Right.
Yeah.
So we'll see how it goes in the
future.
But I'm not going to set up an
online university for the reality of what's going
on at this point.
I'm not inspired to do it.
I'm not encouraged to do it.
And I don't see the advantage of it
either.
So there you go.
So we just best thing you guys are
going to get or this week, once a
week on this pathetic little sonic event or
maybe a podcast with Sam in the future,
maybe, maybe that's about it.
Yeah.
So let's see.
Let's go down the line.
So just to tie into that one more
time, you know, people say they don't say,
oh, you didn't even have any knowledge of
it.
They don't say that.
People usually say as a comment, they say
he didn't even have a clue of it.
Right.
You ever hear that?
Oh, you don't have a clue.
They don't have a clue.
They don't say they don't have any knowledge.
Well, you got all the clues.
I'm giving you clues.
I'm giving you hints.
Right.
So people say, oh, it doesn't mean knowledge.
No one says that.
They do.
You didn't even have a clue where you
got more than enough clues, more than enough
hints, more than enough suggestions voluntarily, just freely
given.
So that's my point there.
Generously donated.
Oh, yeah.
More than a thousand times more than you're
going to get anywhere else or ever else.
You're going to find that anywhere.
Nope.
And then once you learn how to piece
it together, you're going to start building it
up and get on the rectangle, which is
easy.
It's easier than when I was growing up
doing research.
I had to make time to travel to
the library.
Then I had it when I got what
when I got to the library, I had
to travel within the library.
Believe it or not, the library is like
a self-contained world of its own.
Oh, yeah.
And because sometimes if you get you need
to develop a rapport with the people that
run the library, i.e. librarians, and they
have their own levels of staff.
And when you get to know them and
you let them know the subject matter, they
have storage.
Also, they have things in storage that are
not out.
Right.
Not everything in the library.
And then you have them look in there.
And then it gets really fun when they
look in the area of storage that hasn't
been fully correlated yet, where in other words,
it hasn't been broken down in category.
That's the real fun.
Right.
Especially when you're like a young adolescent and
the librarians like in her early 20s and
kind of hot.
But anyway.
So anyway, and then you're eventually going to
find out that you need a bigger library.
That library you're going to is not specialized
or good enough.
You see how what it was to find
bits of information.
But I'd say about 60 to 70 percent
of what you could do could have done
that.
You get on the Internet almost instantly now.
But what about the other 40 or 30
percent?
Not not on the Internet yet.
Sorry.
I have proof of that time.
You still have to go still even fairly
decent universities, which are all crap, but the
more better, more, more better ones.
What they do is the new students, they
in the book, they in their dorms and
in the bookshops and stuff, they have these
little cutouts they put out and they say,
well, dear student, you know, you're new in
our college or university, whatever.
Don't rely completely on the Internet.
Not everything you need to research is on
the Internet.
Right.
So still and the danger of putting it
on the Internet is changing it, just like
George Orwell.
Who was not George Orwell's fantasy, just like
the guy who did Blade Runner as a
fantasy.
You remember the movie Blade Runner?
Real futuristic.
Well, guess what year that took place in
the movie.
Twenty nineteen next year.
Hey, folks, just like I said, you ain't
going to get no flying car.
So, yeah, look it up.
Blade Runner.
The year is 2019, right?
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, the Pope's work schedule.
You ain't got none of that shit, do
you?
Mm hmm.
Right.
None of that.
And you ain't going to get it.
Even if you went to the year three
thousand nineteen, you're going to get nothing like
that.
You're going backwards.
So the problem with most governments try to
figure out how to get rid of their
populations.
And I mean, like most of the people.
And I haven't gotten into detail because I
in the discussions I've had with people that
were hinting at this that don't want they
I see the problem is surmountable.
Let's say they had a scenario to, let's
say, eliminate, you know, three quarters the people
of the United States, which they want to
do like 80 percent of the United States
by 2030.
Right.
The problem is just picture either a city
or a suburb.
You got a house and a car, two
cars, a house and a car and two
cars.
So you go and you wipe out a
family.
You got an empty house and two cars.
Right.
You wipe out the whole block.
You got a couple of hundred houses with
all these cars sitting there.
Right.
It's not getting rid of the people.
That's the problem.
It's how do you rework the infrastructure?
You want to need no one needs cars
anymore when you reduce the population by 80
percent.
So we can do all these hundreds and
millions of cars in the U.S. So
if you want a metal.
Well, what you do, if you got more
than two sharpened pencils or two iPads, figure
out how to quickly dispose of cars without
getting into environmental mess, because it'd be great
to be able to throw an entire car
into a muncher, but you have all these
fluids and stuff could catch fire.
Right.
So if you have an invention on how
to get rid of an automobile very quickly
and efficiently, you'll do quite well in this
world.
Just send it to the appropriate parties and
they'll prop you up.
You'll just make their agenda a little easier.
You know, getting rid of the houses and
all that is easy.
You could burn them down like they did.
Most most houses are still flammable.
Even brick houses are mostly flammable because the
roofs with the inside timbers will burn and
collapse.
And once the collapse, you have something called
roof thrust, which will take the walls down.
Go watch go watch some old World War
two movies when or whatever, when they have
real life footage of burn buildings burning, even
the walls are masonry.
Once the roof burns in, you see the
walls come down.
You ever notice that because the roof doesn't
come down evenly and they're pocketed into the
masonry anyway.
So if you have a inventive on how
to figure out how to get rid of
cars and houses and all the junk that
people have quickly, you will probably be propped
up in advance because you'll be viewed as
being important in this hidden agenda, which is
a very real agenda, by the way.
Yeah.
People working around the clock, how are we
going to get rid of 80% of
these morons?
I mean, get rid of them completely.
And the remaining morons will not be in
a panic and also help us do it.
Right.
Not the government that because when you talk
about the government, city, local, state, or Trump
or whatever, those are the administrators.
They're administrators.
They're not the government.
The government is the will of the shareholders,
the ones that own the country.
Right.
Lock stock and all that.
So anyway, this is, you know, I'm not
for them.
If they said, you know, they got the
plan in place and eliminate 80% of
y'all tomorrow.
Fine.
Just let you know, I'm out of here.
Or if I have to go to fine.
Fuck it.
But, you know, if they're not going to
do it, that's fine, too.
Fuck it.
Right.
Don't make no difference in the big picture
sense.
So either way, pair of walking shoes.
Yeah.
But I just brought up some of the
logistics.
So you hear all these idiots say, oh,
they won't eliminate most of the people, but
they never stop and think, oh, what are
you going to do with all the stuff
they have left?
That's right.
Garbage now.
Well, obviously, you could redistribute on an equitable
or semi equitable level to the survivors, but
you're still going to have four times more
than you need.
You got to have to recycle it somehow.
Yeah.
So if you didn't have so much stuff,
they would have gotten rid of you a
long time ago, probably around, you know, 1950s,
1980s.
But anyway, that's stuff people don't like talking
about.
But anyone wants to brainstorm on that, I'm
sure there's plenty of people who want to
listen behind the scenes because you think they're
smart.
They're not that smart.
The best way to get rid of cars
and everything is with a big plasma beam.
Literally, they use it for mining, by the
way, where they it's very hot plasma being
anything that goes in it, regardless of material,
it turns to liquid or vapor and you
have ashes going vertical.
And, you know, anything like steel will turn
to ash and rise like mashed potato flakes
or or like laundry detergent flakes.
Right.
And anything heavier than steel or denser than
steel or alloy will fall as slag.
It looks like glass, like rainbow colored glass.
Yeah.
So, in other words, to get rid of
the cars, you can have like an eight
foot diameter plasma being two of them.
You just drop the car in there and
doesn't doesn't there isn't dwell time is not
required.
In other words, as long as it passes
the beam, it turns to the plasma or
very high.
Right.
And these are very various ways to generate
the plasma.
But anyway.
Mm hmm.
So there's your your little idea how to
get rid of all the cars.
They're ready to just get a guy.
I figured this thing about cars.
So they're really hounding this the CEO of
Nissan.
They got rid of him because he's using
was just like 20 million in Japanese money,
which would be two hundred million yen or
whatever, two billion yen.
Again, is about a penny.
They all do that.
So I wonder why they put him in
the.
You know, I wonder why they put him
in the.
Yeah, this is like, you know, no more
cars are no good.
Right.
So anyway, no, they're not.
So next time you're out there and you
see all these people, you got to thank
your car.
And that's why you're all still here.
It's not the getting rid of the people
that's involved is we're going to do all
these cars sitting around anyway.
OK, off the subject.
I don't see anything else going on.
Any questions?
You know, I should check out the email,
maybe.
All right.
So but I haven't been I've been looking
at the email for a while and I
haven't been answering them.
So if you send an email, I do
get to it and I usually answer it
within two or three days.
But I think I see here some more
than a week that I've not responded to.
So a couple of real long ones.
I have someone I think is a writer
or writes very freely regarding free will.
And I think people pretty much understand that
concept.
It's not free will as much as it
is basically choices that you have within a
confined setting like a ship going from London
to New York.
Everyone on there has free will to go
wherever they want on the ship, but they're
all going from London to New York, whether
they like it or not.
Right.
But but while you're on that ship, I'm
calling it free will.
But is it really free will or more
like choices?
It is choices or choices.
You're going to go sleep in your cabin
place, whatever they call that game where they
slide discs on the deck.
Right.
Shuffle shuffle board.
Yeah.
Or in the theater or, you know, go
look at.
Yeah.
Go look at all the fake.
Look at the women, all the fake implants
and and tattoos.
All right.
No, whatever.
You know, you guys movies.
I mean, some of these I recently saw
a video where it was like a vintage
break dancing thing.
These guys came out and this this vintage
breakdance or a guy who was a breakdancer
back in the 80s was an old now
old, much older.
He these people, young guys, modern were trying
to do breakdance lesson to the white people
on the ship and cruise.
And I thought it was a mall, but
it was actually a cruise ship.
That's how big they look.
It looks like the inside of a mall.
Anyway, it was funny because the guy in
the video, he comes out and he's giving
the white boys instruction.
I can imagine why they're trying to break.
So he comes out.
He just does incredible breakdancing because he was
the breakdancing champion in Canada in like 1985.
And they were like, oh, where'd this guy
come from?
You know, right.
It was funny.
But but the reason I brought it up
is because I thought we were inside of
a mall, a shopping mall.
You know how the lobby, you know, the
inside rotunda is looking.
But it ended up being a cruise ship
because they have these really fast moving glass
elevators and all that.
So I keep forgetting on how elaborate they're
like basically cities that float.
Right.
Floating cities, literally, you know, if you in
other words, if you lived in a small,
medium sized town and you went to one
of the big malls, I like the one
in Tennessee.
What is it?
The shopping mall of the Americas, the biggest
one in the country.
I've been in Nashville or something.
It's been in that one.
But anyways, it's it's it's more than so
if you're on a week cruise is more.
There's more.
You can spend more than a week and
still not see everything on the ship.
Yeah.
That's how they're set up.
So anyway, I'm giving that as a metaphor
for life.
So do you really have free will in
the ship or do you have lots of
choices?
Right.
Because your ultimate free will is to jump
off and be shark food because then you
wait for the resurrection.
You'll be just fine.
So anyway, I don't see much on the
emails.
Yes, there's quite a few emails.
Let's say last week was what?
The 20th, 21st or 20th.
Let me see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16,
17, 18, 18 emails.
I've seen them all since last week.
So it's not much, but nothing much.
Either answer back or I will get to
them.
Right.
Nothing really to bring stuff I brought up
already.
Yeah.
OK, if I don't know nothing else, anyone
else?
Nothing at all.
No.
All right.
Well, oh, another thing I'm experimenting with.
I think I brought up kratom before, right?
K-R-A-T-O-M.
It's an opioid.
It's legal.
It's an herb.
It's in the coffee family.
People that are trying to get off of
prescription painkillers have a problem.
Actually, I've gotten some emails since I've mentioned
they've tried it and they got off of
some medication that was real nasty without getting
the side effects of withdrawal using kratom.
And I recommend the green.
It's also good for pains and other things.
Some people, it gives them a higher sexual
drive.
Other people, it kills their sexual drive.
So whichever, you know, you got to experiment
and see which way it works for you.
But there's another one called Moringa.
It's M-O-R-I-N-G-A,
Moringa.
And it's a leaf.
It's on its own genre.
It's not like kratom, which is in the
coffee family.
And it's 24.
Moringa, it's similar to kratom.
It doesn't.
It's not an opioid, though, so it won't
have the pain killing properties.
And it may not help with withdrawing from
chemical opioids and heroines and things like that.
But it is, giving an example, it's more
nutritional.
It does give a feeling of euphoria.
It is antibacterial, antifungal.
It is an organ stimulant, antioxidant, and it's
25% protein by weight.
Let me say that again.
Let me give you an example of that.
Chicken.
When you eat chicken, I think you get
15% protein by weight.
So this is a plant, and it's 25
% protein.
Beans are like 7% protein by weight.
I'll give you an example.
So Moringa, if you want to type it
in the chat, I'm not in front of
the computer, and I'm going to make a
coffee, either for the Sonic, if we're going
to continue or not.
But try it out.
If anyone wants to experiment with it, it
ends up being about $10 for a half
a pound.
It's cheap.
It's like 20, I don't know, less than
10 cents a gram.
Give it a shot if you're looking for
a supplement.
It's a euphoric, it's an energy.
Yeah, it does every organ in the body
pretty much.
Well, all the soft tissue, it aids soft
tissue organs.
And I just got some today.
I've been playing around with it.
And it gives you like a little bit
of euphoria also, but it's not an opioid.
It's not an opioid like Pratam.
So that's another thing for the toolbox.
I think I gave it a quick whirl
on Amazon.
I mean, Amazon shows up, they sell it,
like 12 bucks for a pound of it
or something, organic.
Yeah, Moringa.
So anyone want to try it out?
What I do with that is when I
try something like that, I have a Popsicle
stick.
You just get a pack of Popsicle sticks
at the arts and crafts or the dollar
store.
Sure.
And you just dip like a half inch
into it, whatever comes up, scoop, put that
on your tongue, have it with a warm
liquid.
You don't want to ever do that with
a cold liquid.
It's always a warm liquid.
Right.
Not hot either, just warm.
And yeah, it smells like hay.
I would recommend it's on the on the
thumbs up list, like the Pratam.
Sure.
You know, for people that want to look
for something.
The Pratam actually has saved certain people's lives.
And I've gotten that firsthand.
People who are certain painkilling drugs that couldn't
get off and had various body aches, backaches,
injuries, mood swings, whatever.
Wow.
Yeah.
The Pratam has actually saved people's lives, believe
it or not, because, you know, withdrawal from
certain a lot of these prescription drugs that
are painkiller or whatever, like Prozac, even in
the mind control, things can drive people to
suicide or, you know, to the point where
they don't want to.
Right.
Yeah.
So.
And I'm not saying like suicide is bad,
like when you see in the movies, you
got a ship full of people and the
alien is going to eat him and he
says, well, I'll stay back with the alien
and blow it up.
OK, great.
You know what I mean?
Right.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Yeah.
We'll let the we'll let him come in
and you guys get on the escape pod
and I'll blow him when he gets in
here.
So, I mean, that's valiantry or whatever, you
know.
Yeah.
But these people are all depressed.
Of course, if you're not, you know, if
you don't have the causality of depression, you're
an idiot.
You know, people say, I'm depressed.
The world is unfair.
Well, it's like you got to hear it
from a depressed person.
Shit.
Of course, everything they say is true.
If you don't know that you're a fucking
moron, of course.
I mean, it doesn't mean you have to
be lethargic and complaining and whatever in a
way that's, you know, some people say I
complain, but I'm when I find it sounds
like a complaint, I'm filling in the rest
of it to make it edifying, you know.
Right.
Exactly.
So, there you go.
Moringa kind of rhymes with moron, Inga.
But anyway, Moringa, M-O-R-I-N
-G-A.
It's got the thumbs up so far.
Look it up.
The other one is Kratom.
K-R-A-T-O-M.
Get a green.
I prefer I've tried the whites and the
reds that don't do much for me actually
makes me feel like part of the furniture.
But the energy, the upper, the green Malay
or green horn, I like.
I enjoy that.
Yeah.
Fascinating.
You could do them together.
I think I just did some earlier, a
little bit of the Kratom and then I
waited and then did it actually about a
couple of hours and I did the Moringa
to try it.
It's pleasant.
You ever have a really good vitamin smoothie
or whatever or vitamin drink and it gives
you like that momentary, lasts about 20 minutes
feeling of euphoria because you just got an
energy drink or whatever.
It's kind of like that.
So, there you go.
And it is tropical.
So, if you're having problems with staying warm,
if it's cold out, probably unseasonably cold by
you, Bruce, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm still aiming north, by the way, with
the weather guns for two weeks now.
I haven't moved anything.
I have a large gun that's just parked
there open with water dripping in it only
because the valve doesn't shut all the way.
And remember, it doesn't freeze here yet overnight.
Right.
And I have another translator that's pointing north
and it's creating a tremendous amount of weather
on the entire northern conveyor all the way
to the Middle East.
It's just creating these large spinoffs because years
ago, when I talked about certain things with
Trevor, he says, oh, never block the north.
Never.
Whatever you do, don't block the north.
So, guess what I'm doing?
Blocking the north.
Never block the north.
So, good.
What if I block the north?
He says, no, don't ever do that.
Well, it's given me great weather here and
fucked up weather downstream.
Sure.
So, what me Wimmer Mad Magazine?
What me worry?
Yeah.
So, I give it a nudge every day
too, which is not fair because if you
don't move it around just even a sixteenth
of an inch, it gets ignored.
Right.
But we'll turn it around maybe in a
week and we'll make it really warm where
you are.
How do you like that?
Do you want to do that?
All right.
You'll have to coordinate.
I go, I always dress appropriate for it
no matter what.
Yeah.
So, anyway, again, these powders and leaves and
botanicals that I mentioned, they're technically botanicals, are
tropical sourced, but they are dehydrated and ground
up, which does change them not as much
as a pickle would change something, but it
is dehydrated, it is slightly changed.
It will eventually catch up to you if
you're in a really cold climate, no matter
how processed or pickled or transmuted, in quotes,
a tropical source food is, it will still
have a negative effect on you.
Right.
Because I remember a couple of times I
was out in the field and it was
15 degrees during the day and like five
degrees at night and everyone had coffee and
I said, I'm having coffee too, and that's
why I'm having such a hard time.
So, I stopped the coffee and I felt
better.
Yep.
I watch how much I drink during the
winter.
Well, it depends.
Here, it's like 75 during the day Fahrenheit
and as cold as 40 at night, for
midnight, towards the morning.
Right.
But 75 during the day, so it's okay.
Yeah.
You're not breathing cold air every time you're
outside.
As a matter of fact, it's still, if
you go into a closed car in the
sun, it's hot, even in the winter.
So, it's Southwest, right?
Yeah.
That's where all the old people go to
die years ago.
You know this, or does it go down
as Florida or Southwest?
Florida gets all the Jews and the Southwest
gets all the white people from the Midwest.
Oh my.
All the Jews from the North Northern seaboard.
Yeah.
From Jersey and New York and Massachusetts go
down to Florida.
I mean, it sounds like I'm being whatever,
but it's true.
If you ever go down to Boca Raton,
you ever go down to Miami, it's very
strong Jewish presence.
It was like many, as a matter of
fact, the Duke place is called Hollywood, Florida.
Anyway, as usual, not much going on in
the chat.
No.
With the new Greeks chat and nothing in
the emails that I see noteworthy.
And I guess we'll just call it a
Sonic.
Alrighty.
We can do.
Okay.
We'll see you again next week.
Thanks, Bruce.
Okay.
You take care now.
You too.
See everybody.
Yep.
Okay.
Bye.