And we're on live with the Greek and good evening Greeks, yes Yes, good evening late late afternoon some places of places all over the night.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, so What's cooking?
I I don't frequent Chats, I don't frequent Emails that much I check them about once a week There's not much.
There's nothing on the uncommon site I no longer link to the streams because a lot of red that site tends to Carve, you know dump a lot of stuff.
So just kicking back So, uh, there's many things to discuss.
I've been working on some interesting very interesting
Projects, it's really a singular project but involves many things like for example, if you're working on a car
You know, it's it's thousands of pounds of rubber steel and glass, but they're formed into forming different functions
This has to do with a sound recreation I've worked with a
Company called TBI to be I sound for a long time more than 12 years
Indirectly designing I designed some other stuff
Assisted with them and I've left
Working with them completely because I've noticed that anyone in the industry has to follow the industry and
reality no longer
Well, let's just say what people are doing in industry is does not reflect reality again, let's go back to the car
Ask any car mechanic or engineer to tell you what a car engine is and they're all wrong
Some will tell you well, it's a machine.
It's an air pump.
The only one says it's a reciprocating combustion.
It's none of that right It's it's very simple very it's basically anything anytime you set something in motion It wants to go to rest it doesn't mean rest does not always mean not moving rest just means a Pressure mediation of balance of pressure you see, right?
So if you have something that is creating extreme vacuum on one side and extreme high pressure on the other For it to balance out it might balance out and yield a positive pressure, right?
It's kind of like saying what's minus six and plus four what's minus two?
It's balanced out But it's still on the minus side, right?
So when it comes to things like sound for example You know, there's a for it.
There's a tree make sound in the forest
No one's here to fells and no one's there to listen to it
Well, there's you could look at it practically and practically
The only reason we perceive light and sound is because we have the organs to do so
right like the eye in the ear correct and if you understand how the ear works and
It's attached to a body that has tonality bone muscle blood
Water plasma minerals all these things.
Mm-hmm.
So when you're listening to reproduced sound Typically have stereo setups except for everything's going the opposite way There's disregard for it now with a little Bluetooth devices and cell phones, right?
But what people fail to recognize you that everything produced in reality is produced in mono When you there's no stereo like when you have a clarinet playing as one clarinet, that's mono There's no left and right anything, right?
Right?
So the idea of stereo, you know is to capture the source from two Receivers known as microphones and play it back on a similar setup to create the holography of sound right?
Hello Holography I call it right Okay, so ultimately no matter how you're doing whether it's multi-channel or single channel The tonality of the devices meaning the loudspeakers producing the sound must be in line with the human body Otherwise, it'll create fatigue I've been around like high-end audio systems where I think the most expensive system.
I've been around In someone's house to reproduce sound was about half a million.
This is a living room sound system, right?
Right and the average audio file could be anywhere between ten thousand to a hundred thousand.
That's fairly average For a stereo home stereo, right?
Mm-hmm.
Now all that's high-end.
That's like saying cars, you know, Ferrari, right?
You can't listen to any of that high-end stuff for more than 15 or 20 minutes without being irritated because it's made out of aluminum beryllium titanium various forms of compressed wood Right, right.
So what and also all the modern loudspeaker drivers have aluminum and plastics in them
Yeah, and the tonality regardless of the music that you're playing the tonality that is given off
Will irritate you like for example if you've ever seen any old rock and roll bands
They go on stage and they have these guitars and the lacquer finish is worn out
And mm-hmm
Why don't they refinish it because it sounds different when you do it, right?
Just putting a coat of lacquer on a an acoustic instrument will change in what type of lacquer it is And we also talk about what the Stradivarius the way they can't duplicate it It's because of the formula that they use to seal the wood, right?
Okay, and they can't tell the people what the formula is because it would be viewed as offensive vulgar and criminal, right?
Let's just say it has to do great, you know one human sacrifice, but it make a long story short Speaking to someone recently and there's Medicaid makeups that have human placenta and foreskins in it You know 400 bucks for a little bottle of facial cream, right?
Oh, you can look it up online It's it's anti-aging cream.
So it's not too far off but make a
short story long here
We noticed that
You're when you want to reproduce sound you want neutrality, but in essence the loudspeaker ends up being an instrument
So you have to still make it neutral because you don't want it to add coloration its own sound, but the material must be
materials must be natural so any kind of adhesives that are used in the paper or
In the wood of the cabin and all that must be natural
It can't be synthetic like people use and vinyls and things like that, right the drivers themselves
You have to go back to mid 20th century 1950s
Ultra-thin paper drivers with paper voice coils.
No aluminum or plastic Right, and then you have to understand a field like Ken Wheeler says There's not a branch of science that can define what a field is It's all you it's a wave a wave is not what something is.
It's what if something does what it does So when you have sound or light or anything projecting into a room the back side of it also wants to find a dissipation mode so What we're talking about here is we designed a structure inside the cabinet Which is an acoustic an aperiodic acoustic inertial plane acoustic?
You know what it means a periodic means it covers many frequencies, right?
This is periodic which is one frequency or a group of frequencies and it's it's a plane It's a very thin area inside the loudspeaker Very small gap because if you understand Bernoulli's principle the smaller the space the higher the velocity the lower the pressure Right, okay, right.
So you want it, right?
So so basically it's a it's an acoustic a periodic acoustic inertial plane
Now this is very similar to something TBI is doing which is an embedded transmission line, but there's such knuckleheads
They can't see the reality of it
So I took the idea of the embedded transmission line and thought to reconfigure it even though it's patented
Then I figured out the entire concept is wrong
You don't need an internal mitigation something to mitigate the wave because there is no way of the way of a secondary
You need an inertial plane.
So now we have an inertial planes first time in history We can actually put together a small loudspeaker with the total qualities that I described that has no Characteristic of coloration and It's actually quite unnerving to hear like when people want on a headphone that's set up this for a loudspeaker.
They kind of jump
They're like it's unnerving
They're like who sounds really like they're here and you start and you start hearing things in the background and also it requires very little power
Interesting
Yeah, well, that would make sense
That would make sense
4,000 4,000 cubic room a cubic feet room
Right requires only two and a half watts to bring it up to 95 decibels a human voice is 50 decibels, right?
Right Wow, so so it's very efficient.
So So this kind of thing So maybe I'll have some things available in about a year or two if I'm still around To market or you know put out so other people can get it right now.
I have a bunch of prototypes I've been working for quite a while on putting this together some interest in it, but what happens is They fail to understand.
It's kind of like Greek speak.
Mm-hmm You know the Greek speak is like stuff that anyone can comprehend and understand.
They just fail to do so, right by the way Speaking of the opposite of failure.
I want to thank Jay.
I did receive something from you It was extremely generous and it all came intact in an envelope.
Thank you very much
Also, I wanted to state this is the first person I've run into in about eight years
Maybe there's two others that have actually when they send notes in the mail have done it properly where they record the serial numbers
The only thing that was missing was a demand for lawful money on 12 USC section 411
But it seems like no one still seems to get the most basic stuff
That's why part of me is like I even why bother talking about anything because people always agree agree agree
I got it.
They don't got jack shit but You know what?
I mean?
So so even even during interchange even during interchange between one party and another you should always throw that in there Well, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course all your records, right?
It's a record Yeah, because I do for records, but I didn't know we had a man for lawful money And the end of the year you just don't let the IRS IRS you're doing that and they're like and they'll just send you back Whatever they took out all of it matter.
It's not a return Right between a return and then and then somebody taking something that they shouldn't.
Mm-hmm And it's still not lawfully.
Here's proof that you know what Dimitri says Dimitri Kalas of this, you know, the the sovereign state owns everything.
You don't you have non-redeemable money I mean slaves don't need money.
No when you're at it Well, if your whole life is a Monopoly game, you're gonna argue where you're gonna go and redeem that monopoly You can never get off the board, right, right?
so anyway, yeah, it's just Very interesting Greek very interesting.
Well, you do it.
Also.
There's a spiritual side to it That's why most people think they got it.
They actually I could prove you they don't they don't understand they think it's just a Something novel.
Well, here's the thing.
A lot of the Greek speak stuff is very novel and new You know Novell mean I guess to them So they think that they because it's new they get it, you know or because it's true They get it and I'm telling you very few people ever have it because it has to do with Let's just say doing the right thing, right?
Right and it's nearly impossible to do the right thing
So you have to try to do the right thing
Which means you can have to make a lot of compromises
so
Not not to sidestep you but I was speaking about your your inventing and I look forward to hearing more about that in the future
Yeah, well, you're not really inventing you're rediscovering and you're being challenged by problems and you and no one like stress
It says has ever invented anything in their mind.
Really?
You have to keep doing things to
Find out what works, you know
I mean like I I don't want to get into what I'm doing, but I still have to turn down
Consulting because they'll bring me like for example as a project where they were taking
Agricultural waste and processing it into hydrogen and they had this black goop and they wanted to take clean it up
And I was like, this is not
This is not water with black goop.
This is goop with water in it You just dehydrate or you can use this as a fuel.
This is primal, you know form of petrochemical here You could use burn it in generators and they freaked out They're like no We can't do that because we were just told the EPA says we should just clean it up and we're like no burn it And you put it, you know put it in a diesel and they're like, no, no, no.
No, so I'm like what's wrong with you you know, um so yeah, this And you know, there's just stupid people So after a while you got to say well Do I still want stupid people in my life and the answer to that is no then you find out pretty much being alone Right, even in the business realm, right, right.
So so you just manage and Yeah, however, you can't go on the boat.
Yeah Yeah, so with that said I didn't I usually I preempt if there's nothing going on I won't do a sonic but we're doing it We're here.
Is there anything?
Going on.
I'm in the kitchen right now making some Java, of course.
Mm-hmm And also I want to thank a few other people.
There's a couple of people very consistent Every month now for over a year and I like when they put a notation for six and coffee Right and again, I just want to thank Jay out on the east coast in the States It should be anonymous whatever but it's a few months of cigarettes and coffee and you know What my budget of cigarettes and coffee, you know, three four hundred a month.
So it's very thank you very very much again it was very generous and Yes, blackie I got a very talkative I have a colony of cats that have adopted yes, I remember you saying that Yeah, they're outdoor, but I have an old doggy door and I made it real small and they're free to come in and go They're totally they're free creatures.
It's real interesting to see how free creatures operate, right?
No, and they're trainable as well.
I've got I've got them pretty well trained
And they're hardly ever around
And you know, it's funny, you know, sometimes you'll you'll
You'll wake up and they'll bring a bird to bed, you know
Yeah, and they look at you and they're like you look like you need a little more nutrition
So I brought you this dog, right right or a mouse, you know, they look at you
They're like you look like you need some more nutrition.
So I brought you this mouse.
You're like, ah, man.
Thanks a lot My gift knows no bounds So here's this Wash all the sheets guy because it's dead.
Yeah.
Yeah But I try to make the sheets at home as unclean as possible.
If you know what I mean, I can correct so Okay, so what's going on in chat, I'm not in front of the laptop about 30 feet away Scroll up a bit here and see if we can find there was a Anyone want to call in to yes.
I did post that in the channel Would call in but have to go to bed early any discussion on God's more details Perhaps on things to come some info on coming seasonal changes dreading the cold water weather What is what is called sad seasonal effect disorder and how to cope with seasonal changes less sunlight?
And also idea of the Jews still expecting a Messiah when the Christ Messiah Yeshua Already came and showed slash proved the resurrection.
Is this false Messiah the coming Antichrist figure?
I realize this is a Explain that already.
Yes in a new time New Testament topic
So perhaps not to be discussed publicly if that goes into the book of Revelation stuff
Which is off-limits publicly and privately
I mean, I've had Skype conversations for years and I'm like, I'm not going to discuss the book of Revelation even in private
It has to be the right people and I haven't seen any right people in a long time
Let's just say are they the wrong people?
No, they're not the wrong people, but are they right people?
No for sure See and then there was another one here if it's appropriate to ask Greek to comment on one of the post links above it was from the bite show that featured a Shmo Asher Was curious about his leaning towards not eating meat as a way to keep what he calls the everlasting agreement If we are not to eat animal meat, why was the law given on which meats to eat?
Yeah, right.
I mean who's a schmuck is that guy gonna throw drop some Talmud on your ass the bite show Here's a comment on the bite show years ago.
I found out about Georgia and here's a her she passed away Yeah, yeah, she's what I call a goat you'll she'll interview someone and Talk about the most high or whatever like that seal off idiot.
Oh, you're so amazing.
That's so wonderful Thank you, then she'll interview another person say Yahweh is two-faced God or whatever goes.
Oh, you're so amazing Thank you.
I mean, she's like a goat, you know, she's anybody who's in front of her Anyone who's in front of her is the greatest, you know, whatever.
It's just a bunch of crap it's like all the other shit you see out there, but That's what the feeling I get whenever I look at the bite show.
I'd rather not listen any of that stuff because of her And then you could just look up the I know who's the who's the interview the guest on that?
shmol Asher Oh, that's very Jewish a tribe.
Oh, yeah, sure.
It's a Syrian.
That's a Syrian Jew probably Sephardic also Sephardic or Syrian Is he dry was he what does that go?
What does he do?
Come on there and drop some Talmud on your ass?
What is oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah big time big time Two to three hours worthy Did you listen to it?
Yes, I did.
Yes.
I did take any notes.
What are the salient points?
Oh silly.
Oh boy I don't Just give me notes and I'll tell you let's see soul harvesting Moon is hollow and that is a place where they're harvesting In sending back the soul without memory and all this kind of stuff.
You know what the soul is you could saw Like people right hyperglycemia, you could harvest the soul in a brown paper bag.
Just exhale Okay, next next subject more dummy.
Yeah, well based on just what has been presented so far I guess we can say that there was a high concentration of brown 25 to corn and Well, there's always the the topic I've discussed this for many years now.
There's going to be more interest in the topic Will any of it be accurate?
No, is it as a general thing?
It needs to be thrown out But like for example, I have a CD player that died recently.
Mm-hmm.
I was like this isn't irreparable.
But wait a second I know if I open it up I could pull out a transformer You know, it's an high configuration winding.
I could use that.
Yeah, sure Sure, I mean, I just put it on the shelf because if I go to Elliot's electronics to buy one They're gonna charge me 12 or 15 bucks easily 3 amp 3 amp winding, you know 3 amp, you know 120 volt winding so why why not just pull it out and put it in a box with the rest of the windings, you know And pull out a couple of Mylar caps in there.
They had some pretty high-value 50 microfarad mylar caps that were small.
I know like those are 20 bucks apiece Easily same thing with this.
This is a dead.
This is a dead interview But if you can get something out of it, but you have to have discernment.
It's very well to ask that question At whoever did in the chat means they lack discernment I mean they could it would have been better off they put in This guy thinks the soul can be harvested.
What a moron the soul is, you know I would rather than a question is a person asking question The chat tells me that they're not listening to Greek speak either.
They don't get it You see so why bother?
Okay It's skimming around here Question before about okay the Weather-extreme weather like as you get older pain and heat become I mean cold and heat become more painful Tolerable look when you're young you can go out in regular clothes No jacket and play in the snow your hands turn pink.
You can't they're numb and you're fine You try to do that when you're 50 55, you're not a good idea.
Yeah, not a good idea It's like bone-wrenching pain, right?
No now
If you are more susceptible to the cold and that season is coming
Well, obviously one of the credos is to avoid tropical foods
But now you're gonna have to go the other way to aid your body into adapting
So not only do you avoid the tropical cold foods now you try to seek out traditionally
What was done in cold climates which would be if you're gonna have animal flesh, it should be dried and cured fatty and salted
Right if you're going to have veg it should be pickled
Right cured.
Mm-hmm if you're going to have Food it should be very well cooked overdone Right.
Mm-hmm Because it's easier for you says different energy actually puts time to roll up root Root vegetables things that are under the ground, you know If you go to a farm in the middle of Minnesota when the freeze what can you get nothing?
But you know if you if you if the soil is not that hard You could dig down and pull potatoes out and they're just fine, right?
You can go down with two feet right during the frost line.
There's pretty good.
It's like two feet to 16 inches at least Yeah, but if you go below the frost line, it's good So those things that are hardy in the cold you should eat like I know Things like collard and kale will survive a freeze Right, you know collards and kales.
They won't survive a hard freeze, you know Which when it stays cold for a long time, right?
You seek out very very very robust greens and root vegetables that again the root vegetable should be Temperate climate not of tropical nature, right?
So there's your simple Solution to making it even better in terms of seasonal change.
It works.
Also if you're going to go to an extremely hot place You not only avoid of course normally the foods that were grown in temperate climates But now you're going to seek out things that bloom or grow well in the heat and that will aid you To adjust to the heat.
So right
Mm-hmm
So that's simple and the other
What was the other question regarding the Jews and the Antichrist that goes in a book of Revelation stuff, but the
What you have to comprehend is what happened with Moses and Exodus Moses was an Egyptian
Okay, one one second you can mute if you want yep, I'll do that
so Moses being an Egyptian then a leader of the Hebrews, I'm using that term loosely and
Then recognized as a prophet that gave them the law
And that's how basically the Antichrist is going to be and is actually a parallel there
that's why
in your
crap
Bibles it tells you in Exodus 34 Moses came down as he had his face was shining
Right well actually he had horns and Michelangelo knew that because when he sculpted the Moses
Seated in one of the basilicas in Rome you have Moses for these little goat horns on his head right or lumps on his head
That's why when you read about the Antichrist.
He's accompanied by someone that also has horns See, so that's why you'll never gonna understand the book of Revelation because you never understand them The written the Old Testament and what's called the Old Testament and It's how we got ourselves a caller Greek Okay, let's go.
Yep.
Okay.
I'll get them in here And caller go ahead oh Hello greetings greetings cell phone while you're traveling Yeah, I'm traveling right now Okay, but Yeah talking last time.
I called in there's a reason why I got cut off so sometimes when you're talking about the gods you have to kind of calm down and Use your big words for a little bit, but I wanted to say Just calling about using the Greek speak.
I took your advice.
I found a an art skill and I excelled in the art skill now.
I'm teaching and Yeah, it's pretty good it's pretty pretty good so far.
Oh good yeah, I'm just calling in and say thank you and God I had a whole bunch of stuff.
I wanted to say but anyway think of it right now.
Oh, no Where were you guys talking about before?
You want to tell us more about the art skill and maybe how the method what methodology used and maybe a little roundabout outline if
You want to keep it anonymous, so maybe someone else can use it as an example
All right, so listen if you want to fill us in on your endeavor
Yeah, so I started listening in Greek speech probably for about a year now, and I've been applying it for about
almost a year Pope work schedule and it's been
It's been helping me tremendously
And you still kind of around some people that you know friends and family.
They just don't get it so you kind of live in this dualistic mindset that schizophrenic type of deal and But I've been using a green you do or they do yoga I like this you have to like well, cuz what what woke me up the most was um the kid was a baby goat and Finding out that I didn't know that until I was 24 years old, and I just found that out.
I'm 25 now and
that was almost like
Reality shattering almost around me because I've been calling kid
I've been calling me a kid all my life
and I did not know that and I've been to petting zoos and everything before too and
I like to call that almost like a snapple fun fact
Like I've like almost like a you know like a school of whales is a pod
But I didn't resonate with me until a kid was a baby goat for 24 years almost 25 years and
That was a pretty pretty
Awakening for me and I almost went to my demise for a little bit.
So I had to kind of pull myself right together I found an art yoga.
I Was kind of successful in it really successful It was kind of like almost a hidden hidden talent I had and I'm part of the studio right now.
It's a high-end studio.
I'm from the Golden Ghetto Type is the Golden Ghetto the southwest With all the McMansions around so it's not It's a pretty high quality studio But um, yeah, do you teach the ladies happy baby pose?
Yeah I'm Surrounded in the Vipers gun around justice is everywhere.
So that's all I've been seeing lately this past year is justice This justice that justice.
Oh, yeah Yeah, they don't know what they're asking for but they're gonna get it.
All right Yeah, so then Venus so we're in Mercury retrograde right now right and then so Venus is coming up to almost in October Right, right Yeah You're gonna see that in the West it's very bright It's not a star looks like a very bright white golf ball.
You can see it with the naked eye Okay, we keep an eye out for that Yeah, and then rises in the And then in California right now, there's a bunch of fires going on a new fire They're calling it Yeah, I let it burn, right?
Yeah, it's it's a for it's it's that's natural By the way, but for that to happen, but it's not natural.
I mean they Someone's having their fun.
You know what?
I mean?
The
Technology today they were recently here like in the southwest about recently ten years ago
There was a huge fire and they didn't want to put it out
I mean someone was having their fun and
They wanted to bring in a Lucian 7, which is one of the largest freight planes in the world
Russian flight plane to just jump dump, you know 100,000 gallons an hour on and they said no, it's too big of a plane
So they're just having their fun
I want to go back to terms of having fun when you when you hear about all the pedophilia scandals
with children being abused or raped or eaten
Nothing is ever gonna be done about that in a big sense because if you listen to the Dimitri
Kalashov video, you're not people your property.
You're not free people So for these elites, for example to do what they do to children From a juristic point of view they have every right to do so.
I'm not saying this I'm not saying that they do but they do because they own you you're like property It's like they're not doing it to the children of free people.
They're doing it to children It's no difference than if you went to a planet and they were raising people in tanks for food Right, you what are you gonna say to them?
Stop doing that?
Well that we've been raising people for food for thousands of years.
So that's why you're not going to see anything done with human trafficking or Pedophilia rings or child sacrifice because those are not the children of free people.
Those are the children of slaves You see what I mean?
So your yeah, yeah, they've never they never Ever dare to touch me.
They never dare to touch me, but I wish I can say something about my friends But oh, I know.
Yeah, it's more rampant.
So when you bring up the children So what they do is they have the goat thing in your mind constantly See the state uses and the corporations and the schools and the churches use the kid kid kid to keep reminding you You're nothing but a piece of meat.
You're not a free
Lawful society you're nothing but a P and now I'm not saying I'm not condoning this
I'm not saying that children should be I don't think anyone should be abused
I recently someone is wants to adopt a bunch of beagle puppies and one just took a big poop
You know in front of you, you know near a shoe is that what you can't beat the dog for that
You shouldn't know as any people whether there's slaves or free
but I'm saying nothing will be done in a juristic point of view from the powers that be because you are not free and
Your children are not free.
You're just material So the the abuse of children the rape of children this human sacrifice is not going to stop Because they're not doing it to free people.
They're doing it to their property.
I Don't want to hear the New Age moral shit.
Well, they're humans.
No, they're not They're humans humans can take various status and you have the status of property.
That's why nothing will be done
It doesn't matter what political or moral leadership is put in is put in front of you until you say
So anyway continue about let's I don't I want to just turn around and go all the way back to the yoga
so you're pursuing the yoga and
You're trying to apply Greek speak and all that and everything's I yeah
I I've been in fine Greek speak and I've been excelling in it and
I've been having all these opportunities come up and I
Like a the thing about this video.
It's not really new agey.
So well yoga subjective And so it's whatever you want it to be and I'm putting the objectivity in it And I'm telling all that you learn the Buddhist story the love story and everyone's digging it and it just made me Like I've only I started practice.
So using the Pope work schedule for simplicity reasons, but last October I started I got into it last October and then I They had the teacher training coming up and I wasn't gonna let the money stop me because you know Money is just a credit.
So it's $3,000 and to most people be like, oh my god
$3,000 I kind of just did it and then I had some all these opportunities come up and so the money wasn't an issue and
Yes, I did the teacher training and so then I just started teaching and then I started getting they're starting paying me in credits
That's how I went to the bank and I went to all these different banks and I knew I was doing it wrong when I signed
Right, but they wouldn't they literally wouldn't let me they wouldn't do business with me and that's I
Signed on that pad.
So I kind of screwed up on that one Wait, well when they want you to sign the pad Just say your attorney that they freeze when you say your attorney your accountant wants you that wants you to give them something on paper Mm-hmm.
So just have them don't tell him you want it.
You always use a third party when you read the biblical text
It's all the Christ speaks in the third party
Yes, nothing, you know nothing yeah, yeah, so I did I did that same thing
The
Administration in the hospital because I had to go to the hospital and had to go to the ambulance
And so I went to go get the cash receipt and I was talking to this lady cash receipt
She didn't know what I was talking about.
And then there's
My attorney needed it and then right when I said my attorney they froze
exactly
Because they're ruled by the attorneys
They use the attorneys for thousands of years now to rule the slaves and don't don't misinterpret
The attorneys not knowing any law at all because if you're an attorney and you learn law you're fired
So just like a priest with the biblical text or a rabbi same thing.
So or a doctor with the body Essentially the do you know what let me just quiz you here on the spot Why would you ask for a cash receipt for a hospital registration form?
See, that's what I was trying to you need a cash receipt because there will there I'm trying to figure that one out.
So I Because that registration form that registration form has a cash value They don't tell you what it is.
It's a blank check Yeah, and then they write whatever they they can on it right and then they Write the back of it.
Yeah, same thing and they say yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
So the This your signature has a cash value right anything any time anything administrative right anytime you endorse anything and you're the only one that has a that's basically a check and Imagine you had you're a billionaire An open check so you want say well instead of a cash receipt Why don't you give me a receipt that you you that you actually wrote you filled out the form?
It don't don't say cat
You know if it is say I want a receipt for the form not a copy any the separate receipt you see
Or I would like to have one you see that's where they kind of freeze those
I'll give you a quick story a while back a lady had a
Corporate people with insurance they had a baby and they still got a bill for 50,000 because they were just being screwed with
You know and I told him go in and ask the hospital
Administrator for a cash receipt for the paperwork you sign and then what happened they called back a week later
Do I owe you guys 50 grand says no you don't owe us anything
You get it well
Is it a baby signed it?
No because they knew they were being messed with
Yeah
Like when you get a credit card, and you get you spend
Let's say 2,500 bucks a month on you get a bill end of the month
You don't know that you don't owe that there's that money to pay that doesn't exist
I'm not saying if you think you owe it you do owe it right there is messing with you
Let's say you have an Amex American Express card, and you get a bill at the end month.
That's not American Express That's an administrative office that uses American Expresses letterhead and letter express Which was strong-armed years ago by administrative authorities and the owners of the country and attorneys to do that to give out their You know and there's different Companies you know so the thing is anyway.
It's a lot.
It's it's
Ultimately they've established that all of the population is not entitled to a redemption you see what I mean by that
So yeah
At least at least if you and let well okay
And the last thing you want to do is tell another tell one of these slaves something like that they get upset
You know they don't you know you heard me say like even family members
They want you to do better, but secretly they're saying I want you to do well in life
But not don't do better than I'm doing right
So if you go to the bank
Yeah, when you go to the bank and you deal with them
They they don't want anyone coming in there that thinks that the note
They know more about banking than they do they get offended the same with judges attorneys and doctors and priests right anybody
So you that's why there's several things you might read somewhere appear as
Harmless as a dove and built be as wise as a serpent.
I'm just loosely interpreting that But that's okay, I just this is an interesting What's okay?
Is that you're trying it and you know when you do it one way how what you what result you get because if you didn't
Try these things you wouldn't know you wouldn't have any result, so thanks for sharing that
Yeah, yeah, and then I wanted to say about I guess about scripture knowing what we know about scripture and America is going to
Be like the second power or whatever to the Middle East Union
Right if you did have a bunch of money in the United States, and it's in US dollars
And you needed to convert it over.
I don't know.
I don't know what kind of currency.
They're going to use everything use the shekel
Most likely something really unified well they have the real the shekel the dinar
So it depends on we're going to see how that pans out, but it's all credit remember in the end
You know what people invest in stocks to hedge off
Losses in in earnings in the economy that they might be
right
eventually you might want to consider substance based things, and I don't mean just silver and gold but
right now unless
Unless it threatens your livelihood.
I wouldn't think about it too much, but always research it you know what I mean Yeah Financial advice one can give on that, but it not I did not have a drop of a hat like that You have to really get into a pretty detailed discussion on it.
You know So whoever's listening can can have a more informed decision in other words what you would might be let me just rephrase what you might Be asking how do you make an informed decision that will be profitable?
Not it versus.
What do I do?
Exactly Because if someone asks you what do I do and then it doesn't work out then they're stuck But if you understand how to make informed decisions as the conditions change you can change with them you see Yeah, I can see that and then Kind of bring him back.
I only have a like five more minutes, but bring him back with the conversation You guys had with Sam and everything You guys are talking about how this is kind of like a game and everything different levels well I'm almost he was I wasn't he was you were because he's a game boy.
I wasn't it's not a game But that's okay, it's not a game.
It's a lease agreement It is a lease agreement right and then so what does the justice have to do?
She does she have any agreement on this lease or she's just running a havoc
Both there's many many many many many many gods you don't only have and there still are
Subcultures that don't have a female deity you know there is a lot of the Zaroastrian stuff going on
You have a mixed bag of things going on, but the justice or the goddess religion will prevail
As it is as you see it prevailing, and I think I've described what the purpose of it
Is it's basically to create a superior race by male unions and female unions, and then the children know are asexual or bisexual
right
It's to destroy the natural order.
Yeah of Not only with humans, but with plants.
That's why you have GMOs with drugs All kinds of stuff anything to destroy the way the mechanisms work You know with a male female and and procreation any procreation plants animals humans She's against that Yeah, it's gonna be yeah So many people have tattoos too these days.
Oh, yeah, I'm lucky more.
I never might have never gotten to that Yeah, but yeah, okay, well um good.
There's a much more.
I can say I got it.
I got to run in the studio right now, but You guys have a great great rest of the evening.
I would like to call back next week, maybe Okay, thanks.
Thanks for doing so Yeah, yes, and thank you for calling in And no problem.
Have a great night.
All right.
Bye.
Bye be safe also.
Bye, okay?
I Was a good bit in this I guess or you know Yeah, I would suggest that anyone and everyone that I've ever discussed Privately and publicly that they have adopted something out of Greek speak.
They've all stated on their own
Volition that the their lives are better
Mm-hmm over overall overall and and because they also most of them do appreciate that they're living around scum
bags, whether it's parents friends family brothers sisters workers neighbors
You know it's better to know the reality
Of these people than to be living in the pink bubble right like I've had a lady once she was an attorney
She goes.
I'm not saying what she told me.
I'm not saying what you're saying is wrong I just don't want it to break my pink bubble.
I like the illusion that I'm in that the people around me are good She was honest, and I'm like yeah And I'm not saying that humans are Assholes or scumbags the ancient Ritz do so and actually they can be proven correct as a general whole That's why why do you always see for example even portrayed in what you call Hollywood?
For many years the aliens are always aggressors against humans right right right like when I watch one of those movies
I'm rooting for the aliens
You know nothing
Even though I'm yeah, I'm embarrassed not because
You know I choose to do that it's because that's the truth look the aliens are trying to clean it up
You see I spend way more time now by myself
And I'm more pleased than ever to do so
Absolutely yeah, yeah, yeah, and there's an option
There's an option that you can take but at the option always reminds you of that
Absolute solitude that was where the real stuff gets done.
Mm-hmm.
You see what I mean.
Yes, yeah So and if anyone doesn't believe me you could go look at even philosophers not even the ancient Ritz especially the scripture Which is inspired?
very poorly Throughout the ages humans are spoken of very poorly.
I'm not saying that there should be wanton Violence against them right just like just like you shouldn't go to a swamp and kill all the piranhas for no reason But you recognize they're there Simple enough yeah, or the snakes or roaches.
You know there's no reason to kill all of them No, or whatever you know or violence against them.
No not at all.
They have their spot, and I have mine I
Mean I have a large composting bin for the garden and they get these
Large American roaches that could be up to an inch and a half long oh my and they love the cut they love the compost
They're in the backyard sure sometimes they get into the house right or whatever
But yeah, they can fly they go up to a high area, and then they jump and they fly down
They kind of hover down.
Oh my what when they when they develop their turf you walk over to the compost I had one that was like pre-dawn They all scattered away, and then one turned around and kind of sat up like I'm gonna defend this you know and he could squash But I'm like why should I squash him, but most people have the impulse take your shoe off and step on them Yeah, I'm looking at the guy.
I'm like wow what a cocky son of a bitch right really Like an attorney or something you know right right so or a doctor or a priest Them a little scooter of the yeah, yeah, I just leave him alone.
You know there's no reason now some people have been brought up to to Automatically destroy them like instinctively yes sure yeah the instinct to be violent right All right people like that Actually, not a whole lot in the in the chapter Greek not a whole lot.
Yeah, at least in the one that I'm at Yeah, okay, but that that's we got a caller, and I was also if Haven't you noticed I think or whoever that was the lady that called in was it have you Whoever I Whoever it was I mean who that was she that was a good Call in this person also whoever you know having a slightly different Input on these sonics is helpful as well.
Just to see it in measure where people are yeah I mean from a from a an altruistic point of view the Greek speak is not for this society.
I've said that before Whether it's few or many, but I would have rather have spoken publicly than not I've ever spoken publicly you know right right so Yeah Well, I'm glad that you did.
I'm glad that you did.
Yeah.
Yeah, good.
I'm glad you that you're glad very glad
Mm-hmm
It's so a very welcome change to this last year and
Coming up on a year now or so I believe and and
Still going strong Greek still going strong
And you know just to confess I did go down the rectangle this morning
I spent a couple of hours because I need a hunt down some materials
Mm-hmm and I looked around
See what's going on and just to state it as a fact do not expect anything on the rectangle
By the way in terms of like alternative media or whatever it's still all the same
Stupidity it's all politically based, and you know these are just ignorant slaves.
You know across the board Not some of them all of them Occasionally you get a gem like Dimitri and look at Dimitri's status He's like one of the videos at the end.
He was like well.
I want to do more, but I don't think I'm no one's interested I'm not getting any support right yeah, I know if you go.
Yeah look at real dumb shit They have a hundred thousand subscribers, and they could make a living you know easily shows you what kind of trash is living on this planet Yeah, they want to talk about you know whatever you know look at all the I mean people you know that you've heard me Speak with in the past on the internet.
It's all garbage I did it because it was there, and I figured I'd probe into it and give it a shot You know yeah, it's all rubbish all of it, and there's no exception you might have an exception like I said by looking at some Old historical stuff.
You know how years ago people used to transfer video to DVD so they could preserve it Yeah, there might be some old stuff that you read about or heard an audio book.
Maybe that's worth listening to Or I don't know Reference technical stuff, but in terms of mainstream or alternatives are all idiots with no exceptions at all And it's just trash And on one hand that's a fact that on the other hand the other fact is if they weren't Trashy they wouldn't no one would follow them Right here support right?
So you're living on a planet and a social norm is to be trash
Yeah in order to succeed and to shovel it and push it around right
Yeah, and there's no speaking of which speaking of which we were touching on
Subject of my knee which I twisted today coming down the ladder, and you're gonna speak about lymphology and
And I'm still wrapped, and I'm still got her wrapped and everything so
Yeah, let's just matter of fact.
It's a detailed.
Yeah, someone might be listening actually they prefer me not to discuss it And I forward it to the point where how do you know if bone is broken?
Do you are you familiar with the signs on the skin?
You know without an x-ray.
You know how they saw discoloration massive discoloration type of discoloration on the skin It'll be a yellowish tinge, and I mean a yellowish like an ochre yellowish Like a turmeric color yellow right a deep yellow.
Yeah, I'm gonna have a slight greenish blue mixed with it You know blotches and red and pink So if you bruise yourself Let's say let's say you suffer an injury or damage to the body, and it's just red It's most likely muscle and lymph if it's black and blue you know red and Very dark blue.
It's the muscle has been damaged.
You know the fibers have been Misaligned right if you start getting the yellow color the blue the green and the red you have a broken bone Yeah Or fracture in the bone by the way, I just a sign see now.
It's ridiculous.
I've seen in emergency rooms.
You know someone falls And they hear a snap in their leg actually the people around them heard something snap like a bamboo a piece of wood yep They go to the emergency room.
They're sitting there for three hours, and the doctor's like yeah, let's take an x-ray another two hours later Oh your bone is right hit.
Yeah
Stupid oh
Weeks right yeah easily easily
But if they wrapped it immediately and actually even if the bone is broken even if it was fragmented very tightly
The healing process starts immediately very very very very rapidly ever heard of
Well actually you might have experienced it if you get like a very fine cut from a razor or a paper cut or something
If you do this methodology you ever know right away you ever notice the next day
It's completely healed you could almost I'd say 99% healed yeah
If it's a very clean cut not a jagged break
Correct right and I've done that I've done that and yes
But if you don't do that
By the next day for sure a cut it'll last a few days or more
Right so the bone works the same way in the bone is a very interesting thing because the bone is I would say inert in
the body
That's why the most ridiculous thing is bone cancer.
No, that's those bones don't get cancer you have cancer sitting on the bone There's a difference.
Yeah, you see and then with that area where it's anaerobic it can eat away at the bone.
Just like you know Rust on a car how it eats through right mm-hmm, so but nonetheless a very tight wrap again I mean, there's many many levels to this of course an entire School of study and application can be put into how the human body really works and apply it medically Medically meaning you know medicinally right, but it's not going to happen in this society.
No doctors
Shouldn't well do you remember there was a congresswoman shot and
The president came to speak and the chief of surgery who worked on her mm-hmm
Did a public speak as an Asian guy, I'm getting too detailed well that guy told me he needs me to work on his staff
Right Wow
Yeah, yeah that guy famous guy great reason he's one of the best trauma surgeons in the world so
And he's on my ass about I need for you to come and work with Malik.
I don't have an education Don't worry.
We'll take care of that Because he's seen what the books yeah, yeah I get a phone call so you know Someone's in here.
I go there and the trauma and and the person's going home their intensive care.
They're going home the next day
Not from the I'm talking from intensive care now, yeah, yeah the I see you in it, right
Yeah, right home the next day released
Yeah, even if you go into the hospital, they're not gonna let you go home in it, so no
Make a short story
even longer here
That I'm not that stupid no matter what this idiot says because he's an idiot
He will eventually get in trouble or I'll get in big trouble
Because it's not allowed the owners of this country and the owners of this planet well just a little system alone
Right the attorneys will not approve of it.
No these are morons So you know is what I'm speaking of is not temporal meaning this society like these old farts that say oh things used to be Better no they weren't better because if you were so smart it wouldn't have let it go into this condition, right?
Right it should be getting better if the older people were wiser and smarter and a better generation
Why is it degrading because they're they're not they're just at a higher rate of speed might I ask
Right and if they were better they would get better you see so they're no good
You know and when you read in the Bible respect your elders
It's talking about those that are within the the covenant of the scriptures and lawful people right you see
You know the headhunters
You know it's a go kill all of them the old the young the children the animals all of them didn't say oh
Don't kill the old people you know in the in when they were Joshua was told to go into the land
Yeah, yeah, so people don't understand the context of Scripture
still
It has to do.
That's why when I say Forget about the scripture has got nothing to do with you.
That's very accurate for most people Mm-hmm really doesn't now it doesn't mean that you can't take it and Learn from it and apply it because even you know a savage headhunter pagan or whatever it can improve their lives, right?
But you're still into the gods you're still a savage pagan headhunter right because the gods don't look they look at bloodline
Unless you really make a big quote-unquote repentance where you really turn around and then you your main goal in life is to
Commune with the gods especially the most high then they'll notice that and they'll say look this guy is just some scumbag like the rest
Of them, but look he doesn't stop bothering us right
You see that's where your free will aspect is in there you see
So it's like the cruise ship.
You know the everybody's going from point A to point B But if you're always on the deck in one position there, what's this guy doing?
He's not moving from that position He's you see that's your free will you know you don't have to be you could right?
But everybody's still going to go to that you know condition point B.
You know yeah, right, so that's where people don't understand It's so simple.
You know that the of course all the various sects from the You can pick take your pick there are thousands of religious sects They all have a certain view and they plug that view and they and they're blinded to everything else There's there are sects and that talk about free will and the it's all or nothing.
I'm telling you It's not it's a MIT you have to understand the the concept Mm-hmm, it's not a game.
It's not an experiment.
It's a lease.
What do you understand about a lease you that you know?
when you lease a property or something location or a
Holding to someone as a tenancy yeah, you still call the shots
But they are the tenants so what humanity is going through is not a game
And it's not an experiment to the immature it
They try to
Communicate it as such because they're immature, and they don't they lack knowledge
But once you see that it's obviously a leasehold
And it's mentioned several times on how this world is under the grip of these particular entities, right?
Right their hold you know it's not theirs.
It's their leasehold.
It's it's a tenancy Yeah, but it's not a joint tenancy.
It's just a tenancy joint tenancy means both are there Equals a yeah Yeah, but I would say that I recently got an email about You know how do we get rid of the evil spirits and just do the good ones is what makes you think that the evil?
Spirits are working on their own the good ones are sending the evil ones That's the thing everyone still thinks is good and evil As separate oppositions like the History Channel did a stupid thing God versus the devil or Satan Oh boy, it's no such thing.
There's no God versus.
It does no challenge there at all It's like for it's like saying three-year-old baby versus his father kind of straight Let's pick up the baby and throw him out the window very easy.
There's no challenge
It's ridiculous to even suggest that but you have to you see for the for the idiot subjects on the planet
They have their what they desire to do in life, so let's say your job as a slave is to cut wood all day
Well the only thing you need to know is about cutting wood outside of that
You know it's not it's none of your business
But let's say you the society becomes a little loose and they tell you that it's good to learn about other things
Do you think they're gonna bring you real information?
Or they're gonna just fill your mind with bullshit
Because they want to keep the only thing that you need to know that is true is sawing wood
That's your job, but everything else is bullshit because you know that
If it's bullshit inherently you're not gonna really want to study it more, but if someone asked him is it bullshit
No, that's the truth because they said so but they know deep inside
That it's bullshit, but they don't want to I'm not interested you see so the last thing you want to do is get the slaves
True information about things that that are not need to know
Because then they're gonna start quote-unquote resonating with the truth and noticing more and more and then after a while
They're gonna notice that maybe I can achieve something else other than
Cutting wood or being a doctor or a lawyer or a bus driver or whatever
So they have to put bullshit in front of you like church and Christianity Judaism all that crap
Yeah, you know Islam.
Whatever.
That's all they have to lie to you Because they have you tuned in to what you think is the truth then how many times you still have new age Well, that's your opinion.
That's your truth.
You know all right all right, so you know they still So that's part of the leasehold and here's the thing if you're operating in truth And in a high level of morality and lawfulness you can't do it here Even the most high will tell you that you can't do it here Because this is I've uh this is leased out to Satan.
What are you crazy?
Good luck, that's yeah, well, it's more than luck.
Yeah, yeah, that's why that's why he says you do it Anyway, you're they're gonna kill you he does say that description anyway They chop your head off.
They'll torture you your own family.
We're talking about now about the Popo the police or anything
Right or Leo, you know Leo law enforcement right or nothing like that no no no
Talking about you by the way the malevolency that's brought on you is in scripture is brought on you by your own family by the way
That's more than implied
so anyway
And
He tells you that if you insist on doing the right thing and they do harm you for my name's sake and for my sake
That's fine.
That's very honorable.
No You see still, but yeah, that's where a choice.
Maybe you might want that's gonna be a heck of a battle though Yeah, do you want to really suffer because you know you if you stub your bare foot on the kitchen chair it hurts, right?
Imagine right what these assholes can do to you, right, right?
There's many levels to it, but just keep in mind.
This is not the place for lawfulness morality What's good and whatever you do have good and evil here put on the earth.
Yeah
Yeah, but it's not good versus evil no not at all
Sorry, it's the the the malevolent like the people who have the the bad dreams those negative spirits are being sent to you by the good
powers you see very
But it doesn't mean you have to go back
That's why you can go back and and be angry at the most high and all that about that because you you don't understand it
Yes, it's very emotional
You know to find out someone is putting you through suffering of something that is unpleasant
Because suffering means you you go through it, right?
But if you look at the whole thing in its perspective It's okay to have the anger and all that but you have to understand how to dish it out respectfully, right?
correct, right so
You know, I mean anyone that understands the truth of the matter sees that it's not this
bullshit
morality or
Religiosity or morality, you know, whatever you want to call the good and bad good and evil or good in bed
He bad contrast is not one or the other it both come from the same place
I think it's a book of Jeremiah that says both good and evil come from me
In book of Jeremiah, I think he says in your me Yahoo
Show me a city that disaster has befallen that I have not sent
I'm just paraphrasing.
Mm-hmm, right?
Yeah, oh yeah it over it.
Yep You won't set yourself apart on it Yeah, you can set yourself apart on it is best Always, you know, even the evil ones set themselves apart in their own way Because how can they plot and design the things that they need to produce the evil in the open?
You see they have to do it secretly So setting oneself apart is always the right thing to do for both the dark side and the light side You know like a bunch of guys conspired to rob a bank.
They're gonna talk about it at a cafe.
No, no They're gonna set themselves apart in a place that no one can hear right?
So
From you setting yourself apart from the rest
essentially
These things are very basic and they should well like fresco says, you know, give the children the tools
These are tools that no one has and no one
Get you know, they or uses because they don't know they exist yet
there's so simple when I say no one has I mean if you look at the formality and the
What do you call it when something is growing formative aspect of what people learn about things it's all bullshit
there there isn't
Critical thinking discernment looking at the past looking at accumulation of knowledge and let's just say wisdom
You know wisdom is knowing how to apply the knowledge
And all this especially with children, especially with lawfulness with the natural world with you know
I think that was the biggest culture shock that I had when I first got introduced to
the concepts and in the thinking
It
Took it took some time to to just wrap my head around that, you know that the many measures.
Yeah Well, you could say you were censored before because nothing has changed We didn't see a billboard.
You just got a few hints
Someone right someone in the background putting together website, by the way a pretty elaborate one on Greek speaking
Okay, okay, and they do communicate with me infrequently and they've written articles long articles about all the various things and
Recently they I was asked to edit an article about cosmic censorship
Which I didn't because really the whole thing has to be rewritten or just leave it and that's that person's writing style
Let's say right, right
And I would leave it that way as really but
when you look at the cosmic censorship, and I have also heard an email someone about cosmic censorship on how it's
You know, I say it's easy, but it's not it's actually quite difficult
Well, it's it's neither here nor there whether it's easy or difficult is it you have to consider
The cosmic censorship is outside of you with it's not the free will aspect you see
Otherwise, it wouldn't be cosmic censorship.
It would just be discovery But even that rate it's if they let it go on the other side So when you poke around and you can't get through the censorship, it's the other side.
That's not allowing it to happen That's the the heavy part about it, but once they do Let you around you see it was there.
It was like a curtain Not a brick wall, right, right.
Mm-hmm so but but but even though you You you let's say not able to get through the censorship if you do internalize that it's a very light veil But it's opaque.
You can't see through it.
You have to go around it because it is a complete baffle complete obscuration Right, right.
You still keep that in mind.
So you there's no That's what you call it trauma or stress About it.
In other words, there's no dynamic.
There's no dynamic Expression that'll get you through it.
Like if I said go through this curtain Okay, and then I said go through this brick wall.
You're like, okay.
Well, that's gonna take a lot more I need a sledgehammer.
You see.
Mm-hmm.
I'm telling you you don't need a slit.
There's no sledgehammer Explosives bulldozers or anything for this?
It's a very very light opaque veil and right think of it as a curtain that has a brick wall painting on it Right.
Yeah, we're in a mirage All right, but I'm telling you that if the other side doesn't want you to see it You will not see it no matter what you do So now that you know, let's just take this a little further Now you have to understand who's on the other side just to begin Work this that's why I've had some discussions with people from Israel and They're reading.
That's what they call the Tanakh in Hebrew They don't have to go to the King James and they go directly and they and they basically tell me It's basically it has to do with your personal relationship with them you know the Christians use that a lot but that there is this stupid but the from from the from the Hebraic point of view someone who is immersed in it.
I could read the old Hebrew without Looking around for an interlinear basically says this is all personal stuff This is up to you this information what you do with it, right, right?
So unless you have it like I said earlier talking about the Antichrist
You have a mosaic type figure who is a prince of Egypt literally and then befalls that entitlement into
a prophet of the Israelites
Right and then establishes a
record
And that record holds many things law event history
Right and things to come
So when you put all that together from Genesis all the way down the first five books, what do you get?
You have to hold it all together.
That's why I looked at that Peaked at the that bite show Oh, yeah, the title has to do about Genesis, right?
Cannot discuss Genesis without discussing all of the five books and the purpose of The information that is given in Genesis you see I don't know what the guy said.
I'm sure it's not accurate I'm sure that you know, you get a little bit here a little bit there But the purpose the reason I'm saying I know it's an accurate.
Here's the thing I wish it wasn't I'd stop and I'd say go listen to this guy forget about Greek speak, right?
Right, but the the essence here is if I think I've discussed in the past Doing a study on Genesis.
First of all, I've said before it doesn't say what what you think it says on The when you read it, it doesn't say that at all Right.
In other words, you're gonna have to go in into an interlinear and even with the interlinear You can't trust that they are giving you the word down below correctly because they'll switch it around Right, right you go from forms to create it back to create it back to formed.
Mm-hmm, right?
things don't mean You know that there's no creation is very little creation in Genesis there is reforming mostly.
Mm-hmm.
The only you see so In in the global sense, right?
Man is created
But it's from a spiritual point of view this type
You see so then when you go through Genesis you start getting into Abraham and then you get into
Well, you get into the flood which is very important and then you get into
Abraham and then all the other patriarchs right with the right development of Israel as as the as the group right and the
Promise and you have to understand that throughout Genesis you ever notice
It's the gods that are making all the agreements and the promises man doesn't really have to do anything
Right other than no, I don't they aren't right
The only basically only time man is told to really do anything on his end is to build the ark
Right and attend the garden and very little but as you get later man has to do a lot when you look at Leviticus
All the laws all the things you have to do.
It's not what the gods are going to do They'll basically offer you protection and prosperity But you have to do all these things when you read Leviticus, right?
616 really like 200 things the other 400 roughly are don't apply to most people.
So
What's interesting is when you start looking at the dynamic through the first five books of Moses
then you can go back and look at Genesis, especially the the most confounding aspect is the first couple of chapters and
Overlay the mindset of the first five books back to Genesis you see I just gave a big secret on how to comprehend Genesis
the first couple of few chapters and also then forget about the chapters try to read it without the chapter in verse because those
Who why why did they decide to stop and start there?
You see don't write don't pause, you know
Try to get something that doesn't have chapter and verse or ignore it if you can
Mm-hmm, and it has a different effect on the mind even if you're looking at intra linear
Because you have to bear in mind the creation
Sequences have historicity and also they're given
Relevant to the other five books in Genesis in in that Moses gave they're all together
When I so in other words the first few chapters of Genesis have to be read along with Exodus Leviticus numbers in Deuteronomy
You know in terms of the month.
So in other words, you notice when you read Genesis
you get first five books you get a different mindset than when you go after the
After chapter 5 of Genesis right before the flood the mindset changes and then it changes again and again and again with Abraham and Joseph
And you know and is Jacob and all is then you go to Exodus is different mindset and that mindset changes again
The numbers changes a mindset
Leviticus changes your mindset Deuteronomy changes your mindset
So when all these mindset changes are leading on building to a greater mindset that you take then
That you've exercised these various mindsets that the various
Portions of the book create you get a feeling of what's going on here and then you go read the first
two chapters or three chapters of Genesis and now you're going to really see
Why they give the creation and the formation the way they do and all this
And I can and I know I could get more specific but it's not necessary
that's actually something that we have to go back and and
Get an idea that whoever's listening has access to what I'm talking about meaning a good interlinear
Has went gone through it's when I bring up a point
They don't have to search for it in real time.
You know what I mean, right, right?
But even without an interlinear, you know, you don't need an intro because I could basically tell you Well, this word is being used here.
It means that Well, yeah, I don't want you to believe me.
You're gonna have to go look it up yourself.
You see also you learn it And not because you need to learn it from memorization purposes, but because now you see the point of view Correct.
You see correct.
Mm-hmm, but there's no information
Being given widely even narrowly regarding these things because
Whenever you bring up anything scriptural biblical still it's a religiosity aspect to it
You see and until that goes away, you're not there isn't going to be any understanding of it
In other words most people no matter what lip service they give they still think this is a joke or it's something that's religious
Most people do and I know it doesn't matter almost but still even people listen to Greek speak
They think this is like that's just one aspect, you know something, you know, it's not important
You know one or I have to say it's important because it is but I really don't think so
Wow, and the thing is you can't consider it
You really have to meditate on how important it is
In an isolated way almost like a thought experiment because you cannot understand how important these things are because your life is too short
60 70 years 80 years is not long enough to contemplate these things
No, especially when you have to go search it, right?
So and if the end and if the first 50 of them was wrapped in waste cosmic censorship, but you You're on a short end of that's real Right.
Well, you still can't do it with
Experiment thought experiment imagine, okay
When you you can you think about something for five minutes and now I want you to think that you thought about that
Not for five minutes, but you thought about it for ten years the same thing
Mm-hmm
Not that you did but just imagine you did and then you actually catch up
In your mind in your spirit and your psyche to the point as if you did and it really gets buried a little deeper
Let's say in that palace.
We call the mind, right?
You know the many rooms Yeah, that's one aspect.
There are many other things regarding memory.
Mm-hmm
But the memory schools were popular
Well, I shouldn't say popular because they were you know for people that needed to know again
Mm-hmm up until they wrote what they call the Renaissance
then it was like now we're gonna completely enslave everyone and the last thing we want is slaves that can remember and
sort things out
So
that in itself
But again, just to beware if you do look at interviews or whatever out of who posted that
That doesn't matter who posted it.
No but if you If you whenever you look at any kind of biblical commentary there's I'm telling you it's going to be bullshit and Come because it's going to be mixed with bullshit because it's coming from a religious perspective, right?
Mm-hmm the
The reason why I'm saying this is because the amount of caveats the warnings that you have to give
to settle to set the
Mindset is longer than the topic that's going to be discussed
Like if you're gonna walk into a room or do an internet thing or whatever and start talking about Genesis
Even if you want to do a two-hour talk on Genesis
You're gonna have to do at least two hours to show how people no one even knows
Either the condition of the information, you know
King James is not a translation.
The the the words are not being translated, right?
Everything you've seen in art media and religious is wrong, right?
There is no Apple.
There is no tree.
There is no serpent like a snake, right?
You know, you're gonna have to go in and make so many qualifications
Before you get to the point because if you think you're gonna go start talking about anything in the Bible people are thinking about
What's been putting in front of put in front of them through the circus through Hollywood and all that
There's no way what you're doing is going to work
It's like making a paper bucket to carry water or basically you're serving poo
Are you putting good corn on top of poo?
Where it would have been perfect corn as long as you didn't mix it with the poo So most people's heads are filled with poo.
So when you try to put something in it, it's going on top of the poo So you have to empty the poo clean the vest, you know clean it out You see Mm-hmm.
So the amount that amount of work makes it That most that it what do you call it when you shouldn't do something because it's a waste you see.
Oh Whatever Right.
Yeah, when you do something if you do it's going to be wasted Yeah, so on most people because their heads are so full of poo That you can't talk about these things.
You can't talk about the human body at all Because they're they're full of blood blood pressure and absorption and This that in the other you can't tell that's why I make my most of my time is just squeeze it Just put a good squeeze on it.
You'll be fine.
You don't need to know anymore Mm-hmm and even if you wanted to You know you the the level of cleaning house cleaning in your mind.
It has to be done Now here's the other thing some people can do that some people can abandon preconceived notions very quickly Right.
They do exist.
All right, so You know like for example recently I had there was an author You wanted me to write a segment for his book regarding weather control, which I did and we had a conversation He just found out he's in his late 50s.
He just found out that the moon landings never happened, right?
So he's trying to send me all these things and I'm like, well, no, no, no Let me show you something there's something called lunar transit or Earth transit, you know transit is when one that's how you get eclipses, right?
The moon goes right in front of the Sun or the earth goes in front.
That's when one thing covers another Okay, you can go right now and just based on the NASA's paperwork sign of your paper How big the moon is and how far away it is and how big the earth is and all that?
If you're standing on the earth looking at the moon, you could see the moon is about you know
Twice as wide as your thumb three times as wide as your thumb or whatever
Correct because of its size and its distance now if you're standing on the moon
And in the earth is as big as it isn't as far as it is when you're looking at the earth
It's not like they show you in the NASA pictures are like twice the width of your thumb
Very fills up three quarters.
It fills up three quarters of the horizon.
It's huge
So that's your first notion that the NASA's the moon landings are fake
Right as they show you the astronauts on the moon in the studio with the little earth in the background Earthrise or whatever
Right, it's not the if you are on the moon looking at the earth
The earth would fill up the horizon about three quarters of at least half of it would be huge
It would look like you could reach out and tell you would be overwhelming.
That's your first thing.
They know that it's a fraud Because they have stupid people working as scientists I mean if you are not stupid you wouldn't be a scientist if you are smart Let's say intelligent you went to work for a government agency or university.
They wouldn't hire you they would say you're not fit Just like the police.
You're not you can't do this job get out of here
So there is no video
Anyone who knows about astronomy can and has at least two or three sharpened pencils or a stupid rectangle can do it on their own
The how big the earth is how big the moon is and their distance and just basic algebra you look at it
And if you're standing on the moon again looking at the earth rising the earth would be huge
It would cover you know if the horizon is a meter wide the it would be like 500 centimeters 600 centimeter
You would just completely cover the her you wouldn't yeah, you wouldn't see any space.
It wouldn't be dark at all You would just see the blue big blue marble.
Yeah Yeah, yeah Basics this is basic stuff And it doesn't matter how if your earth is smaller and bigger or further away by accuracy 10 or 15 percent still going to be Like that it's good.
So right away what it's going to be massive So that's why when they show you the pictures of the astronauts of the moon the earth in the background is that right away?
That's bullshit.
No one's calling it because of the earth transit.
It's huge Compared to it so anyway, I know what yeah, I mean it's stupid you know That's what I'm saying when I say you're idiots with no exception is pretty accurate Yeah, I mean yeah, and you know whatever well the film set only had so much room yeah Could have slid the projector.
Oh, it's it's like the airplanes like the airplanes going into the Twin Towers on TV, right?
He's like really bad Photoshop or whatever program.
They used mm-hmm Very nice, and it's like you asked that question one time who was controlling the media that day Exactly no one's asking that at all.
No.
Yeah, so stupid people.
Yeah, these are earth idiots.
Yep Earth idiot would it be EI instead of AI yeah, yeah versus the EI the earth idiot What what kind of a bunch of morons?
What kind of media or university or even alternative media?
They're gonna do Laughable bullshit, and that's what it is and they take it serious They prove a point on how well they could get everything Collated together and in organized together Yeah, I was I was impressed with that that would that took some effort In other words they have the tools yes, they have the tools to organize the bullshit.
Yeah Yeah, yeah And I'm sorry.
I cut you off in the middle of your point again.
Sorry about that.
No, that's fine No, you didn't they have the tools to organize, but that's to organize all the the crap and corn and Bullshit, they're not capable of the rest again.
It's cosmic censorship spiritual oppression.
They're being oppressed By what's called familiar spirits, you know that foul follow them along for generation after generation The they have the chemical thing happening from the goddess religion bad food, you know, so today I wanted I'm gonna be making some Japanese food some yakitori with various things and I wanted to get some chicken and I'm like, oh There's no way.
I'm gonna get these channel.
I went to this Korean market.
I said, could you have any chicken from Korea?
I want real chicken
It doesn't have to be a whole chicken even chicken parts or chicken liver or something just something that's not American
Great, you know, there's no they don't import it like damn
So it's like we don't even know what real chicken tastes like unless you grow one, of course
And by the way, when you do harvest a real chicken, it's nothing like
No, well alive, you know
The breasts are real small and there's hardly any the the real drumstick is like a wing is a very little meat on it
You know when it's right because they tend not to get fat when they walk around free range.
Yeah But even the free range is is you know, it's yeah So eating animal the more, you know, I think about it more and more, you know, it's like I Don't think it's something I want to do you know, I would like to Encourage anyone out there to open a vegetable sushi You know how sushi is a thin slice of fish on rice to call that nijiri sushi, right?
well, what about curing veg and
cutting it the same way as you would sushi and
Putting that on rice because you can there's so many varieties of vegetables in texture flavor color
Mm-hmm taste, you know ever of every, you know, you got bitter sour sweet
depending on the soil and
You can cure and produce vegetable sushi
So someone can go out and have an enjoy because it's the sushi is not the fish
It's the whole thing about a warm rice or cold fish in the dip with tamari and wasabi.
It's the entire The form of eating it's how the form of how the food is presented, right?
Mm-hmm It's like sometimes I you know, you want a hamburger and not a steak.
Well, it's both beef But just you just want that ground meat meat consistency, right sometimes and sometimes you don't want the ground meat consistency So, how about we do the same with the veg?
How about do a fillet of an aubergine or a zucchini?
Or something and put that on a nigeri with rice with a dipping sauce instead of fish animal Why not create that I think it would go really well But it has to be delicious You can't do like these white people that go vegan because they can't cook and then when you serve you food This is terrible.
So I was not terrible.
It's vegan Or is there's an excuse, you know, I'm like these cookies are terrible.
No, they're not they're vegan Like we're talking about vegans delicious Is this much or they use it as an excuse, you know?
So but I'm talking about people who really know about food and know how to prepare food and make some delicious Vegetable sushi.
What's up with that?
I mean, I'm believe it or not.
I'm I'm doing it I'm not gonna I said believe it or not.
I'm experimenting with it, right?
And it is quite delicious and quite satisfying.
I mean, there's so many ways to prepare a veg
and
Which veg adds flavor and complementary and all that and you feel really good
do you feel your body adapts to it and
starts
You know recovering from eating the animal flesh
Which has no vacuum, you know, it's dead right where if you have fresh veg vacuum is still maintained
Actually making me hungry Greek
Yeah, yeah and and cooking rice I recently got some really good rice
I don't have the I transferred it.
I have it somewhere.
It's in Japanese.
It's a Really good pearl rice if I noticed that doing a two hour or three hour soak and Rinse and rinsing it several times in the beginning you say well if you rinse the rice a lot you lose some of the flavor Don't don't go for that.
Give it time to mature and soak Yeah, you do lose the perceived flavor But the more you rinse it the better it cooks less starch that won't stick together as much.
Mm-hmm And if it's a high quality rice It'll it'll work out really well, I'm preparing some of that got some pickle Japanese pickles So, oh see how that yeah Have you ever messed around with natto and a Nato is fermented soybeans.
It smells like really bad gym socks and sticky.
No, no, you'll kiss
Yeah, no, I have not
Yeah, that's an interesting that's a good way to put acidophilus in the body it's very hard to find
Unfortunately, I have a market that has like six varieties of it and if you can even find it a market
Yeah, and and I got a bunch of that that's Asian prepare
Yeah, yeah, not those
fermented soybeans very stinky if you go to a Japanese restaurant and
You're a white person and you order not so if they happen now, they'll say no.
No, we don't serve it to white people Say they see it's offensive to them, you know, oh, it's very very strong.
It smells like really bad gym socks and toe cheese and I mean just this it's It would be like not that I know what those things really smell But I'm just giving like with children say right sure like Lindenburg Lindenburg or cheese or gray or something But it's vegetable and it's very loaded with acidophilus.
Okay Which is a very high in other words, it will completely readjust the way your intestines induce food It might be difficult if you've never had it before and you do have it You're gonna have some problems going to the bathroom either too much or too little And you'll be waking up in the middle of night with your stomach gurgling.
This is not know my report This is reports.
I've gotten from other people Okay, and my report would be a mixture of that until you've resets your body to that vegetable base of Makes sense.
Yep, that would make sense.
It's a very you know, you the prima dophilus acidophilus, you know intestinal
intestinal fauna
It's the strongest variety you can take and by the way many of the natural
I shouldn't say that many of the ailments that people suffer today are because they lack that for natural fermentation
And you can't get a lot of it from cheese because cheese again is animal based and it's very rare to get good cheese because
It's read they use rennet
Animal rennet, which you know as a piece of it to you to make fermentation more rapid.
Mm-hmm So, you know, you know right finding rennet list cheese is very difficult So not oh would be the easiest way to do to recorrect the body So anyway, I do have Asian markets around here, I'm gonna definitely check into that Greek Yeah, I asked them for a nacho.
Yeah, look it up.
Yeah, I Mean, you know how cheese is stringy when it's warm like a mozzarella or pizza.
Mm-hmm.
That's how this stuff is natural You just pull it's just really really slippery nasty mucus kind of looks like Mixed with brown soybeans and it smells like Lindberger with gym socks and Thanks for the heads up Yeah, yeah, it's very intense and it's acquired taste Okay Imagine like a three-year-old drinking a strong beer for the first time.
I'd be like, ah, what is that drain cleaner?
Right?
All right, right Okay Yes Yeah, I highly recommend it only as a Midget from a medicinal point of view, correct, correct.
You get some natto in your body every three months.
It'd be a really good way to start Getting into more of a healthful way of eating I don't know how else you'd get those positive intestinal flora and fauna in your body You can try to make yogurt at home an animal, you know Milk it doesn't make you unclean but eating beef does right?
Right?
Yeah, the milk is not the the dead animal So the eggs are oh, you know is an egg a dead animal.
Yes, and no, I mean, it's a goat either way Because you know, it's not yeah once it's out of the shell.
Yeah It's basically a whole chicken, but I'd say milk is Ovo-lactic pesco-lactic, you know fish Mm-hmm and milk as a form of animal protein and then just milk and then no milk I think milk is fine as long as it comes from a goat or sheep or a cow No donkey milk or anything like that, right?
Oh And I tried the warm milk idea on cereal Much totally different different day.
Yeah, what a whole different perspect Very enjoyable very enjoyable.
Yeah.
Yeah more more delicious.
You really taste within the cereal more My daughter's been experimenting with the making yogurt and Haven't really had a chance to touch base with all the progression is going but I I look forward to favorable Input at least and yeah Right, and then you could graduate to like what they call a cottage cheese or curds, you know Mm-hmm you can get milk now here locally where I'm at there.
I finally can get raw milk.
They just started offering really Yeah, yeah, believe it or not.
I don't know how they're getting away with it.
I was just gonna say I Don't know how they're pulling that one off Yeah, maybe they're gonna get in trouble Who knows, you know, it's a totally different substance there.
You got a big organization.
That is Mm-hmm got a whole bunch of legal people in it That's not a good combination No, no, those the gods will take care of the attorneys.
Don't worry all of them.
Don't worry Yeah, that's a I kind of I kind of sit back and say this is a natural Progression of things, you know what in order that's how you know a society is getting bad.
You have more doctors and attorneys Because the thing is you really and the doctors you they're like restaurants, by the way.
Why do you eat out?
Why don't you cook at home?
It's healthier.
Why don't you train the population on healing how to you know, do first aid and Even basic surgery on the body Yeah, I don't like our base on that once before there should be more places for healing You know, yeah, and also and how to procure Aid to someone who is in you know been injured.
Why do you have to have a separate class of?
You know, it's I see individuals a very bad thing.
There should be very very few doctors for highly specialized things Yeah, and and and most people say well, they're good people.
They don't know I'm telling you.
They're not good people.
They're not inherently They're not good.
I mean overall because I mean Because basically ignorant people are dangerous, right?
That's why when you go visit and they're ignorant When you go to the mines the large mines that give out hard hats, you know You know, there's like a little place to check in.
They give you a vest and a hard hat Yeah, and all the hard hats have different colors, you know Like the guests have a different color the engine the chief at the head the senior engineers have a different color right, the the engineers that just got a college have a different color or a Marking code on the hard hat, right, right.
I wants to I went to a a Action tell the story that's okay But anyway back to the attorneys you ever heard right where there's an old There's an attorney because I want to get the mining company in trouble right but There is a Becker just to go finish up here but back with the attorneys we'll just turn around here Return back to them.
I'm gonna tell you the joke There there's a small town and there was an old attorney there and he didn't have much business He was going broke Had to live a very more Modest life than he was used to and he kept scaling down because he wasn't getting any kind of earnings from anyone in the town Well in comes this young attorney.
He moves into the town and now both attorneys are rich.
Ah You get it, oh, yeah, you see how it works.
Yeah.
Yeah So just like the doctors the doctors weren't wealthy until the pharmaceutical companies came in more sick people great You see Yeah, so again back to the attorney He's got nothing to do here comes another attorneys to start stirring the pot creating Controversy and then they obviously they're both gonna prosper from it.
So usually this is the condition.
Yeah Yeah, I mean even on the alternative me.
I see these these people in the corner called government They're indicting them and the guys some some idiot general or colonel or somebody He had to sell his house to pay the fees and all that.
I'm like why?
What an idiot Yeah, it's the wrong court.
First of all, he took him into a judicial court.
It should have been administrative.
Yeah Well, what happened?
He his dog bit somebody Is that why they're taking him to a federal judicial court his dog?
He bit the dog bit someone.
No, this is all Political stuff is administrative.
It shouldn't be in a justice court at all There's nothing to do with anything like that But it's a you know, these people this is a machine that eats you up like a monster, you know It just comes through and and it's all ignorance that you're right on.
Yeah.
Yeah Yeah, so it's just for Danny and the alternative media is just so stupid all of them.
Not some of them all of them You know, what are they gonna do?
They've got not to disparage Chuck, but they got the JFK Researchers, right?
They already got a confession on who did it Now, what are they gonna do the JFK researchers gonna hold their swinging Cod?
That's an old term if you know, right?
Yep.
I remember I just know what a cotton.
Yeah, okay All right, what is the 9-eleven truth is gonna do when they figure out it was a nuclear thing What are they gonna do nothing?
Yeah, they're swinging Cod.
It's all bullshit It's all bullshit all of it the UFO people, you know, we're gonna take it to Yeah, these people they need they need the ignorance they need the stupidity and No evidence in the world will satisfy them.
Like there was a college professor publicly said I Believe in the moon landings and even if the astronauts confessed that they didn't go I'd still believe that they went This is how this is how fucked up people are.
All right, so so you're gonna get an alternative media talk about anything that makes sense or a University that's going to talk about anything.
I mean, this is a joke.
This is what's going on here on this planet It's an utter joke.
I mean you have to you know, laugh or cry, right?
So Yeah, yeah All right, if there's nothing else we've been on for I don't know how long here let's see Suck down a cup of coffee an hour 40, but a order hour and 40 something here Okay Yeah Well pleasure was mine Greek definitely.
Yes.
Yeah, great.
We'll do it again next week, I guess.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay All right, and thanks you have yourself a good night Yes, well, very thank you very much for your all your your work.
Oh Sure, you're welcome Take a minute.
You have a good one.
Bye.
Bye