And live here with Greek, and how are you doing tonight?
Greetings.
Doing okay.
Yeah, let's do another Sonic, I guess.
I've noticed most of the stuff that's ever been said is beyond most people's comprehension, and it's very safe to say they'll probably never understand most of this stuff, but it doesn't mean it shouldn't be voiced.
You know, I've been finding out that just by replaying some of the old events, which I do, and I keep them rebroadcasting out there for folks in case they want them, and I catch myself doing it, and just little things, you know.
I'm still fascinated by Genesis.
Just can't get that book out of my head, Greek.
I revisit it over and over.
It's funny you said that, because I revisited it today, and it's so obvious once you start to...
Well, let me just say it this way.
It's very obvious why Genesis, especially when I say Genesis, the first chapter, the first four chapters really, why it is the way it is.
And if you just drain the mind of everything you've been told about it, and what you've been told about the Bible or any religion, and you observe it in context as you proceed through the rest of it, it makes total sense why it's done and the information is given that way.
I think I've ventured to give information little bits and pieces here.
I like to just do, like someone says, Greek, you speak in parable, but that's okay with me.
And I said, well, there's no other way, because
you don't want to cast pearls to swine, and on the other hand
it doesn't matter in terms of
giving the whole story out clearly, because the background, in other words, it matters
ultimately, but at this time it doesn't matter, because
even if you gave the background
about what is meant in Genesis, it is so contrasting to the way
people think, and the rationale that's employed, that it wouldn't matter
you see, because it's very contrary.
That's why I put the Dimitri Kalasov, the 9-11 sadistic, seditious I still love watching him.
He is one of the few people You know, in pursuing that a little farther I see why you're held back on some things, but there's a lot to be gleaned.
Well, I always found it interesting when they said the word Saddam
Well, that's
I make fun of white people usually, because
they represent the degradation of human culture, really
In other words, if you go to a place,
a venue, and it's leadership, whether it's de facto or
I'm not talking about politics now
If the rulers are the leaders
I'm talking about fashion trends and all that, trend leaders also
are influencing the degradation of society, well, you can easily point a finger
Why are you following this group?
Because look, they're making everything worse Oh yeah, I see it now.
That's what I mean about that aspect
When I said that to you, I was talking about the
S-A-D-M
That's the standard ordinance, small, that's the real small
That's the little boy
Or way little, it's literally only about 40 pounds, 20 pounds
And that was around the 50s, by the way
And what I wanted to get to was, east of the Mississippi, it's nuclear
West of the Mississippi, it's nuclear
What is that bomb that went off in Japan?
What kind of bomb is that atomic bomb?
If they say nuclear, you're west of the Mississippi
If they say nuclear, like nucleus, they're east of the Mississippi
That's an easy way to know where someone is from
No, it is funny, but I put that up about Dimitri because he's one of the few gems that just speaks plainly
Most people, even those Dimitri, I read some of the comments and videos
The recent ones that were put up, something to the effect of not a lot of seditious questions
I found his book very fascinating
And the way he laid it out, and the way he even put passwords in there to make sure that you read through
Got to the end, and then could use the passwords in order to go to the next one
I thought that was pretty clever
To verify, yeah
What's interesting, I mentioned to Dimitri years ago, is one thing that no one has spoken about, even him
And he laughed and agreed, because what am I supposed to do?
He could have easily done a hundred hours, or a four thousand page book
But one thing that everyone has sorely missed, which is important, is the walk like a duck
Looks like a duck, smells like a duck principle
There's very little discussion, but easily verifiable by looking at things that were written
I even found something, 1946, August, New Yorker magazine
And one of the things they spoke about being around an area where a nuclear device has been detonated
I.e. Hiroshima, was the smell
The smell is what everyone misses
Thousands of people in New York, which was the original Manhattan Project
Was in Manhattan, and then they moved by the Woolworth building
And then again, what they call 9-11
I had spoken recently, 5, 6, 7 years ago to someone in New Jersey
And he kept calling the EPA, like what's that smell, I can't sleep at night
I have my windows open, and it smells like electrical fire, and it's constant
I know it's coming from ground zero area, and they told him, well there are a lot of electrical wires in those buildings
There's some writings written, annals about
The American military that was experimented on, during the Nevada testing
The atmospheric atomic bomb testing
So they started coming out and putting out their journals, and one of the things was the smell
Of ionization, and there's just, I wouldn't say a lot of it on the internet
But there's enough from the Hiroshima detonation, there's even a book called 7 Hours to Zero
I believe was written about the accounts
And the one over in Russia, they had a lot of, there were some mentions, I should say
It was liberal at best
So if they tell you it's a car bomb, and it smells like a very high powerful industrial ozone machine
Or an electrical wire fire, you know, burn
It's not CDX, or dynamite, or TNT
Or Cordex, which is a pre-igniter
Or oil, yeah
Oh yeah, the fertilizer bomb
So it's really hard to describe what an apple tastes like, it's really hard to describe what strong ionization smells like
But if you've been around, it smells like bleach
Chlorine bleach, if you do laundry with the sodium hypochlorite
Chlorox, pretty much
She's distinct at best, very very distinct
And I would say for those people that are not around devices like ozone machines and corona discharge
You know, fresh lightning strikes
Get yourself a bottle of bleach, and if you've ever remembered that smell, that's what it smells like
Working with TVs way back in the day, you know
Corona discharge, and the high voltage cage, and horizontal
And if you've got dust and other things in there, they burn up and add to the smell
Yes they do, you know I had one time where the guy complained of this strange odor
Coming out of his TV, it was one of them big old brown tubers
26 inch, and it came in there, and here's this mouse
Stuck in the high voltage cage underneath the circuit board, I don't know how in the hell it got in there
But man
Hey
So were you, just for the listeners, circa 70's?
Yeah, mhm 60's, 70's With the 7355 pentodes or whatever Yeah, well you're bringing up some memories There were some real common ones that everyone used and they thought they'd make the tubes better But yeah, so diodes, triodes, pentodes, you know whatever Based on the cathodes, how hot the cathodes were Cold cathode, hot cathode, we just lost everyone right?
Yep, I think so
If we start talking about Gameboys and Nintendo, they all perk up
Anyway, yeah
That got me onto Genesis and all that kind of stuff and the Ether
And a little bit of discussion from last times conversation
Just got me going, but I always seem to fall back to Genesis
There's just so much in there that piques the curiosity
Well let's spend a little bit of time on it, I'll maybe say things again differently
How many times have you heard me say when you read anything in the Bible, it's not for you?
Right Let me just equalize here I'm making a big step outward, I'm going out to the back, outside the house Am I still audible?
It's not written for you because if you actually read it, it says who it's written for
And those people, their job was to hold the gist of the message
For everyone and or use it as a way to show how you're set apart from the rest of the people
And or the rules of a nation, how to run a society
And or history
So when you look at Genesis from it's historicity point of view
Not just the order of how things were laid out historically from beginning to end
Because there's a timeline there
But the historicity, that was penned by Moses, not written, but penned by Moses and his crew
Because if you read Exodus and Numbers very carefully, he had people helping him all the time
That were surrounding him, many
It was penned thousands of years after Adam
Roughly 2,000 plus years after the fact of the things that are mentioned in the first 4 or 5 chapters
6, 7, 8 chapters, 9 chapters really
Actually the whole book, everything that's mentioned in the book came at least 500 years before him from the end
So it's a recap, it's a rehash, it's a recap
And what is it there to do?
What do you notice, what's interesting about scripture and the narrative
It doesn't tell you everything that's going on or went on or will go on
But it offers information and the narrative offers the correctiveness that's required to have a fit and proper mindset
I'm going to say that again, different way
You notice there's no iPhones in there or man is going to fly with airplanes
Or the way the Romans are going to do this or that
Or the Egyptians, what their medicine was about
Or anything like that, no
The narrative of the scripture again is to offer a corrective, almost in a remedial sense
Contrast, corrective information on how to establish a fit and proper mindset
It's kind of like a supplemental manual
When you study, you were talking about TVs
Let's say you work with TVs or electronics and you're registered with the people that manufacture
And they know you're part of the service agencies
They update you, they'll send you a newsletter or an update on a service tech
And the updates on the service manuals
Are so you maintain a fit and proper mindset as you continue in the field
So when you read Genesis and all that
You use that as your main reference and also to your rudder or your compass
To maintain the fit and proper mindset
So this way when you
That's why it doesn't have everything in it
Actually I'm not going to go there right now, I'll save that for the next few years if I'm still around
Let's just skip that topic
So it's about using it as a moral correction
And a basic supplemental
Because if you want to know about man's history for the first few thousand years in the society here
There's so much that can be discovered, well even though it's been secluded and hidden away
And very often you're shown something and told it was 50,000 years ago when it was really just four or five
So you're using Genesis to supplement things
Like you'll know the plants came before the fish and the birds and the animals
And they came before man, right?
So it gives you that proper order so you comprehend things properly, quickly and efficiently
There's so much more to discuss there and I've done it in private
Actually not so much lately in the past four or five years
But in the future maybe I think an open discussion on Genesis will be more pressing
Let's just say appropriate
I don't think it's appropriate yet
In other words the questions have to be urgent enough
So I would suggest that when you find stuff
Well okay, let me just say this
When you find things in the scriptures that you can apply to your life
It's not just what you apply, what you look at is what is forbidden
And if it's not mentioned as something that's forbidden you can almost say that it's expressly encouraged
But when I say that I mean you don't legalize, don't try to twist it
It's very clear, use rationale
That's why it's so difficult to suggest doing what's in scripture because you need to have what to be able to do it
You need to be able to have a rational mind
As I can see and hear as I can hear
Have you booted the correct operating system I believe would be a good terminology
Yeah, but you do it backwards
Because you know you haven't been booted when you approach scripture
Because no one is really teaching scripture
Most people that really know scripture did not come from a culture of it
Or even a familial culture where their parents did
Most, not all, I would say most
So you were probably booted with the wrong operating system
With eyes to see and ears to hear
Do you ever see those geometric patterns that appear to be moving but there's nothing moving
I'm not talking about a gif image
It looks like a kaleidoscope, it's a series of squares in a circular pattern
And when you start pairing them up you look at it and it looks like it's moving
But it's not
And those are also things that are going to be done with sounds
So most people will fall for that, including anyone, because that is specifically designed to thwart perception
Whoever you show that pattern to, no matter if they're rational or irrational, will see something moving in it
Even though there's nothing moving
So now you have to overcome that
Because how many times have you heard people see things in scripture that are not there
And or say it's in scripture and it's not
Continuously
Even recently
I'm not going to mention any names, usually when I say that means I am going to mention the name
But someone said, oh that and the lunar calendar, again
You know there is no such thing as a lunar calendar, right?
That's the dummy load again
That's someone who spends too much time on the internet thinking they're going to find something that's going to make their lives better
Might want to clean that corn off a little bit
Yeah, there is no calendar, sorry
As soon as you hear that it's like, oh boy, they've got just enough information to make themselves dangerous
Not better
So yeah, there is no calendar, that's the other thing
Let that sink in for a minute, I'll give you a moment of silence on that
There is no calendar, lawfully
Clearly written in the book
Well, a calendar is a pre-planned schedule
For time alone
What I should have said
Like saying that this day here will be that day is pretty fucked up
There is no calendar in lawful calendars, no such thing
Because it's observation
And being a society of headhunters or bloodthirsty cannibals that we're addressing
They usually associate themselves very well with the Aztecs and the Mayans
Who one of the reasonings for doing human sacrifices was to appease the sun god
Because if we don't, the sun may not rise tomorrow, what do we do if the sun doesn't rise
The mentality, goodness
Well, the thing is to say that this day here will be this day of the month here
If from the past it is negating observation
One thing I wanted to bring back on the Dimitri videos I put in is
How many people understand what a sovereign state is?
Raise your hand
So it's a new creation or a corporate government, it's a front
Here's the thing that the mob does all the time
They acquire influence on a company to have it change so they can acquire the company
Meaning at a better price because if you just approach a company
There's negotiation and the bargaining can go either way and you're probably not going to get it for a good price
But if you influence the company then you can drop the asking price
Then you acquire it, you see
And then you bankrupt it and liquidate it
But in this case what they did is they didn't liquidate, some countries were liquidated
They bankrupted it and then they knew they just had to give everybody monopoly money
And it's called a credit line known as a birth certificate and the funny money
All your credit transactions that you're doing, so you're really living in a nightmare
Well I should say it's a lawful nightmare but fortunately most people are too dim in terms of wit, intelligence
And I say literally intelligence in this time in the meaning
Because everyone has the same intelligence potentially
And intelligence has been dimmed and their perception has been dimmed and their spirit has been twisted
And perverted enough that they cannot notice that there's nothing lawful anymore
Other than what the nature is doing, like rain
I just don't think the generations it was ever brought up to question
I can't remember any time, no
I was just thinking about that as you said that and I was like
It just accepted it, it was there
What you do is you eliminate the generations that are aware of it through war, famine or disease
Or starvation, depression
It's controlled
Amazing
There's a full on control, it's best that most people don't realize what's going on
But I think they should realize enough that they should stop having children the way they do
I don't mean no children at all
I am for the human race continuing but not in this spiritual condition
That it's in, all child rearing should stop
Not absolutely, in an absolute sense
We actually did a sci-fi film where no more babies were being born, I forgot what it was called
Children of Men or something, a movie a while back
I don't mean like that, but there should be
I'm not talking about a chemically induced thing, I'm just saying where people start saying
Take control of themselves
Here's the thing about child rearing, that's what they focus on
Do it for the children
Whenever they want to get sympathy calls, they show someone holding a baby that was injured or something
Like on the Murrow building in Time Magazine
A fireman holding a dead baby
Once you eliminate the possibility of creating a family like that
Then you can focus on more responsible adult things
Because when you're focusing on children, you have to be a responsible adult
But you're not focusing on responsible adult things, you're focusing on rearing a child or raising a child
The other thing is when you have a child in this society, that's when you become more of a target
Medically and institutionally
You have to send the child to school, right?
Also it degrades the financial system because each child is another piece of property added
The more property you add, it thins out the credit system
So if everyone just stopped having babies for a year or two
I'm not saying trying to have babies, no, you should try that every day
But either way, if you're not shooting blanks, use the proper protection
Or do the old-fashioned way, pull out for the guys
Or the women, pull off
That is one of the keys, by the way, to showing
Do you remember how there used to be strikes?
There's no more strikes, have you ever noticed that?
Very rarely
Maybe one or two mention of or something else
That's the way that you show your disapproval of the quote-unquote system
Is just stop having children
That and protesting has went to an all-time low
Occasionally you get some groups up there hugging each other
No, you don't need to protest at all
The protesting doesn't scare them at all
If they expect the protesting and nothing happens at all, it gets really quiet
That's when they're terrified
Like voting, if no one ever showed up, and I mean no one to vote
They would be completely terrified, anyone in any official capacity would leave the country within a few days
Because they'd say, holy shit, something is going to happen
They've figured it out
It's all backwards
Essentially what's really backwards is the forces that have been leased
The leaseholders, I should say the leasees, not the leasers of this planet
Or the evil spirits
They're operating on an IQ of 2 million
What's being discussed here is not even still contrary to what they're doing, it's minor
But I'm just saying how simple it is from a human perspective
Because it works two ways
The spirits influence mankind to act a certain way, and if the mankind is strong enough spiritually to resist that
If they can, if it's put out in a way that they can resist
If they put it in you in a way that they know will really get in, then you can't
But if they put it out in a way that you still have not only the appearance of choice, but the possibility to act on it
You still can change things
But I'm not saying that you will or should or anything at this point
But it's so simple, all these things are very simple
Anything going on?
I don't have any messages coming in Questions or anything?
I was just going to say, we will take calls or anything
Questions, that would be fine also
I've gotten emails recently, it's like if you never did another sonic event, it's still 50-100 times more than anyone else has said on the rectangle
Oh easily
Unfortunately people are not sending me links of approval, I haven't gotten any in a long time
That's a good start
It's really a good start
And I entertain some of them, I have to laugh my ass off when I see what people are trying to do on the internet
The rectangle
You see they're coming from the same old institutional mindset
They're so far removed from reality
That they have to talk about all the fictions and make it real
One thing that should be something you cite right away
When someone says you have to worry about this, or what do we worry about
That word worry, when you see that come up
Or what can we do
I'll put that on my list of things to do
You don't fight
It's even shown again in the fictional movies
When you have the superhero show up, you have all the soldiers or whatever
He's trying to help out, they're fighting their asses off unloading all their ammo
He shows up, what does he do?
Stands there
A little observation
So if you just stopped everything, that would be a very clear signal in many ways
But that's not going to happen, too many
But here's the thing
When I say people will never comprehend the meaning of the ever that they have left
Because when things are opened up completely
What they don't comprehend will be so obviously
In front of them that they're going to ask to learn to comprehend it
Well right now, even if it was in front of them
They don't even see what's right in front of them
So there's no way of comprehension at all of anything, any subject at all
Of humans as a whole
But anyway
The thought was fleeting
But the thing is, because they have no comprehension of any subject, anything at all
They have to just go through it
Like most people, you can look at a various consensus and say, well if these people are really old
They don't have a long way to go, and if these people are really young, they potentially have a long way to go
That's how usually the thought goes, right?
And it doesn't matter, because it doesn't matter if you're going to live for a thousand in this state or five days or five years
Or fifty years, if you have the chances of comprehending what's going on in any capacity
Whether it's who you are, society, money, medicine, anything
Any subject at all
When you're so closed off from a comprehensive point of view, where you don't understand or comprehend anything
It doesn't matter how long you're around for
So it's not any longer a condition of, oh well, you're older, you know more
No, you don't know shit, because it's the same old mindset
For example, I went to this sushi restaurant once
And I kind of knew the guys there, and I said, who's the old guy?
And he said, well he's got thirty years experience
In other words, he shut down after a year and he still makes sushi the same way that he did when he first started
And the answer is the second half, they all broke out laughing
So a history, and just by looking at anyone, any human
You'll see that experience means nothing
In the grand scheme of things, and actually even in the middle scheme
In a minor way it does, in some cases, people are just too, let me say the word, stupid
For experience to make a difference
In other words, they see so little of what they're interacting with, and I mean anything
Whether it's personal relationships, anything in the sciences, anything in the spiritual arts
Mental arts, same thing, cosmology, any subject at all
Well when you looked at Dr. Day's work
From 1969, and how controlled that was
And what the repercussions of it were
And then you factor that in with low food quality
Oh yeah, environmental toxification
Spiritual toxification
Well they have no concept of history, they have no concept of the natural sciences at all
Very little, only on a chemical basis
That's useful for industry only
Like all these engineers and scientists, what they say is science is not science
It's industrial science
How do we stamp it out and make it for manufacturing
And then once it's out in the field, how do we maintain it or
Discard it so we can have another version, a newer version of the same thing
I speak to people in industry, and some of the older people are like
Yeah, just because it's newer doesn't mean it's better
And they'll get into some rationale, but they still don't see that the science that they're using is strictly industrial
It's not physical, in other words it's a form of fiction
Like if you know anyone that's a medical technician, aka a doctor
I'd say more than 90% of what they think they know is medical fiction
The 10% that is not medical fiction is the undeniable part
That you don't have to be a doctor to know
Because essentially if you take any doctor and press him
To the core foundation of what healing is
Or recovery or health, he says the same thing grandmas do
Or little children do
Just get some food and rest and the body will heal it, that's all they say
Well you don't need a medical degree for that
And usually orbiting around that and beyond that is all fiction
They know that, that's what makes them, to me they're offensive and vile
The medical people, and in the future fortunately they will also be considered criminal
See right now some of them are not considered criminal as a whole
That's why not much is being done by the people, but I'm telling you they're a criminal
What they're doing, and of course the legal community also
And also the teachers, the education community
The political community, the religious community
In the future just bear in mind what you either accept or not accept or want to laugh at
Or point a finger at, because maybe you've heard some Greek speak
Might offend you or you might find it vile or laughable now, but I'm telling you in the future it will be criminal
And they will be dealt with very harshly, what you see as the norm right now
Not because I say so, because the gods say so
And you can check up on that
So, in the meantime when you bring up such contrasting analogies
Meaning contrasting to what will be and what is, what do you do?
And the answer is very simple, nothing
You don't do anything about all these esoteric concepts
What makes them esoteric is things are not as you're told they are
And once you figure out what they are they kind of become beyond esoteric
When you try to explain it to the common moron
So that's where it goes back to the old credo food, clothing, shelter
And even the common idiot says that, what does that have to do with the price of tea in China
Well guess what tea in China is, it's food isn't it
Very often you might bring up something that is dismissed
And they usually give a food analogy, an economic analogy which is shelter
So there's really not much to say or do
It's actually been rather quiet newsworthy wise
Little things sure enough
Growing season, yeah
Growing season is the most activity and that means it's quiet
Because in contrast, let's just translate that into language that people understand
There's a lot going on but they don't know how to report it to the morons at large
And in other words there's so much going on
That they don't even want to refer to it so it's kind of quiet
I assure you the summer is the time of growth
There's tons going on but it's just not on the rectangle or on what's called the news
What will happen usually during the fall
Is a burst of things going on because you just can't contain them
And they are reported in their twisted manner
Here's the thing, how can you actually give people the truth when they wouldn't recognize it
I've said in the past, you can't have real education
It's not possible, it's not at this point
It's a Nazi moron
Well if you provided it no one would go because they wouldn't recognize it
That's why I've said they're unrehabilitatable, you can't fix it at this point
It's like the old car analogy
You can't fix it, so what do you do?
You just drive it until it dies and that's exactly how humanity is going to go
But it's not going to die, it's going to be influenced
I had an old Volvo, a 68, I think it was a 4L or DL
And we wanted to junk it and I said let's see what happens
We took the oil out of it, there might have been less than a quart
And we ran it for a week, not constantly, but drove it and then it finally seized
Has there ever been an engine that seized?
And I was like wow
This was 35 years ago and the car was 30 years ago, 35 years ago
Or something like that, or 20 something years ago
It was more than a 50 year old car and if I would have known that and just maintained it I would still have it
Right
There were some small ones that I fell in love with back then
So humans will be fine, and you don't need many of them
You could start off with 2 and then finish off with 8, but there were more than 2 before that
There were millions before the 2, but that's part of the other discussion
The other thing is you started off with 8 again that we're told about
There were more than then again also
In the next two decades for sure there will be less than 500 million people on the earth
If not less than that, on the whole earth, which is still a pretty big number
When you think about it
It's still a very large number
We've got 16 in the stream
We can make this a real short one, 40 minutes or so
What's in a name?
I just came into the office again, let's see what's going on
Sunburn remedy, not really
You did have an interesting observation on light, internal light and external
That's going on to the ether discussions which I've never done
Remember once I said let's do something on the weather, it would be 90% about the ether
But the sunburn remedy, yeah
You could use intense blue light if you're familiar with chromotherapy
You look up chromotherapy, C-H-R-O-M-A therapy
Dinshaw Gaudiality, if you're familiar with that
Using color and light to heal
You did put that in a link a long time back
Dinshaw Gaudiality, he's one of the few people, he had a house in New Jersey
He was running a clinic out of it in the 20's and 30's and the army bombed it
And they said in the newspaper the lab exploded and had a fire
But all the neighbors were like no, an army airplane flew over and dropped a bomb on it
So this is still going on today
Have you ever heard of Waco by the way?
Sunburn remedy, just get yourself some blue light bulbs or if you have some blue mylar
Like the film gels, are you familiar with theatrical lighting, they're those big high wattage lights
And they use gels in front of them
Or blue glass, you can take a blue glass bottle and put a spotlight behind it
And for a few hours you take a nap in a room with the shades drawn
I'm here in the office, one of the windows is tinted out completely blue because I'm in the high desert
Blue is a general overall good color for that
Yeah, that would remedy a sunburn or a burn
Green would regrow skin back, yellow is for the internal organs
You can look up Dinshaw Gerialdi or Chromotherapy
That's a good topic
Yeah, it's very basic, you just have to be patient with it and you have to be diligent with it
I haven't had a lot of success with it other than the sunburn remedy
Yes, and that does work, if I had a sunburn I would do the blue light for sure
In three hours that should make all the pain go away and if you do a few more sessions in a few days
Or within that same day it should probably reverse it
And don't eat food that makes you photosensitive
Like parsley and there's a few others
You could look up what foods make you photosensitive
Obviously chemical foods, artificial sweeteners and things like that, processed foods
Basically it's a standard American diet
Yeah, the color of one's skin is dependent on the internal ether light that they have, which is not a visible light
That's why you get a tan
When you expose the exterior of the body to let's say a light load, an ethereal load
That starts to overcharge the interior, the skin gets darker to filter that out
To preserve the level of internal light for that being
I've been around someone who's Northern European
And if I go out in the sun I tan very quickly and they don't
You'd think they'd tan faster because their internal light is much higher than mine
And I did a long talk about this years ago and people were crying racism
Like you're trying to say black people got a low internal light
No, I'm not trying to say it, I just said it
It has nothing to do with it, it's just to do with the internal ether
And eventually you've got lots of phrenology or something
No it doesn't, it's provable
This harkens back to water and air and all the constituents to it
And also you can understand skin ailments more
And then the reason for lawful clothes or fibers
There's a lot of connection between that
There is, but they always go astray
Ultimately, for not eating pork
Because they didn't have refrigeration or pork tends to have more parasites
So does rabbit also
But that's not necessarily true either
Because you can segregate and inoculate in a way in the womb
Of baby pigs to not have that
Even though it gets transferred, but they will develop it
Ultimately the reason why you do it is because my dad said so
I hate to bring up this analogy because it's really a play on Simon Magus
But it's not that
The main reason why you should do it is out of respect
For example, when I used to have clients that were from other parts of the world
And they lived in America and they spoke very little English
I spent a week or so learning their language
Whatever language it was so I could communicate
Not because I would be a successful communicator in their languages, but out of respect
So when I'd greet them, if I had a Korean client
I'd say, annyeonghaseyo, bangapsumnida
And they're like, wow, thank you
Out of respect, obviously my Korean sucks
But it starts you off on the right foot
And you do it out of respect
Which isn't really taught much these days by the way
No, and it shouldn't because there's no reason for it anymore
But many people always try to go back to a scientific reason
For you doing biblical, let's say what's fit and proper or lawful
You could, but that should not be something you should even lean on a little bit
For several reasons.
One is the science is flawed Two, the science is purely material, where in scripture it's beyond material You know what I mean?
I'm not saying it's not possible to lean on what's called good science But the science that is taught is so material based that it's almost It's just not going to work So ultimately you do it because it's the right thing to do That's the moral and ethical question.
If you study morality and ethics There's very little direct tangibility to those things But the tangibility to having morality and ethics is something that develops After you establish the morals and the ethics So let's say you go to a society and you instill bad morals and ethics Well, we just instilled these this past week.
How are we doing?
We're still doing fine Oh, but go check on that society a year from now or five years or ten years from now.
How are they doing then?
Tangibly terrible, you see So let's say you discover what's lawful, fit and proper The right thing to do.
It doesn't change much and you're not going to find much tangibility in it right away That's why I tell people you could learn this stuff, but if you don't live it, it means nothing Because that's where the tangibility comes in It's the same thing, for example, when you work Even back when you had a good possibility, not even that it was good A possibility of a good education.
When you got to industry, what did they tell you?
Oh, you're just out of college, you don't know anything
Now it's kind of going back and forth because so many people have realized
It's like the birth rate or something now
Well, yeah, because they realized it was bullshit
During the times of Jimmy Carter, people had a lie on their resume that they had a Ph.D. because no one would hire them
They had a lie that they said they only had a high school diploma so they could get a job
And they were over-educated with nothing
But for them to keep the lie going, now they're putting emphasis on it, but it still has no emphasis
But the meaning of the tangibility of knowledge only comes through in practice
Just like, again, the college graduate that's fresh out of school
He goes into industry and they have to show him how we do things in industry
Yes, he can use what he learned in school, but until he learns to tie what he learned in school together
What's in industry, does he get the tangibility out of it?
There are people that refuse to make their knowledge tangible and they just stick and become teachers In the conventional sense You see what I mean?
But in regard to doing things, you would do it because it's the right thing to do How many times have you heard that?
Well, you know, back in the day when Dad used to say, don't
You agreed, but at the same time, later on in hindsight, you got to understand maybe the reasons behind it
Which usually gave you a lot more information on it
I guess in some ways I find that the same respect
It gets you to understand who you're respecting
The reasons behind it
To understand them is quite puzzling sometimes
But the little pieces that you do get are quite fascinating
Behavior
The last comment, I just came in the office again
This is food, this is not
Well, no, it doesn't really say that either
It goes under the category, because you can eat anything, you can eat human
That's food
It's what you do, remember that when you read the Bible, that's not written for you
Out the box, you have to decide, here's the thing that people miss
The people that the scriptures were written for are long dead
Or some of them are just very young right now
I know it's kind of a harsh statement, right?
Anybody in between, it's really not written for them, really And the prophets included And I had a discussion with someone recently from Israel And I was saying, you ever notice the prophets were not popular people?
Because if they were, there would be a hint that they were
It doesn't say that they were liked or popular
The way you deal with someone that you didn't want to hang out with when you were in high school
Right, the ditch
What's interesting in scripture is that it's voluntary
Once you learn about this, you have to think about it and decide
A yes or a no
And this is the part that proves, in my mind at least
This is an opinion from a theoretical, let's say academic point of view
That man is not finished yet
You ever notice when things are being tested in industry, like cars or airplanes
When they test them for durability, they don't really care about whether it has the finished paint job on it or not
Like planes, they're tested green
It doesn't matter
If you're going to bench test a TV, it doesn't have to have the walnut cabinet on it
You just needed the chassis assembled
And it's grounded
And back then they didn't care about grounding too much, it was two pronged, remember?
It was all isolation
And you found out real quick when you weren't
So what's interesting about it is there's a higher way of doing things
And then there's the way of doing things
Notice I didn't say lower
The lower, like I said, I've looked high and low for you, but I couldn't find you
So I didn't look low enough
Recently I watched, just to get off of this a minute, I watched a thing about the Holocaust
I think it was a Netflix production
It was about making comedy out of it, because what happens when you have a bad situation
If enough time goes past, you can laugh about it
And it was interesting, they had these old comedians
And there was two Jews and they wanted to kill Adolf Hitler
So they go where Adolf Hitler lives and they're waiting around
They were told he'd be back home by 8 o'clock so they could do their deed
So 8 o'clock comes around, Hitler doesn't come around
Another hour goes by, still no Hitler
Another two hours go by, no Hitler
Another three hours go by, Hitler still doesn't come home
And one Jew looks to the other and he says, I hope he's okay
Anyway, it's a joke, right?
The interesting thing about all of these things, if you're going to deal on the higher level
You have to understand, things are the way they are
Because how can you give out a leasehold to the earth, to a malevolent being
And then impose what's right to do
That lease would be defunct, it would invalidate the lease
And even if it didn't, I don't see those conditions in the lease
It says you can do this to set yourself apart
Or my people will do this
Because it's implied, more than implied, that this reality has been given over to the malevolent beings
Period
So wouldn't that mess up the plan if you had to eat or had to wear or had to do this
Well, the decision was already made
Right, so what happens is the lease is given to the earth to these beings
That influence mankind indirectly and directly
And then the option is still visible
That's why in scripture it says this is how you make yourself what?
That's good, no, that's how you make yourself set apart Or my people versus the other guys people You see the point?
And up until now, I can say this comfortably and with confidence also
There hasn't been this kind of talk in over 2000 years
And there's some people that have tried doing it in the past
But the moment they say G-O-D and not God's, right
God is not accurate, God's is
Or J-E-S-U-S, creature, they use that all the time
Not only to me, but spiritually that wipes away the rest of what they're doing
You get it?
Or Christianity, when they bring up a good Christian or a real Christian They've wiped away that is all work of the adversary I've done the experiment with people in public I told them, close your eyes, I'm going to say something The J-E-S-U-S, do you get an image?
They all raise their hands And I told them it was a guy wearing a diaper nailed to a cross Now if I say, Joshua, what image do you get?
And they're like, I don't know, I don't really get one, do you still get the same image?
And they're like, no, I don't get the same image Right, you see?
The Greek speak has actually been the first time in thousands of years
Publicly where you have this kind of talk that's been done at all so clearly
And it's kind of sad and pathetic, I should say
You've got so many people and only one place where you can get it pretty much straight
It's kind of sad, but at the same time it is
There's people in the past, again, for thousands of years that have tried
But what do they do?
They go right back to the territory
They have to be comfortable in the territory, they always say the Christian thing
Or the Jewish thing, or the J-E-S-U-S thing, or God thing, there's no God
If you're going to use that term, it must be plural
Or if you're referring to one out of a plurality, but the one cannot be necessarily plural
Then you should name it
Then if you start dealing with plurality, it's like, give me the tools from the shed, you know the tool?
Yeah, that one, for the tire, no not that tool, the tool I was talking about for the windshield
That tool, that tool, no the tools, you know where the tools are, the tool, just get the tool
Come on, let's work, how about screwdriver, hammer, open end socket
Why don't we start getting more accurate, you can't, not allowed
And by the way, like Dimitri said in one of his comments
The rulers, the people behind, their God is the adversary by the way
That's why at a recent sonic event I said, if anyone's flying by the planet
And you pointed to the earth and said, this is where the sons and the daughters of the adversary live
That's a very accurate statement
It's on the billboard, on the other side of the moon
When you hear stuff like lunar calendar, or the J-E-S-U-S, or Christianity
Or real Christian, or messianic, or all this stuff
That's still talk and rationale and reasoning within the lease
The lease holder, if you know what I mean, within the adversary
They're trying to just, what they're doing is, they're creating a negotiable territory
Or a negotiable realm within the adversary's realm
I'm not saying there's a way to revolt against it either
The only thing to do is set yourself apart, and that's what scripture does
It doesn't say do anything, does it?
Respectfully
And I mean on a social scheme
Not on a personal scheme, there's always lots to do
Well on a personal thing, the thing to do is study
And that's the thing that people that are always looking to someone else to tell them what's in scripture
Are never going to figure it out
I don't need to explain that, that's obvious
If you don't handle the scriptures directly
And you're waiting on someone else to tell you what's in it, you're never going to get it yourself
Not because there's dependency or anything like that
But because you're just not going to get it, it doesn't work that way
Well as I mentioned before we went on, I'm just always drawn back to Genesis
And this has been for the last four or five months easily
After getting done in different parts of the book
Especially when I touch other subjects
Especially one with Ether and everything
Well it's non-material
Yeah the issues of counter space
I did that one with the grandson about the dot on the paper
And gave him an analogy that way about that
And he got it
Good, and I'm not saying that's what it is, that the dot on the paper is the end of a line
To massage, to start flexing the mind into that possibility
Because we can't really go into counter space
Because the very nature of our perception is materially based
And I've given you an example that if you didn't have that round organ in your head called an eye
You wouldn't see things, and I mean that eye that humans have
You wouldn't see things the way that you do
If you had the eye of an insect or an animal or no eye and you're a spiritual being
What you call light appears very very differently
And you can prove this very simply by using methods of diffraction and filtering
There are sensors that you can use, you've heard of different filter sensors or frequency sensors that only see infrared
For example, you're not going to necessarily use that to determine the color of wallpaper
There's no color in most of the perceptions that exist
Only we have this sense of color that we have
And a dog has a sense of color that he has because his eye is different
And we can see how things, no pun here, how other creatures see by dissecting the eye
Cryptochromes and various aspects of structure and layout
We can hypothecate and infer how sight would be to that creature
But one thing that we cannot infer is what would sight be like to a spiritual creature that has no material sense of sensing light
They sense it beyond, or they don't see, like the gods don't see, for example, a green wallpaper like we do
Well, the fact that in Genesis, at the beginning, he separated light and dark
Right, well there's also the concept of
The concept of, let's say, attribute
In our world, darkness doesn't have an attribute, it's just the absence of light
That's the most we can attribute to darkness
But in Scripture, there's actually aspects of darkness where it's substance-based
So that means it's counter-spatial
Counter-spatial reference
So when things are mentioned in Scripture as a substance, or inferred to as substantive
That are without substance or attribute in our world, that's a counter-spatial reference
I have a short list of those, a short list of about 20 items
And I have not talked about those publicly or privately much
And here's the other thing, in privately, it has been over 12 years or so that I've discussed some of the stuff in Genesis or Revelation
Even privately, I used to have calls with people on a regular basis
And I would not discuss the book of Revelation and other things like that
So I really don't discuss many of the stuff at all for a very long time
And I've actually tried to increase my awareness of these things by meditating on them
And perhaps even, I should say, begin to study again
But it doesn't mean that there is a time coming that, you know, there has to be a demand for it
And it has to be appropriate.
It's not appropriate, either for me or anyone, I believe To just come out and start running their mouth on the, what I would call, even though I don't think they're respectable The ancient sages would say that, if you understand something, good And if you don't, just be happy with what you do understand You know what I mean?
So in other words, it's not for you to need to know basis But there is a time where if the, let's just say there's an insurmountable demand Then that demand must be met.
Or if the equation becomes so large That it needs to be equalized, then you do it.
But otherwise it's fine to go to your death And not reveal it.
But on the other hand You can say it's neither this or that because knowledge and knowing is its own reward And that's satisfactory.
Since when do you get a reward and you share it with others?
Then it's not your reward.
Then it's a communal thing And what I'm saying is knowledge, what people, you can infer this It may not necessarily be the whole aspect of it, but knowledge is a personal thing It's not a communal thing.
And that can be proven logistically
In other words, you can get a hundred people in a room and give a base of knowledge
And if you interview the hundred people, they're all going to give you a version of it
But the one who gets it may not be able to communicate it
But he got it, so he did get his reward
Give an example, we're in Exodus, you know
How was knowledge a reward on the community level when they were being led out by supernatural and paranormal forces
And they were still grumbling and complaining
Why is this going on?
We'd rather be in Egypt where we have the leek and the garlic In our comfort So that proves right there that having an even overt display is not a reward for the community And it's right in front of them Since when has a depository of a great library been a reward to the community?
Since when?
Never.
Only to those that actually go in there and find the gems that are held within
So knowledge is a personal reward
Just to consider that
And you don't have to share it
And even if you tried to share it, you may not be able to
Right, you may not be able to communicate all the fine points
That's why I go back to saying, like I said earlier, there are many still that rely on others to tell them what's in Scripture
Without, let's say, an onward assault on the Scripture themselves
And yes, you're going to have to assault it, meaning assault as being an affront
Because when you start in the society that you're living in, you're going to have to go through all the layers
In a very almost militant way
The first thing they throw at your feet is aversion, and you're going to have to assault it
You're going to have to say, this is crap
Then you go to an interlinear, and then you assault that
You keep going back and back, and then you find things that are said are preserved, and you find out there's things missing
I had a conversation with someone
I'm not going to mention names recently, usually when I say that I mention a name, but I won't
And I said, do me a favor, this did not exist by the way a few years ago, it exists now
On the internet
Go look up, just do a regular search in whatever browser you use
Verses removed from the New Testament
I'm serious, there's some good study, I did that a few months ago
And actually there's a few people that in a scholarly way said these verses were in and now they've been removed
And they give you the history of when they were removed and maybe why
And then do another search, a total separate search
Verses that were added to the New Testament
Just put that, verses that were added to the New Testament
And you're going to see at least 10 to 20 verses that were added in the versions that you have that were not
In the Aramaic or Greek even
Or you'll see ones that were added in the Greek later
I have three Greek New Testaments and they're all different, what does that tell you?
I'm doing that as we speak
You'll see there's a couple of websites out there where they've actually done the work
And they'll cite, especially most of them tend to go around the Erasmus, the Texas Receptus
That's like around the text that was used to give you the versions that you have today which is really screwed up
Around that time you'll see the discrepancies
But again, the homework might be for anyone inclusive of what I'm saying in terms of being a militant assault on the Scripture
That you have to perform in order to get close to it
Is do a search in the browser, verses that have been removed from the New Testament
And then do a separate search, verses that have been added to the New Testament
And you'll see lists and lists and lists
And you tell me if you have a valid document, and I'm telling you you don't
Somebody asked a question about, do you know something about the three brains of the body?
I'm familiar with the concept of brain tissue in the heart Right?
And then there's a part of the brain that's in the mouth, actually brain tissue on the roof of the mouth Are you familiar with that?
With this I'm going to have to lean on the ancient Egyptians
When they mummified people they had special vessels for all of the organs and all that
But if you ask them, where's the vessel for the brain, they say that's completely useless
They would just put two rods, like knitting needles through the nose
And stir it up until it became liquefied and then pour it out
That's how they got the brain out without opening the skull
They'd just stick a bunch of knitting needles through the nose and keep stirring for a few hours
Until it goes into liquid state and they just pour it out
Yeah, I just repeated myself to give a more accurate thing
So people, I guess they do the Halloween thing, but anyway
Yeah, you pagans out there might figure some technique
Anyway, so I think it's useless for many levels, the brain
Because it's a receptor, you can see it's basically an embedded folded transmission line
You know how the intestines are all bunched up?
If you look at all the folds in the brain, just stretch that sucker out I'm not saying that you can, but you see how it forms I can tell you that most people can live a pretty normal life without a brain right now You get it?
Like Jack Fresco said, normal just means fucked up
Adjusted
Yeah, so I don't think there's much discussion about the brain
I tend not to go there because most people don't need it
And even if you want to go on the other level, it receives from the external input
And we've already established what your input's going to be like
And your output will be the same
Otherwise, unless it's set apart
And then if it's set apart, you realize the brain is just the condition of your antenna
And of course there's motor functions that extend into it
Just like all the organs, if you go to some medical practitioners in other cultures
In the western, they only look for a heart and lung pulse
Breathing is actually a pulsing in the heart, but in other cultures, each organ has its own pulse
And it does, you can measure it
It's very faint, some are actually pretty prominent
Different rhythms
I think in this society, for the past several thousand years
The discussion about the brain is irrelevant
But nonetheless, is there anything provided about the three brains?
Let's see, I'll go back to there I'm not near a computer now, so I'll be short Nope, changed on to something else Gurdjieff's teachings I'll have to look them up Anything else?
That's about it Park used to be storage in the old fattened barrels When the old timers didn't have refrigerators, at least in Cuba For people in the countryside We lose you?
Stirring in some coffee I guess if there's nothing else, maybe we'll just Any other thoughts?
Like I said before, it's a neat little ritual once in a while
The weeks, by the way, by doing what we call a pagan Tuesday
Is not once a week, but it appears that it is
It appears, yes
And we will take call-ins
If you'd like to call in with your questions, that would be good
Stir up the conversation, or screw up the conversation
Stir it up
I usually see it as a screw up, but that's okay
Did you have something good to eat, at least in the past few days?
Because there is that concept
The chances of having something really good to eat every day
Is quite rare for most people, by the way
Especially in the Western culture, or actually anywhere
I'm actually very hot up this way, so I've been eating rather light
It's interesting how that works
It really does
Are you dressed for comfort, are you dressed lawfully
Are you dressed in a healthful way, and the same with your surroundings
Are you comfortable in your shelter, are you warm when it's cold out
And are you cool when it's hot out
And other than that, there's not much to do
Wait it out, I think the real fun in this whole thing is going to be after the resurrection
Other than getting caught up in all the machinations and all the bullshit that's coming
There's plenty of dummy load out there
To keep you occupied
Okay, I see here
In regard to ground zero, you mentioned three terms, I don't know what that means
Well, ground zero is in a technical sense
Let's say you work in that field
You work in that field
Which is the nuclear technology
When it comes to devices that detonate
You have ground zero definition, which is the location on earth, above the earth or below the earth
Or the water where the device is detonated
The device itself is called a zero box
It's not called a nuke, it's not called a bomb, it's not called a whatever
It's called a zero box
It's like, hey man, where's the zero box?
And then when the device goes off, that's called zero time
And for civil use and peaceful use, most
I'll say it, most detonation mechanisms
I wouldn't say it's directly for international treaty
But most detonations, especially in the civil use, are structured
To be 2959 zero time, so 30 minutes
So you have 29 minutes 59 seconds and then on 30 it's called zero time
So you have ground zero as the location on the earth
Zero box is the device itself and zero time is when it goes off
For the car bombs and the other forms of terrorism that they're using
The zero time would be when they trigger it
They tell you it's a terrorist car bomb and then it has a yield of 200 tons of TNT
Well, it was a milk truck
Well, let's just see, a railroad car holds about 50 tons
And that's about four times or three times the size of a milk truck
And you need the equivalent of four railroad cars to meet the 200 ton yield
So how do you put that in a milk truck?
Yeah, but not that much Not even 50, but still 50 to a railroad, where is it?
The stuff that you can get away with on people is just unbelievable Don't even try to wrap your mind around it and rationalize what people believe You know what else I found fascinating?
Is that back in the day when you used to watch these quote-unquote news programs
Even local stuff, you used to have a place on the website where you could leave comments
You don't see that no more, period
They'd have their own little websites
They don't want you feeding back and putting your two cents out to the people
Here's a good reason for that
Go read the comments on any YouTube
So stupid, any YouTube
Even if you go to a fairly sane, benign subject
You can see their brains are mush already
But at the same time, cutting off the communication
Another form of it, I just found it interesting
And that's been the last 10 years easy, 15 if I wanted to go on a limb
Interesting how that's cut away
What could people possibly say that matters?
Well under a subject of a man breastfeeding his child
Which was an interesting one in today's little piece of trivia
Oh God
I'm getting a question in Skype, it's fairly long
It's regarding the Elohim and the Elim
Well that is a deific
Different Elohim, Elim, it's basically a language thing
The different gods that you see calling on the name of Yahweh
When they began to call the name of Yahweh
If you read that in context, it's actually more than just calling on the name of Yahweh
Because we're talking about an early population on the earth
But in Genesis, this is going to have to go into that discussion I didn't want to do
But if you, for example
The various forms of El, Elim, Elohim
Are the various language and dialect as well
If you try to find the oldest preserved text of the book of Daniel
It's not in Hebrew, it's in Aramaic
Because it was penned along the Babylonian cognate
Or the Akkadian Aramaic cognate
Now, El, you'll see
El, El-Yi or El-Allah
You've heard of Allah, right?
El-Ah is God or The God, El-God, The God
The God of Gods, El-Allah
So you know how they give you the typical Arabic cognate of Allah, Allah
It's not Allah, it's El-Allah
It's the God of Gods or The God, so there's no name even with Allah
I've pressed several Muslims and said, yeah we don't know his name
They literally tell you that, it's not his name, yeah we know that
Most Muslims, they're like Mormons, they don't know anything
Or whatever, Catholics or take your pick, any religion, they don't know anything
But if you try to structure a rational definition around what people are using
It's basically language changes
I think I've mentioned this before
When you hear the Muslims say Allah, that's Al-Allah
That's an Akkadian cognate, old Arabic cognate for meaning the God of Gods or The God
There's no name there, so that's interesting how that is also negated
What I liked about that is Dimitri brought that up
How Taurah is Torah in Arabic and that's really fundamental Islam
I haven't gone through too much discussion on that
But what you had in the Middle East up until what's called
The Islamic Movement 1500 years ago or really less than 1000 years ago
It wasn't until the Ottoman Empire kicked in that it really started becoming more formalized
But all the descendants of Abraham and thereof
They came within the concept of law that we consider the concept of law that's Biblical
Even if you listen to these Patriot idiots
They'll tell you, oh America, well it's Biblical law
If you understand the UCC code, the 72 hours of writer refusal
Commercial laws go back to Biblical law
The entire world at one point was under Biblical law
The known world let's say
But that overlapped or was overlapped over it depending on how you want to look at it
The pagan stuff
So that's why very often when you look at the various aspects of Islam, it's territorial
Just like the various aspects of Christianity, it's territorial
Because those are the regional pagan traditions
And they just eventually say, well just make it another form of Christianity
For example, American Christianity, you have the Baptists here, you have the Mormons here
In Utah, Arizona, Colorado
You've got the Catholics on the East Coast, typically
And in Rome, you've got the Catholics and that part of Roman influence
Western and Eastern, you've got the Eastern Orthodox
Then you've got a different form of Catholicism in Mexico
And then a different one in Asia
So basically, they adjust
In Islam, different parts of the Islamic world have different parts of Islam
That are based on whatever political thing was overlapped
Over the pagan local geographic entities
It gets kind of complex, and I think I've gone through these analogies before
On various sonics, but not in detail, there's no reason to
Because what is needed is to equalize the stupidity
There's almost no depth to the level of stupidity that's in the world
So why not just try to balance the equation
By just making a short, succinct, clear, rational way to look at what's called the truth
But with the analogy I gave about all of the various religions
You can see through historically what's known as
Like Demetri said, God's law
Meaning the one that we find given to Moses, codified
When I mean codified, meaning it has a pattern
It has a meme and a story behind it
Like Leviticus, the first five books of Moses centered with Leviticus for law
That was known, not in its entirety, and not in its whole
Maybe in part, but maybe in some places throughout the whole world, especially the Middle East
And actually I've also mentioned before
There's over a dozen mentions, direct mentions to Moses and the biblical law in the Koran anyway
Well it's good that you gave the history on that also, that helps a lot
Sure, and again, when you speak about
I think Demetri in his video was talking about the western world
One thing that people don't understand is
There is no safe place, there is no better place
How many times have you folks heard me make references, well it's earth
The whole earth is under this negative lease
There's no place to go, there is no place geographic
Dirt under your fingernails place of safety, it's a spiritual one
This is what people don't understand
There was a big movement from the 19th century to the late 20th century that there was a place of safety
That you have to find, and that's like the wrong, again that's
Has to be in accordance with the stupidity that's been put out
And that's why I think it's important to, if you've never heard of counter space
Get a, I wouldn't say familiar, sometimes there's people
Years I've discussed this, I still don't understand it
In other words a reality where none of your reality works the way you comprehend reality
Is the reality of the gods, the spiritual world
That's where the safety is, and that non-physical world controls the physical world
All right, so I'm going to dip, I think we're at about an hour and a half
That's an old word, remember dip means I'm going to go right, so thanks everyone
Anything else Bruce, otherwise we'll just close it right here
I think we've ran out of questions
We had 19 in there tonight
Oh that's fine
Three or four people is enough to balance the equation on a planetary level believe it or not
That's four times more than we need
You take care sir, and thank you very much