Greetings folks, we're live with the Greek, and
how are you doing tonight, Greek?
Greetings, okay, we're here.
Yeah, another Teriyaki Tuesday.
Yes.
So, I just got in and looking at
some emails, I guess, and I don't know
if there's anything pressing.
So, anything you've seen in the chat?
A little bit of activity in here.
Okay.
Yeah, there was a few, now that I
recall.
Let me get this box out of my
way here.
Actually, I'll open one up that is listed
questions here.
But, yeah, not much going on other than
it's the winter season, and it's pervasive to
what to expect in the winter season.
For the folks that are upside down, it's
the middle of their growing season, or beginning
of a hardy growing season, depending on the
crop.
So, yeah, but everything goes cross-latitude on
the north in terms of prophetic stuff, and
what you might consider the ways of the
world, the seasonal ways of the world, is
where the northern hemisphere dominates.
I don't think the southern hemisphere ever dominated
on any cultural or even phenomenal stuff.
I can't recall anything either.
Hey, I was going to ask you, anything
that you noticed with the rotting season this
time around?
Yeah, it came sort of like right before
winter and fall.
Here, it's very balmy and warm, and then
winter comes, which is still just cool, not
cold.
Rotting season for this part of the world
came around fall, end of fall like it
usually does.
There seems to be one that comes either
in the middle of the winter or towards
the beginning of spring for some.
The rotting season is interesting because it is
really sustained by its geographical location.
What I mean, sustained, it is in essence
part of the geography.
It's not like spring, summer, winter, or fall.
So it would be in different places?
Yes, it's different.
And again, the rotting season is, if you
kept, let's say, something perishable at a constant
temperature, it will spoil faster during the rotting
season.
Wounds don't heal as fast.
Things that are fermented tend to over-ferment.
Interesting.
I've been keeping an eye out ever since
you brought that out, and it just kind
of periodically just crosses the mind.
Well, at one point I was crazy enough
to do a basic yeast culture in a
jar with a single hole in it so
it could breathe.
You know how you put the insects in
a jar and you put a hole on
top, right?
With a ballpoint pen was the classic way
to do it back in the 60s and
70s.
Well, you just do a small yeast culture,
very little.
You don't need a colony, you just need
evidence of reaction.
With a tiny little hole, because a lot
of CO2 builds up, and you just watch
it.
And you have to redo it every week.
You can't just do it once and let
all the seasons go by.
You have to do it every seven days.
You dump it out, put a new one
in, and you just monitor it.
You'll notice during the rotting season it just
goes crazy, and you start getting multicolors like
purples and reds and blues, where at the
other time of year you don't get that.
Very interesting.
But you know what I have to say
about that, right?
Why bother?
Who are you going to tell?
You're not going to be allowed to do
this academically, and most people can't listen to
it anyway.
It's just good for one's own knowledge.
Yeah, they're very small.
In other words, that's a good time that
if you were going to do, let's say,
pickling or preservation, or even wrap a bunch
of notes that you're going to bury in
the backyard or something, or something that you
want to put away for a long time,
don't do it during the rotting season, because
it will be more susceptible to decay when
you're putting it away.
Very, very interesting.
So there are a lot of reasons why
you want to understand that particular cycle for
the person that is considering those things.
When do you have more decay than others?
I guess the reason I brought that up
is I myself, I work basically with cardboard.
Opening this, taking that out, in a repetitory
kind of way throughout the day.
And throughout the whole year, not a problem
with the hands.
And then all of a sudden it's like
super dry, super cracked, super, what the H
is going on?
And I'm thinking to myself, boy, this is
just too winky dinky.
Okay, a very simple, considering your age, you're
older than 35, and considering where you are,
typical skin cracking, dry eczema, dandruff even, things
like that, or too much protein in the
diet, specifically animal protein, and or highly processed
oils, fats.
Not regular fats like olive oil or just
fat you'd have on meat, but processed fats.
Yeah, too much protein in the diet.
Which also causes inflammation.
I would use what they call macrobiotic diagnosis
on that.
You'd have to look at your face, you'd
have to look at your lower eyelid, your
lower lip, your chin.
Take a pulse in the abdomen, the various
glands, and to see your state.
In other words, whether you're typically constrictive and
forceful internally, or very relaxed and, let's say,
flowing.
If it's relaxed and flowing, then it most
likely is not a yang manifestation, and it's
just a manifestation through the skin alone.
But typically, like for example, in a lot
of the ancient healing arts, people who had
bad skin would go to these healers and
they'd say, what do I do about this
bad skin?
And they're like, are you joking?
That's a blessing.
Because people who have bad skin typically are
manifesting some sort of adverse reaction externally versus
internally in the internal organs.
It's an interesting coincidence.
Also, you could look at people who die
of severe cancers have beautiful skin.
Very interesting.
Yes.
Right.
So people who tend to have bad skin.
I'm not talking about a skin condition.
I'm talking about eruptions, manifestations that come and
go, whether it be called acne or sores
or whatever, that it's actually better to manifest
on the skin than have sores on the
liver.
You're right.
Exactly.
Typically, people who have really bad skin, not
bad skin, but typically because their skin looks
battle-torn because they have multiple manifestations on
it during their lifetime, have pristine internal organs.
Very interesting.
It's very interesting that you brought that up,
though.
So if the diet was the same throughout
the year, so the winter months with the
coldness seems to bring out more of a
manifestation to the hands then?
It could be, but also the hands are
an extremity, right?
So it's furthest away from the core.
But also, even though the diet is the
same, is it?
Is it the same chicken or the same
hamburger?
I'm not saying you eat that.
Or the same bean or the same rice?
No.
The crop changes.
So let's say you were on a veggie
diet and that happens.
What's your source of food?
So someone says, oh, I'm vegetarian.
I eat rice and beans and potatoes all
year round.
Then I'm getting this, right?
Okay, well, it's not the same crop.
Most even organic.
You know, most food that you buy at
the stow is done cooperatively, meaning you have
the label, the big label, and they buy
from lots of different farms.
And then they take samples and then they
batch it all together to get a crop
quality that they want.
Makes sense.
It really does.
Yes.
Thank you for that.
That's where it pays to be a local
vore, to eat locally only, if you can.
If you can.
You know, there's an old photo.
I think I might have seen it on
the Rectangle a while back about eating whole
food.
They had two brothers that were separated at
young childhood.
The photo was about 80 years old or
50 years ago.
One of the brothers lived out in the
country where they were born, and the other
brother, they were separated at five or six,
was raised in a suburban and urban environment.
And then they show a picture where they
met.
And the guy that lived and ate off
the farm had all his teeth.
He had great skin, great hair.
The guy who had lived in the city
looked 10 years older, was missing some teeth.
I'm not saying, you know, he could have
gotten into a fight and lost his teeth.
But still, you could see he was weathered
and worn.
Right.
You know, that's funny you bring that up.
I was talking to my mom a while
back, and she mentioned all the people that
she knew that stayed on the farms and
lived are still living today.
The ones who moved to the cities, no
more.
Most likely, yeah.
It's not because cities are bad.
It's just the way that they're put together.
I think it's bad, meaning not good.
There's a lot of big changes from moving
from the country to the city.
Big, big changes.
You know, diet is definitely inclusive.
Well, there's many levels to it.
You know, the cities for the past century
have been experimental, like guinea pigs.
If you live in a city, you're a
guinea pig to the sovereign state, essentially.
I mean, how many times have you heard
of all the experimentation and all this that's
going on?
So, you can't control people if they're rural.
There are not enough bombs in the world
to get rid of people living in the
country, but if you pack them in a
city, it's easy to control them.
Easy peasy.
Yeah.
Which is, you know, I mentioned the bomb
thing.
You know, they've been scaring people with, you
know, nuclear holocaust, meaning burning up the entire
world and all.
That can't happen.
They don't have enough ordinance to do that.
It can't be done from land-based operations.
No matter how much ordinance you have on
the earth, shooting it to another part of
the earth, you will never...
The most you can do is, like, maybe
1% damage.
The most.
In order to destroy a planet surface, it
has to be done from off-planet.
So, never bother about...
I don't think the people are stupid enough
that listen to this to go fall for
climate global warming and nuclear...
Destroying the whole world with nukes and all
this.
I think they're above and beyond that, but
I just wanted to make that point because
I don't think I've really said it before.
It's not possible to do that.
You know, one scenario...
I was having a discussion with someone at
an auto parts store recently about that.
And the reason why is, let's say America
launches a thousand nukes towards Russia and vice
versa.
The moment one or two nukes start going
off, it renders all the other ones useless,
right?
Yeah.
I mean, people are not too smart.
They just believe whatever they hear because everyone
else does.
Yeah, so anything I haven't looked at the
chat, I just kind of...
Oh, yes.
I have a couple of email things here.
Wes sent a bunch of questions.
This guy Dave sent a bunch of questions.
Lawful money questions I just got today here.
Someone sent a thing that says, Greetings.
I was curious if there's a way to
monitor internal health of the body without the
prankster-style monitoring, like EKG, blood pressure, etc.
My simple answer to that was, maybe living
it is better than monitoring it.
Right.
I was working in the bicycle industry years
ago.
There was a guy who was diagnosed with
testicular cancer, pancreatic cancer, brain cancer.
He was given three months to live.
So he came in and spent five grand
on a bike and all the accessories to
do a cross-country trip.
He figured he'd rather die on the road
on a bike trip than in a hospital.
Comes back six months later.
There's no cancer, nothing.
He lost 40 pounds.
He feels great.
So what is...
Serious.
And he ate hot dogs and hamburgers all
the way there.
Yeah, that's a testimony right there.
I think I brought up on the Ocelli
about how diabetes has nothing to do with
sugar and insulin.
That was a fascinating little drop of info.
Oh yeah.
Although I've never really gotten into that.
I need to write it down or do
a specific sonics on just health.
We talked about food.
But I've got a whole list of approaches
to the causes of all these things that
people talk about in terms of diseases.
I gave the diabetes out because I was
working with someone on that case with success.
It worked.
It says nothing to do with blood sugar.
That's like you get a burn from a
heat lamp and you don't tell the doctor
what it is and he'll just say, Oh,
that's just a rash.
Here's some cream.
They don't know the causes of things.
I think someone posted in there a warning
about 20th century medicine.
These people are horrible people.
You should, by the way, read the writings
of the Rockefeller Center, turn of the century.
Their whole purpose was to enlist people that
were cruel and powerful and whatever because the
law of the jungle and they need to
inflict whatever they feel like on the society.
The stuff is just amazing when you read.
The sick people, the medical people and the
legal people.
For example, you know how they did the
CIA torture years ago with the Bush administration?
You need to torture people.
No, you don't.
Because they have all the telephone conversations recorded.
They already know everything about you.
The reason they're torturing people is because it's
part of their religion.
They just like cruelty stuff.
Just like animal testing, they don't need to
put acid, straight up acid, into a rabbit's
eye or a dog's eye to find out
how bad it is.
These are sick people.
I'm not saying this because I read something
online.
I've actually run into people that worked in,
let's say, testing or something of food products
and makeup.
These people are sick.
They just hurt animals just for the sake
of hurting animals.
They're sick people.
Just like when you run into people in
the military.
I know Vietnam vets and they're like, man,
I'm glad I got out of there.
Those people were sick.
They just wanted to kill people.
It didn't matter.
Even just now, I've read letters sent home
from the Iraq war around the 2003, 2004,
2005 period from colonels, officers.
We're not talking about infantry grunts.
They're saying my own men are killing each
other more than the enemy is, so-called
enemy, and I'm more afraid of them.
You hear a lot of that.
Oh, yeah.
We're talking about the psychiatric society, which is
crazy themselves.
They've declared 28% of the American population
as insane.
I think it's in the 90% range.
The 30% should be locked up or
put on a boat and sunk or whatever
you've got to do, institutionalized.
So in a sense of discussing things in
a sane manner, considering that you're going to
be going out into a neutral environment and
practicing sane, healthful, and productive things is ridiculous.
Because you're surrounded by just crazy people.
You can go into the spiritual side, and
of course they're being oppressed demonically, but eventually
the root cause may not matter in this
case because either way it's best to stay
away from them.
Whether it's just chemical, spiritual, or cultural.
So on one aspect, I think that it's
good to share knowledge, really, about all kinds
of subjects that we've done.
But on the other subject, I think it's
best to do it on a need-to
-know and when it's asked.
If you start putting out too much, you
might actually become a target.
Unfortunately, I don't do YouTube.
The business world, they have a thing where
I know 10 years ago, or a little
bit more than 10 years ago, if you're
a company and you started getting above $150
million a year in earnings through the IRS
monitors and all that, they infiltrate you.
It doesn't matter what you are, even if
you made clothes hangers.
They put someone in there to watch you.
So everything is controlled.
YouTube with 10,000 subscribers, you start saying
stuff, you're a target.
By the idiots.
Because they're afraid of their position.
They're afraid of the people because their position
is very weak.
If I ever speak about any kind of
leadership in a negative way, that's not because
it's negative on its own.
It's because the people want it that way.
It's the masses that are wicked and evil
and corrupt, not the leadership.
And you might say, well, Greek, that doesn't
make sense because it is.
Yes, it is.
But if the masses, let's say, were not
wicked, evil and corrupt, 90% of them,
if not 99%, the current leadership would not
last more than a few days in anything,
whether it's the medical, legal, religious or whatever.
It doesn't matter.
They can't last.
There's no way.
A few days and they'd be gone.
It doesn't matter how big they are.
People talk about the Federal Reserve or the
FBI or the CIA or the Queen or
the Pope.
None of that.
The Pope would last a week if the
people knew what it was about.
Oh, not even.
Not even a week.
A week maybe underground.
Maybe a day on the surface and a
week underground.
They'd still fish around.
Yeah.
It's not them.
People are like, oh, what are we going
to do about this corrupt people?
What are you talking about?
That is a product of the general society
and every society is that way.
You might even have a condition where a
smaller group, like 20%, right, will grab the
power and hold it.
But even then, they have to maintain the
others in ignorance and acquiescence.
The National Socialist Party, what they call the
Nazis in Germany, the most they've ever had,
I think, was 21% of the people
acknowledging their right to rule.
The most they had, right?
And they didn't last, obviously, right?
Right.
They had to leave.
You know, I think I mentioned with Ocelli,
oh, boy, I don't want to say this.
You know, Ocelli, I like him.
I really do.
Yeah.
But it's just like after a while, it's
like, oh, man, okay, I've got to get
off here because it's just I'm losing him
and I'm losing the audience and it's just
the wrong whatever.
But I do appreciate all this stuff.
I think you did a very fine articulated
piece of work, this last one with him.
Very fine.
Yeah.
You know, I don't have anything prescripted, so
I have to think about what I'm going
to say and have a flow.
And then he comes up with things that
are just like, you didn't just say that,
right?
You know, you didn't just say that, did
you?
But you didn't let him bother you and
you just ran through it, which was good.
I ran it a couple of times because
there's got to be someone out there with
a couple of brain cells to get.
But anyway, the whole thing is, you know,
and actually, believe it or not, here's the
thing about Ocelli.
We make a good team, by the way.
It's like Abbot and Costello, who was on
first or whatever, but in some cases better,
in some cases worse.
But in a sense, like some moron listener
said, you know, Jordan Maxwell said about the
Nazis and the Nazis.
Anybody makes a reference like that?
There is no such thing as a Nazi.
That is a pejorative term written that was
created by a journalist named Haydn.
I think it was Haydn.
I'm not in front of a computer.
Look it up, H-E-I-D-E
-N.
He was a journalist, and he was a
harsh critic of them in the 30s, and
he called them Nazis as a pejorative.
Right.
When that was brought up, I was like,
give me here the niggers.
Well, the niggers are a tribe, N-I
-G-A-R, in the Netherlands.
Right?
Right.
So is that a valid term?
Yeah, as a tribe.
But if you say nigger regarding black people,
that's not a valid term.
So why are you using Nazis?
Right.
That's the same thing.
It's like saying gooks, bick, nigger, kike, whatever.
Why are you?
And the academic community is using it.
It just shows you how stupid people are.
Look it up.
The term...
Hold on.
Let's see if I can get it up.
Who invented the term Nazi?
I think it was Haydn.
He was a journalist.
Nazi invented...
See, it even tells you, even in Wikipedia,
that it was a derogatory term.
Yeah, Haydn.
Conrad Haydn.
K-O-N-R-A-D-T-I
-D is the one who invented it.
A little mealy-mouthed whatever guy.
Here, there's a little thing here.
It says, meet the Jew who created the
word Nazi.
The term Nazi along with Nazism is a
political epithet invented by Conrad Haydn during the
1920s.
Okay.
The means of denigrating Hitler.
The term Nazi is a variation of a
nickname used to reference...
Okay.
So anyway, it's just like, you know, it
doesn't make any...
I mean, just the path of humanity is
absurd.
So, you know, you should look like you're
going with the rest because they're dangerous, you
know.
You ever watch a good spy movie and,
you know, he has to create a distraction
to get out because they're on him, right?
Mm-hmm.
And then when he gets into the crowd,
he kind of acts like everybody else.
Right, right.
You know, it's just, yeah, this is the
real reality.
So, yeah, there's a couple of ways to
approach any subject, but unfortunately this is not
the society to do it in a way
where it's exceptionally truthful or outgoing.
Outgoing in a good way.
If you're going to be outgoing, you better
look like everyone else.
So, and I'll go through a bunch of
other questions here, I think.
There was a fellow asking about families being
broken up.
Of course.
You mentioned that before, and he was wondering
if that was found in the Bible, that
particular...
The Bible, yes, it is, actually.
Father against son, mother against daughter-in-law,
brother against brother, and children will rule over
you.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
I've talked about something called a mindset, right?
Mm-hmm.
It's part of the operating system and part
of the program, not the information.
You have so many people being fed information,
whether they remember it or not or have
access to it, they can't discern it.
So when you discern Scripture, basically what you
get out of the whole thing is there's
a time limit to why things are going
on, and it tells you what's going on
and how it's going on, and not a
lot of the why.
Very often the why is a very general
statement, because they're unlawful, because they're greedy, because
they mistreat widows and orphans, and you get
all that.
But if you put it all together, you
basically see that the historicity of Scripture shows
you that humans are divided and ruled by
patron and matron deities.
The chief creator takes on one country as
an example, right?
And then when this example is set, you
see that there's a recurring theme of the
people chasing after other gods, which means other
laws, other culture, other...
And now, okay, what's wrong with that?
Well, what's wrong with it is the nature
of it is wicked and evil.
It's based on human sacrifice, child sacrifice, lying,
stealing, this, that, and the other.
Now, if you look at, for example, from
a corporate sense, whether it's a business or
a family, meaning the bodies coming together, one
of the promises that are given, general and
specifically, that these corporations, meaning the family, you
know, corporeal, meaning people coming together, or nations,
or groups, or religions, are going to be
broken up because they're basically practicing demonology.
Makes sense.
So, if you can look, when is it
important for families, you hear about them traveling
and coming together cross-country all over during
the holidays, and the holidays are 100%
demonic, right?
Right.
So you're not going to stop, you're going
to keep doing that?
Well, okay, so if we break up the
family, now you can't come together because there's
no family to come together to.
Right.
Right?
Yep, makes sense.
You know, like they want to take away
the guns, I'm like, well, just take away
the ammunition.
Right.
It's like, take away the cars.
No, don't take away the cars, take away
the fuel.
Right?
Yep.
So, you want to get rid of people,
take away the food.
Done.
And the water.
Don't go after the people.
You want to kill a monster, don't go
try to kill the monster, especially when it
has impervious defenses.
You just go after its food source.
The source of what makes it go.
So what's making families go?
There are these wicked holidays, so they're not
going to stop.
So, okay, it has to stop.
So if they're not going to stop, then
we have to get rid of the family,
you see.
This is not direct in scripture, but it's
part of the scriptural mindset.
It's very simple, like, you know, where does
it say in the Bible that anybody who's
got tattoos is going to be killed?
Well, it doesn't say that exactly, but if
you understand the premise of the law and
when it becomes severe, what happens?
Right.
Right?
It's very obvious.
Only one outcome.
You do understand that the current world powers
in the future will use biblical law as
an international law.
So if the entire earth is under a
misused and overly applied law form, when the
law form calls for exile, where do you
exile them to?
Right.
Nope.
Six feet under, or in a furnace, or
whatever, in the ocean.
So, there's a mindset that most people lack
in anything, any subject.
You want to look at the legal community,
they don't know any law.
The medical people don't know any medicine.
I've had many conversations, for example, with doctors
of senior level, and instead of discussing and
being inquisitive about the actual conversation we're having
about biological vacuum and many other things, they
just constantly refer to their training and education.
I'm like, leave that aside for now.
Let's just have a free conversation.
And if I bring that subject up, they'll
say, well, they taught us this.
We always do this.
It's like, okay, I know.
Just stop for a moment.
And we're not talking about young students.
We're talking about people in their 50s, 60s
that are still practicing medicine.
Wow.
They can't handle it, because what does that
tell you?
It tells you that they're relying on their
training.
Yeah, they all are that way.
And the ones that aren't have left the
industry.
Yeah.
It's really sad.
Yeah, once they've got that nudge in them,
you can't shake it from them.
No, or when they figure it out, they
leave.
They can't stay in the conversations that way.
That's why I want to make a statement.
The Supreme Court justices don't know any law.
They don't.
Because if they did and tried to use
it, they'd die in a car accident or
suicide or whatever.
Or they'd have to quit.
All the district attorneys, all the people, they
don't know any law.
Because the moment they do and they try
to apply it, they're out of there.
All of them.
There is no exception to that.
That is a hard fact and truth.
Same with the medical doctors.
The moment they figure out how the body
works and they try to use it, they're
out of there.
Not a one is in there that does
that.
Not a one.
You can't.
Not only is the system set up to
do that covertly, but their own colleagues are
trained to do that covertly.
And overtly.
The same with the police, the Leos.
None of them know any law, law enforcement.
None.
The moment they do, they're out of there.
Two weeks or six months, they're done.
They're finished.
Done.
It sounds like Greek, that sounds extreme.
Yeah, I know, it is extreme.
That's the truth.
This is the same with all your subjects.
None of the priests, none of the ministers,
none of the pastors, none of the whatever,
know the Bible.
The Scripture.
None of them.
And the moment they do, they quit, or
they have to be out of there.
None of them do.
It's very simple.
That's not a general statement.
That's a very specific, that's like gravity.
You know, or air.
Here's a question.
Is there anything you can discuss regarding self
-defense against an immediate threat of another human
being?
Well, that's an oxymoron, because most human beings
are an immediate threat.
But, yeah, Bruce Lee was asked that, he
says, run.
Distance is the best, right?
Self-defense is an interesting thing, because if
you're moving, you don't have to defend yourself.
Defense means, it's like when I hear about
defense, like you're cornered, and you can't go
anywhere.
That's a whole different subject.
Then you need to defend yourself.
Right.
There's very little defense, by the way.
It's always offense.
That term is in competition and defense.
Those things are completely misunderstood.
There is no such thing.
Even on the playing field, when I say
we're playing defensive, they're not.
Because it's a psych-out.
In other words, if someone, if you know,
let's say you have two opponents, whether it's
sports or military or just individuals or whatever.
When someone puts up such a strong defense,
the other person doesn't become offensive, because they
view the defense as being so great to
their offense, that it's futile.
So it's the same as them being offensive.
Right?
And usually a defense requires firing back or
blocking or disabling in some capacity.
So there is no self-defense.
So movement, separation, distance.
Okay.
Are there also subtle preventative measures to consider
regarding one's vibe when willingly giving off to
other people via communication, eye contact, posture, pace,
that affect the chance of one being targeted
as an insidious onlooker in the first place?
Yes.
Because you're there.
If they can perceive you, it's not good.
You should walk like a shadow unless you
want to make yourself known.
Don't peacock around.
We can get into this a lot in
discussion in terms of vibe.
Like how many times have you, anyone rhetorically,
gone traveling and you stop at a motel
or a hotel, they give you a perfectly
clean room, and you're like, no, I don't
like this room.
I'm not sure what's wrong with it.
I'd like another one.
Or you walk into a conference room that's
clean and empty, and you're like, this doesn't
feel good.
Well, maybe if you find out what had
just happened in that room, like just two
people arguing that left, they leave a vibe,
a lingering vibe like that.
Right?
So that's the subtle stuff.
If anyone wants to do more research on
like Emoto, you know, where you, Misoro Emoto,
the water, where he cursed one glass of
water and blessed the other with rice and
various things, and the one that was cursed
was, you know, okay.
If anyone wants to do more of an
objective outlook on that, because, you know, he
had to sell it to the new age,
and he was kind of new age himself.
But if you want to figure out how
the vibe works and all that.
His experiments did speak wealths of information.
But, unfortunately, he handled it a little cockeyed.
See, when I hear people saying love and
hate, they don't even know what that means.
So even though the outcome is positive when
they say love, and the other thing is
hate, and the negative outcome, that's still just
description-based.
It doesn't help anyone.
Right.
In terms of furthering it forward.
They can just do these little petty experiments.
They say, see, it works here, too.
Yeah, but they don't know why.
How do you develop that?
Because they don't know what love or hate
is.
And why that change in that structure, given
those things?
I mean, are we influencing, or is it
just a natural phenomenon within the water?
Yes, well, it's more than natural.
It's esoterically natural.
That's why when I say love, most people
feel they can't define it, but they like
it.
Because it's the esoteric emotion, meaning you can't
explain it.
It's measurable.
It's an esoteric thing, too, you know.
Right, it's an esoteric.
Another thing is to take it out of
the esoteric and make it practical.
Like a touchscreen 40 years ago was esoteric
technology.
Now all the rectangles have them, and it's
normal.
If you took it away, what happened to
this normalcy, right?
So in other words, when I say taking
it from an esoteric point and making it
practical, no one's doing that.
They're stuck.
They're censored.
Because that's very important to understand.
The censorship limits man's development until it's time
to develop.
And you can't do it on your own.
Like if a 10-year-old wanted to,
let's say, get in a car or whatever,
it can be done.
It's best done with an adult around.
I wouldn't just give them the keys and
say go, right?
Right.
So, I mean, we've done that.
By the way, I was maybe seven or
eight and a whole bunch of us at
a gathering, and there was a bunch of
Cadillacs and Jaguars outside with the keys in
the ignition.
And all the adults are by the pool
party, and we're like, hey, let's grab a
car for a joyride.
And it was scary because you couldn't really
barely see over the dash.
Barely.
I mean, especially those older cars with the
bench seats.
You sunk in, and you're like, oh, shit,
I can hardly see, but I can fly.
I could fly this thing, you know, like
a boat.
It was like driving a ship, you know?
Yeah.
You know how when you're on the bridge
of a ship, it has a very narrow
window?
Big old boat.
Yeah.
So, I mean, you can do it.
It's not I don't recommend it.
So that's the thing.
People just won't have it until the time.
This is like stuff for the next society.
Again, because if you did substantiate why saying
love into one thing makes it helpful and
hate in the other degrades it, when that
becomes more practically based and explained, obviously it's
going to be used negatively against people.
It's going to be weaponized against.
But I think there are people that know
about that, but they're limited also.
I think the weaponization and the stuff that
is available to those that do know and
the owners of all the nations or whatever,
they have a tremendous amount, not of it
necessarily being new, but of most of it
being things that you've heard in legend, you
know, like even like the Vamanas that you've
heard of.
You know, there's evidence of the Vamanas as
recent as 800 years ago, which are the
flying, you know, craft that were around, and
there's evidence of them 2,000 years ago.
So, you know.
That's interesting, yeah.
Yeah, so.
Oh, there was an interesting thing you dropped
in the channel about Tatara.
Tatara, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The mud flood.
That's kind of a dummy load, that's like
flat earth.
Okay.
Yeah, that's like flat earth, but the thing
is, the part about flat earth or mud
flood or all these other things, that what
I do enjoy about that, right, is that
basically, except that everything you've been told is
a lie, and then we have to revisit
it, right?
Right.
I found it interesting with the pictures with
all the absence of people.
That was kind of eerie in itself.
Yeah, but I've seen that in Manhattan, living
in Manhattan years ago also.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, on a Sunday, what they call in
the Pope's work schedule, Sunday morning anywhere in
Manhattan, it's going to be pretty much no
one around.
You can go online right now and look
at Manhattan empty streets, and there's tons of
photos, any major city.
I mean, I like to, like when the
pagans have their holidays, I like going out
in the morning and traveling through town.
It's like a ghost town.
Yeah, yeah.
That's pretty simple to do.
Yeah.
But again, what I do like about that
and the flat earthers and whatever is that
instead of presuming that we are informed, they
presume that everything is a lie, which it
is, but they don't have the tools or
the discernment or the mindset to see through
it quickly and come to a more holistic
conclusion that can help anyone.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, they lack that, but that's fine.
When I see flat earthers and mudflat and
all that other stuff, it reminds me of,
what's the book written about where the children
are shipwrecked on an island?
Lord of the Flies.
Right.
Yeah, so here you have a bunch of
five-year-olds to 11-year-olds that
could start a society, you know, and they
can't.
They'll just end up being the worst, representing
the worst of.
So in essence, part of the flat earthers
and mudflat and all this other stuff and
a lot of the JFK read 9-11,
in one essence, researchers, represents the worst possible
alternative thinking, right?
Okay.
Because they just jump to conclusions, and if
you don't believe this, you're a government agent
or you're screwed up or whatever, you're a
shrill or whatever.
Yeah, so they're pretty  it's like Lord
of the Flies.
They're too immature.
Yeah.
As a general rule, there might be some
exceptions, like Dmitry Kalazov is one exception that
I can name.
And then there's others that have done good
work, but they can't get out of their
own way, you know, and then you just
got to  that's where you pick the
corn out of the edible poo, and after
a while, you're like, you don't want any
poo at all, so then you got to
leave that also.
Yeah.
Research.
Let's see.
Greetings.
If there is a sonic tonight, I wondered
if the Greek would expound on what's going
on with the vacuum when hiccups occur.
Diet appears to be a cause and a
solution, but wanted to inquire for the sake
of better understanding the vacuum.
As always, thank you.
Yeah, the hiccups are electrical, just like digestion
is electrical.
So remind me about the hiccups.
Another question here.
I just want to finish this particular email.
Okay, go ahead.
Is stigmata just another example of demonic entity
screwing with humans?
Nothing I'll see here.
Or dummy load both?
Yes.
If people could see what's around them.
Right now, anyone listening, if you had the
spiritual vision, you might see anywhere between 5
,000 to 5,000 demons around you.
I mean, that's how populated they are with
humanity.
There's trillions of them on the planet right
now, especially after what they call 1998.
They're unleashed on the world, right?
What are thoughts and what is thinking?
How are they different?
How important is to know the difference?
I haven't really gone into this much.
I brought up the concept of external input.
You know, there's really nothing inside of you.
Even scripture, you know, the kingdom of God
is near you.
It doesn't say it's in you.
There is no God in you.
That would be like a nightmare for a
God to be inside of a human.
You know, only demons do that to an
occasion.
So everything is external, by the way.
So thinking is very simple.
And thoughts are one thing and thinking another.
A thought that comes in or occurs is
like you go online and you download something.
That's the thought.
The thinking is when you start working on
the monitor or on the computer what you've
downloaded.
It's executed.
So, yeah, the thinking is on the hard
drive.
Like, one is, you know, and the thought
would be RAM.
You know how thoughts escape people?
I change the thought.
Okay, the thought is the RAM on a
computer, random access memory.
And the thinking would be what's on the
ROM, what's on the hard drive.
Or chewing the cud.
You know, thinking would be walking the aisles
at a supermarket, let's say, or a store.
And, I mean, thoughts would be walking the
aisles in a supermarket or a grocery store
and thinking would be in your pantry.
Okay, right.
Thoughts are optional.
And the thoughts are external and the thinking
is the processing internally, which is still not
really internal.
It's just that you're on your cloud server
that's dedicated to you.
And I have many thoughts on that.
Like, the beings that operate the cloud server
that you interpret as thinking have to be
neutral.
They're not benevolent or malevolent.
They have to be neutral because if they
were all, you know, by order having to
work only for the benevolent, then they would
filter out and prevent bad thoughts and evil.
So they're neutral.
They're like in a total neutral zone.
But I don't have a handle on that.
Greek prove that.
I don't, but there's a pretty good thesis
that can be written up about it once
you understand external input.
But I constantly tell people, all the scientists,
they know a lot about the brain, but
they know nothing about the mind or the
spirit.
Right.
So that, you know, even though I say
it's internal, it's not internal.
It's just like having, if you had an
external server somewhere that you were accessing, you
still have the random surfing and then you
have the stuff that's downloaded on the server
to work.
Sure.
Right?
I think Max Tom Browser is all external
now.
Whenever you bookmark something, it's not really on
your computer.
Right.
Unless you dupe it somehow.
So the question about hiccups.
If you ask any gastrointestinologist, pathologist or whatever,
any people that work with internal organs, they'll
tell you it's all electrical impulses to keep
them going.
I mean, the hiccup almost feels like an
electrical impulse, doesn't it?
Think about it.
Yeah.
Huh.
So it's like a short circuit of some
sort then.
Yeah.
They say drink water.
It's not really the water that does it.
There's a technique where you drink the water
from the opposite side of the glass or
something that someone does that always works with
hiccups.
I'm serious.
You drink it from the opposite forward leading
edge.
Usually when you drink from a cup, it's
the trailing edge.
You tilt it towards yourself.
But this time you try to drink from
the opposite side of the glass.
It's very awkward.
And what that does is it starts firing
up nerves and muscles in a way which
are also electrically not used to.
It creates this ball of extra static electricity
in the body and it shorts out the
hiccup.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
Some people have hiccups and they can't get
rid of them.
It could be life threatening, very rare, but
it can be.
Oh, yeah.
I would go for an electrolyte, salt water
or something.
Yeah.
Or literally if you are set up for
bioelectric medicine, do some of that, which is
sitting in a chair, barefoot, copper plate on
the left foot.
Are you familiar with certain setups where you
have the copper plates on your feet?
You're talking bimetal here of some form?
Yeah, it could be bimetal where you have
a galvanized pipe of iron on the right
hand connected to a copper on the left
foot.
And vice versa.
Yeah, I mean, again, that's a whole other
sonic.
I mean, that could be, you know, it's
like, why bother, you know?
I mean, any of these subjects, I could
stand up in front of an audience and
speak for eight hours on them without repeating
myself once.
But it's like, you know, and I look
around and I'm like, this world, nah, not
this planet.
So I think the only way it would
be done is for other people to come
around and, you know, writers and just put
it together and sell it.
It should be sold.
It shouldn't be just given.
It should be given freely, but not in
the sense that people consider it.
It needs to be part of, let's say,
an agenda that goes to those that work
in the field, not just, you know, the
common person.
Oh, that's going to be a good thing.
Because it's ultra premium stuff.
But on the other hand, you know, the
best things in life are free.
And, you know, that's why we do these
sonics.
I mean, here's the thing.
When I give out the thing about what
diabetes is or the hiccups, I mean, that's
like more than a major hint or a
clue.
It's actually a statement that anyone who's interested
can take that and build on it.
That's like you want to build a house
and here comes like five cement trucks and
they pour all this concrete.
Well, you got your foundation done.
All the heavy work is done.
So if I come out and speak for
30 seconds on something, you've got 90 percent
of all your foundation to go.
Go.
Fly.
Go, birdie.
You go.
You're ready.
There's no need for me to do a
one-hour explanation on it.
You've gotten a thousand times more than anyone
ever gave me, I should say.
So go for it.
That's all you need.
Actually, because when you give a lot to
someone, they get lazy and complacent and then
they want more.
Then they're pencil pushers, you know.
They're not getting any dirt under their fingernails.
And it's not for this society anyway.
Let's say someone wanted to back this up
and put a million bucks behind how the
body really works.
You'll all be dead in six months if
you push it through all the channels.
If you push it too far.
Yeah, yeah.
It'll be shorter than what I'm thinking.
Is that where you want to go?
Yeah.
Those accidents on trees are just that.
Speaking of dead, I wonder why they've probably
been meditating a little bit on the news.
There's some Navy moron, the Admiral, that they
say committed suicide.
Do you know how rare it is for
that to be in the publicity?
Yeah.
For the Navy Admiral to commit suicide in
Bayron?
Now, if you need to translate that into
plain language, what they're really saying, well, there's
no information on how the suicide took place.
So it could be two or three bullet
holes in the head, right?
Right.
The other thing is, if it was a
suicide, and they always call it apparent, what
they're telling you, okay, let's say it was
a bona fide suicide.
What they're telling you is a degradation to
the Navy, because in this culture, when you
say suicide, it usually refers to a coward.
Couldn't handle it.
He broke, killed himself.
So what they're telling you is the Navy
is run by cowards, or that branch of
the military are cowards, worthless.
Right?
Now, on the other hand...
That's a slap.
Oh, yeah, big time.
Because cowards only...
By the way, there's nothing against suicide in
any of the ancient texts.
Right?
It's just people, the religions frown on it,
but none of the...
It's not unlawful to do that, by the
way.
Checking out.
Right?
The religions tell you not to do it
because they want to keep you around because
you're a pretty good slave.
But there's nothing in scripture about it, there's
nothing in any ancient text, or holy writ,
that says you shouldn't commit suicide, by the
way.
So don't be confused with the demonic religion
stuff.
You forgot to mention prophet.
Yeah, prophet as in F-I-T.
Right.
So, in essence, they're telling you that this
guy is a coward, his Navy is run
by cowards, they're worthless.
Right?
Or they're degrading it.
Okay.
On the other hand, if it was a
suicide...
But on the other hand, if he was
taken out, that also doesn't look good, because
why did they take him out that way?
Why couldn't they get him to step down
and retire?
Well, there's two ways.
You know, taken out meaning three bullet holes
in his skull.
He shot himself in the mouth with a
shotgun after he crushed his skull.
Right?
That kind of stuff.
Right.
Right?
Or he jumped out of a window, or
he was locked in a duffel bag with
three holes in his head that was zipped
up.
That kind of stuff.
If it was like that, which I think
most likely it is, is because...
Remember how I said that all the people
in power are blackmailed, right?
Right.
All of them.
They're not going to let anyone in more
than a few months...
That is not.
I need some leverage.
He probably...
The other thing is he probably figure...
I says, you know what?
Screw this blackmail stuff.
So what if they got a photo of
me with a penis in my mouth?
Right.
Or screwing a young boy or whatever.
I don't care about that.
I'm just going to tell people that's how
it works, and I'm going to go out
and give them this, tell them what's going
on.
And they got rid of him that way.
Yeah.
So...
And they're all like that.
And it's so stupid.
It's funny when people that like TRUMP and
other people that don't...
And it's just funny to watch them.
And I'm thinking what photographs do they have
of this guy?
Is he humping a donkey?
Is he humping a boy?
Is he filleting a black man?
I mean, what's going on?
How is this guy up?
You know, there's none of them are there.
None.
Zero.
Without being compromised.
So when they're taken out...
The same with Kennedy, by the way.
Kennedy was compromised.
All of them are.
It goes all the way back before, you
know, up to the Civil War, by the
way.
Lincoln was also.
So anyway, Micka...
And actually, what I'm saying Lincoln was compromised
is not a secret, by the way.
He was a whoremonger and many other things,
and they did have cameras in those days,
and testimony was more important than photographs.
But the interesting part is that if he
broke out of the deal, which is, you
know, we've got the dirt on you, ultimately,
one needs to consider that's in a position
that is compromised, that blackmail means nothing, because
when you break out of it, they're just
going to kill you anyway.
Because they don't want you to say, well,
I'm repenting.
So in essence, it's a really bad...
So when you go into power, like in
any, you know, medical, legal, military, political, you're
screwed.
You have no way out.
And the blackmail is not what keeps you
in control, because if you repent from that
act, and even though it is subversive to
your character, when it's brought out, you say,
well, that's okay, but I'm also bringing this
out.
You're going to be killed anyway.
So you see...
Do you see?
I hope I did a pretty good...
You did.
I think I gave a pretty good translation
of this whole story.
So you're either...
It shows you they've got you in lockdown,
there's a problem with the Navy, and the
people have to know it back in their
minds, or the guy's a total coward and
the Navy sucks.
That's what they're putting out in front of
you.
It's all controlled, by the way.
There are people being taken out in many
positions on a daily basis, you know, people
in power, in the military, legal, medical, political,
and you don't hear about it, though.
Right.
Ever.
But why would they put...
Remember, everything that you hear publicly, especially on
the Internet like that, it's a show.
It's like they're trying to create some kind
of...
There's no...
It's so controlled right now, it's like a
B-movie.
Right?
Worse.
Yeah, I mean, that's why...
I mean, I'll never do a YouTube channel,
never do any of that stuff, because it's
just rubbish.
It's just like you dirty yourself to go
there, you know?
Actually, I found this years ago with YouTube,
I was speaking to someone, I was at
a cafe, this was back in six, seven
years ago, maybe more, and he was talking
about all this stuff he's...
Anyway, I don't want to give this a
whole other subject, but it turns out he
was working for YouTube and Google.
I was like, that sounds bizarre, you know?
You know, it's like real bizarre shit going
on there, you know?
Yeah, in other words, not a smart individual,
but an individual that was not in the
best interest of what people think is how
it's presented.
And I wish I would have spent a
little more inquiry, but at the time I
was like, no, I would never do any
of that stuff, you know?
So I didn't really care, I kind of
pushed it to the side.
Sure.
But I was like, oof, this is a
really bad organization.
A proof of it is there's a couple
of YouTube videos, ironically, of the CEO of
YouTube, this bizarre woman, you know, like a
pre-menopausal, she's like in her 50s or
60s or whatever, real nutcase, feminist.
I'm not saying, you know, feminism or masculinity,
you know what I mean, like the radical
idiot type.
Right.
Right, bizarre.
It's like, oof, and this is the norm.
All of your leadership is like that right
now, because the gods have a sense of
humor.
So basically when you put a bizarre group
of people to lead in any field, the
other people, those that can see that are
like, oof, we're really screwed.
Any hope and optimism around this just wipes,
you know, not in the way that people
think what hope and optimism is, is ever
manifest with what you have in place.
That's why it's got to go.
That's why when you listen to a Greek
sonic event, you know, an optimistic must happen
is the cleanup.
So you can't fix it.
You know, most people still anticipate, well, give
it enough time, it'll correct.
No, it won't.
It'll just get worse and worse and worse.
You know, I've watched like entropy setting, like
if you have a car or a house
or anything that you don't maintain, it just
keeps falling apart.
You're not going to pull up one day
and all of a sudden everything's fixed.
Right.
So the level of entropy that's kicked in
and everything humans do is at a maximum
point that it could still sustain some cohesion.
And tomorrow, that's why, I mean, today's a
little worse than yesterday, but not as bad
as it's going to be tomorrow in a
very small increment and continual.
That's not a bad thing.
It's a bad thing if everything was purely
random and up to chance, but there are
higher forces controlling it and it has to
be this way.
So you just have to know where you
are.
Yeah.
Yeah, you have to know where you are
in that timeline because you just have to
be patient.
And, you know, like I said, you'll probably
run out of life before you run out
of patience.
Right.
Like if you knew, for example, you know,
the end was going to come in 500
years, well, no matter how patient you are,
you're not going to see it.
Right.
So you'll probably run out of life.
But, you know, the benefit of being around
now is you'll probably see the end before
you run out of life.
And, of course, the gods have a sense
of irony.
It's always the opposite.
When you look at, for example, the Christ,
he came at the worst possible time, quote,
unquote, of Israel.
Right.
Actually worse than when they were during the
time of judges because at the time of
judges, you know, they were basically able to
revolt and rebel.
You can read about it.
You know, he says, well, go to this
guy, you know, and stab him in the
heart and I'll support you.
You know, Yahweh said to the prophets, right?
And they did that.
But he didn't say, go stab the Caesar
in the heart and I'll support you.
Did he?
No.
Came at the worst possible time.
You know, the Christ also came at a
time in Scripture where historically, if you understand
history, there were many Christs running around, so
-called Christ, people calling themselves the saviors of
Israel.
Like, I'm going to bust us out of
this Roman occupation and I won't let, you
know, the Easterners get us either, you know.
Kind of like a Christian.
And restore Israel.
Yeah, yeah.
It was a big deal.
You can read about it in the New
Testament where, you know, Nicodemus was pleading with
the council to let him go.
Don't we have a lot of these guys
saying and doing what this guy does or
saying what this guy says, you know.
I mean, when they just chase him away,
they run to the mountains, they don't come
back.
It was very common, you know.
So, he came at the worst time.
So, the end is going to come at
the best time, if I were to sum
it up.
The end of man's society, meaning every culture,
is going to come when they're at their
best, having their best time.
Which is, you know, world government, world currency,
harmony, peace.
It's kind of hard to fathom if you're
uninformed.
But if you study and are informed, and
you know timekeeping, and you know prophecy, and
you know the law, and you know what's
written in scripture, and all other cultures as
well, they're rich.
It's as clear as anything.
It's razor sharp.
Well, sans the cosmic censorship.
Correct.
If you're censored, then you'll never see it,
and it's best to just go watch Netflix
or something.
Which I've been doing also, you know, just
to escape.
And there's not much on there.
I find myself watching the same movies once
in a while, over and over.
Just to, whatever.
Or go through a couple old sets.
Yeah, it's vegetation.
It is.
In my case, I want life and patience
to run out.
You know, it's just like, yeah, waiting around.
There's nothing you can do.
My list of things to do never seems
to grow short, so I'm always keeping busy.
Of course.
And if you don't, entropy sets in, or
someone nagging you about it.
But here's the interesting part.
What there is to do, there is something
to do.
And I'll take it back, waiting for patience
and life to run out.
That too.
But what is precedent over that is very
simple.
When there's nothing left to do, you have
to give warning.
Imagine a ship going down.
You can't plug up the hull.
The best you can do, other than running
and saving yourself, is yelling out and letting,
knocking on the door as you're running down
the hull, all the cabins and people, get
up, the ship is sinking, right?
Why run down the hull towards the stairs
for the upper deck silently?
Right?
You should be running down the hull towards
the stairs for the upper decks, shouting, the
ship is going down, the ship is going
down.
That's all there's left to do, right?
You're going to still get, but then maybe,
the ship is not a good analogy here,
because now if you excite more people, your
chances of getting a lifeboat or a vest
are diminishing.
Right.
Right?
But this is not that type of thing,
because there's an infinite amount of lifeboats, and
actually everyone's going to get a life vest.
You know, it's interesting, I was listening to,
I was mentioning to someone, the best thing
that came out of church were black gospel
singers, and then they become background singers for
bands.
And it was a whole genre.
If you look at the entire folk movement,
it all came out of the churches.
That was the best thing that ever happened.
But I was listening to some of the
songs that the gospels, and Christianity has mind
-fucked them so bad, they think when they
die they go to the pearly gates of
heaven.
Right.
You notice how the Christians completely bypassed the
resurrection?
Completely.
They think when you die you go to
heaven or hell or whatever.
Instantaneous gratification.
Yeah, they completely bypassed a little detail known
as the resurrection.
Because everything else they've done has bypassed anything
true.
So, anyway, yeah.
If you run into a Christian and say,
so you guys bypassed the whole purpose of
the Christ, which is the resurrection.
That's all you've got to say.
They have no comment.
They're idiots.
So you were at the gospel music.
Myself?
No, you were talking about the gospel music.
Oh, the gospel music is the best thing
they can add to the circus, the church.
Right.
The black gospel singers.
You know, a lot of white singers try
to sound black too.
Talking about the 60s and 70s, like Joe
Cocker, Rolling Stone.
Right.
There's a lot of wannabe in that kind
of thing.
A lot of white people trying to incarnate
themselves.
But hold on.
The black gospel is very specific because you
don't get it in the African continent.
And you don't have it in other parts
of the world.
You only have it in the American South.
So it's the particular tribes that were brought
over here that had that in their culture.
Western North and Western African people.
And by the way, when you talk about
slavery, one thing you have to remember.
Always, people are enslaved by two ways.
One is by conquest or volunteered by your
own people.
So typically slavery is you conquer a people
and you enslave the remaining population.
Or your own people sell you off.
Your own people sell you off.
Right.
That's why, for example, I was having a
short discussion about this.
Well, Greek, how come they took informant off
the birth certificate now?
Like the mother being an informant.
Right.
Because they've been doing that for four generations
now.
They don't need to presume you're a slave.
They know you're a slave because they have
four generations of slaves now.
Right.
So of course the woman having a child
is going to be a slave.
They don't have to do it anymore.
So you're going to see, if you're paying
attention to the legal demonology, they're changing their
paperwork in the past 20 years, most likely
five years the most.
So in that point of view, they would
have had to change the premise for that
earlier.
Right.
To smuggle that in.
Well, in other words, the earlier paperwork, 20
years and beyond, they had to always capture
you on paper, get you to like the
same paperwork you fill out when you donate
a couch to Goodwill.
Right.
Right?
Now they don't have to have you say
that you're giving this or pledging this for
the good of the state or the mother
is an informant, meaning the child is a
product of a criminal act.
They don't have to do that anymore because
your parents were enslaved, their parents were enslaved,
and their parents were enslaved.
So they don't have to produce the presumption
anymore.
A preponderance of evidence.
Yeah, because you're all enslaved now for so
many years.
Of course we don't have to give him
unconscionable contracts to state that he's giving away
all of it.
Because he can't.
He has none.
Because his parents and his parents and their
parents and their parents were enslaved.
So of course he's a slave.
There is no other way.
That's why the paperwork is changing.
So anyway, it's very simple.
Lots of ways to cross-reference that, I
would think.
Yes, and if you don't have the mindset,
and if you don't have the mindset, you're
going to start knocking on doors and asking
why do they take informant off, and you're
not going to find an answer because the
people you're asking don't know either.
It's very, very simple.
Three or four generations.
Has it or has it not been three
or four generations since the Federal Reserve started
telling the governments to monetize, you know, IMF
monetize your own people?
Of course it has.
Been three or four generations.
Easily.
And I don't mean in a strict biblical
sense where each one is a separate 40
years.
I'm talking about having three or four generations
living under one roof, like children, parents, grandparents.
See, that's what I mean by that.
Of course the grandma who was enslaved and
doesn't know it, her children are slaves.
They didn't really know it, but now the
children of those, they don't have to ask
anymore.
If the grandparents are slaves and the parents
are slaves, you don't have to ask if
the children have been enslaved.
But if you just brought this on to
society, yes, you have to maintain the presumption
constantly.
And you cannot live in a country that
has that system as a non-slave by
preponderance of they can just tell you, we
own everything, even the air, up to 100
feet up, so you have to leave.
They can do that.
So I like that because Dimitri says that
on some of his videos, you know, like
what if Trump does this or what if
this guy does this?
It's okay, we'll just kill him.
He's our property.
He's a rebelling.
We have every right to do that.
That's the thing I even told Ocelli in
private.
When they killed Kennedy, they had every right
to do that.
Whoever did it, you see?
Martin Luther King, all these assassinations, they have
every right to do that because those people
are beyond preponderance of a doubt registered with
the state legally as property.
Why?
You throw Kennedy's rocking chair in the fire,
no one complains, but you shoot Kennedy in
the head, you complain?
What's the difference?
Legally, it's the same exact thing to them
because it's just property.
Actually, the man has more production value because
the chair is inanimate.
But all that aside, ultimately, common denominators are
both property to be disposed of at will
of the owner, period.
That's why many times I've said all the
stuff, the worst stuff you've ever read on
the internet, the reality is even worse than
that, much worse than that.
That's why it's best to know.
That's why I think the best credo is,
you know what?
Why bother?
You're going to know more than you think
you should know, so you can lay in
bed before you go to sleep at night
and all of a sudden the whole room
starts spinning?
It's best that you don't.
Be hopeful, but unfortunately, what most people can
put their hope in is false.
It is a very, very bad situation.
So, you go back to food, clothing, shelter.
Are you comfortable?
Were you comfortable yesterday?
Are you comfortable today?
Do you think you might be comfortable tomorrow?
Beyond that, it's foolishness.
Okay, I don't see much else.
I think we're just going to wrap it
up unless you've got something else.
No, I'm all out on this end too,
yes.
Let the madness accelerate.
I think that's a given.
All right, so we'll see you again next
week.
Thanks, man.
Okay, you take care now.
Thank you very much.
Bye, everyone.
Bye.
Good night now.