And greetings folks, we're live with the Greek
and how are you doing tonight here Greek?
Okay, greetings.
Yeah, we're approaching the 10th month roughly.
Yes, we so Yeah, yeah, I think we
were having conversations.
It was around the first month.
So Yeah, which was around springtime.
So I don't know what's going on.
Anybody got anything to just went into the
chat I think I was in the chat
yesterday and very early this morning.
Yeah, I see You're up with I don't
know I Guess everyone's pretty much mastered everything
and they're become apathetic Either that or they're
not a very talkative bunch This is a
pretty this chat is the one new Greeks
be the new Greek speak chat tango one.
It's kind of like Inert almost, you know,
but it's alright, you know when I talk
about the chat being worthless It's not the
people in the chat.
It's just the chat itself This is where
the because I don't know who's on or
not, you know, really he was watching it
I know there's roughly 70 people that asked
for it when we flip to this one.
Mm-hmm But yeah, there's not much going
on which isn't a good thing because I'm
not if the chat was active in questions
and people were fastidious or at least doing
work Then I would have to be more
involved and take up my time for nothing
So at least I know if I go
to the chat, there's tumbleweeds and a you
know, minimal stuff the same usual subs suspects
Mm-hmm on Let's see 618 the 7th
yikes crazy me a river a bunch of
air.
So who's Smoke every God you are man
smoking trees, son No, what's up, man?
Lay off the trees son.
Let's get a Smoking trees.
Okay.
I can't do that crap.
It just it.
Yeah.
Well, well look it's it's crap to me
But if it if it works for you
use it It's it's lawful it's green.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know even have a derivative like
cocaine or heroin is still lawful I'll tell
you a lot of the medicines that they
use the standard legal ones are not lawful
Because they have monkey pro testicle proteins and
pork and insects in them, you know All
the joy Yeah, the straight-up satanic, you
know mainstream, but you know, they're they're accommodating
the people you could go So anywhere out
your door it has to be part of
that, you know accommodating.
Yeah, they know what they're doing.
Yeah That's why I'm totally against whenever I
hear about protesters and this it's like I
just want to go and throw Like condoms
filled with sour milk at them Because you're
stupid the reason why things are the way
they are no matter how horrific it gets
it's because it's accommodating The typical surface-dwelling
inhabitant scumbag, whatever you want to call them
taboo human, by the way, not only you
know I might seem misanthropic which is actually
duly So it's appropriate but if you were
to go off-world by the way in
the spiritual realm or whatever Humans are like
the scum of the universe, right?
All right, so You know, this is we're
talking about triple-t rating truth truth and
truth We're not here to make friends that
you're not, you know, you're not going to
get better.
The earth doesn't need saving Yeah, you're gonna
get worse and he's just gonna get wiped
And and you know, there's going to be
a small remnant and it starts not all
over again But it definitely starts over on
a new foot let's say and literally on
a new foot you will you won't yeah
It won't be the same.
So, um Yeah, there's nothing wrong with the
truth Unless people have been so groomed that
they need to hear things the way they're
used to and then they don't like anything
else Like with Ocelli, you know, it's like
I agree with you on this or I
don't agree with you that so to see
Because you agree with me.
It's true, right?
You see the consensus.
I don't mean to pick on Chuck He's
a fairly decent guy, but he's a good
representation of you know What you hear out
there you hear all these people or I
call morons and they're like, oh, yeah, I
agree with that Rosie, I agree with that
too.
And the poor sap that's listening to these
idiots is like, oh, yeah That's the truth
because they all agree with it.
Yeah You say so high mentality of some
sort, you know in conditioning Just baffles just
sometimes Okay here we got a question just
came in hi Greek and Bruce thanks for
let's see what it is Thanks for these
sonic events quick question Greek.
You once stated that when you clean up
crew starts Well prior to okay, we will
need to I read ahead of myself.
We would need to be three days No,
you don't need to be three days walking
distance from our fellow earth inhabitants Do you
still think this is the case or is
it pointless is a serious question?
Thanks again I was looking forward to your
insight Cheers It's I would suggest yes for
sure even now three-day walking distance is
good And you notice I said walking not
driving because there won't be great cars Yeah,
you know three-day walking is what 45
minutes a half hour by car.
Yeah a comfortable 10 miles 10 to 20
miles depending on your fitness Five miles is
a pretty good walk.
Yeah, if you you know, if you were
to set your day Yeah, if you're gonna
set up for walking with a backpack food
and all that You're depending on your fitness
and your pace, of course, like you said
a slow pace fast You're out of shape
for something like that You're gonna knock you
know, you don't get to know it real
quick Five miles if you're out of shape
would be arduous 10 to 20 if you're
a fit and a high pace.
Yeah That's the mileage or you could do
the kilometers So I would suggest even now
look I wish I was three days walk
I wish I was three days right driving
distance from people I really do not because
I'd never want to be around people I
do but not the sort that I see
on the planet right now So and they're
just like robots Which which is what makes
them dangerous, you know, stupid people large numbers
are dangerous, right?
And they're everywhere and don't be me.
Hopefully people that are listening.
I have not Still I'd have established not
to be misled by the entitled classes, you
know You know meaning like if someone says
they're a professor.
Yeah, you're just a propagandist.
Someone says they're a doctor Well, you're just
good with band-aids aspirin and painkillers and
you're propagandist, you know an attorney.
Well, that's Representing the demonic forces on the
planet straight up Politician that don't even consider
it's a non entity You know a priest
a rabbi a pastor, you know representing demonic
forces So, I mean, what are you gonna
do?
You know, I mean this I'm talking the
commoner is just filler Like sawdust on the
floor when I say people are not Happening.
I'm talking about you're the best of your
best not you're The commoner, you know, they're
there if they're not even they're non entity
completely so anyway as As things go on
for those that are sort of a quote
-unquote entity of some sort It is the
season of winter still and it will be
approaching the middle of it soon By the
middle of the next moon Or so then
era, you know, then when the days start
getting longer people that are on the other
side of the hemisphere I'm speaking to them
as well.
They're in there, but in the opposite sense,
they're in their main growing part, you know
center of summer But it's a center season
type thing.
So basically what you're going to see is
more buildup of what you've seen the past
few weeks So anyway Middle East is what
you got to be watching if you're looking
for what real You know global or earth
changes are going to be that's been the
case for the past 20 some odd years
So if you see like a dramatic event
in Venezuela or Canada or the u.s.
It doesn't mean that it's going to That's
not what it's about.
That's not gonna it's it has to do
with the Middle East.
Here's a good example 9-11 Where did
it happen, New York City USA, right?
Well, guess what it affected the most Middle
East now You see well, I have the
morons here, you know, like the Patriot Act
and the NDA all that stuff's already in
the Lieber code When they pass all these
draconian laws, you know where they could detain
you and hold you forever.
That's been around since the 1870s Just go
look it up.
The Lieber code was it's a army manual
for engagement of an you know Peaceful inhabitants
or belligerence in the field for army engagement
in the field So that's why you have
a credit-based economy.
You don't need money because we knew the
military you don't use money use what's called
script And you don't have medicine you have
military medicine Right, if you don't believe that
you ever heard of an emergency room or
a hospital.
Those are those are not civilian Yeah, that's
all military stuff.
So anyway, I Don't say see there's about
eight or nine people in the chat.
I don't know what else is going on
They haven't I've got a bunch of emails
general roundabout stuff.
Not much.
I don't think are worth addressing.
Okay Yeah, I don't know what else to
say, I mean it's just the usual stuff
It does well once you know when something
is Unfortunately, it doesn't apply to scripture and
ancient writs But some of these codes and
things do the abridged version first find something
that's been written about it right, right and
Because it's not like if you want to
you know, the like the Bible is you
know scripture It's hard to get your head
around right don't I'm not suggesting you go
read something about it You could but but
that's a targeted propaganda piece Heavily censored so
you it's going to be incorrect all around
most of the time but something like the
Lieber code That's fairly unknown.
If something is written about it.
It's going to be fairly candid Yeah, it's
going to be and it may not it
may not give you a sense of the
severity of it like it's being applied right
now, but it'll give you an outline of
The severity the severity again, right?
But any any ancient writ by the way,
even Greek philosophy I was speaking to someone
a couple weeks ago That's studying Greek philosophy
says Greek man.
I kind of doubted you but now that
I'm looking at Greek philosophy, right?
They never really did translate it Looking at
the words.
It doesn't mean what they're you know, I'm
like, yeah.
Well, okay.
Well, I hope you You're getting in touch
with me to impart something new.
Don't don't just Get in touch for me.
Tell me I'm right.
I already know that you know about that.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be saying it I'm not
saying it to be right.
I'm saying it so I can give a
report But that person didn't have much at
the time.
So we'll see what would comes forward in
the future I put a question about Mexico
and Other troubles are having their way the
missing people in the thousands.
Yeah, I saw that before.
Yeah, and there's also something Juice, did you
catch it?
I don't know if you read it or
not But you know here you got all
these people chanting for justice justice justice Oh,
yeah, and then you get a bunch of
them that are chanting to these other gods
Yes, you kind of sit back and wonder,
you know, well you're causing your own troubles
Mm-hmm But there but here's the thing
if you study scripture, they're supposed to go
to these gods Yeah, we're supposed to go
to these gods, you know at the time
of after the flood the the Tower of
Babel They were supposed to disperse right and
and But they didn't so that's another story
someone No one's asked could he will you
talk about the Tower of Babel or the
rest of you know?
So I don't I don't I don't volunteer
information anymore, right?
It's very easy to have an Agenda, you
know what they call academic agenda.
You make a list.
So we want to I don't do that.
I'm finished with that So the the thing
is the The gods and all that are
hostile.
In other words, they have changed also they've
gotten worse towards man Let's just say in
a nutshell, right?
So the God of Canada and that has
gotten worse now than it was let's say
a hundred years ago God of Australia, but
actually they might share the same one because
they're a part of the Empire, right?
But also there was a recent you're going
to be seeing more Normalization about cannibalism and
death like there was something I caught today.
I turned on the small one of these
small devices and it gave me a newsflash
a woman in Morocco cooked and ate her
ex-boyfriend and Served him up to his
friends in a rice pilaf type dish And
the way she was caught the police were
looking for him and they found one of
his teeth in the blender because she blended
Up his body.
I ate a piece by piece.
Oh Yeah, she also asked the neighbor to
help her get rid of the body so
this has been going this is not like
oh look This woman was on the Pope's
work schedule, whatever it is, November, whatever it
did this No, no.
No, this is going on every day all
over all the time You know, it's so
many wonder how much of it's not getting
out, right?
It's as thick as the old telephone book
if you catalog how many people are eaten
just in one, you know country I mean,
it's it's many many many there's a what
eight million people go missing every year Yeah,
and on the planet generally, so it's like
really like 30 million people go made a
hundred Thousand children in the u.s. Under
the age of six and they don't get
investigated Yeah, I mean easily, you know, you're
eating human flesh It's being what do you
think Walmart is benevolent or malevolent?
Do you think when you go buy pork
at Walmart?
It's big Every every time I mean, come
on, you know, or you know can be
a chili that has pork in it You
think that's really pig pork?
You've got to be stupid and totally asleep.
You're not eating human.
They're not giving you human flesh based on
a prank You know, I caught my eye
when I got on here today was Six
of 18 there went and posted something and
it looked like a Walmart species a wall
Martian Well Martian.
Yeah.
Yeah, I wanted to oh, yeah.
Oh the one with the double visual image
Yeah, that's one thing why people don't age
well and they don't look good when they're
out of shape I mean, I'm not saying
mother but they fall apart very quickly Yeah,
when they when they fall apart boy, it
does it, you know pick up speed.
So anyway Yeah, there's always a lot of
quote-unquote good stuff to talk about if
you're talking about developing food clothing and shelter
You want to avoid?
Anything that people are interested in Because it's
been corrupted so even let's say for example,
I remember back in the 80s, uh, you
know So I started seeing Especially in the
late 80s more mainstream talk about organic food.
I said, oh, that's it.
It's going to be corrupted Yeah in less
than a decade.
It'll be crap.
It won't be as good Well, it still
is good But you know so anything that
the populace gets into they have a so
many demons following them that they're gonna jump
in and wreck it so What I mean
by that is that's why I never talk
about new scientific discoveries politics medical discoveries You
know because none of those discoveries are really
discoveries.
They're just general academic pranks And also, you
know having some discussions recently with someone someone
in academia.
They fully admit They were nodding.
Yes to what I was, you know, basically
the Greek speak on academia, but they're like,
hey, you know I set myself up for
it and it's a job and I'm like,
yeah and Every one of them says that
when you get to know them Just like
just like every attorney that you know will
tell you the law doesn't matter You do
what the judge says and basically I don't
need to know the law When you get
to know them you call up an attorney
now, and you're just some, you know cold
call Whatever.
So of course we go by law.
No, of course.
I know the law.
Yeah, because you know, that's their facade, right?
Yeah, there is no doctor that is licensed
or works that knows how the human body
works and you and practices it openly Because
if he did he'd lose his permission to
be a doctor, right?
This is a horrible horrible condition, but you
know, I'm giving those as examples that what
people praise is Totally worth it belongs on
the bottom of you know, some giant shoe
but Doesn't mean that you can't How Would
you say when you cultivate something right when
you make something we discover something you yeah
You cultivate you make it grow food your
own food clothing and shelter the best you
can here's the interesting thing I've told you
know, I've said, you know in two years
won't be able to eat out anymore I
said that a year ago So I got
about another year because I've noticed it's getting
worse and worse and worse Right and I
won't be able to really get any meat,
you know animal In the next two or
three years, I will not be doing it
because it's going to be that poor, you
know I see it coming.
It's it's and the signs are very clear
to me They may not be to others,
but it all starts with anything that has
to be stewarded You know or controlled by
people is going to get worse and worse,
but at the same time You're going to
be building up a golden age.
So go figure how that works.
It's not a dichotomy when you understand scripture
You know, how many people think the cell
phones are a good thing, you know, raise
your hand everyone raises their hand well, and
then of course, you'll have someone that shows
you what damage it does and What it
you know?
Well, we could talk about the spying also,
which is something else, but right the eavesdropping
If you told people that we're not aware
of the technology the plot positive and negatives
They wouldn't use it because of the negatives
But the people feel that the negatives the
positives overcome the negatives and they still use
what I mean So like if you went
back to a culture a hundred years ago
and said these are the positives and then
there's a no way We don't want it.
It was negative.
The positives are not worth it, right?
You see So that's what I mean by
what what's coming you'll be used to it
and you'll take it now in terms of
the spying Like they say NSA government agencies
and there's no such thing as the NSA
It's a it's an agency, which is part
of the government not government.
It's part of the government a Semi-autonomous
and most of its clients are private people
and private dealings He just like you know
I knew someone that worked at the DEA
and he's like yeah for a hundred and
fifty thousand dollars in 90 days notice We
could move a satellite Anywhere to follow someone
or whatever or beam microwaves down to them
and fry their ass or whatever You know,
there's satellites more satellites than you know, and
I was like, wow, okay cool, you know
Not cool, but you know, this is it's
very common you they still have to pay
in other words If FBI goes to NSA,
they have to give the NS is a
bill.
They have to pay the bill So don't
think that they're been conglomerate and there is
nothing viable in what you're saying You know
what?
I mean, just like I speak to people
over the world I say oh you're completely
surrounded by morons and they all always agree
why I've never been to where they are.
They never told me It's freaking obvious right,
right So it's pretty obvious that there's nothing
anyone can say that they're the quote-unquote
You know eavesdropping on cell phones is being
used for because they know you're all a
bunch of idiots there what they're doing is
Categorizing it based on what you're saying or
who you are in metadata to monetize it
when it comes time to Mix it with
Department of Justice and their criminal side, which
is all monetizing, right, right So, for example,
you know how you think they monetize a
YouTube channel, right?
Based on activity and all this stuff, right?
Sure When they when they survey someone the
more they survey them the more they can
monetize it It doesn't matter if you're talking
about crackerjacks, but obviously they're not tell you
that They tell you you know, it's evasive
and we're looking for terrorists There's no such
thing.
They invented determine the procedures for terrorism.
The whole thing is ridiculous It's all about
monetization and they will kill you for it
You are nothing because you'll end up in
a can of chili with pork on the
ingredient and everybody will eat it happen I
think it's pork This is the real existence
Look up Oats, if you really want to
know what's going on spiritually on the planet
Go to YouTube.
There's a oats studios just like the hot
oats, you know the oats, you know, I
grow old oats, you know Yes studios Yeah,
it's scroll down like to the middle maybe
a year or so ago.
There's a there's a 20-minute film There's
a there are you there like a YouTube?
Internet film company they make films for the
Internet and you look for something called Raka.
I think it's r a k k a
it's like This is a reptilian species come
over to the earth It's very well done
and in the end Sporny Weaver's in it.
She did it.
She liked it so much She actually kicked
in her time She donated her time for
it because she's like the ultimate princess of
the alien and sci-fi, you know, so
Gordy Weaver, you know and she looks like
somebody's granny that's really fit and she She's
in the end the film there, but check
out Raka and that's what's really going on.
Hmm behind the scenes not over Oats studios.
Yeah, you'll be that's what is really going
on.
So But not not like they're sure but
you know, that's severity right now and it's
gonna get worse so Yeah, there's plenty of
stuff to do that that can make your
life.
Well Better, I don't know because it's gonna
you know, you're gonna be you know how
they say it's an uphill battle Yeah, you
know, it's it's more work, right?
So you're gonna have to invest more time
and energy and Effort I should say into
anything that you do if you want a
quality life so and Forgo a lot of
things like I don't do any banking Right.
I just you know use the Federal Reserve
note and I properly monitor, you know properly
recorded Indexing on title 12 section 4 1
so if anyone wants to talk to me
about you know Any authority or whatever about
it like hey, look, you know I'm redeeming
it for lawful money and this you know
But I know all you need to do
to redeem for all the ways make sure
that you're making a demand for it because
they're not Going to give you Yeah, I
can't engage in the it's so easy to
I mean any bank will open a bank
account for you and do whatever You don't
even have to go to a bank.
You could do it online, but I choose
not to because it's a criminal enterprise through
and through for a criminal society through and
through so You know might be another part
of it, yeah, yeah, I just rather I'd
rather Suffer the lack of it because it
is inconvenient in a lot of cases like
The other day I was at Home Depot
and they said no cash all the register.
They redid the registers They don't look like
registers anymore.
They look like counters.
Oh my and you don't even see a
drawer for money or anything And it's all
cards, you know, you know Yeah, so there's
all the things that can't take cash all
the drawers won't open There's only out of
all the registers at a Home Depot only
two or three take cash I was like,
you know screw this But who's the one
getting screwed because the local hardware store and
lumberyard now is a restaurant and they kept
the name Right also as a lumberyard and
it's like outdoor seating and music.
So there is no choice You see so
so what do I have to do cut
down trees or no trees here in the
desert to get wood?
So, I mean, I'm gonna have to figure
out it But if I had one of
those cards, I just swipe it and just
like me be on my merry way Like
all the other morons.
I'm not any better because I don't do
banking.
I just I just prefer not to today
For for different ways to approach the issue.
Yeah, it's easier to see what's coming and
the changes when you're not involved in something,
right?
it's like if let's say you worked at
a corporation and Someone is really good at
reading, you know Updates on that corporation they
find out that Chances are because of the
financial service they're gonna fire workers If you
work there and someone tells you that you
might lose your job, but now I don't
really haven't heard anything like that here No,
I'm fine.
I so You're not going to be able
to see it coming if you're in it,
you know Not that anything's coming because there's
no money.
Anyway, I think someone does a custodian or
whatever he he's seriously obsessed with the credit
system and I I Know it through and
through and I know how to work it.
I mean, but I don't because it's unlawful
I'd rather not do unlawful stuff like that,
you know, look it's it's right in your
in the laws You go look up the
RESPA FTC PA and the FTC TPA Laws
if someone sends you a dunning or a
bill And it has to do with consumer
credit.
They have to validate not verify.
They use they try to trip you up
According to those federal laws.
They say one word.
They say verified.
They say valid verification and validation are two
different things Otherwise, there's there's no debt.
So you just deny that you owe anything
and it goes away I mean you might
have to actually threaten to sue them That's
the best way to do it and it's
five and it's every time they contact you
It's five hundred to a thousand bucks.
You let them contact you 25 or 30
times before you take an action There was
a guy that worked as a janitor and
a couple of other jobs a few years
ago that discovered this There's a group called
what lies in your debt.
They're pretty censored, but they're very good at
putting this stuff together I had gotten I
had already known and used this system in
the past Previous but when I found out
about them, they had really put it together
very neatly.
They made it more simple It doesn't mean
it's going to be easy But this guy
worked barely making it now All he does
is use credit cards and he and plus
he makes a hundred to a hundred fifty
thousand a year So you just run the
credit card up and say where's that, you
know prove you have a debt Oh can't
and it doesn't go on the credit report
And if they try to put on the
credit report You sue that you go after
the credit card company, you know, it's them,
you know, and then they take it off
So the credit report spotless Right So the
thing is they have an army of repossessors
when you try to do that with boats
cars planes motorcycles or homes They don't care.
They just run it through and take it
away from you It's kind of like you
go to a sandwich shop you pay for
it And before right before you go to
sit down they take it from you and
they get make someone else pay for it
and before They take a bite out of
it, you know, they might even take a
butter They take it away and sell it
to someone else the same thing over and
over.
That's what they're doing.
It's completely criminal enterprise, but the people Here's
like prohibition, you know, they did that by
the don't believe that they did prohibition to
think the nation be better to stop alcohol
It was to boost the black market and
see that if it would fall into line
The black market and prohibition wouldn't have worked
if the people you didn't want to drink
it, right?
If the people said well, it's country and
jurisdiction says no alcohol.
None of us will do it Then there
wouldn't have been no black market and we
probably still to have been in prohibition, right?
Right, but they found that the black market
wasn't as good as taxing it and they
couldn't control it Yeah, just like the war
on drugs They're just telling you that now
that they're getting into drugs and every time
they you know When they tell you, you
know the homeland security all this anti-terrorism
means that they're getting into terrorism now Everything
is backwards.
Yeah when they tell you FDA that means
they're going to start poisoning your food and
your drugs, right?
Right when it's like yeah, you see it's
so simple.
I mean, where do you think you are?
I mean, you're on planet Earth, you know,
this is how things work here Regardless of
what the people are saying, they don't most
people if you ask them where they are
None of them will tell you I'm on
earth They'll tell you the city or the
state whatever they're so brainwashed to think it
has something to do with something It's just
a district right very few people.
Where are you now?
I'm on earth where you know, I'm on
this part of the earth No one thinks
like that That's that's why the they're being
treated the way they are and that's why
things are the way they are because they
don't see it on that level You know,
even when people Were you know horse and
carriage and walking on foot we're talking like,
you know, no tech or you know hand
tech I call it and pure analog tech.
They always considered what was around the earth
or whatever You you only hear about their
local nationalism or whatever because they had to
protect it Right.
That was a concern, but they're always Murdered
land Like in if you were in the
u.s. Most where you said China that
was a mythological place up until the 1800s.
Mm-hmm I know it sounds kind of
crazy now In other words in the early
black and white films They had white people
in films dress up like Chinaman because they
didn't want to put a real Chinaman and
scare the white people Because they had never
seen one.
It was mythological place, but known as the
Orient.
Yeah you see so Yeah, it's just a
pretty shitty place The place is great.
But what people and and the thing is
can you blame the people, you know, very
often say well They don't know Greek Well
it but I'm not I'm not giving the
reasons All of the veritable reasons why the
people are stupid and wicked or whatever I'm
just telling you the fact that they are
and you're not going to change it So,
you know what I mean?
So if you just act with the facts
as people are dangerous and evil and whatever
you'll be better off and saying well I
know they're they're capable of danger and evil
and all that but that's because they don't
have an education that Propaganda as you run
through the whole it doesn't matter because the
minute you interact with them the potential of
them Being the worst is higher than the
potential of them being the best So you
stick with the facts good kind of like
again like a court scene, you know, what
is the fact it's a fact you know,
they Just the facts the facts are that
Where I'm not talking about how or why
they are the way they are.
Yes So if they are intentionally it's a
first degree, but let's say they're all they
the majority of the people are of second
degree right Yeah, there isn't a good portion
of them that are first degree evil and
stubborn and wicked and stupid But the majority
doesn't matter a little nudge and they'll go
up a little bit.
Yeah, so And this is gonna just go
on and then you know There's not much
to talk about other than you know, as
anyone want get into anything Otherwise, we'll make
it a really short one again.
I mean, let's see.
We had a couple of At the risk
you something about the resurrection here At the
resurrection people will neither marry nor be given
in marriage I have always pondered on this
We'll go look at go look at that
word by word in the Greek The New
Testament is that you haven't is worthless has
no value in in the English it's been
so scared in other words read it, but
then go study it and You're not entitled
to asking questions on New Testament stuff unless
you've studied it and study.
It means an interlinear You can get away
with the what's called the Old Testament a
little bit better But any if you bring
up anything in the New Testament It has
to be looked at word by word in
the Greek because I'm telling you they've really
screwed it up It's has no value.
It has no value other than the place
Actually what's in the New Testament is tremendous
value But what you're reading has no value
unless you've validated it through the interlinear word
by word Sorry, and then you have to
go back and also ponder the law and
also ponder the Aramaic if it's available so
But anyway regarding F.
I don't know I'd have to go It
sounds like it's fairly fluent meaning, you know
from another thought prior to that That's the
other thing that these Christian demons like to
do the especially the the biblical ones that
say they use the Bible They take only
one verse out of context But if you
actually look at especially New Testament stuff You
you have to take it in chunks go
like three or four verses prior three or
four verses after to Create the context even
if it's at the beginning of a book
or a chapter believe it or not So
certain book in them and the one that
the people use oh, it's horrible It's a
joke that's why a lot of people that
are anti Christian or whatever they use the
New Testament Against them which they should because
you know because if you're gonna rely on
such a poor version, it's not even a
translation it's a poor version you deserve to
get hit over the head and over it
and disregarded But anyway, do you want to
want to just review that question again the
one or the Let's see if we go
work with it.
Yeah I'm not in front of a computer
right now, but I will be Get her
back up here Oh as a wreck as
the Resurrection people will neither marry nor be
given in marriage.
I have always pondered on this Afterwards yeah,
Mary.
Well, that's pretty interesting right well What's the
purpose of fidelity when you say marriage is
fidelity right usually even if it's multiple wives
ultimately, it's it's to continue the It's to
continue the species if you're resurrected.
Do you have any concern with that?
No, you don't Yep That's usually the the
entire resurrection because there are going to be
resurrected beings.
They're going to be running the scumbags that
are left All right, right, right because it's
not gonna this is the other thing that
the la la land Principle the people that
are going to be left are just going
to be a representative sample of the scumbags
that are here now Right.
I'm using the term scumbag as a Navy,
you know, if you're in the Navy, that's
a common term It just means like that
was a used prophylactic wasn't it?
Yeah, right Yeah, it means like you're you're
you're new you're stupid product.
Yes.
Yeah, you're here.
You shouldn't be here You know, you know,
you don't know what you're doing, but we
got it.
We need bodies Mm-hmm Fairground sailors, especially
submarine people that comes out of their mouth
constantly.
Oh, yeah, they're on some submarine people They're
like, oh this we had a scumbag coming.
I'm like, what did you say?
Anyway, I'm not in this is not a
Navy call.
It was a Navy called be normal.
Oh, yeah, but yeah, there's going to be
Representative sample don't think this la la land
that this this JES US creature is coming
back You know looking all effeminate and all
that and gonna do, you know, there's by
the way, you know There's gonna be no
churches and no Christianity in the future Thankfully,
but no Islam either or Judaism as you
know it or Buddhism all that shit's gonna
go Hope you guys will realize that So
none of that stuff's gonna be around.
We're talking real stuff.
You're gonna see real technology again Go back
to the question Think about it.
If you're a resurrected being like these these
idiots go around to call themselves born again
Christian or whatever Years ago.
I did like a Bible study thing a
couple times more than a couple of times
as long as I'm born again I don't
need that.
I'm like you're born again.
You see that parking lot across the street
I want to see can you show up
in that parking lot?
I just what do you mean?
Well, if you were born again, it means
you're resurrected.
You can just appear right there.
Go ahead Pop on over, you know, I
can test you up on or you can't
do it.
Oh, you're an asshole Imagine that Hmm They're
all like that all the all the groups
like for example If you go to university
and you look like there's a particular school
like physics school, right?
Mm-hmm.
The students come out the proof.
They're just a little carbon copies of the
professor They're they don't they don't have they
don't have one authentic creative thought in their
minds ever in their whole lives That's why
they're there.
They have no critical thinking none You talk
to them and they're all just like little
copies as they've just been told what to
say none of them are thinking That's why
you know when you look at the Internet
for example on scientific discoveries They're always showing
these teenagers in graduate school or you know
early 20s It's not head whatever repeating, you
know, and you're supposed to be impressed.
So a bunch of rubbish You're just trekking
along another words society This is like the
old there's a lot of poems written about
it.
The only reason society is around It's not
because of anything that you're doing.
Well, actually two things.
What is the Sun?
Rises and sets and you have the growth
cycle The other thing is that you've separated
your wastewater and your freshwater far enough not
to be sick.
All right In other words your sewer pipes,
hopefully are not running into your feed lines
and vice versa that was the case of
all these sicknesses not because of the and
On all these neurological diseases are called by
caused by insecticides and chemicals not by viruses
so That's it pretty much the rest of
you just trucking logistics day in day out
breath here breath there you know what they
give you out the Say the word grocery
stores And you that's my most people are
overdosing on all these different Additives that you
know vitamins and all this and you can't
oh, yeah, imagine a toxicology on that over
a period of time Yeah, and the degradation
that that does to one's self So it's
it's yeah, but it's a testament to the
robustness of the body Human body it takes
a lot of abuse now.
This is all done I was having a
conversation yesterday with someone About technology and force
and power and who runs the world and
all that and the military by the way
It does not have any power unless it's
attached to the spiritual realm Right.
So every military in the world just like
you're the Troy, you know Agamemnon sacrificed his
daughter to get the sails, you know the
wind blowing to move the ships This is
still being done today.
You're American.
They call them Satanists, but they're really You
can judge them as Satanists basically that category,
but you know, if all your major major
religions are satanic They're there.
They're also satanic But they're what they're doing
is specifically evoking demonic entities that are for
fighting war elementals, right?
US military all of them, you know Don't
look at the generals and the people they
put in front of you.
Those are PR people Yes, they know what's
going on you know, they have you know,
and Yeah, you don't make four star or
whatever unless they have pictures of you with
a black penis in your mouth Yeah, you
know, I'm serious or something.
You know, you don't make those positions.
Yeah, you know I mean, it's it's you
know, if you're white and if you're a
black general Then I don't know what they
put in your mouth probably not still black,
but I'm just being derogatory here This is
the reality of of you know, the world
you live in not not what I'm not
making this stuff up Look up cherry marine
By the way, if you know about that
now you can't be in the higher ranks
in the Marines unless you're you you they
put you in gay porn or You know
got you photographed with a child.
I'm serious, right?
This is not Fantasy this is reality.
Just like your your Hormel can of pork
chili.
Do you think that's pork?
You're you're an idiot you know, so I'm
not saying that all of the pork on
the market is not pork But I I
know for sure these people are sick enough
for sure That they're putting human flesh in
the pork food supply for sure.
Can you trust that?
Yes Yes, it's actually been known for hundreds
of years that to get rid of the
body usually if you didn't have a seriously
agitated You feed it to a pig or
a pig farm nearby.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's how it was done.
It still is done today But now you
have the level of pranking That is beyond
what most people can imagine you can be
what they call an imagineer Just sit around
all day and that's your job to imagine
shit And you can't I bet you still
won't be able to come up with anything
that resembles the truth too much Right because
that's how far you know removed you are
from it.
So Anyway, I'm gonna go back into the
office here in a moment, and we'll see
if there's anything else Bruce.
Do you think or?
short was wondering If sickness can be transposed
like parents eating their children Can it happen
that a child's actions transposed to the unknowing
parent?
Yeah, yeah, of course Well, yes based on
susceptibility and Based on the and the element
behind that disease if it's a very powerful
one, it'll transpose for a three block radius
If it's a fairly weak one, it won't
be able to its individually target Yeah You
know, it's possible You know to you know
start a pattern of discernment based on this,
you know, what's going on spiritually around a
person also You know to answer that biologically,
you know, okay Like parents
eating their children can it happen that a
child's actions transposed to unknown parents Oh eating
their children I thought it was getting sick.
Oh, I've been wondering if sickness can be
transposed hmm,
I Don't quite get that Say it reword
that Take a few seconds to get down
the stream Just
made its way down Yeah, but the eating
of children and child sacrifice is happens every
day by the thousands or hundreds In just
you know, pick a large country like the
US or the European Union.
Let's say which is a Union.
This is normal I mean, I remember visiting
Greece a while back and and I wanted
to see this cave because I had a
postcard of it They're like don't don't go.
We don't want to go to that.
The locals are no we don't want to
go to that cave No, no, no, you
shouldn't go I said why because that's where
the priests take the children to rape them
and it wasn't like that's where the priests
Took the children a long time ago to
rape him.
No, this is currently where the priests take
the children to rape them Whoa, I was
like, whoa, you know, you still got these
fuckers around you don't hang them Yeah, you
know burn their houses down and all that
stuff.
If you know that's happening.
You see what I mean?
How they're culpable also, right?
Yeah Yeah Yeah, the thing is now that
the society, you know, just like with the
homo the sodomites and the transgender and the
violence Oh Violence a violent.
We don't want any violence.
What are you talking about?
If you do it so fast, it's not
considered but define they can't define violence if
you go up to a There's a trick
that you the tablecloth pulled from underneath all
the place setting sure, you know Set like
that set a table for five people, you
know, you could pull the tablecloth just right
It leaves everything there right if it's heavy
enough, but if you don't do it just
right, it looks pretty violent, doesn't it?
It does Right a well-placed blow Yeah,
so years ago if they even today it's
still going on today in the Midwest and
places that are More rural when someone is
a problem to them, you know their family
or the society They follow there's certain people
that are chosen and the sheriff's know about
this the local the Leo's, you know, a
lot local Law enforcement agency people know this
and they just wait for the person, you
know like maybe they will go out in
the middle of the night to get smoke
a pack of cigarettes or something and they
never come Back and and then they're not
missed It's not like well, he didn't come
they might say well, he didn't come back
last night, you know, wink-wink, you know
big deal All right, and they're not missed
and this happens all the time.
I Mean in Colorado what they do is
they just tie you to a tree and
rub peanut butter all over you Same in
Alaska, they have grizzly bears.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, you're not gonna find anything Actually
tying you to a tree is not very
good because the way the bear attacks is
they have to pounce on your chest and
They eat your face off first.
So but they'll still they'll find it.
They'll get you off the tree Yeah, so
anyway, this is normal human activity folks.
It's not violence Like you've been brainwashed.
I'm not promoting it because it's not gonna
help anything No, wait, but it actually will
because it's going to be extremely violent Oh,
we've one of the gods do it when
they eliminate 95% of y'all it's
not going to be peaceful when they do
it by the way and it's gonna happen
over several a good poor a third of
That's going to be done by yourselves to
each other The other two-thirds a little
bit more than that is going to be
done by the gods and it's not going
to be peaceful But it'll be swift.
I Wouldn't say painless it could be I
think to a certain degree When it's a
form of accounting when someone has to be
taken out by the gods, I don't think
they make it painful We have some Evidence
of that when the Assyrian army during Hezekiah
was put to sleep 180,000 by an
angel it didn't say they died violently or
painlessly.
They just all went to sleep and they
never woke up I don't know but getting
hit by it with an asteroid is that
could be painful ouch You know, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah Yeah So it's just that you know,
it's it's not possible to speak as time
goes on every day It's harder and harder
to speak to people about real things Do
you know just generally, you know?
Mm-hmm like There's really nothing going on
I mean other than the progression towards a
Middle East Union you know and then a
progression towards Normalizing wickedness through amongst the people,
you know, like wickedness would just be normal
sure and learning more about things that are
hidden and doing things that you normally wouldn't
do and Gathering, you know a biblical law
being reinstated For a short time enough to
get rid of all the sodomites and all
people with tattoos You know I'm not saying
you know, I'm just saying this is you
know the scenario.
Yeah so Yeah, this is a pretty crazy
stuff, man And this is what's coming.
Welcome to earth Mm-hmm Well, also, you
know a lot of other groups are going
to be eliminated And the ones that you
will see the practices that are death offenses
in Scripture or exile offenses Mm-hmm, you
know what an exile offense if you're if
there's an exile offense where you're exiled And
if that law applies to as a constitution
of a given area, well, the exile is
quite possible You bring them to the edge
of the border or whatever and you say
you can't come back But if it's on
the entire planet, where is exile?
There is not it's you're finished So I
don't think they're gonna send you up to
join the Germans on the moon But anyway,
yeah They wouldn't want them Oh,
I see what he's saying The the spewed
out vile words constantly one of their parents
of terminal gastrointestinal illness.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's possible That's like I'm very you've
heard of like even in the in the
popular culture spells Mm-hmm.
You know, they're actually people like that can
master the The whole range of what's behind
words and they're known as what's called witches
or spellcasters, right?
Spellcaster is just someone that is mastered as
command of The way words apply to the
spiritual realm which then comes back and applies
to the physical realm.
That's all it is that happens when you
are You know projecting words towards people especially
in a familial environment, you know, they'll read
okay the reword the question I know of
someone that spewed out vile words constantly and
one of their parents developed a terminal gastrointestinal
illness Mm-hmm Yeah, that's like just a
general broadcast well because that person received it
differently the way they were programmed or set
up to receive it It's it's you know,
what makes the gods the gods is their
technology and it's not made in China No
You know what I mean get the manual
Well, we do have them.
No, we don't have the manual on their
technology we have the manual for us that
gives us a roundabout outline of what's possible
when through historic interaction and Also in history
when I say historic meaning future see when
you read stuff in the prophecy is history
Meaning that it's so sure it's going to
happen That you might as well call it,
you know strike it as being done, right
So it's basically later on after the resurrection
even the resurrection itself is a technology and
I don't mean there's a switchboard pushing buttons
there could be but it's all Non-material,
you know, it's not it's the same dimension.
It's just within the dimension, right?
So unseen to us so I I would
Say one can investigate what technology the gods
use but you've been blocked from it We
know that it has to do with thought
and all it has to do with intention.
We know it has to do with words
Yes so there you go, and if you
Look at prior arts, which are dubbed negative
and because they are negative In other words,
if you use a knife to kill someone
or use a knife to cut your dinner
One is negative one is positive, right?
So the prior art which has a negative
connotation to it, which are spell casters, which
is oracles, whatever They use it to gain
power, you know, like the pagans do like
the only reason Pagans are pagans is because
they interact with their gods to get something
done for them You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm Whether it's battle whether it's food
whether it's good weather, you know So it's
hard Yeah, they know they it's for their
benefit meaning either from personal one individual a
family or a group all right, and they're
dealing with low-level entities that are Basically
not friendly and they know that you know
all the time you're there's You know opposing
groups working with each other for you know
on a commercial level So, yeah, I mean
this is there's a really I mean there's
I think I've opened up enough topics over
the years with Greek speak That any one
of those topics whether you know, it's the
human body timekeeping Scripture real, you know real
physical sciences real physics Just the study of
how we perceive all these things good can
just be continued and and and I have
continued them in many ways On my own
study, but I don't see much reaction So
why you know, I'm not going to be
pushing and volunteering anymore.
Like I said, that's why I always come
on and ask for questions I mean, there's
a ton of subjects that can be brought
up that I haven't been that haven't brought
up Like the other day I was discussing
with someone.
Why did why do people animals have to
sleep?
What what's this whole thing about sleep, you
know, it's like wow, it's like no really
talking about well you need to rest Well,
I know that but why how why how
did it you know, what would be the
right you see?
So I'm not gonna start a whole new.
I mean guys got plenty to chew on.
I Put out I put out more than
some put out in the past 2,000
years It's enough.
This is lots of things to discuss and
you know Yeah, but yeah, why guess what
yeah, why bother yeah Let's see.
I have noticed.
Yes.
There are a lot of demonic possession movies
lately, especially this work Yes, it comes That's
like I think part of the 40-year
cycle like if you you know that there's
a 40-year cycle on that There's a
20-year and a 40-year cycle up
on them Like when did the Exorcist come
out, you know, it was about 40 years
ago No more than 40 years ago like
good.
Yeah, 45 years.
Oh, and it was a big cycle and
then it went away That's coming back now,
but when it comes it's different now now
it starts incorporating more symbolism about things You
should be of known about You know, right
or more Applicable to the common man where
before the omen and the Exorcist were wealthy
people or whatever exclusive Entitled now, it's it's
gonna be more applied to the to the
common Joe blue-collar, you know, right if
that makes any sense it does No,
I'm here I'm just muted out cuz I'm
fiddling around with something that was noisy so
oh, okay Yeah What's going on anything?
Otherwise, we just call it a call that
was pretty much the last of it there
Yeah in the meantime, I mean, I don't
know what people you know, everyone's got their
own little thing whatever they're into It's just
passing time Whatever you could do to pass
the time You know make your life a
little better in your life.
I mean in a sentient way or in
a in a Not philosophical.
Well, I could tell you specifically how you
should make your life better.
You should eat better.
You should sleep better You should feel better.
You're you know Mm-hmm You're you should
be comfortable in your clothes and in your
dwelling Comfortable and clean That's pretty much it
and then you die No, what that's like
such a revelation, isn't it?
That's it.
There's nothing else to do man.
You have other interests like for example Well,
I have interest in model trains or studying
this that's fine do it because time goes
by faster when you do that, correct Yeah,
this is Yep, there's not much to do.
I mean depends, you know, if you if
you think that, you know, even all the
knowledge in the world that you can do
or attain is Still gonna you're still gonna
die and you're still susceptible to the resurrection
and at that point You're at the most
absolute minimum level.
In other words after after that point you
will see how little even the wisest had
known right, so Pretty
much sums it right up, doesn't it?
Yeah Hey, yeah, it's just past the time,
you know, obviously like, you know, if I'm
still speaking publicly or we're still doing this
In the future and things start forming, you
know, what are we going to talk about?
See I told you so Right.
I mean, what are you gonna say?
I mean, what would we okay?
This is happening.
That's so what?
You know the the real reason for knowing
really if you and I've mentioned this before
Is to make it easier for the other
side, which is a higher side by the
way To do what they have to do
and they will use you for it So
like one of the example the reason I
say what I do is to make it
easier for the other side to do What
they have to do So because they will
not come and begin doing what they have
to do meaning, you know To wrap this
era of humankind up unless humankind has an
inkling of why it's going to happen, right?
All right, like when someone is lined up
against the wall to be shot by the
authorities They read this the the charges the
counts and the sentencing all over again So
they have to be a cognizant not like,
you know, I don't agree with that.
No at that point You're you know, you
see what I mean?
so mankind has to know why the asteroids
are going to hit why their Population is
going to be reduced to know, you know
5% of what it is now Why
And they don't have to know it and
put up a billboard.
They just have to admit it for a
second not much So when I tell you
that if this society is completely unlawful, basically
you're run by criminals and which makes this
whole society criminal Literally criminal not just a
figurative adjective or whatever from a lawful perspective
And I'll tell you why exactly why not
just accuse it in accusatory tone But lay
it out that now the guilt is on
you You see.
Mm-hmm So when you tell people, you
know birthday cake represents eating human children Well,
I you know, like I don't believe that
well, and I'm gonna keep doing well Did
you hear what I said the moment they
say yes, what did I say?
And they repeat it then that's it.
Your job is done.
That person is ready to go next You're
not gonna in other words I haven't said
it quite this way before When you tell
people about lawfully and who the creator is
and what real law is or what they're
doing wrong Don't expect to change what you
need to expect is some kind of a
response.
This is imperative This is why it's done
that they acknowledged what you said not acknowledged
the in a factual way in a repentive
kind of way or any you know, in
other words the terminus the the final point
of the or of the interaction is that
they understood and heard you You're done then
that your job is to go to the
next one because that one's ready to go
now You know what?
I mean, right?
He's ready to go so, you know when
the time comes it's fully, you know, it's
fully up This one's got the green light,
you know to get that, you know, the
head cut off right you see right because
he heard it Yeah, you just basically Letting
them know what they're guilty of this is
very it's in Leviticus, you know I said
first chapter if you see your brother doing
wrong and He doesn't know it he's not
he's not culpable right he's not Responsibly, but
once you tell him what he did and
why it's wrong now, he's responsible so telling
people About the birthday cake is you know,
it's not good.
That doesn't help All right, that doesn't help
him is it?
The birthday cake is humans resembles human sacrifice
and it's not good It's unlawful and it's
very negative very bad thing that you know,
you right I've seen some people just say
well, that's no I don't do that because
it's not good and they kind of like,
okay fine That that didn't do anything Right.
Yes.
Tell them why it's right What the what
these religions are doing is demonic and why?
Why because the demons are the ones that
control the institutions and that's how they control
the people through the institutions and the guy
up There is lying to you every religion.
They're all lying to the people Contrary to
what's in them you tell them why and
it doesn't matter what they say What matters
is that you it's like the sticker There
was a film that I saw where they
put this red dot this this creature put
a red whatever put the red dot would
explode When he hits the button, all right,
they had a red dot on it, right?
So basically you walk around these red dots
you just put it's okay, but the red
dot won't stick unless they acknowledge What you
said not if they change So they're not
going to change They're they're horrible people not
because I say so Scripture says so so
anyway The reason why there's Greek speak and
the reason why you should tell you the
thing is follow through things I have very
rarely.
I mean like Bruce.
I don't know you well enough I don't
know what you do in your personal life
But but generally the people that I have
seen been around no one can articulate what
I'm saying So that to me tells me
it's time not time yet or whatever and
even if you're when I say articulate I
mean just regurgitation just repeating exactly what I'm
saying.
They can't do it.
They can't follow through.
I've seen people try it I'm like that
didn't make any sense is what they look
at me and they're like, well, you know
what?
I mean, I said, I know what you
mean, but the person you just talked to
doesn't you didn't articulate it This whole thing
is a failure in terms of you know
Promote you're not promoting but then not Greek
speak but promoting what's in Greek speak, you
know Yeah, the reason I was talking to
someone says oh, I think you're better than
me I said, no, I'm not better than
you but my information and my knowledge definitely
is for sure What I know is better
than we what you know But I'm not
better.
You see if they can't just they can't
separate that right?
That's because they're stuck in the idolatry mode
What I mean by that is like, you
know When you when you have like a
football star or a movie star walk into
the room Mm-hmm.
That person is better than everyone else to
the pagan to the idolater, right?
They're everything about them is better.
So can I have your shoelace?
well, you know they find out where a
Movie star lives and they take some of
his grass or some of his bushes to
see that from his house, right?
This is the stupidity the idolater, you know
In other words the right proper thing is
this movie star?
Whatever probably makes more credits than you and
is more known and more liked than you
But he's not better than you but the
average human doesn't see it that way.
They're a star They're a god amongst men,
you know, I mean, you know, I'm talking
about like the president through or the whatever
Kardashians or I don't know what the hell
people or it does stupid shit.
They idolize these days They're not better than
you.
They have a better social position.
They have make more credits than you the
various things perhaps But they're not better.
They don't see it that way, right?
You see so right away when you start
Charlie they see what you're saying as a
chance they think right away Oh, you're not
worth being idolized You see no That's not
the point the point is do you see
You know a superior way of thinking a
superior way of eating a superior way of
speaking a superior way of acting or interacting
Why bother Separation is so much easier Yes,
but when you do interact with these idiots
make sure you have some follow-through meaning
right the follow-through means that when you
say like for example, the This is unlawful.
Do you have to tell them wives?
It's a lawful.
I don't do it.
No, never mind that you didn't They didn't
get that little red dot on them.
That's gonna you know, you're not making the
angels job any easier You know what?
I mean?
So the whole thing is to make the
the the Let them understand what's lawful and
unlawful.
So the angels get the green light like
hey, this guy's telling people what's off and
unlawful So they're done already.
We have the green light on these assholes,
you know what I mean?
Instead of we have to wait her but
this is already pre time.
I'm not saying that you're gonna change it
I'm just saying, you know, this is the
way it works, right?
I don't really get that opportunity at the
job So I Just stay separated from it
all at that point I don't think it's
an opportunity to be sought after but for
several reasons One is you know, you have
to interact with these idiots The other thing
is, you know, you might get to your
head thinking that what you're doing is More
correct to the point that now you really
start seeing them as inferior to you You
know, it's a very slippery slope.
It is it is no, I don't see
people as being inferior I see them as
being morons idiots scumbags assholes, whatever.
That doesn't mean they're inferior You see what
I mean?
That's it.
That's a deaf.
That's a character problem that they have in
other words You could rip out one person's
kidney.
Let's say if they have the same blood
type and put it in another they're not
inferior Right, right It's it's sad it's a
very sad state But the facts are this
is what it is that the higher on
a higher level and if you want to
get to the higher Level, which even makes
you want to separate even more is that
things are the way they are because of
divine beings period Right the people.
I mean, are you gonna blame a chess
piece For being on the wrong square No
But it does get taken off the board
though.
Oh You see it does it is the
one that's making the moves and Eliminated or
move forward.
That's people.
You're just chess pieces, but then again, I've
discussed the the finer aspects I believe of
what free will is Not ultra fine, but
finer aspects of it right, so You do
have free will enough.
In other words people know so little that
They know that they have free will based
on what they know In other words the
average human even a very smart human knows
so little about reality That that little that
they know which is a lot compared to
others Let's say it's still not enough to
let them know that there are constraints.
In other words, they don't know about the
gods They don't know real history.
They don't know how the mind works or
the body.
So they see everything as being random Even
if they're of higher education, let's say and
they feel like they have complete free will
or really you don't You see right?
so in other words Look, the people that
study scripture like to argue sometimes about is
there free will or is there not and
it's not an argument It's do let's examine
The aspects that listed in scripture for example
on what free will is now Let's examine
the aspects of what predestination is and then
reckon them together not oppose them one or
the other Like it says don't murder.
But how come there's so many death penalty
offenses if you're trivial and Uneducated you're gonna
see that as a schizophrenic psychotic thing You
see right, but if you're if you look
at it Why does it say don't murder
and then why does it say have a
death defense and you start analyzing?
You know it the scripture is not going
to tell you that they're opposing each other
or they're for each other just The two
realities co-exist Right, you see, you know
I mean, why is there an animal sacrifice
to be and why does it another place
to say anytime you even just touch a
dead animal?
You're unclean.
Well, how does that work out again?
Not just take one blunt side on educate
like the you know Religious people do or
even the academics are bluntly stupid like that.
That's why the people are stupid because they
look at those morons So and then once
you can ponder that and you could leave
everything that you think you know about it
at the door and start fresh Then you
start then you're on the path of what's
known as knowledge and wisdom Because the wisdom
is to be able to learn how to
regulate what you know And if it's useful
or useless towards this new learning path, that's
really the wisdom in it You know like
a fool would say well, I thought they
told me this in church.
So this subject is closed I know it
because they told me in church.
Well, that's a fool Right, it's right away.
He's using a foolish something that doesn't even
belong a Church, right?
This doesn't belong anywhere in the thing To
garner you see where a wise person would
say yeah, I know it's all I got
a star all over I go I got
to do when I have the time Where
I got I can't do it alone.
I have to do it with someone else
or I better make sure that I You
see get organized for it or whatever Most
people are too foolish you know, I Mean
they still have elections.
I mean, what a scam.
I mean you still have Christmas.
What a scam.
Yeah What a scam everything that they're doing
it look so having elections Yeah, and Thursday
that which is you it has to be
every Thursday because it honors Thor you slay
a winged beast Yeah, but the thing that
still because they just had what they called
the midterm elections in the US and all
over the world I'm sure in other places
that The very fact that the the governments
are having elections is like they're rubbing your
nose and shit and saying you are so
fucking stupid That it's been over a hundred
years since this has been a corporation and
we have these actors Right, which have no
value Running you as your leaders and your
demigods and we still you still think you
can vote you have no money.
No medicine.
No schools Demonology for religion.
I mean on and on and on and
you think you're gonna vote Wow Are you
screwed up?
That is beyond you couldn't write a fantasy
science fiction novel.
That is as bad as a horror movie.
It's that is what's going on Not just
in the US every country.
Yeah so Yeah, it's just yeah anyway Wow,
and they're just accommodating the moron and the
moron loves it.
That's all that's what I observe You know,
and the reason why they're a moron is
not relevant at this point because they ain't
gonna change You know why you fell off
the bicycle and scrap, you know why you
You know, you got a the child has
a you know What a scab on his
knee or whatever?
Well, it's not as important as treating it
once it happens, you know Did he get
it falling down the stairs or off of
the bicycle or he slipped on I so
whatever it is It not as irrelevant as
treating that so right now you see the
morons around you.
You can't treat them They're untreatable Right.
That's what I mean.
Now if you want to go back and
rehash how they got there You're gonna see
they're really untreatable.
Yeah, you see pretty much a close It's
a closed-loop thing.
It's just yeah, just put it out on
the curb Well for the garbage truck come
pick it up, which it will in 13
years or less Okay, I don't know if
there's anything else I mean that was the
good news I guess yeah, and it seems
to be very similar You know, why bother
and do what you like as long as
it's lawful You know and and it helps
you pass the time Thanks gents got any
good tips for making pierogi I do pierogies.
Yeah, that's like a dumpling.
Basically.
It's a Thanks, yeah pierogies I like You
can that's a flatbread recipe if you remember
the just Basically liquid and flour of some
type And a filling, you know roll it
out obviously and they let it relax roll
it out again and put your filling in
there use a appropriate cutter and Fold it
over pinch it roll it over and dunk
it in water and pierogies are very simple
Yeah, you get most of your flavors from
like dumplings and pasta You know things that
you cook in water and then strain out
of the water when the water is flavored
Like if I want to make a delicious
pasta You know like regular, you know, that's
different than rice because rice you're relying on
the absorption All the whatever flavor you put
in in rice water, let's say for cooking
when you Are finished with the dish?
There's no draining of the rice, right?
It's it's in fully the liquids fully incorporated,
right?
right, but when you're doing pasta or dumplings
or raviolis or Anything that's parboiled or anything
like that What you're doing is You're using
the water to cook it.
It's a wet cook, right?
Steaming can be done sometimes as well But
in this case the water the liquid will
impart flavor So what I do for example,
let's say I want to make a delicious
pasta whether it's store-bought dry pasta or
fresh pasta We you know, which means a
minute cooking two minutes cooking versus ten minutes
because it's dehydrated What I do is I
keep celery stalks around or cuttings from carrots
You know if I and I just throw
the veg the you just the celery stalk
you just break it So it fits in
the pot don't chop it up because then
you're gonna have to try to fish it
out But just throw it in the pot
throw put the water and that whatever you
put in there is gonna infuse flavor in
the pasta Like if you have if you're
doing a meat dish, you could throw bones
in there, right?
Lamb bones or whatever to infuse the water
with something, you know Vegetable is the best
for pasta.
So Another thing you can do is if
you have let's say an abundant amount of
sauce.
It's a doing a red tomato sauce Start
with a lower level of water in the
pasta throw a couple of tablespoons of tomato
sauce in the water or tomato paste and
Cook it like that and then add your
water have a kettle or another pot on
the side So as the pasta if it's
not fresh pasta Begins to cook you you
subsequently add more water to increase level, you
know, you always add hot water to hot
water, right?
so if you have a Let's say you're
cooking a stew or something need to add
more water Don't go over to the sink
or your bottled water and put cold room
temp You bring it up to temp and
then put it in right so it doesn't
disturb the cooking cycle, right?
It will taste different by the way.
I've experimented years ago.
Let's say you have a stew or something
cooking You know do an experiment when you
add the the non boiling water to it
or simmered water it will change the dish
So yeah hot to hot cold to cold,
you know temp It's a form of tempering
if you never if you're gonna add eggs
to a dish make sure they're a room
temperature or better You always add a tablespoon
of the hot liquid to the eggs whip
it again and then put them, you know
tempering You know have the meat in the
middle Instead of adding a cold liquid to
a hot or a hot to a cold
have them Gradually, you know meet in the
middle a little bit more than just shocking,
right?
Yeah, yeah most of the Anyone can learn
about cooking anything on what's called a recipe
Mentality, but I found that it's like one
of a thousand people are good at it
at cooking You know, is it talent?
Hmm?
I don't know Jack Fresco does that really
good with the drawing thing?
You know, you could take a five-year
-old and show them the technique of scale
And he draws like an artist everyone should
be doing because I see adults still try
to do sketches and looks like children It's
not to be blamed.
Well, how dare you know, it looks shameful.
You're an adult You can't drop but they
never got the training and the worst thing
you can do is the children when they
just do their four Five years old in
school.
They pass out crayons and draw.
What do you mean draw drawing is a
skill?
It's like they never they don't know what
the game of baseball is and they just
throw a bunch of bats and balls and
Gloves in the middle of the field go
play play what we don't know the rules
of the game.
What's going on, right?
We don't know we'll play what so when
they the worst thing is they give the
children the crayon paper draw and they draw
the Little stick figures and they pin it
up and they say oh great.
They're praising the child's ignorance No, you have
to show them what drawing is So the
same same thing with food you taught, you
know, I've said run into people, you know
They don't know about see they cook all
been cooking for years and actually work in
it.
They don't know about seasonality They don't know
about skimming off the top of liquids.
They don't know about tempering.
They don't know.
So what are you doing?
No, well, I don't know.
No one ever showed me Like wow, it
should be required within the society It should
be part of the common parlance whenever you're
communicating with someone or asking someone to do
something You should have also integrated somehow in
your society either even if it's written or
not some training for it Yeah, I was
always studies titles Yeah, I was always stunned
and amazed how little training you get to
do quote-unquote driving a car with you
know A car is a five three four
five thousand pounds of steel and glass hurled
down the road.
It's a weapon You know, it's a horrible
thing If it goes out of control and
the minute amount of training and the flakes
literal Flakes and and just insane people that
are allowed to do it.
It's just shocking You know, I used to
whenever it would I used to be on
roundtables with Seth on that idiot radio station
Whatever radio Not AFR the other one People
who come in with comments Greek, I always
wanna make a comment.
I don't agree.
But I said whatever the subject was Sometimes
I'd say do you do you drive a
car?
And they're like, yeah, I do.
I said well, that's freaking scary man There's
someone what that mindset is behind a wheel.
Never mind.
So what does that have to do with
blah blah blah?
It is it has a lot to do
with it It's scary that you're allowed to
behind the wheel of a car with that
kind of mindset so anyway Yeah, all right
with that said I'm gonna get back to
this little project here and I'll see you
guys next week unless there's anything else probably
not Some of what Cooking the cabbage any
longer.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cabbage is pretty strong.
It goes from sweet to rancid so But
no cooking the cooking the pierogies and cabbage
water would be yeah, it would be a
plus Especially if you've got it salted and
you have some fat in their vegetable fat
or animal fat like butter You know Interesting,
yeah, you could even Play around with nut
butters meaning sesame seed butter sunflower seed butter
They were tried if you like peanut butter
Put a volume button on a peanut butter
jar and turn the volume up to super
delicious That's sunflower seed butter ever had some
or almond butter I've had on experiment those
mm-hmm.
Yeah different.
It's not it's it's it's kind of bitter
Compared to peanut butter peanut butter is a
good all-around er you know when I
say vegetable fat would be a butter a
nut butter or You know you don't have
much choice other than oils after that and
then there's animal fats from dairy Which is
clean by the way, right?
It's a clean food, you know the beef
fat is not clean because it's dead right
then Adam Okay, thanks, okay.
Yeah, you have yourself a good night Greek.
Thank you very much next week next month.
Okay.
See ya