Greetings folks, we're live with the Greek.
And how you doing tonight, Greek?
Greetings.
Doing.
Yeah, as usual.
Yeah.
Another week has gone by.
I'm reckoning that's around the 16th or so
of the 8th.
Is that close enough for you guys?
Yes, I believe so.
Yes.
Yeah.
Thereabouts.
16th.
Yes.
Yeah, thereabouts might even be.
Yeah, I would say possibly the 17th, but
around the 16th.
Whether you're doing what they call Sunday, Monday
as the Sabbath.
Right.
Where is it?
Monday, Tuesday.
Right.
So if it's Sunday, Monday, it would be
the 17th.
Right.
So Monday to be this.
It would be early 17th, depending on where
you are.
Mm hmm.
Interesting book you had there that you posted.
I just got the audio book regarding.
Oh, yeah.
I spring regarding that today.
OK.
Wow.
That's something I did about 10 years ago.
I was looking into because this guy, Joe
Blankenship, was alive.
I could say he was a mentor to
a certain degree, but we hung around for
about a decade.
But after the first year, he was learning
more from me than I was from him,
even though he's twice my age.
But I know that sounds cocky.
But but he had this Joe Blankenship.
You spell it as this is a three
hour video where he's talking about his life
experiences.
He's done a lot of stuff in the
Southwest and in the West Coast.
Him and his brother got into a lot
of trouble doing just stuff in ingenious ways.
Yeah.
I got stories from that that he's told
me and and backed it up.
Yeah.
But his family has come from a family
of many brothers born in the 20s and
30s, and they all came down with polio.
And it wasn't polio at all, obviously.
Right.
Yeah.
So that stories about that.
And he knew there was something wrong with
that.
But he went along with the program because,
you know, when you're when you're really young
adolescent and you have a question, you ask
your parents.
Right.
There's no there's no Google or whatever.
So, yeah.
So you ask your parents and then they
go and ask the doctor who is clueless
also.
So, you know, whatever.
Right.
So.
But there were during that time period.
Oh, I would say as late as the
early as the 50s, as late as the
late 50s.
A panel of doctors at Congress talking about
the spring of insecticides is the cause of
polio.
You know, actually, this said that there's no.
Yeah.
But it's such a bizarre world.
So what else did you get?
Did you get a book?
Oh, God.
It's this country's a waste field from the
way it's way it's described and the toxicity
of everything.
I agree.
It unnerved me more.
I went to it just because it was
the amount of information.
Number one, which seemed she did a lot
of grunt work, that girl.
And yes, she did.
Yeah.
But it's a testament to the to the
robustness of the human body, how much punishment
it can take.
Yeah.
That's why the only way to really bring
the species down in, you know, is is
through psychological, spiritual, you know, where they start
killing each other and poisoning each other more
deliberately.
Good goal at that going.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
A supermarket food.
All pharmaceuticals, media.
Oh, you know, I think I've talked briefly
about how the chemical stuff is part of
the goddess religion that, you know, you can
see it.
Because it's the gender bending and even throughout
all cultures, the sorcerers or the ones, you
know, typically had wizards and witches mixing toxic
brews and things.
Right.
Typically, women were the poisoners, you know, to
administer it.
But this is not on a gender basis,
on a human gender basis.
This is on a spiritual basis as well.
She's into that, whatever it takes to distort
everything and take credit for it through through
justice.
Working overtime.
So, yeah, I used to, you know, I
never here's interestingly, I never got into activism
in terms of save the environment or the
vaccines, you know, causing, you know, destroying the
children and all that.
Fortunately, I studied scripture before I got I
studied that stuff, it almost in parallel.
So I knew, but from studying scripture from
an objective point of view, that the chief
God is going to come in and clear
out all the other gods.
Right.
But, you know, just like any political thing,
you have the people are too hardened to
repent.
So they have to go also.
Right.
So like when when you have to get
rid of a leader, you have to get
rid of the people as well, you know.
So the people have to go.
So how is that going to be done?
Well, you know, toxification.
Then I started realizing being around people actually
that had babies when I started studying now
that they're almost 20.
I realized that there turned out to be
scumbags just like their parents.
Not exactly a carbon copy.
But you know what I mean, right?
Almost the same.
So it's like, oh, it makes total sense
that they should toxify the children with vaccines
and all that.
Because it's not that the children are innocent.
It has nothing to do or guilty of
the innocent people.
How do they know who's innocent?
It's a numbers game.
And it's a it's a statistical, again, thing
where if the gods are going to go
and the people are being led by these
gods, the people got to go.
Because they're not going to go look at
your average religious person.
They don't study anything.
They don't know what's going on.
The real reality, you know.
Right.
So it's it's yeah, it's just a thing
you have to look at.
And don't go for the do it for
the children stuff.
They're just little people.
It's either people or not people.
You know, it's either people or not people.
You know, don't pull the children heartstring sympathy
bullshit, because they're just little miniature people are
going to grow up to be scumbags like
the bigger people.
So in general sense.
Right.
So the reason why I use that term
scumbag, it's an old Navy term.
I mean, someone who's new and doesn't know
what's going on kind of thing.
Right.
But you could use it.
However, you know, you know, they go from
scumbags to morons to professional assholes to professional
assholes.
Basically a typical human at this point.
It's about as misanthropic as you can get
on the Internet.
But either way, all this stuff makes perfect
sense, by the way.
Once you understand the big scheme, it just
doesn't mean, you know, the choices.
Is it for you or not?
You know, meaning you personally and your family,
let's say.
But the rest of them screw them.
That's this is this is made for them.
In other words, if it's not made for
you, it's made for someone else.
Right.
Just like when you go to buy clothing
or a car or whatever, you know, it's
not.
Well, you know what?
Do you have it in another color?
Why?
You saw lots of those.
Well, that color is not for me.
Right.
So it wasn't made for you in the
first place if you're not going to buy
it.
So it is a personal preference, you know,
and you separate yourself.
But the problem is you can't separate yourself
if you're an activist.
No, no, you can't.
You have to be into it.
Yeah.
Got to have your feet all the way
in.
Yeah.
That's a waste of time.
Activism.
Complete waste of time.
It belongs in the East.
Mm hmm.
I came up with that a long time
ago.
I was doing a sonic with some moron
out there and I opened the fridge to
get milk for coffee.
And I have some Red Star and Fleischmann's
yeast because I make my own bread.
Sure.
And it said active.
And I was like, oh, yeah, it's yeast.
That's about the only fundamental aspect of activism.
Right.
Yeah.
OK.
Any questions on the I'm not in front
of the computer right now.
We'll be sure to see anything going on
or nothing, really.
I mean, I know there's an email with
a lot of questions on it.
Keep them anonymous somewhere regarding previous sonics.
I think I did with Ocelli a couple
other things I mentioned.
I could actually answer most of the stuff
on the email without looking at it.
I also gave props to the gentleman that
was made the Greek speak dot com audio
boy.
His name was very nicely done or very
well done.
You should you should know who that is.
But I don't think I do.
I just haven't.
Yeah, I don't I don't endorse anything, by
the way.
Not even the chat or not even the
website.
I do.
There are people want to do it.
That's great.
I'm just surprised that it's being done somehow
to the point where, you know, it looks
like it might look good, like someone's putting
enough behind it.
So and it comes up right away in
searches, which is good.
Gets it right out there.
Very well done.
OK.
At least somebody is getting it all, which
is good.
You know, here's the thing.
There's enough people that have heard it and
actually done something with great speak that if
it were all end right now, it would
be a very high resultant factor.
You know, considering all of it.
I think there's over 50 or 100 people
that have actually done something they wouldn't have
done before or stop doing what they were
doing before either way because of Greeks.
So that's a lot more than anything that's
ever been done before in terms of the
real stuff, you know.
Right.
Versus the bullshit, you know.
Yeah.
It's basically food, clothing, shelter.
That's the bottom line.
Yep.
And remember, one third of the Earth's population
is fixed on scamming and pranking you.
So if, you know, basically one out of
three people you'll meet can't be trusted right
off the bat, not because of their character.
Well, their character has developed, but because of
their upbringing, their grooming, their mentality, their mindset.
Right.
And the other third are just, you know,
walking space heaters.
And the other third, you know, you might
be able to relate to on a very
superficial level.
That's a really bad profile for a population
on a planet, by the way.
One third being completely worthless, one third optional,
and one third being totally hell-bent on
pranking.
That's not a very good place to be,
by the way.
No, no, not either way.
Yeah.
Not very good.
But that's why, you know, there's no changing
it because the, in other words, the strength
of numbers and the strength of the, what
do you call it when someone's convinced of
something?
Conviction.
Right.
Behind this, what I just mentioned is so
strong, you know, the worthless ones versus the
optional ones versus the, not versus, but, you
know, along with the pranksters.
Their convictions are so strong that any form
of remediation or whatever is totally, you know,
futile.
So you have to navigate that way.
And, you know, the best is when you
get a concentration of the more positive, which
would be the optional ones, the ones that
have some sensibility and sensitivity.
You know, a disproportionate.
You don't want a proportionate slice of humanity.
Yeah, that would be the best way to
go.
So, anything else going on in the chat
there?
Not really what's seen here.
I can run past.
We had some music in there.
OK, well, on the email, from what I
recall, one of the initial questions was regarding
on the Ocelli thing I mentioned.
You know, why don't you look through a
crystal and see if you could see anything
latched onto your body, right?
Right.
And in the email, it was sort of
like a little bit going into that the
crystal that I somehow suggested was used for
healing purposes.
It's optical purposes only.
I never suggested that it would be for
any form of healing.
And that's what the New Agers do.
It's purely optical.
If you go back in history, quartz was
used for optics.
They're finding highly polished quartz telescope lenses all
over the world now.
But they're not reporting on it.
You could look it up.
I think the last one was a month
ago, somewhere in the Middle East.
And the one before that was somewhere in
Northern Europe, like the Vikings had telescopes.
I mean, like the stuff that Galileo would
have had or Newton, right?
Are you up to par with that or
better?
Yeah.
There's no healing.
So, part of the email was about, you
know, these people talking about using it for
healing.
It turns gray.
You can't use it.
No, no, no.
It's purely for optical.
Because I've said several times, you only see
what you see because it's coming and activating
a fleshy eyeball.
Right.
Spiritual beings don't have fleshy eyeballs, so they
can't see a red stop sign like you
do.
Right.
We don't know what they see unless they
tell us.
But they are able to communicate with us
about what we see because they somehow are
able to receive that.
Right.
So, in terms of healing and mitigating illness
or demonic oppression, which most illnesses are, by
the way, if I were to say all
illnesses are demonic oppression, it would be kind
of, I think, overboard.
But you could safely say that, by the
way.
But demonic oppressions and illnesses, crystals have absolutely
nothing to do with mitigating the condition at
all.
So that was the first several points in
the email about using them for that.
You can't.
Because we study the ancient writs again, healing
is done by another entity, and it's the
creator who sends it, right, or relieves you
of the oppressor.
Right.
So it has nothing to do with healing
at all.
So most of that part of that email
is moot regarding that.
I just wanted to address it that way
that, you know, again, very often I say
people are, you know, they try to listen
to what I'm saying, but you have to
match it up to what they've already learned,
and very often it's contrary to that.
Right.
And they store it as if I had
said something they already heard about, and it
wasn't at all.
Interesting that you could do that with a
crystal, though.
That still amazes me.
Well, any form of you could do it
with infrared and ultraviolet cameras as well.
Interesting.
Because you're not using the standard receptor of
the eye.
Right.
The standard visible light, anything that prevents, anything
that it prevents, anything that allows you to
see a spectrum, spectra, the visible, normal visible
light, meaning bright light and dim light or
whatever, you know, like, for example, a manipulation
of that would be looking through a form
of quartz, which is crystal, which is not
glass, which is liquid, by the way.
Yes, glass is a liquid, you know, even
though it appears to be solid, it acts
like a liquid.
That's why you have antique glass at the
cathedrals.
It's thicker at the bottom than it is
at the top because it's flowing, right?
Right.
So the aspect of using ultraviolet and infrared,
sonogram is another way to do it.
It doesn't mean that you're going to have
success with any of those.
It is just something that I brought up
with Chuck.
Because I always like here, I call it
picking on pagans, P-P, P-O-P,
pop.
These guys that think that they're, you know,
most people say that they're pagan or whatever
because they just don't want to be part
of the mainstream, but they don't know anything
any more than, it's a pop culture type
thing.
They're pretty ignorant.
Paganism is just deifying the material world.
That's all it is, it's materialistic.
I never got into talks about that because
why?
People are immersed in it.
You want me to tell you what you're
doing?
Yeah, we could.
You know, you meaning what's in the society.
Right.
They're just materialists.
They don't know anything about the spiritual world
unless they're ready to do barter with some
demon.
You know, I'll do this for you, you
do this for me, right?
It's an exchange.
So, but that's more on the evolved end
because now they're actually tampering.
You know, the word to be utilitarian and
to be tampering on camera looks the same.
You know, utilitarian means you're doing it the
right way, tampering is you're not, right?
Right.
You know, like they have tamper-proof seals
on a, let's say, bottle of something, you
know, medicine.
Why?
You're not supposed to open it anyway?
Of course you're supposed to open it and
take it.
But tampering is when it's done in a
way that it's not supposed to be done.
Right.
Malicious.
So the best a pagan is going to
do is tamper with the spiritual world and
they're ignorant.
So that's actually what the word means.
Not a good combination to be doing that.
Oh, no.
So I always like to bring up stuff
like that just to contrast what real knowledge
is versus the pop stuff that people are
spewing out of their mouth.
Yeah.
Not because I have real knowledge, but, well,
first of all, well, I do only because
I'm not as lazy as the rest.
You know, you have to work on it.
You have to work on a principle, then
you have to work on what's been memorialized
about it, and then you have to see
if it matches.
And not make it match, not whittling anything
down, just seeing if it fits.
Right.
So another one of the questions from memory,
I should go into the office soon here,
is that regarding, I think, towards the bottom
was, it's very interesting, I remember the top
of the email and the bottom of the
email, underground bases and things like that.
I guess DUMBs, D-U-M-Bs are
underground bases, right?
Right.
Back in the East Coast, like in the
area of Brooklyn, there's DUMBO, which is the
Down Under Manhattan Bridge Organization, right?
It's an area, but when I see that,
I have to remember which one it is.
But there's a fellow up in Breckenridge, Colorado,
actually, I'm not going to say anymore because
I just narrowed it down really well, that
is involved, it still is, making underground bases.
And since the late 90s, they're building them,
they, you know, the owners of the governments
via the government, because you're going to use
government slaves, right?
Right.
So when you want to make mud bricks,
you use pharaoh's slaves, let's say.
They've been building them nonstop every year at
a rate of 3 million square feet per
year, like very deep underground, you know, miles,
you know, a mile plus.
There was an article about who controls underneath
the ground, and it was a topic.
Don't want to know.
Yeah.
And I think it was very well done.
It was very well done.
Well, they're guided by real knowledge that you
shouldn't be on the surface based on the
conditions.
But they've somehow evaded the aspect that if
you do that to evade the conditions on
the surface, you still won't survive.
Actually, you'll wish you were on the surface.
Enormous operation.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Serious, serious stuff.
When they're digging underground, they'll break through tunnels
that were built prehistoric anyway.
I mean, big, large ones.
Right, right.
Yeah.
So, no, in terms of the mentality, the
mindset is that every day is your last
without the panic, right?
Right.
Because, in other words, there's no future in
the stuff that you've been told the future
is about.
In other words, futurism, where you have a
progressive culture that evolves into higher forms of
existence, that's not going to happen.
It's been all downhill since before Victorian times.
By the way, has anyone looked into what
was going on with Victorian?
Yes.
I saw a couple of videos on the
servers about the Victorian servants.
There was a BBC documentary.
It was filled with a little Brown 25
in there.
But the overall discourse of the conversation was
very well done, gave a lot of history.
It was in a good time.
Well, there's a lot of stuff that was
going on with the medical and political, banking
and industrial community that you would downright now,
which was openly discussed.
But now, even with this, civic society would
be considered downright immoral.
That was openly done back then.
So they kind of made a collective awareness
of what will transfer over to the next
century and omitted most of it in public
view, but it's still going on.
Like if you get into any of the
baby farms at all, or any of the
using human corpses for medicinal purposes, it was
very widespread, by the way, even in children's
candies.
The way the courts, the star chambers were
working and the medical community, the way that
worked.
So when you study Victorian times, you know
that World War I or World War II
was a blessing to clear out a lot
of that garbage and start another form of
system.
In other words, if you're still living in
Victorian times, you would have human body parts
and snacks listed on the ingredients, literally, openly.
But you still have Child Protection Services, which
is basically the children farming, and most of
that stuff is still in there, but that's
when the sovereign state concept became worldwide.
In other words, let's stop this Napoleonic, which
was the last imperial mindset.
Let's stop the imperial mindset and figure out
various systems of what they call modalities of
government, like socialism, democracy.
Republics were in place, but they were bullshit,
because they were put in place by attorneys,
if you know what I mean.
Whatever, communism, whatever, and they'll just be corporations,
and we're going to own them using paperwork.
I had a discussion recently with an academic.
I said, if you go to the third
grade and you write proper nouns in all
caps, you fail and you won't make it
to the fourth grade.
But every government form is all caps.
In other words, nothing in the government goes
past the third grade level.
It's all improper, because it's not – in
other words, what's going on, it's purely commercial.
Have you ever seen forms for credit cards
or these shopping cards or in schools where
they ask you to write the name and
every letter goes into a box?
That has nothing to do with them being
able to delineate whether you wrote it right
or what each letter is.
They've been doing that in the schools since
the 70s, really.
It started in earnest, really, in the 80s,
everywhere, for sure.
Those tests that they used to give.
Yeah, that's part of the CUSIP system, the
Convention of the Universal Securities and Investment Protocols.
So whenever you see the name or information
in those little boxes where each letter has
to go in a box, that's the Convention
on Universal Security and Investment Protocols.
That means that action, that act, it's called
an act or an action, the filling out
of the form is being monetized.
In other words, they're using credit.
They're turning it into credit.
It gets a value on it.
I've actually tried to explain this to even
people that were retired bankers and they didn't
get it.
And like a year later, I speak to
them.
They're like, oh, yeah, I looked up what
you said.
It's all true.
And I'm like, man, you worked for Goldman
Sachs for 30 years and you didn't know
that, huh?
Wow.
What are you doing?
You could be replaced by a robot or
machine.
Easily.
So there's so much to talk about.
I mean, here's the thing.
I'll say years ago when I was on
AFR, I was like, oh, yeah, we'll do
a private call.
We'll talk about more stuff in private, a
few members thing if you want to join.
And I was like, after a while, I
started saying to myself, who am I going
to tell this to?
There's only like five people that can hear
it because all the people that work as
professionals in these fields don't know it.
How is the common person going to know
it and how are they going to use
it?
So why bother?
You know what I mean?
Right.
So then it's like, oh, just relegate oneself
to just, you know, going a day to
day basis.
If you get past this food, clothing and
shelter and good company, you're way ahead of
the pack.
That's right.
And the good company part, learn to love
animals and learn to love who, you know,
knows about what love really is.
All right.
So there's a course.
Here we go.
Healing with magnets.
Nothing really on healing with magnets because you
have to learn how a magnet really works.
It's not north or south pole.
There's a vortex that goes right through the
magnet spinning the same way.
It gives the illusion that there are two
poles and there's a block wall.
It's called a block wall, B-L-O
-C-H, or an inertial, dielectric inertial plane,
as Ken Wheeler says.
All right.
That you need to avoid to get the
effects of a magnet.
So magnets are very subtle.
Yes, there could be healing, but I have
not investigated and neither do I have a
desire to at this point.
Three bloodlines in Genesis.
You mentioned during the chat with Achille, would
you be willing to give more explanation?
Not really, because eventually you're going to have
to make it evidentiary, and I don't know
any of the three bloodlines physically or anyone
that I can invite over to speak about
it.
But essentially there are writings about you have
the Adamic line and then the hybrids with
the Adamics, and then we don't know if
there are any survivors of those that were
before Adam.
Right.
We have to presume there weren't.
I suppose it could be a 50-50
chance if you took care of the wives.
Right.
And then there's a fourth one, which is
the hybrid with those, the hybrid with the
Adamic, the sixth day man.
Right.
Potential.
I think we'll know more about that on
a need-to-know basis as time comes
around.
But it's good to be aware of it,
so if anything pops up anomalous, you're like,
oh, yeah, I know there are four bloodlines
potentially, but three most likely.
Right.
So the vast seas under the crust of
the Earth.
Remember you mentioning them in relation to earthquakes.
How many?
Formation and genesis.
Yeah, that's a water.
Earth is mostly water, by the way.
There is no molten core, by the way,
and there is no magma.
There's heat under there.
Yeah, it's water.
It's all water, all the way down.
And then it inverts like a sphere, like
a clay pot.
Think of a terrestrial clay.
I like to call it terra more than
earth.
But imagine everything inversing, and you're walking on
the surface of a terracotta sphere, and there's
a hole at the top or somewhere, and
you walk inside.
And then you walk along the inside upright,
but you're upside down compared to the people
on the other side.
Right.
Yeah, it's not a hollow earth theory.
It's really how it is.
So let's see.
In terms of genesis and all that, well,
it's a need to know again.
We're not given any information on the formation
of the planets, really.
No.
We have no information on that.
Chronicles.
Book of Chronicles.
Parallels between Queen Sheba's visit to Solomon and
the Magi's visit to the Messiah.
Sort of.
Not really parallel.
Not much to expand on.
And Sheba is not Egypt, by the way.
That's on the other side of the Nile.
So that's one thing I could put out
that most people presume that it's Egypt.
I would say that the Magi are higher
in authority than the Queen and King, by
the way.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So Solomon would be on par with the
Queen, but the Magi would not.
Solomon would have been shaking in his pants
if they showed up, and so would Sheba's.
So, the resistor that is on the stars,
would that be more creator-binding spiritual entities?
I'm not sure what that means, but the
stars don't really exist unless you have something
to see them through, like an atmosphere.
Right.
Like what Eric Dollar says, they're basically like
transformers.
You know how transformers work?
You've got two coils, right?
Right.
OK, so no one can explain how it
goes from one coil to the next.
You know, whether it's an I-core or
an E-core, you know, the core, the
laminations?
Sure.
I didn't give a background on what I'm
talking about, but if you guys look up
how electrical transformers work, no one can explain
how the voltage goes from one coil to
the next.
From the primary to the secondary, yeah.
They call it induction, but there's far more
to it, I would think.
Yeah, but how?
Because the way they explain it, all the
loops are captured within the iron core, the
laminations, regardless of the shape.
It's an I-core and an H-core.
Yeah, but still there's no explanation of how
it goes over.
So, you know, but even with saying that
it's a transformer, it only becomes a transformer
with an atmosphere, or a device that allows
some kind of filtering.
Right.
You can't see stars or the sun with
the naked eye in what they call space.
So let's see.
The weather devices you used last week, you
mentioned if you leave them unattended longer than
20 minutes, they're ignored.
By who?
Oh, the ether will ignore it.
If you think of just a hollow tube
that's grounded, which would be the most basic
form of affecting the atmosphere, atmospheric ether, if
you look at the rooftops of many houses
with plumbing, you have something called a vent
pipe that sticks out on the roof.
So, you know, you've got millions of these
weather devices sticking out of houses, you know,
of houses in the country everywhere, it would
be screwing up the weather if the ether
didn't.
But I assure you that if you're around
a building where they're building these ticky-tacky
houses, subdivisions, or someone's putting up a house,
the moment the plumbing goes in and the
vent stacks go in, there's a slight weather
change if you follow the weather every time.
And then it's ignored.
Hmm.
So, this is something you won't find in
any of Reich's writings, or this is post,
you know, this is developing, this is post
-Reich, post, you know, late Trevor James Constable.
Yeah, there's nothing about this.
The water pipe in the lake, I think,
was the example on that one.
Sure, but if you leave it there long
enough without movement at all, let's say you
were to cement it in place, yes, you
would have a radical effect initially, and maybe
subsequent, you know, effect, plural effects, for a
little while, and then it just no longer
has any.
Right, because if you think of it as
a form of dielectricity or dielectric, once you
establish short, the pathway is established, right?
Yep, and that's it.
Right.
Equalized.
So, yeah, it either establishes a short and
the pathway is broken or it's established, right?
You know, like if you drop a wrench
over a car battery, the part that touches
vaporizes, and if you don't move it, it
won't short anymore because it's vaporized.
Or if you maintain the short, it will
completely short out the battery and then go
back to some form of stasis, right?
Right.
And nothing else will happen after that.
It'll be ignored.
You know, you'll have a pile of molten
plastic and liquid everywhere, and say, what's that?
Oh, that was when the battery laid on
the wrench.
It kept the contacts going.
Yeah, just ignore it.
There's nothing going on with it now anymore
because it burned out.
Or it didn't burn out, it just blew
up the wrench, and if you leave the
wrench there for, yeah, if you leave it
there for 20 years, you'll say, oh, just
ignore that.
Dropped a wrench in 0.2 milliseconds or
microseconds, it vaporized, and there it is.
So it's the same thing.
Think of it as how dielectrics work.
When I mean dielectrics, I mean electricity.
Right.
It's, you know, these are subjects that are
easier to answer when you're on the subject,
but I figured I'd bring them up because,
you know, when you start throwing out stuff
like that with someone who's listening, what is
he talking about?
I don't know anything about electricity.
Right.
Or, you know, these paths and things, but
just throw them out there.
So the who is the what?
The ether, or the system, meaning the system
that we call weather or space.
Well, space has no attributes, but the ether,
we should use that term.
Do you feel that there's many levels to
the ether?
Manifestations.
We don't know enough about the ether to
say that there are, yeah, but there are
manifestations.
Like if there's ether that keeps things living,
if you set up, let's say, a power
grid for electricity, is that energy that's living
energy?
No, it's not.
As a matter of fact, if it's AC
and you touch it, it'll kill you, right?
And then you have the water attracting the
ether or ether attracting water.
Well, is that living or not?
Not really.
Is water necessary for living beings after the
fact?
Yes.
So that's why it's easy to categorize its
manifestations.
But it's all the same ether.
Because there is parity with the human body
and electricity.
You know, there's electricity.
Sure.
The difference between a metabolism and no metabolism,
which is a dead body, is the presence
that's measurable of electricity.
A dead body will actually still give off
electricity, but it's towards decomposition.
Right.
Chemical.
I bet if you took a cadaver and
you stuck a copper pole up his ass
and one down his mouth, you'll have a
voltage going across it.
Yeah.
You know, the two wet sides, you know.
Used to have conductors.
Something going.
Just like a potato, right?
When you put two nails in a potato
and a voltmeter.
Right.
So that may be that analogy of electricity,
but it's the type of electricity again.
Okay.
Ethiopian dam.
The project was murdered a few months ago.
I wonder if you had any insights on
the project.
Not really.
Future political insight.
Well, water.
Anything with water is bad right now.
In other words, what people are being told
is that you're running out of water.
And it's limited resource, like oil, you know,
or air.
And these are things that are constantly being
renewed by the environment.
And so, yeah.
Manifestation of a new prank.
Remember, the A1 agenda of the world controllers,
whether it's Imps, Demons, or Sons of Gods,
is to eliminate as many people as possible.
And there's many reasons for it.
One is, you know, I think out of
their own honor, like when their time is
up, it'll be revealed on what's going on.
So the fewer people that are around, they'll
be less shameful.
You know these Gods and Demons?
Right.
They'll be less ashamed because people will be
able to see them.
So if you get rid of them, they're
hoping that they won't be resurrected kind of
thing.
I mean, there's an entire, you can cast
a broad sense of reasoning why the hostile
entities, spiritual entities, want to see the population
go down.
Because, you know, they're not very familiar.
They know about the resurrection.
I don't know how much they trust or
know about that everyone will be resurrected.
So they figure if they get rid of
as many people as possible, by inspiring others
to do so, right, they won't, you know,
you don't need to, right?
If you want to, you just go to
the guy in charge.
That's why a lot of times people, like,
Greek, I went to this company and they
didn't really do what you said.
I said, well, you're speaking too low on
the totem pole.
You got to go higher.
Right.
See?
So the top guy can push a button
or direct others to, right?
So these entities, again, you tie it in
with water, energy, petroleum, food, yeah.
But the whole thing is you have to,
if you're going to, even people, you know,
there's something called a Judas goat.
People who run farms and ranches, you know,
cows, before they're slaughtered, they go through long
ramps and labyrinths, right?
Right, right.
Yeah, so, yeah.
Yeah, and remember, I've said for many years
and a long time, people are unrehabilitatable, you
know?
Right.
And it's like when you go to a
club and you're not invited, the guy says
you can't come in.
Then if you ask the guy, well, where
do I go?
He says, I don't care where you go.
Right.
You just can't come in here.
So the new society that's going to be
on this planet, there's no room for most
of the, it's not a place for most
of the people that are alive now.
I know it sounds kind of crazy, but,
yeah.
But that's the truth.
Right.
So, and there's no hotel on the moon,
you're not going to be accommodated.
So, and either way, whether you look at
what they call the new world order, what
they're planning for the future of humanity, or
the, you know, revealing the spiritual world, you
know, with the end of days.
Either way, the future society, there's no room
for the people that are here now.
You see?
Right.
So even if the gods weren't returning, there
is no room for the future society that,
let's say the Illuminati, Freemasons, or the powers
that be want for the future.
There's no room for the people that live
today in that world.
And also there is no room for the
people that, in the future world of when
the gods return.
I mean, just look at how, you're going
to have to actually, you know, completely redo
their minds.
And, you know, but they have the resurrection.
That's the positive side about it.
Everyone has the resurrection.
So, either way, the current mindset in the
humans, for the majority of the humans, there's
no place, there's no future for them.
Either secular or spiritual.
So either way, you know, it's locked.
You know what I mean?
Right.
It's kind of like the bridge is out,
and you're not going to make it across
because the bridge is out.
You can, whether, well, if I go fast
enough, can I jump the gap?
No.
And if I stop and don't go over
the bridge, you're not going anyway.
So, yeah, the bridge is out, folks.
So, yeah, to the future, for most people.
There's no bridge to the future.
And it's just part of the reality of
the days that you're living in.
Saying such things 100 years ago, actually, it
would have been popular with the Millerites in
the middle 1800s, when you convinced a group
of people it was the end of the
world on a certain date, you know, using
the Pope's work schedule and some bullshit prophecy
stuff, prophecy interpretations.
Christians, of course, you know.
Okay.
Regarding solar noon and the length of the
evenings, I've been recording solar noon intermittently as
the weather has allowed since you mentioned it.
I've noted swings around the 12 noon mark.
Marissa Grado, okay.
This is a rather long description here about
measuring noon.
Okay.
Now, you can measure it, but it doesn't
really tie in with anything else, like the
clock or anything.
Of course, no, because it's observational.
All right.
Thanks for answering these queries.
Okay.
Well, thank you for asking.
You know, I was invited once to speak
to some people, let's say, okay, about time.
Someone, I should say, someone asked me, can
you come speak to my men regarding time?
And I said, okay.
So he said time, and I went over
there, went into a place, which was inside
of another place, which was inside of another
place, which a bunch of guys there that
were trained to do certain things, which is
certain things that, you know, pretty much you
could drop them off anywhere in the world
to do things kind of thing.
And I just talked to them about time.
I really wanted you to talk to, you
know, you to explain to them.
So the first thing I said to them
was, do you know that the sun rises
and the sun sets exactly the same time
every day?
Right.
And they were bewildered.
They were like, I could see in their
eyes, no, because in the summer it rises,
you know, if you're in the southwest at
5 a.m., and in the winter it
rises at 637.
So what are you talking about?
One guy got it, and I said, okay,
I see you got it, but you can't
explain it.
He says, yeah, I kind of see what
you're saying.
Well, how do you know it's sunrise?
That's sunrise.
Right.
How do you know it's sundown?
That's sundown.
And sunrise happens exactly the same time every
day, and sundown happens exactly the same time
every day.
You get it?
Yes, I do.
Right.
So noontime happens exactly the same time every
day.
Mm-hmm.
Chew on that for a while.
Okay.
Sunrise happens exactly the same time every day,
because how do you know it's sunrise?
Well, that's sunrise.
Right.
Noontime happens exactly the same time every day.
How do you know it's noontime?
Well, because sun is directly overhead, there's no
shadow east or west.
Right.
Every day it's exactly the same time.
And now sundown happens exactly the same time
every day.
How do you know?
Because it's at sundown.
Right.
Okay, now once you use those three aspects
only for time, then you will start to
see how other things can be revealed within
that scope.
What you'll be relying on is shadows, markers,
landmarks, positions in the sky.
The Book of Enoch talks about gates in
the horizons.
Sort of, yeah.
I think there's a better translation for gate,
but that's good enough.
A gate is a place that you come
in and out of.
He was very specific about that.
It's one of these, yes, and also intercalation,
which I've found to be lost in interpretation,
whether it was accurate or not.
It was pretty close.
I haven't really looked at specifically what I've
recorded.
I've gotten really loose on recording, keeping records
the past few years.
Actually, since I've been really vocal, maybe eight
years ago I was pretty tight on the
records.
Now I'm not at all, because it's an
internal thing for me, and I know when
the feast days come around, I know what
they're about.
But I do know real time, right?
I do know what real time is, or
lawful time.
See, that's the thing.
Do you know it?
And picking up a form of record keeping
where you can, I don't know, I wouldn't
say make mandates, because what are you going
to do?
Tell people, well, today's the first day of
the seventh month.
People, what are you going to do?
You're in a headlight look.
It's about the only thing you're going to
get.
You're not going to get anything done with
it, but you know it at least.
Right.
That's why food, clothing, shelter, preparing meals really
well, understanding what quality food is about, clothing,
dressing yourself.
Well, we never discussed food, like eating seasonally.
We never discussed seasonal clothing.
You ever notice that?
Oh, yeah.
And shelter, we haven't discussed a lot either
about seasonal and all that.
Because shelters, I've noticed, architects, like psychiatrists, are
pretty fucked up in the head.
Use that medical term.
They're a pretty screwed up guy.
I like what people, I mean society, within
society.
I like what Fresco says in one of
his lectures.
He shows all the city.
He says, well, think of the city skylines.
That's not order.
That's utter chaos, and it's ugly.
It's total chaos.
It's all ego.
Each time you see a building, it's someone's
ego.
And there is no ego, meaning they're expressing
their mark on society, manifesting and building.
But in terms of clothing, you know how
you acclimate, for example, when you go to
the beach or water, and it feels cold
initially?
You kind of jump in, and then you're
in the water, and it doesn't feel so
cold.
We're not talking about water so cold you
get hypothermia.
Right.
You acclimate and adjust.
You acclimate and get adjusted, yes.
It's best to, like, for example, here in
the American Southwest, it's turning into winter or
late fall.
It's a beautiful fall.
Yeah, I noticed that you lost a little
cold air coming your way.
Oh, yeah, because of the rains.
And also, since that hurricane left, I pulled
out a couple of more translators and set
them up, and I haven't moved them since.
And it's taking over a week and a
half, but it's drawing the entire jet stream
from the Northwest.
And this is the best time of year
to do it.
And you can see, it just comes down
and then goes exactly right into the translator.
I mean, exactly where the translator is aimed.
So I have one West and one Southwest.
It must have been a smoother way, too,
I think.
I think North.
Yeah, it was North, yeah.
It was a good cold, though.
Well, with clothing, you kind of do the
opposite.
When the winter is coming, in other words,
I would rather overdress now while it cools
down than not, right?
So in other words, more clothing.
But even also in summer, you're always better.
Here's the simple thing about clothing.
You're always better prepared or slash overdressed than
underdressed.
Right.
Because it's easier to take off a layer
or a jacket than to put one on
when you don't have one.
Or if you can have it.
So the idea here is to – and
it also has to do with age.
You know, parents always tell their children, you're
underdressed, and the children are not because they're
older.
And as you get older, you have less
tolerance for cold, right?
Yep.
But still, the rules with clothing are very
simple.
It's easier to take off a layer than
to put one on that you don't have
available.
You know, so if you have, for example,
a motorized, engine-driven wagon, you know, a
minivan, let's say.
I have a little box in the back
where I have, you know, bottled water, biscuits,
flat tire fix-it stuff, first aid kit,
bungee cords, rope, knife, oil, transmission fluid.
And I have a cotton sweatshirt and one
of these Anorak, like, windbreakers with a hood
that comes out, right?
The hood that's – okay?
And that's in there all the time.
So if I'm ever anywhere that the temperature's
too low, well, I've got a layer I
could put on, and I've got an oversized
windbreaker with a hood.
And there's also gloves.
And it's always in there all year round
because I would rather – you see?
Yep, very smart.
Yeah, so you always do – and I'm
in the desert where, you know, it's hot
usually.
But, you know, desert, you could have 40
-degree Fahrenheit temperature difference between day and night,
which is – Easily.
That's why if you go anywhere in a
desert area city, you'll see sidewalks that are
buckled and bridges that are twisted, you know,
footings because, you know, the amount of thermal
expansion and contraction.
Right.
Okay.
So the rule for clothing is always better
off having more clothes than you think you
might need because you could strip down and
– okay.
Got it?
Very simple.
And the shelter part to get into –
the reason why I mentioned architects are such
scumbags is because they don't understand the subtleties
of orientation.
There's several subtleties with it.
For example, when houses are being built and
you have the house facing the street, you'll
have the bedroom on one side and then
the car garage on the other, right?
If the house is facing the street, let's
say, front door in the middle, living space
in the middle.
Well, when they have a house next to
it, it should be a mirror image so
you have garage to garage and bedroom to
bedroom.
Right.
Right?
Most of these houses are not built that
way.
Most of these houses that you see through
America are a house – you look at
the front of it, you see the entrance
door on the left, you know, and you
go into the living space and the bedrooms
are on that side, garage on the right
or either way.
And the next house next to it is
the same.
It's not a mirror image.
So you have the garage next to the
bedroom side.
So if someone has a straight pipe, cherry
bomb muffler or a Harley Davidson early in
the morning or coming late at night, they
will hear it on the bedroom side of
the house next to it.
You see?
So it should be mirror image.
It should be the garage against the garage,
you know.
You got it?
The house should be mirror image.
So an orientation would be preferential in a
way but not necessarily like you don't want
bedrooms on the east side, bedroom windows on
the east side unless you have people that
are early risers or you should have them
on the – bedroom windows on the east
side because when the sun rises, it lets
the inhabitants know, well, get up.
It's time to get up.
All right.
So you guys ever watch Boondocks on Uncle
Ruckus?
I have not, no.
It's actually kind of harsh to say, well,
I get up anyway at 5 in the
morning, which is about six hours before most
N-I, the N-words do.
So it's just really – you got to
watch it.
Yeah, Uncle Ruckus, Boondocks.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just a trip.
It's beyond – it's beyond like – Okay.
I used to – I have their DVDs
and when I used to have a bunch
of white people over, I used to put
it on and watch them.
This is not politically correct.
Yeah.
Okay.
So anyway, having the eastern side bedroom, right,
and then you have the western side living
room, you're going to get harsh light coming
in at sundown, very harsh light.
So all these things have to be considered.
Now, if you're in a mountainous, forested area,
maybe it doesn't matter.
The other aspect about orientation is are you
actually building the house over what are called
ley lines and things like that, which is
a whole other thing that is almost difficult
to even consider now because what do underground
metal pipes and electrical wiring do to those
ley lines, right?
Yeah.
One aspect of me ethereally would say eventually
nothing because they're so well formed that eventually
they'll be disturbed, let's say, if you run
an underground trench with metal in it, but
eventually I think it returns.
It could be mitigated if you look at
Ibrahim Karim's work with biogeometry.
He says he can mitigate them.
And then, of course, there's materials in homes,
what they call…
Have you noticed you're a homeowner or a
home loan, but never a house owner?
You ever notice that in English?
Yeah, because there's no money to buy anything,
right?
So it's all in your mind.
Yeah.
It's amazing how much when you learn the
language it's there.
But most people's houses they live in are
toxic, especially the ones that are less than
20 years old, especially when I used to
be more social.
I used to run into people that had
young children and themselves.
They acquire a house, and it was fairly
new, and they all came down with allergies.
And I said, well, why don't you leave
the windows slightly open?
Your heating and cooling will cost a little
more, but your allergies will go away.
And they reported back to me, yeah, exactly.
We all feel better now.
Yeah, it's $20 more a month in electricity
or $40 more, but it's worth it.
It's cheaper than going to the devils in
the white lab coats, you know, the doctors
for drugs.
And so what's going on?
I said, all that carpeting and all that
material, that chipboard, all that stuff is toxic,
and it's outgassing, and it will be outgassing
for a long time.
So what do we do?
I said, pull all the carpeting out and
just paint the concrete floors.
And all the cabinetry, countertops, anything that's that
particle board stuff, you need to remove it
and seal the back of it.
You get a really good sealer, you know.
So there's no exposed particle board anywhere.
And a lot of them, actually a couple
of people that have done that, and they
said, yeah, it's much more breathable now.
Well, in the winter months, you close up
the houses, and boy, you can still use
it.
Yeah.
You still should have it ventilated if it's
a new house.
Now, the irony of it is, is the
older houses, if you live, they're leaky.
You know, like the windows didn't really shut
well, you know, and they're leaky.
You know, old houses, you know, if you're
living in a 100-year-old house or
50 years or more, it's a leaky house.
You know, people, you know, they don't pass
energy, inspect your single pane windows.
Actually, those are actually more healthful because they
ventilate any of the modern.
If you have particle board furniture, it'll ventilate
better in a leaky house, an old house,
than it does in a new house.
So Hilda Clark used to say that people
who lived in mud floor huts were much
healthier than people who lived in developed communities.
Well, if you really want a good example,
just get yourself a very high-powered light
and shine it in your house at night.
And just look at the air.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah.
I have a fan that's always a small
fan exhausting in the office through a screen,
and I have to clean it every three
days because you can see all the buildup
on the screen.
And I prefer it that way.
24-7 over at my place all year
round.
There's a little fan that vents out the
window.
It costs a little more energy, but well
worth every penny.
And it's probably more particulate pollution than if
you were living out in the forest.
Yep.
Yeah, because I remember trekking through wild lands
in the past with a flashlight.
I didn't see as much dust as I'd
see in the house, right?
And then the new homeowners have to contend
with how much pesticides were sprayed in their
yard prior to their arrival and ownership.
You've just got a whole mess of stuff
that you'll never know.
Well, again, separate yourself from it.
Water is a good agent to get rid
of that stuff.
I think that a drastic reduction of sympathy
towards what's going on is the best.
In other words, when people get sympathetic or
get into the activism thing or whatever, that's
the wrong thing to do.
The thing to do is to be proactive.
It's not going to stop.
No, no.
It's not going to go away.
So, you're a stranger in a strange land.
You know, if you're a stranger in a
strange land, are you going to start making
waves about how things should improve?
Nope.
Hell no.
How are you going to protect yourself from
it?
That's the bottom line.
Because ultimately, the destruction, whether it's slow or
quick, is well deserved, number one.
Number two, it's inevitable.
And number three, it's not for you.
So, if you start telling people, well, this
is poisonous, didn't you know that, or whatever,
now you're screwing up their calm.
And they're already being messed with, so now
you're messing with them, you know?
Yeah, it's pretty interesting how the worldview is
so far removed from what is really going
on in the world.
Yeah.
Stranger in a strange land would be, wasn't
that a book?
Who wrote that?
Anyway, someone.
It harkens back to something of antiquity, which
is more than 50 years ago, right?
Okay.
So, anything else going on, or we should
wrap it up here?
I was just looking up that book.
And let's see what we got here.
Stranger in a strange land, 1961.
Mm-hmm.
Fiction, Robert Hewin.
Okay, there you go.
Yeah, I grew up reading books.
When I was a young child, there was
actually a library in the house, and I
was able to, when I was grounded, I
just locked myself in there and read books.
At nine years old, I read My Secret
Life, which is, have you ever heard of
that book?
I have.
It's a very torrid, pornographic almost, it's about
900 pages long, bizarre, about a man's encounters
with all these women, and the way he,
you know, erotic encounters, you know.
Mm-hmm.
So, you know, adults would open the door
and say, look, he's reading, you know, and
I'm like, what is, what is, you know,
what is he talking about?
Oh, okay, I mean, sex ed, you know,
before there was.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
So, anyway.
I'm surprised you heard of My Secret Life.
Not many people have.
I have.
It was a bizarre.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
A couple of other torrid things of antiquity.
When I say antiquity, you know, most people,
believe it or not, you know, like say,
you know you're old when most people around
you are younger than you, and you know
you're young when most people around you are
older than you, right?
Right.
So, now wherever I go, I see most
people are younger.
So, you know, like when you were young,
you look around, oh, we all want to
grow up and be like everybody else, right?
Yeah.
Now, you go out and you're like, man,
everybody's younger than me, I guess I'm old.
Right.
You kind of notice, you know, when someone
is younger than you.
Yeah, you do.
Yeah.
So, antiquity, which doesn't quite classify, I don't
know how, and the classification of the term
antiquity, does it mean ancient, like a week
ago was ancient to alternative media, by the
way?
Right.
Those morons.
Or is it 100 years or just a
half a century plus, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
I like the older books.
You know, but here's the thing, it's still
low grade.
I know, I know.
I've looked at stuff, even, you know, here's
something you really want to hear, this might
sound aghast, this might make people aghast in
a certain way, Newton is low grade.
You read Isaac Newton, his scientific works and
his biblical comedies, low grade.
To me, at least.
Okay.
I'm not saying don't read it.
You know, and if you might be impressed
by the writing style.
I can understand where you've come up with
that, yeah.
Well, the way they worded things, you know,
might seem like a higher form of the
language, more command of the English language, let's
say, than you see, but it's still low
grade.
You know, you read and you don't leave,
I mean, you could do an hour's worth
of Greek speak and it'll top anything Newton
ever wrote.
Well, I'm sorry.
That said, we're limited by our language to
begin with.
Yeah, well, that's true.
But I mean, in terms of low grade,
in terms of where they're going with it.
Right, right.
What are you going to leave with?
You know, so.
Yeah.
Well.
Mm-hmm.
Is there anything going on?
No, she's quiet.
Yeah.
Let's just call it a, we've covered a
bunch of stuff.
And mostly thanks for sending that email regarding
all those questions.
And again, just listen to what's being said.
It's a mindset thing.
So when a topic is brought up, let's
say I bring up a topic, it's not
going to be usually, not because I just
want to be contraire, but it's not going
to be discussed and I'm not going to
present it the way you're used to hearing
it.
Because what you've pretty much heard before is
a lie.
So.
That's a tough one to get around.
And just starting off, you know, what we
started off regarding crystals for healing.
They're not used for healing and they can't
be.
I mean, well, some people believe they are,
but that's not what they're for.
They're visual.
They're optical tools, solely optical.
Healing is the same.
If just to finish off, first will be
last, last will be first.
The if I were to say I might
sound ultra conservative in terms of a viewpoint,
a spiritual or scriptural viewpoint that all disease
and is a spiritual oppression.
Right.
Actually, it's true to say that.
But I would rather say that disease, you
know, maladies, physical maladies and spiritual oppression.
The the to mitigate that there's only if
you understand scripture, the the creator sends those
things and retracts them and heals.
He's your only source for that.
Right.
So so that's the the key.
The thing that I again, just to recap
what I brought up, the visual optical aspect
was, look, you know, one of the things
that was used in old times because they
understood that we see through a fleshy eye.
Again, we're taking it for granted.
People just see, well, see what they see
and they take in regard, again, whether it's
low grade or high grade.
Well, do you see?
Well, or do you need glasses or do
you not see?
Well, but no one is discussing the the
let's say the philosophy of optics.
What it really is, is the impulse has
gotten through the eye.
And the only reason photography makes sense is
because they are adjusted and made so we
can interface, you know, fight with a printed
photograph or something on a rectangle that we
recognize.
Right.
Cameras see differently than we do.
You know, there's there's algorithms in the digital
stuff and there's chemistry and contrast has to
be considered in the chemical photography.
So it makes sense to us.
Right.
But, you know, there are people like Kirlian
and Trevor James Constable and others that have
taken photography to the study, the anomalies of
what it can be recorded, you know, and
that we can make sense optically later.
Right.
The infrared and ultraviolet and whatever else.
In other words, is it is it analogous?
That's where you get analog.
You know, ultimately it has to be analog.
Right.
Where you can interface with it, with your
ears and eyes.
And if there's tactile sensation, of course.
Right.
And olfactory.
So.
But ultimately, in the aspect of all healing
or spiritual with the opposite would be spiritual
oppression or illness or disease is, let's just
say the apex or the locus point starts
with the creator.
So you go to him for it.
I mean, whether he'll let you over there
or not is between you and him and
the angels, really, that, you know, I'm just
saying he's the source.
That's the whole thing.
That's the beauty of watching all the stupidity
in the world.
The beauty of it is how calm it
is for the creator.
Or the higher beings, because most of the
people are only used to low grade stuff.
So all the low grade crap gets filtered
out.
So there's really not much getting up there.
I know it sounds kind of crazy to
say that, but I want you to think
about that for a little while.
In other words, the spiritual realm is polluted
with humans making requests, but very little of
it is getting up to the higher grade
level.
Because they filter it out, you know.
Right.
So if you understand what I just said,
just to think out loud for a minute,
get your shit together, figure out what high
grade communication with the spiritual side really is,
because then you could bypass all the pollution.
And all the dumb shit that you see
in religion and all that.
And get to where things can really be
done.
You know, are.
We had an interesting question.
Was not the Christ, let's see, how did
he put that?
Was not the Christ sick for most of
his day, but healing the sick?
You could say that pretty much, you could
garner that from the Psalms.
There are a bunch of Psalms that regard
descriptions that could only be applied to the
actual Christ's life.
Right.
And I've actually mentioned that before, that if
you look at that Psalm, it clearly states
he had taken on illnesses.
Right.
But, you know, that's something, again, that needs
to be studied, because to say that the
Christ took on illnesses and was sickly himself,
if we take the very conservative view that
all illness and disease is a form of
spiritual oppression, he allowed himself to be spiritually
oppressed.
Now, the antithesis of that is that they
had recognized him as the Christ and they
would avoid him.
Right.
Because he had the highest authority.
But, you know, and then again, you could
switch back and say, well, maybe it was
by directive, again, that he was of the
nature, you know.
Because the interesting thing that you can say
about the Christ, actually, which is you can
garner from the text quite immediately if you're
doing an objective study, is he had the
power of invisibility.
Not like the invisible man in sci-fi.
But more like the description given in the
movie Men in Black.
When you meet people, they won't be able
to make out who you are or remember
you.
You'll just be like deja vu or something
to them.
Uh-huh.
He had that ability.
So if he were to be assessed by
authority as a child, they would probably see
him as such.
But others that knew him would see him
in perfect health.
It depends.
That needs to be studied.
But I have gone out and said that
based on certain verses in the Psalms, he
had taken on illnesses, yes, throughout his life.
And it would make sense if we had
more information, historical information, which, by the way,
it was known to many people on who
he was in an academic sense, based on
who he said he was and who others
said he was.
And there is a lot of records about
the Christ, but they're still secret.
And the only thing that leaks out is
through some rabbinic traditions where they speak of
him very poorly.
Right.
You know, especially after, you know, later first
century.
But if you read in the New Testament,
in many places there were scribes that followed
him around and took notes.
In the New Testament, they used the Pinox,
you know, which is a form of writing.
In modern Greek, if you go to school
and someone writes on a board, it's called
the Pinox also.
But in order to gain, I don't think
he gained that kind of notoriety immediately just
when he was doing, quote unquote, what they
like to say is his ministry when he
was going out in public.
I think he was quite well observed earlier
on because there are also Psalms that state
that, you know, the drunkards at the gates
and others were aware of him.
Right.
So so he was quite well acknowledged to
what degree.
I'm not sure.
But I would say that there's enough in
the Psalms to say that he just didn't
appear on the scene later, you know, in
his last four years or so.
He was known about before.
But his purpose, again, is very simple.
And it's not what people think it is,
you know, because, again, why would you come
in and step on the game that was
the game board?
You know, if children are playing a game,
you don't come in and step on the
game board.
So the high the high level spiritual beings
have set the lower spiritual beings to rule
the earth a certain way and they're not
doing it and they're not going to come
in and disturb it until it's time to
do so.
Well, it definitely would also show that he
had permission to do so.
Instructed.
Right.
His purpose was well known to him was
to die.
And, you know, and also within that proved
that everything in Scripture was true.
Right.
Even if you study Scripture, you can almost
say it as a private thing.
You know how I say that if you
don't say it or write it down, the
most spirit beings or spirit beings don't know
because they can't read your mind.
They could put things in your mind.
Right.
They can't read your mind.
There's no one verse declaring the Messiah directly,
you know, who exactly he is and where
he's going to be and when he's going
to come.
Right.
There's no one verse.
It's spread out.
You know, there's no there's no like footnotes
and bullet points on the specifics.
Almost as if it's the prophetic aspect is
hidden as well.
Yeah.
Because the spiritual realm doesn't, you know, unless
you just like people, you either know him
or you don't.
So it's, you know, in other words, he
was not announced cosmically, directly in the scriptures.
He's all over the place indirectly for those
that have wisdom to see it, you know.
So in other words, that's why very often
I always say everything about him is a
secret.
It's a complete secret, you know, whether it's
pre or post or even still everything about
the Christ is a secret.
It's amazing to to look at that because
it's it's a major cosmic thing.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
So so if that's a secret, how much
of Genesis is a secret where you could
say, well, the Christ is one thing.
But the beginning of the world or the
beginning of everything is another.
How much of that is a secret?
Well, that's a big secret also.
You know, again, when you go back to
certain Talmudic writing Targum Targum writings, which are
Aramaic, more the northern part of the world,
you know, there or if you go to
any of the even Native American or sages,
you know, whether it's rabbis or Native American
Indians or what they what everyone is always
stating is be happy with what, you know,
about you to the common people, whatever you
know, and get what you can out of
studying.
But those who do know, keep it to
yourself.
That's that's the ultimate thing.
It's still a world of secrets.
In other words, like if you so scripture
aside, study the Native American culture.
Let's say the DNA people, they call them
Navajo.
And you study them objectively and you really
make progress.
If you were to run into anyone that
held ancient knowledge or, you know, more high
grade knowledge, he won't share it with you.
He'll he'll pat you on the back saying
you've done really well.
But are you happy with it?
Yeah.
OK, good.
Go now.
I know more, but that's for me to
know, not for you to know.
Right.
You see, this is how the ancient sages
were or the people that were studying scripture.
We could call them rabbis now because of
that part of the world.
Right.
They they would study and look at things
and make discoveries and they wouldn't share them.
The people, they keep them within their own
group.
And when someone would appear and, you know,
try to demonstrate what they've discovered, they wouldn't
discourage them, but they wouldn't add to it.
They wouldn't help them along either.
This has been the human tradition.
How many times have you heard me say,
you know, even parents of the children want
you to do well in life.
Just don't do better than I am.
Right.
Yeah, that's how people, you know, I see
that all the time.
Yeah, I want you to do well in
life, just don't do better than I'm doing.
Right.
That's the same mentality there.
This is a human scumbag condition, I call
it.
Because humans are groomed by these gods, by
these various imps, demons, patron deities, matron deities,
their priesthoods, you know, it's real trash.
It's a real trash existence.
And it's been going on for so long
it doesn't make it right.
You know, just because, you know, if you
study tort law, one of the old things
they wrote about tort was that time does
not nullify a void act.
Let me say it again.
Time does not nullify a void act.
Right.
That's the use of English that people are
not used to hearing.
So if someone is voided, you know, has
a void act or a tort or a
harm, no matter how much time goes by
it doesn't nullify it.
It still stands as if it was just
done yesterday.
Right.
So if someone stole your iPad 50 years
ago, ha ha ha, it's no difference if
it was 50 years ago or today.
Right.
Because it's a tort.
So most people are living with the concept
now that these void acts that they call
tradition and culture and ignorance is nullified because
it's been going on for so long.
Get it?
Right.
So when you go out into the world,
whether it's the entitled classes or your family
or your friends or your neighbor or co
-worker or anybody out there, and they pull
that plausible deniability bullshit where everybody's been doing
it for so long now, that's bullshit because
if it's void, it's void.
Right?
Right.
It's not nullified because it's been going on
for thousands of years.
Bullshit.
It's just as fresh and just as it
needs to be remediated as if it was
just developed today.
See?
Mm-hmm.
That's why very often I have such harsh
criticisms for the entitled classes, you know, the
legal field, the medical field, the administrative, I
shouldn't say administrative, but the political side of
stuff.
The administrators are different, by the way.
The religious, just because they've been doing it
for so long, it doesn't mean that it's
okay.
That's basically tort law.
And that's how the gods see it.
And, well, the Most High sees it that
way.
That's why when you read, especially in Jeremiah,
one of the excuses that he gets is
that, well, we've been doing this for so
long, making offerings to Ashtar and we'd be
prospering.
What do you mean?
Who's this Yahweh guy now we have to
heed to?
We're not talking about, you know, for all
these years we made offerings to Asht, Queen
of Heaven, and we prospered.
What are you talking about, you know?
So it's irrelevant.
So, okay, with that said, I don't know.
Maybe we just had an irrelevant.
I don't know how long we've been on,
but for most it would be irrelevant, an
hour and 20 minutes roughly of irrelevancy.
But either way, we'll have another week of
irrelevancy coming up, hopefully, next week.
Thanks, Bruce, for archiving this.
Thank you again.
Okay.
Anything else?
Otherwise, we'll just sign off.
Looks like that would be it there, Greek.
Okay.
I'll see you then.
Thanks, man.
You have a good day.
Bye-bye.
You too.