And greetings folks, you know, we're live here
with the Greek and Greetings.
How are you doing there, sir?
Oh Doing all right.
Oh, that's good.
We're here out of habit now, aren't we?
Yeah, it's kind of looking that way.
Yeah Yeah all right, well greetings everyone if
there's a There's the chat if anyone wants
to go in there and pose any questions
or the email yeah, and this is kind
of like a ritualistic or Traditional now to
come up once a week.
I usually what they call Totten's Day, which
is death day or Tuesday Yeah is the
is we have a little Sam odd and
He's not here tonight.
So It's it's night here on the American
Southwest.
So It's Bruce and I and if anybody
else wants to chime in.
Yes Yeah, sir.
No, no, he's we certainly will take our
Collins if there are them.
I'll pull post that into the channel so
we can Add new people would be more
welcome.
So if you yes, definitely not here before
I'll hold off for a little while.
So And we'll see what happens.
Yes Yeah, and I will go to the
email which is Uncommon-sense radio one at
gmail.com and that's the numeric one uncommon
-sense radio one at gmail.com And we'll
see How that works out And in there
we go Anyway, you got that taking care
of now And that's for the Skype and
there's a probably a call-in number that
you have set up.
Yes I got that set up too So
we can always take people anyway that they've
whatever flavor they feel there you go So
what's what's on anybody's mind anything with you
Bruce, sir?
I was Past events and Unfortunately not taking
notes, but uh it was always good to
Take a second look, you know as you
Specifically when you were talking about the original
text and all that kind of stuff and
all the troubles and where it came through
and God the number of hands that were
involved in that is it's it's crazy.
Absolutely crazy Well, it's not it.
Yeah, it's it's a battle of the gods
and and man is in a terrarium It's
very simple and it's not really a battle.
It's a play but not like a Shakespearean
play It's a play of things that have
to happen you know, in other words a
sequence of events have to happen to say
it's a play the way we conduct plays
is Sort of a metaphor very very lightly
just like I use the man as being
a child, you know, you raise children or
you know Supervised children how they act with
toys and things and I mean that's basically
And one thing I want to bring this
up because I've been getting some contact this
week about some of the recent news events
Which are not news at all.
It's just different, you know It's a different
way of the same thing and the same
thing that that they're procuring That is being
procured people don't understand and I want to
set this Kind of make how simple it
is and set it in a way that
it's you can apply it every time you
see something going on in the media What
you see going on in the media whether
it's a false flag political event or whatever,
whatever.
It's all to preserve and promote the Money
system the monetary system of the United States
or in the IMF Right It's kind of
hard to Just say that and walk away.
So I'm not Like we'll give you an
example Let's say you figure out how to
make a flying saucer and you put it
in the paper for a demonstration And here
comes, you know All the agencies and they
shut you down and they give you a
piece of paper and say why are you
shutting me down?
Because it has a negative effect on the
monetary system of the United States Yeah, you
get it.
Oh, yeah, if you come up with a
cure for let's say cancer The agencies will
come in and serve you a piece of
paper.
You can't do this because it adversely affects
the Get it monetary system the United States.
Well, look at what happened to Joseph Newman,
you know Which is now up in the
archives or uploads by the way Yeah, that's
a good classic example well, even the patent
the circus, you know the court and Everybody,
you know came around, you know the patent
office all you know From the let's say
the formal conventional side said well, you know,
this is tooth fairy stuff, even though it
wasn't But Joseph Newman had the absolute wrong
approach just as Tesla and Schauberger and the
others Yeah, which is I want to do
this.
Yep.
I want to make the world a better
place Look, there is no scriptural figure or
any anyone in any ancient writ that ever
said that either You ever notice so if
you need a mentor We'll look at the
ancient text the Christ was like you guys
are gonna You know get bloodied with rocks.
I mean, I'm just I'm just paraphrasing here.
You're gonna wish you were never born and
woe to you He didn't say I'm here
to make the world a better place Yeah
Yeah, and there is no there yeah, there
is no way you're going to access anything
ancient by the way in English or most
of the languages you're gonna have to learn
to Discern not learn the language is a
difference of the ancient text.
So yes Giving an example.
I recently turned on some lectures on academics
on Various subjects going back as early as
possible and they say well this is from
3,000 BC Like which is like smack
in the middle of the flood, right?
Yeah, right No, and also these people are
categorically ignorant What I mean the word categorically
means without a doubt across the board everything,
right?
And they're telling you how horses were domesticated
and how history was, you know, four or
five thousand years ago Yeah, right ask that
idiot whether it's a live one in a
university, especially the Ivy League Or whatever a
lot of people have contact information You know
how the body works.
What day is it or anything?
They don't know they don't know anything they're
categorically ignorant and they're gonna stand up there
and tell you all this stuff so Yeah,
it's pretty sad.
So but at the same time, you know
The food clothing and shelter thing is being
worked on consistently Yes You know with whoever's
listening Cuz that's all you got really what
are you gonna do put on a lecture
on how?
Horses were domesticated 5,500 years ago.
Listen to some idiot tell you stuff that
the nerd doesn't even exist or it has
existed.
I Mean, come on guys.
It's about food clothing and shelter right now.
It's always been that way really.
I Which you will never find out using
the conventional rectangle or any other means but
You'd have to piece it together to see
so You know like for example, you know
I bring up the Middle Ages or prior
to that the Dark Ages The only reason
they're called the Dark Ages is because they're
dark to us Just like for example a
black ops or a dark project doesn't mean
that it's that way It just means that
it's because there's no information on it.
You see so Very interesting times in that
time.
Oh Yeah, super a little bit that the
little bit that can be garnered out of
that It got shut down and the shutdown
was known as the Renaissance remember it's all
backwards right the winners are the losers and
the losers are the winners and I'm not
saying this in a Philosophical way I'm saying
in an actual way.
So let's see Vandy posted something here We
have food by seasonal info would be helpful
Well, there's what do you say seasonal in
English It means two things one is a
flavor additive a spice added to food or
the other one is seasonal meaning in season
growing meaning Gleaned or harvested at that time
mm-hmm and tomato season there and He
preserves in jars for winter But yeah, that's
the best.
Yeah.
Yeah, I would say so freezing works Well,
but what people don't understand about freezing is
even though you could leave something in the
freezer.
It doesn't spoil for years All right, especially
when you go to someone's house.
I call it food museum race You know,
they have stuff up way back in there
They don't you know know about rotation and
cleaning things storage areas cans and various other
things Yeah, yeah, well freezing is good for
about 30 days 30 to 60 days tops
After that and the reason I say this
after that things do spoil in a different
way, but not spoil in a sense that
You have rot You have a form of
dry rotting actually that happens It's not freeze
drying.
It's a different kind of Thing that happens,
but the the reason I say that about
freezing is because the freezers are not cold
enough You have to be in the minus
90 Temperature range Fahrenheit or centigrade.
Oh, man, you know, it's interesting about Fahrenheit
Saturday And once you get to those low
numbers, they they start being pretty equal.
Yeah, and those are called medical freezers or
cryogenic, you know Not sub cryogenic, but you
know high Above cryogenic cryogenics goes down to
the minus 150 200 Right where you treat
certain metals and things like that and there
you need, you know, a four-stage type
deal The freezers that you typically have in
most people's homes or the sold out there
for as a freezer Is in the minus
20 range minus 10 minus 10 20 20
minus 30 I've seen some of them if
they're well insulated and they run often You
could I've tweaked one to go down to
minus 40, but to go below that you
need two-stage compressor right, so You know
and they get pricey now what people don't
get let's just talk about freezing for a
while most of the commercially available fish is
two years old and the reason they do
that is for to stabilize the market Because
if the fish market was reliant on the
catch of that year What if they had
a bad catch that year what happens to
the fish market?
Right So what they do is they have
two seasons on hand So they just equally
distribute it out.
So let's say you already have 40 or
50 percent of the two years ago fish
stock in these freezers This year if it's
a slim crop will you take like you
take that 50% from the two years
ago and you add it to this year
and you supplement the Supply you see To
keep the prices stable Yeah hesitating about freezing
for the reasons I stated is correct, yes
Vacuum jar preservation seems to keep pretty well.
It's what Van Diemen's land says.
Yeah Yeah, well, you know that's what the
traditional canning did was create a vacuum You
know the heat right expands and then contracts
you get the vacuum destruction Now the mechanical
vacuum will be different Than a if you
do one jar with a mechanical vacuum and
one with a heat vacuum You're going to
have different results because one actually, you know
adds heat and the other one doesn't So
one will produce Believe it or not.
The heating one is better for a more
mild Ecology what I mean by a mild
ecology is if you don't do a heat
canning and just do the mechanical vacuum That
will allow and give rise to more what's
called anaerobic creatures to come out Where the
heat will stabilize both the aerobic and the
anaerobic you'll have a less active ecology So,
oh nice to know.
Yeah, most people are not set up to
do strictly mechanical Vacuuming because again that to
do that properly Requires, you know good equipment
and all that and high quality stuff Yes,
this here uses the old-fashioned boiler type.
Yeah, that's that's pretty good Yeah, that'll give
you a more neutral terrain and when I
say by that meaning the the critters that
are in the container Yep, heat has a
tendency to normalize things that way Mm-hmm
Yeah, I'm gonna go grab a Java I
should go completely wireless here in a second
Okay, see what happens.
I do that if I drop I'll somehow
mitigate that.
Okay, is it three two one?
Oh Okay.
Now it's completely wireless.
That was good, right?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
All right, so Had the same thing on
my mind Oh, no, I'm so good.
Yes.
All right.
There we go.
Yeah Lost you for that was mechanical the
the that was a mechanical fault not a
Electronic one, by the way, something just got
unplugged a little receiver Okay, I didn't notice
so I was like, oh, why is that?
Why is that light not on anymore?
Oh, I see because it's unplugged Oh, yeah,
but you know, by the way, that's the
the simplest thing You know when something mechanical
doesn't work is because there's a fault in
the in the mechanical side first You know
like the old adage with the computer people
at the computers or did you check to
see if it's plugged in?
That's half the time still Mmm, I finally
got myself a little preamp and thing for
for the headset So I'll be getting rid
of my noisy mic and background.
Hopefully in the near future Okay It is
a joy, by the way, if you one
wants to afford it, you know good equipment
is always a joy And believe it or
not good equipment doesn't go out of style
Unless it's the format that changes like from
a track to cassette, right?
You know, I never like for example back
in the audiophile days.
I Never invested in a Nakamichi Cassette deck,
you know $2,000 cassette deck because I
had a feeling just you could never get
you know sound quality out of such a
format right now was good, you know, right
and Yeah, there was a couple of other
European companies made high-end cassette decks and
I was like, yeah, that's not No, I
never yeah Cassette Really real is different now
Real it's not a cartridge type because said
is a cartridge in the alignment issues.
Mm-hmm Severe alignment issues, you know with
azimuth alignment and capstans all that but was
revealed real to real is pretty locked in
oh, yeah, Jen and the you know, the
sensing heads and all that are five times
bigger and So yeah, I remember the Tascam
and Tiac real to real.
Yeah Those are pretty good you can believe
it or not I would say that off
of them if you get a master recording
on a real to real quarter-inch It
would it would best most seat high quality
CDs because it's still analog and you know,
right if you run at a high speed
Right, right faster.
You run it more information.
So yeah more information Per density increases so
but I'll mention this I don't want to
make it an audio talk, but I have
a Sony came out with in the mid
80s.
So he came out with an elite class
of CD players and they use the two
buffers and two pre-amps to stage in
there So they it's you know, it's a
brand new Sony from you know, 1985 CD
player Series, I think it's the 970 or
something and this is over 30 years old
now It's still it sounds fantastic, but you
know to get that kind of sound Yeah
out of a seat and the problem with
when you get really good equipment just like
a fast car is the source material Like
if you have a really good system, it's
hard to listen to Regular CDs and things
because now it's too revealing and you hear
all the mistakes and the crap that they
did when they recorded it right, mm-hmm
a little bit of pleasure just like if
you have a super a super fast exotic
car and You know it, you know, you
know, it does 75 miles an hour 100
kilometers per hour in third gear You're not
gonna be able to really open it up,
you know, at least legally out, you know
Because you look at the you know, the
speed limits, you know So and it's not
like an Autobahn people say all the Autobahn,
you know The Autobahn is a very tough
place to be on because there's no shoulder
You're not allowed to run out of gas
and you're not allowed to have a mechanical
failure, right?
Right, so it's a very strict Setup, but
nonetheless it is a place where you could
exercise look on that kind of Stuff so,
you know exotic supercars, but when you get
into that kind of equipment, I Noticed you're
high and the source material is important.
Look for example There there with television monitoring
and stuff plasma is still the way to
go I mean, even though they've got new
LED LCD TVs, but nothing really beats a
plasma ultimately I guess it's subjective to say
that right?
But But Yeah, when you if you've ever
gotten a plasma television, especially a larger one
The problem is the source material everything looks
like crap on it now.
Mm-hmm, right?
It's so revealing play.
Yeah So you need a really good source.
So you tie that back into we were
saying about ancient texts, especially what's called the
scripture It's you know, once you start figuring
out That you want to operate with higher
level equipment, right the source material that you
have in your Bibles is crap So, you
know, I don't know who this LO cat
all capital LOR D guy is, you know,
right?
Well, I know there's a few hundred of
them in England in a house of LOR
DS, but these people are crazy, you know,
so With their Santa Claus, you know, the
Santa Claus is their chief deity, by the
way No matter how you what you think
whenever no matter what comes out of their
mouth or they say they believe in watch
what they do Yeah, I don't see no
G.
I don't see no JES us with long
hair and sandals in the shopping malls once
a year Do you not a one?
You do see that Santa guy.
So guess who their chief deity is And
the most highly celebrated It's scary stuff, you
know, that's pretty sick people though you're dealing
with right two billion Which reckons that to
be what?
Roughly 30 40 percent of the planet.
I'm just on that category The other I'm
not saying that the other six years every
percent are pretty sick either I'm just saying
let's look at what's saying because this is
a Western convention that we're speaking to right?
Mm-hmm Now you can't listen to what
they're saying Because it's easy to establish.
They're insane.
And the last thing you want to do
is Listen to a crazy person or people
What they do for example with analyzing crazy
people, even though psychology is not a valid
field in any way It's all revealing to
videotape crazy people and watch it without the
sound Yeah, because you can see there's an
actual, you know something really wrong with just
the way that they move and This is
what you when you look at the Western
culture with what religions they've adopted.
You can just look at them That's what
I'm saying.
Don't listen to what they say because they're
insane anyway and ignorant You don't want to
if you're listening to them now, you're watching
and listening now.
Well guess what happens it's a form of
oppression, but if you can just watch what
they're doing and Ignore them audibly which is
recommended you you will get a pretty good
gist a good foundation of what's going on
Anything else going on or this is gonna
be a real short sonic She ran Just
checking out what Bandy had to say there
Translation translation issues Well It depends on what
you're what you want to get out of
it, right You remember when even when you
want to go back?
It's twice the work because even when you
want to go back and figure out what
was really said regarding if it was ancient
Any ancient text you're still going to have
to know what's called the received text You
know what they put out there because that's
what most people know So now you need
to know twice as much about it They're
gonna have to wait to find a way
to couch the differences Like if you if
you run into some people that seem relatively
decent I mean notice I said not are
but seem and they only know the King
James and they want to learn more and
that's all They know well, you're gonna have
to somehow create a bridge to bring them
over to show them where the mistakes are
And it's going to be very difficult to
break through the religiosity of that document Because
most for example Christians don't know they cannot
define Christianity But they can't you anyone can
define them as taking that writ that they
use the King James or it doesn't matter
where the version and Turning that into the
mainstream part of their religion.
In other words, that is the source of
their religion errors and all right, right So
So they have no discernment.
So so when you gain discernment by looking
at everything about it You know what it
came from and what it is and it's
mistakes You have to make rapid-fire decisions
on how are you going to discuss it?
Are you gonna stick on the crap that
they know or are you gonna be a
bridge?
Over and if you're gonna be a bridge
over to you're gonna show the highlights or
are you gonna show the mistakes?
Remember these people are insane So I don't
see it going well Nope Neither do the
gods.
That's why they're gonna do it.
They're gonna do right either to the gods.
So Yeah Anything else going on out there
or a team how do you determine the
first moon of previous years on folks calendar?
Go to a visual Go to the rectangle
put in moon phases and Don't get a
graphic.
Don't get a written chart get a graphic
one, which actually shows the physical calendar You
know with the four weeks and the seven
boxes along each and they show you the
actual moon phase Right, and what you do
there is when they show you the moon
phase you'll see Roughly for three or four
days.
The moon looks pretty full.
So in the middle of those Three or
four, you know on the left.
It's not so full in the middle.
It gets really full.
They're right It's not so full sort of
in the middle There's where you judge and
you also have to know understand that those
boxes on the calendar Represent a midnight don't
they I Think you posted that in chat
a while back a calendar like that or
showed all the moon phases Physically, yeah what
they look like Yeah, but you remember somewhere
But remember when you're looking at calendar calendrical
Pope's work schedule delineations the lines between the
boxes are midnight So you have to shift
everything over 180 or 90 degrees.
So the middle of the box is really
when the day starts Yeah, I was I
used to show I don't really get into
too much detail anymore but years ago when
I got into detail, I had a whole
presentation on how to do the nights the
The deal, you know with timekeeping and he'd
show that just the picture of the calendar,
you know the regular calendar of people hang
up on the wall and I would have
a dotted line a Vertical dotted line in
the middle of each box and they said
that's really when your day starts You get
it, you know because they do night to
midnight So what just keep that in mind
and also noon time.
You're gonna have to figure out where you
are on the earth and the season Right
That's when they do the if you look
at that full moon graphic on the calendar
and you're It all various places all over
the planet.
Well, it's different different days Because remember they've
kicked certain days forward certain days back By
the way, the real date line is somewhere
between Jerusalem and Babylon Around there is where
the real date line stops, you know physically,
right?
In other words the progression of the of
the luminaries Thought I had your picture stored
but Very good reference Yeah,
it's good to kick back on a lot
of details because I'm giving a little detail
is really to get people started right Sorry,
you know it give an analogy, you know
someone needs a boost, you know, the car
doesn't start so you pull up you pump
the Pop the bonnets or the hoods on
both cars and you give them jump Okay,
and then the car starts he says thank
you very much Pat him on the back
is on his way Well, you got something
done, but you're not done yet because usually
the guy who you gave or gal you
gave the boost to They're not done yet
They have to go and make sure check
the alternator or the dynamo is working or
they might need a new battery You see
right?
Otherwise, guess what happens in a day or
two?
They're gonna be what back where they started
So even though you give a little boost
It doesn't mean you're done So I'm not
buying people new batteries or checking their alternators
or dynamos or or their system That's up
to you You know what I mean, right
so that's why I don't do treatises and
reports and on the uncommon site I don't
do anything written at all.
It's just that maybe it's sparse archive or
whatever There'll be one are one of the
archives there not to be whatever say it's
modestly is more information than you've gotten anywhere
else in 2,000 years Just one archive
So in terms of that need to be
discussed That are not how can you all
fall for the stuff including myself years ago
for all the crap that you know It's
put out there so Yeah, you know when
you look back on it how easy it
was to slip into that And that's that's
a scary part.
I Was watching the YouTube from what was
it the group anonymous and they were talking
about Facebook and How people are programmed for
the for the click-high Releasing endorphins, I
mean this guy was very technical about how
they Snatched people into this you know clicking
on it just to get this pleasure of
a like or whatever and it was It
was actually rather chilling to see how cool,
but you know if you live But every
format has that yeah, you've heard of a
shopaholic Someone I know exactly yeah was a
shopaholic and I said oh, yeah is that
buy too much stuff.
I like shopping So let me tell you
what's going on when you go shopping you
go in there with you go into the
shop and You're you got this hunter-gatherer
spirit, it's like going to a casino You
don't know what's going to happen next right?
But you want to win and then when
you find something and the price is right
for you You go to the cash register,
and you get a certain high When you're
at the cash register right to get it,
and then you get out the store It's
a different high because now you got it
right and then you get home It's a
different high then that goes away once you
put it away when you get home And
then you repeat that high just like years
ago.
It was going to the mailbox Yeah, you
grew up.
Yeah, we're getting a telephone We're getting a
telephone call yeah back in the days when
the phone hang off the wall with a
wire Yeah, if the phone rang it was
something important Every time so Yeah, or it
was either something important, or you knew who
it was because of the schedule just kind
of like yeah Yeah, like this week.
You know I look at chat, and there's
like 11 12 people there I'm like oh,
they're expecting a sonic event because we've been
doing it like that for the past five
or six weeks, so It's a certain high.
Let's go to the You know the chat
tango and see what the Greeks saying tonight
You know I'm you know get me high
for a few minutes.
Give me a rush.
You know Because I'm around stupid people all
week or something so yeah Yeah, it's it's
a regular thing.
I you know if you You grew up
with a family of quite a few people
and whatever Demographic the mailbox was like that
what's in the mail.
You know right so yeah, there was something
to look forward to The magazine kiosks, it's
the end of the month.
Let's go see what new magazine is out.
Oh wow look you know and then yeah,
so Like a lot of memories Before that
it was the rate of the TV new
episode.
Yeah, yeah, and the radio was before that
yeah And before that it was the market
the posts Before radio it was postings and
newspapers.
Yeah, or going to the movies and watching
the news on the big screen Yep And
what I mean by post there would be
people posting notices.
Yeah streets On the avenues of things yeah,
yeah Mm-hmm easy know that went Yeah,
and now it's not just faster and quick
instantaneous through the rectangle and It's the opposite
of stone.
It's light It's all being done with light
and plastics And they're making the darkness light
up because these screens are made of plastic.
You know which is oil dark Process so
they're processing darkness, which is crude oil Make
it when it's made in the dark into
and they're running light through it to synthesize
Your communication abilities And again, I've had a
couple of people ask me about it, they're
gonna take the Internet down I said absolutely
not And everything on the Internet is just
a beta test because the real purpose of
the Internet has not come into fruition yet
It won't for another decade It's a set
on good start.
Yeah Yeah being set up Don't feel bad
about it though I think at the end
of this little thing documentary that this fellow
is talking about The first thing he says
turn it off Take a week from it
and and just literally see how addicted you
are to the device Don't let if you
do it often possess you yes If you
if you're on the rectangle often like I
know when I had to do certain research
and things if you turn it Off for
a day that feels like a week Yeah,
whether it's a relief or a strain on
your system like an addict either way by
the way I just got a message from
Sammy's A little under the weather this week,
and he's tired so in he's out in
Europe So we have a big time difference
from here, so he says next week guys.
Just want to let you know Okay Well,
I wish him well Yeah, I'm sure we
all do Yeah, it's not good one slightly
under the weather or Energy well if you
really listen to Greek speak you wouldn't be
sorry Sam Actually there's a difference between hearing
and listening There's a difference between listening under
and then understanding and there's a difference between
understanding and doing is Knowledge power in the
doer or his knowledge power I mean knowledge
power in the knower or knowledge power in
the For the doer and by the way
knowledge is not power.
It never has been knowledge is life Because
scripture says they will be destroyed for lack
of knowledge, so what's the opposite of not
of destruction?
Creating creation or building right so knowledge is
building in creation and life Because you know
you can say the opposite of destruction is
life also Well certainly yes to a certain
degree no from you know something as simple
as that you know So it's not power.
It's it's creativity life and production So again,
you know yep It was just catching a
little bit of Andy there Let's Say what
is what's on the fat FB.
I guess is Facebook.
I called feces book right feces Yes, it's
testing.
Yeah.
Well.
Here's the thing the the people I was
telling this to someone recently The they do
false flag research right let me see who
it is and You know they analyze these
things and they said well, they think the
people public is stupid I said no They
don't only think the public is stupid.
They know the public is stupid.
I know the public is stupid and You
know the public is stupid.
You just don't admit it because you need
the you know the attention from them.
Yeah The public is stupid That's why these
thing and now the people that that sort
of are the actors behind the things that
people complain about Let me ask you where
do they come from alpha Centauri Mars Venus
or they come from the same crop of
idiot human on earth the latter Of course
these things are sloppy and you know it's
just you know the the people that are
in control the state let's say however you
want to define it the the financial world
the religious world They know people excuse me
They know it But they themselves also come
from that crop So you want to call
it the blind leading the blind that's fine
But you you know the the blind are
not going to make visual tricks for the
blind They do it in Braille or they
hit you on the head with the cane.
You know the stick right?
Right so yeah But it's about food clothing
and shelter.
I mean if you could really spend here's
advice I give good advice if you're wise
you'll you'll take the advice the Greek gives
and not because I'm I'm giving it because
it's good advice objectively Spend more time on
food preparation What even if you don't know
what you're doing If you know if you
admit that you want to spend more time
on food preparation, let's say cooking and all
that If you know you're going to spend
more time on it guess what's going to
happen.
You're going to do it Yeah, yeah, hopefully
you'll say wait a second Yeah, you know
I'll just make it from scratch.
I'll scratch it out.
You know whatever make you know so like
for example tonight I've made a great dinner.
I'm not going to get into it.
It's Asian, but Also someone here made a
dessert a tiramisu Which is an Italian dessert
and we used like top-shelf liquor in
the mix instead of you know The stuff
that they usually tell you to use a
brandy, and it's a big difference.
You know I mean Usually when you do
cooking They you know they had tell you
to add a liquor or wine to a
certain dish The better the the liquor or
the wine the better the dish You know
there's a there's an up-and-coming restaurant
I'm not going to give details and they
pride themselves on a regional using regional foods
and regional wines and I saw a video
of them in the kitchen And they have
like this box wine that they add to
the food Like they pride themselves as having
a great wine collection on the floor to
the customers But when they're cooking and they
have to add wine to the dish they
have this this box wine You know you
get a Kmart or Walmart right and like
what are you people stupid?
Yes, they are don't you think that cheap
wine is going to taste like cheap wine
in the food also?
So and by the way, let's just talk
a little bit about wine Usually when grapes
and things are fermented in the form of
wines They end up being quite sweet because
they favor a high sugar content for rapid
fermentation or controllable fermentation Because the less sugar
you have the less fermentation you have and
the harder it is to perceive and control
it right So there's a way of measuring
sugar.
It's an industrial measurement it goes from like
0 to 19 or something coca-cola is
like 12 or whatever and And You get
into all these details if you want to
I'm not right now But essentially most wines
are very sweet so what they do is
they add Sulfuric acid to them to knock
down the sweetness.
That's why when you look at a bottle
of wine it says Contains sulfites you ever
notice that Okay, so but but you know
I didn't say I didn't say they add
sulfites.
I said they adds Sulfuric acid and where
else do we find that in batteries car
batteries don't we?
Yeah, so German here's the other interesting thing
German wines are the highest purity in the
world amongst that we know of as this
is a formal Standard most wines California wines
French wines especially American wines by the way
will never pass German purity laws So I
just want to throw out there I just
gave you know a little bit of a
thing and also you have these people called
sommeliers that are wine tasters and wine They
you know a good restaurant or a good
food establishment of what's called a sommelier which
recommends wines preparing and quality of wines and
history of wines and tasting and all that
rain and I was once present because of
the water stuff that I did The I
challenged someone who sold high-end wines to
go get all the best bottled water in
their own water What they thought was the
best water they brought it And I just
took regular tap water and an overnight processed
it and it was better than all the
waters they ever brought and there was a
wine sommelier there and there was also a
coffee taster and They're the coffee taster and
the wine somebody were arguing They were like,
oh you wine somebody as you look for
40 or 50 characteristics in wine, but coffee's
got a hundred and fifty, huh?
You know, it's really funny.
How they are.
They get it, you know, so the people
that are discerning coffee Is even there is
more to discern in coffee than there is
in wine But we don't it's not doesn't
seem as popular because everyone can drink coffee,
but not everyone drinks fine wine Right.
And by the way people if you've ever
had a $700 bottle of wine or $1
,000 bottle of wine or $400 bottle of
wine It just tastes more like brandy So
I just tell this to people, you know,
no one's no one's discussing me.
And so I'll say it I'll just say
I'll make it real quick.
I was at this high-end restaurant About
two decades ago with a VP from Goldman
Sachs and it was like five people and
it was a $4,000 tab for the
dinner right, so well, why was it so
high because the wine right and So I'm
drinking this wine.
It's a seven hundred fifty dollar bottle of
wine.
I'm not the whole bottle but a glass
I'm like, oh, let's just say it's like
it has brandy in it if you know
what I mean, right?
So if if what I was thinking I
said what you do if you if you've
been around Let's say you're going to entertain
some guests and these people are used to
you know, really high budget wines Let's say
take a bottle of wine Open it very
quickly a good bottle when let's say $15
is a good bottle of wine By the
way, whether you buy a $3 or $4
bottle of wine or a $20 or $30
bottle of wine They all cost about a
dollar fifty The difference is how it gets
to you and what they would care they
put into it, right?
And of course the quality grapes, but it's
not that much Okay, so what you do
is you open the bottle very quickly So
don't let it air out and put in
with a drop or about ten drops of
high-quality brandy Put the cork back on
put it away for two days Take it
out air it out really well serve it
and people someone will say this is a
hundred or two hundred dollar bottle of wine
It's not that easy.
You have to know what you're doing, but
essentially that's what it's like.
So most people are not going to Hang
around with Federal Reserve people and have a
thousand dollar bottle of wine and I'm just
telling you what it's like, right?
so It's no big deal and Brandy and
these things all they are is it's like
it's a form of wine and to stop
the fermentation process While it's fermenting they when
they decide it's fermented enough.
They actually add a refined or distilled alcohol
to it just to The adding of the
extra alcohol stops the fermentation process because it
acts like a sterilizer against the existing You
know critters, yes, and that extra punch that's
why brandy has such a strong How did
we get into this talk about wine right
now?
Anyway, yeah, so I thought this is a
first that I have never heard what I
just said out and it's so freakin obvious
If you know, you know food and wine
and all that and I've never heard it.
So I figured I might as well say
it I'm glad you did Couple of those
for certainly were an eye-opener.
Oh my goodness Yeah, let's see is what
is that is vegan wine a scam Well,
you really can't have vegan wine because there's
critters in it Yeah, veganism is a scam.
Of course it is but it's a simple
form of communicating Just like you use days
of the week if you look at the
vegans in the Vedix and all these people
They were not and they were very low
regard in the society They were fanatics and
again when you in a Western culture when
you hear veganism That's usually white people who
don't know how to cook and they adopt
that form of food preparation So when people
say, oh your food tastes bad, they just
say well instead of saying it's me too
lazy how to cook I just say it's
vegan.
That's why I was vegetarian.
That's why it tastes like that.
What's wrong with you, right?
So they turn it around.
They're pretty you should know that already But
there are some people including myself that do
better without any animal products whatsoever at all
Right, but I remember being in a vegan
restaurant a long time ago and lady was
the waitress I don't know if she was
an actor in acting school practicing to be
a waiter or a waiter that wanted to
go to acting school but she was just
talking too much and About how good the
restaurant was and how there's nothing animal at
all in here ever And I look at
her shoes and she's got leather shoes on
and I look at the wall I didn't
I didn't get on I didn't talk to
her about the shoes because that's too personal,
right?
And So I looked at the wall.
I said, is this a new building?
She goes, yeah, this is drywall or old
mortar and plaster There's your those drywalls.
Did you know drywalls uses alphabetic resins and
animal glues in it?
So this whole wall the whole place here
is is surrounded with animal Glue and she
just walked away and another waitress came These
are idiots man.
So yeah is it's all a scam It's
all a scam.
But the thing is, do you know what's
going on?
And why I had a conversation with someone
once there's a few people and this one
guy He just kept talking about how he's
vegetarian at this but sharing that he gets
off the call and the other person on
the call Is it's like what an idiot
and I'm like, why did you say of
course he's an idiot?
But why do you think he's an idiot?
He says cuz this guy only wants to
do is talk about vegetarianism and he doesn't
know why I Said yeah, I never thought
of it that way.
That's a good point.
Yeah Non GMO and all this other stuff.
What are they?
Well, GMO is another thing if you go
to the shops in the markets even a
farmer's market most of the veggie that you're
gonna Be is GMO You know crossbreeding, but
it hasn't been done Using glyphosate and other
things, you know And even the Monsanto, they
don't know what they're doing.
They're just crossbreeding things and That are not
food food grade You see because if you
have food grade corn and non food grade
corn guess which ones the bugs are gonna
find tastier the the food grade corn so
they just say just like if you remember
if you've been in a big city and
big Skyscrapers in the lobbies.
They try to make them seem more natural.
So they put or a decorative orange trees
or tangerine Have you seen those decorative?
Decorative fruit.
So one day I was going through it
was a place in Park Avenue and 46
Street I think was a Seagram's building house.
We're talking about alcohol again And they had
these Orange trees in the middle New York
City So I pick an orange and I'm
like this thing as hard as a rock
and I cut it open and there's no
nothing inside It's just like it looked like
a piece of yellow styrofoam, even though it
was natural Yeah, because they're not meant to
be eaten there.
They're not food grade oranges.
They're just decorative Right, you can't there's nothing
there to eat.
So there's there are plants that look like
they're food grade and they're not and Those
were probably some if you want to get
into the history of botany how they developed
or originated But also that's all their crossbreeding
and doing they don't know what they're doing
with genetics and all that I know that
I see I used to believe that in
the past.
I was like, oh mesmerize Oh, they're doing
this or they're doing that.
No, they're not.
I started meeting people.
I worked in the fields I've discussed things
with them as they don't know what they're
doing.
So you really don't know what you're doing.
Do you this is not really?
These are not new jacks.
These are people have been working in the
field for 25 30 40 years This is
an experiment And all it all goes down
to the occult You know the hidden stuff
with everything that's being put out It's very
simply just look at the paperwork.
They put out the scientific paperwork read the
conclusion first And at the conclusion tells you
like we still haven't determined what the cause
is or what this is, you know Why
just look at just go back to the
article of the paper look at the pictures
and read the table of contents is bullshit
So, but you they are being yeah that
you have a severe downgrading across the board
Categorically again, that's the word for tonight categorically
Just low-quality crap all all to set
you up because of the very reasons given
in ancient Ritz, so Working real well.
Well, it's like that discussion.
We had that one time on regular food
and then Where they call that that other
stuff that they doesn't you know For love
of me.
I can't remember the name.
No, what's that?
Organic, yes, that's it.
Thank you.
Oh, that's for that's a bad play on
human culture how they can allow The food
to be poisoned and then we sell you
non poisoned food Why don't you wake up
and and go after the people that are
poisoning your food?
It's already admitted that they're people poisoning your
food because it's our everyone admits that there's
organic food.
That's not poison People think it's good I
think it's a very bad thing to have
organic on the market because that shows that
you as a society you're you're screwed We
sunk to an all-time low there.
Why have why not?
Why not all of it be good?
What kind of a sick person but allow
it?
I'm not talking about the sick people that
are putting it on the market the farmers
and the Marketing people in the delivery truck
drivers.
I'm talking about the actual public at large
Why aren't they setting up a scenario like
the end of the Frankenstein movie when they
show up with pitchforks and torches to the
Frankenstein?
March down the street or the heavy protest
or the chanting or whatever is needed, you
know Those space heaters don't need much.
No, they just play just plug them in
they give off heat and They'll complain when
their switch doesn't work or they have a
kink in their cord.
It's an accord.
Yeah.
Uh-huh space heaters No, so they're oh
amazing Absolutely amazing.
I shake my head every time I go
in there Anyway, it's just and by the
way, there still is no rational and informative
discussion You might think you're being informed by
the way out there on the rectangle, especially
or even in print Not much.
The best you're going to do is find
some Unsolicited history, which means like history that's
not put in front of you by these
institutions You know if you go do research
like, you know, for example An interesting field
to look at is like nursing in the
19th century the field of nursing Great.
Well, look at those old books and you'll
be like wow, man.
I got to learn some of these techniques,
you know So, you know and if you
look at you know various, you know subjects
But on the periphery the stuff that was
not included in any university agenda You're going
to find some good reference material, but in
terms of what's being blasted, you know Or
put, you know up and being amplified on
the rectangle University the media or whatever is
just garbage Categorically across the board and it
doesn't mean that if you were dropped in
an infinitely large landfill You couldn't survive you
still have to dig around and find edible
garbage, right?
Right, so people's curiosity and information and things
is surviving and moving along on this edible,
you know garbage, basically the coprofagia is one
way to do it or just like when
I used to Do more sonic events.
I was like dude every time I talk
to you It's like I feel like I
want you know You want to go eat
out of a garbage can when I'm giving
you a three-star meal why you know,
so yeah So I don't you know You
can imagine telling someone I'm going to take
you to a three-star Michelin restaurant and
they're like on the way there They can't
you can't stop them from eating out of
a garbage can after a while.
You're like now I'd rather just go I'll
go sit neat alone so There's many levels
and that garbage can reference is what you're
going to find across the board categorically again
University the doctor's office the courts Yep, especially
the religious institutions And I suppose at this
point we should let people know that if
they want to call in on Skype uncommon
radio Uncommon sense radio one at gmail.com
and if you want to use your celly
phone and call in The area code is
nine two zero seven eight five twenty forty
eight And with that we can proceed Yeah
Well, it's what we've been on for about
an hour.
Maybe you can make it a short one,
too I usually don't get that kind of
input.
I don't know If it's just people or
rather just sit back and be entertained and
like kind of like a circus bear, you
know It's then do I'm going to stand
on a ball and juggle for you and
we got 16 in the stream right now
Okay, well eat in the chat Yeah again
the metaphor for just giving someone a boost
is where it's at I You know, I
could I'd like to go to there are
two different ways to go one is to
write some pretty good stuff all summed up
together or the other way is to just
give you know cursory outline on the beginnings
of any subject and Right, I think the
latter one is the way to go.
Mm-hmm Well, yeah of all the And
here's the thing out of the past couple
years that I've been discussing these things I've
only had really just two or three or
four people That from the public at large
that have come forward and say hey, I
need to learn more about this Not only
do I want to I feel like I
need to Right, right.
That's and that's why I keep saying there's
only three or four people out there, right?
Right.
See so even though there might be 16
on the stream and 10 and chat or
might get 500 emails a year Or something
like that.
Mm-hmm.
It's still only three people four people that
are really willing So I'm not going to
go out and go to the extra You
know ten steps to put together You know
a body of work brain that they could
use it's best to let you know most
most of the people in the chat and
on the streams and on The emails are
just armchair yeah, there's a lot of There's
a lot of stuff going on.
Yeah.
Well, I'm eating better and I'm noticing how
to keep time and all this but yeah,
that's fine Good But there's not a lot
of there's there's no seriousness in the world
right now about this stuff and in the
end on the other On one hand, it's
like oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's too bad.
But on the other hand, it's fine What
are you going to do?
You're gonna you know, like we mentioned the
Joseph Newman earlier But by the way, you
can do the Joseph Newman you can develop
a machine Let's say or an apparatus or
apparati right the plural Yeah, that uses electricity
properly and you'll notice that it's not like
spilling water out of a bucket as long
as you don't Publicly verse that you want
to vocal or vocalize that you are doing
this to make everything better You'll be fine
with it, right?
and then eventually you still will notice because
you're in the early states of developing that
and Just you know manifesting it.
It's still cheaper to use up the power
that you get off the grid Ultimately because
put it this way in order to make
a Newman machine you're gonna need a few
hundred pounds of copper That's almost a quarter
of a mile.
Yeah.
Well it is.
Yeah I mean you have somebody else minded
for you.
Yeah, it's gonna cost you Well in the
form of wire, you don't want to get
raw copper you because making the wire is
the hard part And most copper is they've
reserved for just deep underground anyway mining because
they don't want it easy To show that
it's easy to get near the surface, but
I would suggest that When you start working
with these devices and all that you're gonna
say, oh man There was it was way
cheaper to be on the grid.
Yeah.
So what's your motivation to make the world
a better place?
Well, it better not be So then what's
your motivation you see?
Right, so it's the same thing with a
lot of the stuff that you can get
serious and that I brought forward through the
years You know, no, there's no one to
really talk to about it No, and there's
no one that really cares enough about it
either so either way it's fine, but Yeah
But there's there's just still not much going
on I would say to this point the
Greek is still just a circus bear entertaining
people and Doesn't mean that entertainment does it
you know, you can't take it seriously you
go, you know Look at Star Wars conventions
and stuff like that.
They still buy the hat and the t
-shirt Maybe I should put the hats and
t-shirts That'd be an interesting catchphrase In
essence look at this point now either way
it's it's okay because What you're really waiting
on is just time to pass And time
is just a series of events whether you're
measuring it With the Pope's work schedule the
wind-up toy or using the luminaries the
stars the Sun and the moon or just
in any event You know like someone walking
climbing a flight of stairs as a way
to keep time When you just waiting for
these events to pass and certain knowledge to
come into fruition that everyone acknowledges That's that's
all that's really left.
Mm-hmm Well, of course, you know in
the mop-up crew, but I can't include
them in what you have to do You
know you whoever is listening brain.
You're just gonna be that's why I have
mentioned several times tonight how are you doing
with your food clothing and shelter and Finding
out what the human what your body is
really because your mind is subject to your
body you know if you do eliminate the
body you have no mind and go into
unconscious state and once you pursue the food
clothing shelter quality improvement and discovering what the
body mind and Soul or breath is you
will find out everything there is to know
that you can know at this stage at
least You're also waiting on archaeologists, by the
way, yes Yeah, you know those people spend
their life their life in ruins, you know,
yeah That's what you're waiting on why well
Thanks, it's all the stuff that yeah, right.
It's all the stuff that you can get
access to then you could say I told
you so Right what people don't say I
told you so unless something is second Seconded
right someone says something and it's naysayers It'll
be too speculative when it's confirmed with evidence.
What do they usually say?
I told you so yeah every time Mm
-hmm, so that's pretty much it.
I hope you know so get your popcorn
and ask her and you get it I
hope I entertain people tonight Cuz I don't
know what else to do so Well, we
can do whatever we feel we'd like to
Yeah, there's there's tons of stuff to get
into and to do that you can make
useful in your life today You know, and
those are the things that I'd like to
touch on generally and specifically to you know
within a certain depth Right.
So, you know water food clothing shelter Your
history, you know because people are going to
eventually come across through conversation or contemplation Why
they believe what what they say they or
think they believe in So how to examine
those things and you're going to be no
matter how objective you want to be There's
still going to be elements of subjectivity You
know things that you are specifically censored to
that You can't see even though they're in
front of you your tastes your likes and
dislikes Always get in the way.
So examine those as well You know So
and the time left is relatively short and
I say relatively meaning, you know to the
scope of what we how we understand things
How long things last?
and How do you finish off a conversation
from Greek speak watch the Middle East, right?
I haven't been pounding or hammering on the
Middle East too much But there is so
much going on that no one is noticing
and I mean no one Because I look
at the emails in the chat and I'm
not putting stuff in there to bring it
forward and I say there's no One's no
one's researching really, you know And I don't
mean researching as you know, you set specific
time aside and you you look You know
and to see to find something and whether
you found something is successful and whether you
didn't is unsuccessful Not that kind of research.
I'm just talking about are you paying attention
if you're paying attention to what's going on
in the Middle East?
Right out there is a lot of setting
up going on Major setup.
It's no different.
Let me just give an analogy Let's say
you have an open public park like a
sheep's meadow You ever see some parks have
like a baseball field or something.
Mm-hmm And you know for all your
life you pass by or however long you've
been in that particular locale and you see
occasionally You know, they have a baseball game
or something out there but one day you
see all these trucks parked outside and they're
unloading all this grid and scaffolding and it's
like Okay, there's like a hundred people assembling
something on this field something is about to
go down And they assemble it and then
it's like a big Venue all of a
sudden for a big concert, you know, and
and everyone in the country knows that it's
happening there That's the metaphor of what's happening
in the Middle East right now All the
trucks are parking and ready to unload and
no one's noticing anything, you know And I've
noticed I give that analogy because at one
point I lived a near one of a
very large park in a city and The
same exact thing happened.
It was I think dr.
John.
Do you remember him?
He was a Jazz ish kind of rock
Dr. John was it?
Yes.
Yeah.
Yes Yeah, I played a bunch of music.
Yeah, he wore the glasses in the hat.
He had a mustache.
I covered his face and And it was
that it was a big deal and I
noticed for two or three days or seven
And no one was saying anything until like
the very day.
We're like 10,000 people showed up to
watch it Right, you know, I was like
wait something's about to go down over here
I mean, they're pulling wires out in the
middle of the field that are as thick
as my arm Okay from yeah, so there's
something going on here Um Let's see.
Yeah, this is our keep an eye on
that.
Yeah Here's a dr.
John song.
Let's see if it comes out.
Well There
you go I Don't know if that sounds
okay Oh
There's a blast from the past Not my
style of music, but yeah, it sounds good,
but not good enough for me to say
that's what I want to listen to right,
so Yeah, nothing on the emails I've got
everything turned on in terms of accessible accessories
Yeah, but you know the I didn't hear
from Sam.
There seems to be a customary thing to
do thing with Sam Mm-hmm.
I Turned it on about a half hour
before we came on.
I said, oh wow.
Okay, it's it's called accommodating, you know I'm
on just accommodating So Yeah, other than that,
you know, I don't at this I think
I need to be provoked more about You
know moving forward on categorically speaking on things.
Oh, that sounds like a plan Yeah So
if any but if you got questions or
whatever, I mean, I'm Burr I could burst
at this I'm bursting at the seams of
things that I'd like to discuss and say
and bring forward But I think it's best
to accommodate who's listening And it's not that
I know everything about or anything that could
be asked but I assure you that Anything
that can be asked has been asked before
and if it's done been done before why
not do it again, right?
Sorry Yeah, and the thing is again, it's
really shocking to told you so you can
prove it the the human mind the spirit
is easily impressed with quantity and they can't
recognize quality still and The reason why I
say this is how many websites or pages
are there on the web on the on
the rectangle on the internet?
billions and how much of it is Very
very very little so little it just shows
you what human kind and woman kind Does
or mankind and woman that does with what
they're given?
You could look at the agricultural right?
They'll poison everything and it's okay, and they'll
say well, this is not poisoned.
There's organic Okay, you look at the rectangle
the internet.
It's just garbage and but this is not
garbage.
You have some reference material here, right They're
really just immunology across the board so yeah,
and the scientists are just a joke academia
is just a circus again a show and
if anyone does want to get into Various
aspects of you know, where the basis of
the system that is in the world today,
which is the Greek You know, they call
the Greek world Greco-Roman or Judeo-christian
And when you say Judeo-christian, it's like
basically Hellenistic Hellenistic System if you study the
classic Greek stuff, which is the latter Period,
let's say that there's several golden ages.
I say at least two in Greece but
the one that everyone knows about is ancient
Greek the Philosophy that's come forward in the
science and all that spoke very negatively of
established academia at the time Yeah, I don't
need to say that again do I know
so all the stuff that been the academics
are holding up as being critical And acclaimed
is was actually speaking poorly of them Just
like for example the Christian pastors ministers Whatever
you want to call them Pope's priests They
hold up the Bible that book condemns them
what they're doing everything not some of what
they're doing everything that they're doing The same
with the rabbis the same with the Muslims
Islam or whatever you want to call it
with the Buddhists and their own works condemn
them the same with the quote-unquote government
There is no one in the government that
knows any law or follows any law or
anything The codes or the statutes that they
or their Constitution How's your Constitution today, right?
Right.
How's your kind of constitutional today?
The funniest thing is when you bring up
the Constitution to an attorney, it's a bad
thing.
They'll say are you constitutionalist?
Well, you got to just put a list
in the back of it some and it's
bad.
Yeah Well, there's the the church people do
it, too.
Well, they Any time now that you even
try to go that way, you know just
for conversation, no, you know, it's demonized now
There's a lot more in a sense I
demonize it because it the first 17 words
talks about establishing justice.
I'm right And but I would just use
their own stuff against them is the best
way to do it, you know They have
like lights right now, you know search lights
on helicopters and planes and Adam For 50
years that are what 50 million candle what
they can only burn for a few minutes
something up there.
Yeah Yes, something high or five million or
something.
It's I know it's more than five because
you could buy a five million candle What
for you know now?
Handheld, yeah There are strategic lights and what
they found out is if they point them
at people at close range meaning like Ten
yards or so it could damage your eyes,
even if your eyes are closed Yes, that's
how strong the light is.
All right.
So when you're approached with that, what do
you do?
You hold up a mirror, right?
What does that do right?
It just aims it right back This is
the same with smart meters and all this
radiological stuff.
I call it radiological because essentially it's low
-level radiation Just let them put a smart
meter up Just go get a mirror and
put it up against the wall on the
inside and the mirror facing them smart meter
So you have the back of the mirror
facing the room?
You just cover it with something.
Mm-hmm.
That just sends it right back So anyway,
it's just a Ridiculous situation across the board,
but you know food clothing and shelter spend
a little more time, you know it's good
stuff, but learn how to prepare it and
Wear some good clothes Get the best clothing
you want to afford, you know memorize.
I didn't say can't afford want to afford
because and Shelter keep your shelter clean and
in good order, you know, and and Just
go day by day Watch what develops Definitely
good advice.
I mean, there's no movement.
There's nothing you're going to do That's going
to change anything from the way that it's
been set to be so even if you
pretty much established that and past sonic events
and oh Yeah, well it not even pretty
clear Events are a little boost or a
hint to go look around and you'll see
great Again, then just like I started off
tonight Anything and everything you see whether you
approve or not or whether it's good or
bad is to preserve the monetary system So
when the you know, they have the twin
towers turning into dust and they tell you
it's Arab With box cutters that did that
that is to preserve the money system when
they tell you there's a missile going to
Hawaii It's preserve the money system All right
When they tell you there's was the last
one missile going to Hawaii was and then
that the government shut down You know, it's
like let him let him shut it down
and when it's shut down shut it down
some more Yeah, just keep shutting it down.
It doesn't matter.
These are you know?
Something back to school It doesn't matter the
you know And here's the thing the ridiculousness
about the issue of the government what the
government's do anywhere in the world Where do
these people come from that are running your
government's?
Alpha Centauri Mars Venus, where are they coming
from?
Yeah, they're coming from the same crop.
You could take Joe Schmoe bus driver you
know common and how or Dick and Harry
it doesn't matter Put them up there that
you're gonna be in the same exact position.
Yeah So Yeah, and it's not it's not
a matter of being critical it's a matter
of being objective so It just depends on
what you want to dwell in at this
point I'd rather not be in an anyone's
armpit So Or crotch or whatever they want
to call it You know some unfavorable part
if an opponent grabs you and puts a
squeeze on you with a certain unfavorable part
of the body That's what's going on right
now.
You know getting the human affairs That's what
they don't yeah, and try to rationalize things
and have good thoughts Yeah, and and be
realistic Yeah, you pretty much most of you
will be here tomorrow and the next day
and so on what are you gonna?
Do with it to up the quality of
being here to put yourself in a sense
of?
Euphoria, you know when you have a meal
does it make you feel really good?
you know when you put on a jacket
or a pair of shoes or socks or
or Drawers or or sleep in the bed
anything that you put on your body does
it make you feel good?
Right do you feel good about the place
that you dwell in?
All right all these things just up the
quality of it little by little and if
it's something that you can't change immediately Well,
then just look like what you can't change
immediately to make it better Doesn't mean discarding
it or replacing it right?
right a Very simple way to make things
feel better by the way is like quote
-unquote washing a car something as trivial as
that if you have what's called a Engine
driven, what's not called an engine driven wagon?
Just keeping it clean just feels better.
I noticed that myself sometimes.
I'm like.
I'm just gonna stop I got too many
things on my plate.
I'm just gonna go wash the car It's
an hour Basically that is just taking time
out from anything else you could have been
doing and you just feel good at the
end of it Driving around in a shiny
new you know shiny old ride mm-hmm
So something as simple as that is just
an example Instead of it having just be
this rote ritual that you know people get
used to doing Okay, what do you think?
That's like a plan there.
Yep.
We did a We did a pretty good
chunk there yes Anything comes up.
Thank you.
I got a feeling for the schedule that
you're on I know that what they call
Tuesday nights is good for you for being
up to a certain extent and thank you
for doing you do and If something does
come up again sooner than next week, we'll
probably have Sam next week, or we'll do
another one Okay, any time any time is
good Well, you know the schedule so yeah,
I've got a feeling for it.
I don't know I think I've got it
down too much I know that it works
the way we've been doing it.
Yes.
It is yes, it is Well as always
I appreciate your time and in the information
The shame none of this is out there
but yes It is a shame like I
say I'm embarrassed to Be called a human
or man or anything if the little green
aliens landed.
You know there's no such thing Let's say
but right and say are you will it
you don't know you know listen?
They call these people humans, but you know
please don't count me in with them.
They're on their own Yeah Yeah, and you
don't want to talk to them or their
leaders so Make you okay.
Yeah, go back sign on the back of
the moon.
Yeah the the cab got All right, well,
thanks again Bruce and everyone and we'll catch
you again soon.
Thank you.
Yes, you take care now You are bye
-bye The
fight is fixed
Oh
Oh So
many people you have to be