Bring us in.
And there we go folks, we're live with
Greek and myself.
And how are you doing today Greek?
Oh okay, still here on this rock.
Yeah, I figured we'd just do a quick
sonic event.
It seems like when Sam comes on this
tends to go for hours, they don't have
to be.
You and I were just speaking about the
money thing.
Yes.
And maybe I should just recap that because
I wanted to just get into a little
bit of seasonal stuff for anyone that's listening.
But here's the thing folks, I want to
take it from the top because I recently
met someone, not recently, a few months ago
on the internet.
And I said, how did you find out
about the Greek?
And he says, well, I was going to
this coffee shop.
It was like the office where everybody meets.
Sure.
And one guy said, you know, I've been
studying the money system for 20 years and
I heard of this guy called the Greek
and I listened to him and in 15
minutes I finally got it.
Right?
Wow.
So he got it.
But most people don't and it's not your
fault because most people are subject to the
censorship.
And if it's not meant for you to
hear it or know it or acknowledge it,
you're never going to get it anyway.
It doesn't matter if they drill a hole
in your head and put it in there
physically, you're still not going to get it.
Just think about what, you know, the chip,
you've heard of the mind control chips and
all that stuff?
Yeah.
Why do you think that program hasn't been
put online yet?
I mean it is in certain cases, it's
experimental, but why do you think that hasn't
been affected or super successful?
Because it isn't time yet.
Well, yes, and also the cosmic censorship is
still strong.
Right.
So even if someone is trying to mind
control you or whatever, it doesn't work because
the censorship takes precedence and that comes from
the gods.
And they can censor anyone on any subject.
Right?
Right.
I'll give you an example on how subjects
work.
I was recently speaking to someone on the
phone.
They work in the health industry.
And I brought up, they're a cross country,
and I brought up a few things.
And their secretary or their, you know, they
said, well, they're not available.
They're in a class right now, teaching a
class.
I'll speak to you.
And I brought up a few things.
I said, well, I'm not technical.
I'm just spiritual.
I don't do technical stuff.
Right?
So what I told her was, oh, I
see.
Well, I said, can I get – can
I say a few personal things maybe to
you?
Certainly.
Or will you be offended?
That was what I told her.
Right.
Yeah.
And she said, no, you can't.
I said, this is what – there's no
such thing as I'm technical or I'm spiritual
or I'm into this or I'm into that
because, you know, what you're into is obvious.
You know, like someone like Yo-Yo Ma
could pick up the cello at 5 and
be a concert instrumentalist at the age of
8 is not what I'm talking about.
This is also given to you.
But this chick said she was not technical.
So I said, okay, let me just tell
you a little bit about yourself.
I have never met you.
I've been on the phone only for three
minutes, and I'll tell you about yourself.
And she goes, oh, I'd like to hear
that.
And I said, well, at some point in
your life, probably around your formative years or
just after your formative years, around the age
of 8 or 9, you were around some
adults and you heard some adults say they're
not into technical stuff, and this adult happened
to be either a loved one or a
relative or someone that was considered in respect
and in honor, and they got away with
saying that, and you decided that you're going
to go ahead with your life saying that
same thing because now you know you don't
have to get into exercising the mind in
that area, and because as a child you
realized an adult that was considered honorable or
recognizable or respectable said it, it was fine
for them, it'll be fine for you, and
you took that on to yourself as a
crutch.
And she was really, really quiet, and I
said, are you still there?
She goes, yeah, I'm still here.
And she was just really, really quiet, just
could not carry on the conversation with me
anymore.
And I was like, is there anything else
you want to have for Dr. So-and
-so?
And I said, no, that'll be it for
now.
And I said, did I give you a
lot to think about?
She said, too much.
But I said, don't worry, once we hang
up, you won't remember a word that I
said.
And I spoke, I called back about a
month later and asked, remember that conversation?
Yeah, I remember I spoke to you.
Do you remember what we spoke about, maybe
something that was a little penetrating?
And she goes, no, I don't.
Power of suggestion?
No, no, it's just, remember Men in Black,
the little red flashing thing?
Yeah, yeah.
Neuralizer, yeah?
Right, the neuralizer, yes, yes.
You will be neuralized if it's not meant
for you.
So back to the money system.
It's really, really, really simple.
There is an odd – before I start
off on how simple it is, here are
conspiracy theories.
Here's a conspiracy theory.
There's a legislative body of the government that
makes legislation with a quasi-government agency to
collect taxes to fund government actions and government
things, right?
That's a conspiracy theory.
In fact, that's not what is happening at
all.
Basically what I just said in regular English
would be you have bodies of government that
make laws with another quasi, meaning it's not
really a body of government, known as taxing
authorities, agencies all over the world.
And they levy taxes on people and people
in themselves in their minds think that they
need to do this in order to pay
for government services and things and roads and
whatever and the military.
And I'm telling you that is a conspiracy
theory, conspiracy meaning because there's more than one
body or individual doing it, but it's a
theory because that's not how it works at
all.
What is going on is – let's just
take it from the top.
Whenever you're living in a credit-based economy,
which is 99 percent of all the countries
in the world, if not more than that,
there is no money.
So you're living in a society under a
jurisdiction of a certain government.
No matter where you go, even if you're
a tourist, if you ask someone, do you
know what country you're in?
Yes, they'll tell you usually.
And then this is, well, who's in charge
here?
And they'll usually refer to some government entity,
right, whether it's a monarchy, socialism, republic, democracy,
communists, whatever, right?
They'll either mention an individual or a corporate
body politic, right, always.
In order for those corporate body politics to
exist, they have to have several things.
One of the things is a post office,
right, a way to move the post.
Another thing they have is a military, which
is not necessary really.
And another thing that they have is the
ability to control and issue currency or money.
All the countries have lost that ability and
they were put under a credit system.
So when you are in a country, it
puts the authorities, no matter who they are,
in a quandary for you to be there
to do work because there's no way to
pay you.
So they have to wrap you up in
all these unconscionable contracts or deeds, you know,
birth certificates, registration forms, literally wrap you up
legally.
So if you ever did anything and demanded
payment, well, they could just kick you out
and say, well, you waived that right.
So what everybody is functioning under is credit.
Let me just function.
Let me just go back to the functional
part of this conversation.
In America, there's a little bit of what
I'll cry there was politically and in the
media about these illegal aliens, right?
Illegal is just a sick bird, right?
An ill eagle.
Right, right.
OK, so the reason why there's such a
big deal, it's not because they're taking jobs
or jobs or anything like that.
It's because if you're here and you're working,
you can legally and lawfully demand lawful money
for payment.
You better get it.
Otherwise, it's thievery and slavery.
So it's very important that they wrap them
up with a registration form for citizenship because
then they waive that right to make that
demand within the body politic.
Why?
How does that done?
Because they issue you a number, a green
card, a Social Security number, registration number.
And that actually is not what you think
it is.
It is it goes through various agencies of
the quote unquote government that process it and
create another credit line for you.
That's how the banks work, and that's how
the government agencies work.
So the reason you are being taxed directly
when you work for a corporation, they don't
know anything.
That's why, you know, if you knew how
the money system work, you couldn't be an
accountant.
If you knew anything about law, you wouldn't
be a lawyer.
You know anything about the body, you wouldn't
be a doctor, so on and so forth.
Right.
Even if you knew a lot about food,
you couldn't be a chef.
It would be very because you would look
at all the quality of the crap that
you're getting to prepare and you wouldn't do
it.
All right.
So there's many levels to this.
So the level back again with taxation is
this.
It is simply a use fee because that
credit line is put out by a private
company.
Quasi government.
You know, how many times have you heard
someone taking something for granted simply by location
and time?
Like they have something called common law or
whatever.
And so like if you live if you're
a man and live with a woman or
a woman and live with a man for
long enough, they consider you to be husband
and wife, even though you're not married.
Right.
That's all the taxing authorities have that relationship
with the government because they've been around for
such a long time.
Now, to cover themselves from the beginning, they
actually gave themselves some kind of federalistic or
monarchistic logo.
You know, they make themselves look really official.
Do you know to cover those that are
paying attention?
OK.
So these taxing authorities, when people get a
25 or 30 percent of their paycheck shaved
off, that is simply a use fee for
using private currency.
No different than going to a rental tool
shop and rent an auger or a steamroller
or a jackhammer or a tile saw.
And you take it out for a month
or a year and you bring it back.
Do you just drop it off and say,
bye, guys?
Thanks.
Or do you have to pay a rental
fee?
You're paying that rental fee.
And if you don't pay it, there is
something owed and they take it serious as
a heart attack.
Oh, yeah.
Now, this goes under old laws of admiralty
and seizure and commercial laws.
Now, all of these taxation offices in the
U.S. and all over the world, those
little offices, you ever get a letter from
them?
It's not from the capital city.
It's usually from some other state or something,
no matter where you are.
Right.
Those are called franchise offices.
Whatever they collect, they keep a third of
it.
You see?
And the same with the police and detectives.
Police, not so much.
They get 5%.
Detectives and others get more.
Like DEA agents, CIF, they get up to
a third or a half sometimes, a third
usually, what they seize.
That's why they're so anxious to seize stuff.
So these old piracy laws are still in
place.
Now, they have to give you, if you
look in law, something called a remedy in
law.
That means that you're making someone sick and
then you have to also – if you're
going to make someone sick, you also have
to give them the remedy or the antidote.
You see that in film all the time.
They poison someone.
Tell me where they are and I'll give
you the antidote or you die.
Right, right.
Get it?
This is what's going on with the economic
system.
So there's a law in the US.
It's in the US codes, which have never
been validated as law, but they use this
prima facie law, right?
Just like what I mean by when you
see police, they're prima facie police.
They're not lawful.
If you go see what they're supposed to
be doing and were they ever really formally
in the position through the state, none of
them are.
Never.
It's just one of those things.
But do they still – does everyone still
call them?
Yeah.
You see what I mean?
So it's just prima facie.
Something you call on, it's good enough, right?
If you go to an American food market,
that's all prima facie food, meaning people don't
– they're hungry.
The package looks good.
It's cheap.
I'll buy it.
And if you ask them how does it
taste, oh, it's good or bad.
What does that mean?
It doesn't tell me anything about taste.
There's five flavors in the taste.
Which one is it?
I mean forget it.
It is too far gone.
Back to the tax thing.
What you will find out, the laws here,
Title 12, Section 411, basically tells you you're
not authorized to use that.
USC code, Title 12, Section 411.
United States code, Title 12, Section 411.
It's interesting.
It has a ring to it like 12,
non-metric number, and 411 is the information.
Right.
Basically it says you're not authorized to use
it and you could make a demand for
lawful money.
And there's also Title 12, 95A, 95B.
Those are other rules.
It will tell you about – by the
way, there's someone recently.
Someone sent me a Skype message, a talk
show person on radio, and they're doing like
five years in prison for tax fraud because
they sent paperwork in and they got –
you could basically take a piece of paper,
write half a million dollars on it, sign
it, send it into the right agency.
They will send you a check for half
a million.
But then when they get audited, they'll look
at it and say, wait a second.
We can't do this for this guy, so
let's just tell him it's fraudulent.
And if you don't know how to get
out of it, they're going to throw you
in jail.
Oh, my.
Because there is no money.
They're taking your signature.
Yeah.
So anyway, this guy isn't going to do
anything to you.
I said, are you joking?
No way.
Because – but I showed him a code.
It's in Title 12.
I think it's within the 95A, 95B.
And it states because it's a credit-based
economy basically and it's all spurious, there is
nothing that anyone can do that can be
considered fraudulent and held against them.
Right?
Because you know that comes from just signing
your name.
Right.
So you ever go into a store and
it says bad – attorney general will prosecute
bad check writers?
Yes.
There's no such thing as a bad check.
You can sign as long – because it's
credit, you can take – here's the thing.
You can take a bubble gum wrapper.
You can go into the trash bin right
now and all the used – as long
as it's not used toilet paper.
Whatever you could write on, sign your name
and give it to a banker.
Excuse me.
They can use it.
You can't use it.
Very few people know how to do that.
So here's the aspect of it.
You know I've talked about the cosmic censorship,
one's ability to see or being denied access
to information.
Right.
The word censorship in Greek is logokrisis.
Logo meaning word and krisis meaning crisis.
So censorship in Greek literally means a word
crisis.
But anyway, you have the censorship and then
you have people's infallible desire and unending desire
to want to prank each other.
You get it?
Right.
And you combine those two together, the pranking
and the censorship, and that's a really bad
formula.
And I'm not talking like – some things
they tell you don't do together and you
should.
Like for example, when we were really young,
I mean everyone knew someone was somebody's parent,
a teenager years.
Everyone knew someone had a parent that was
a hypochondriac and if they were away for
the weekend, they had a big medicine chest
full of hundreds of prescription drug bottles.
Right?
Everyone knew someone like that.
Yeah.
So we would all go there.
Teenagers, you're just learning about pot and alcohol.
So this triptych medicine chest with literally hundreds
of bottles and they were like, what should
we do with this?
Because we were – some guys were –
people were already starting to pop pills at
14 or 15.
This is in the 70s, right?
Oh, yeah.
So it was popular then and some of
the best suppliers were like those who had
uncles or dads that were cops because they
would always steal stuff from the evidence or
these medicine chests that were loaded.
So the point here about not doing two
things together is I said, well, if you
want to find the most effective one, find
the one that has the warning label on
it to not take with alcohol because we're
all drinking anyway, right?
Right.
That's the one you want because when they
tell you don't take it with alcohol, that
means you should take it with alcohol for
maximum effect.
Exactly.
Yeah, this is from the people back in
the 60s and the 70s, all the drug
experimentation and all that.
It was never really for me but I
just happened to be in the neighborhood where
I grew up in an upper middle class
neighborhood and this is what they did.
Don't think it's – you hear in the
news that it's ghetto and lower middle class
or lower classes do the most horrendous stuff.
It's actually – I've seen upper – they
can afford more, believe it or not, and
they get into more crazy stuff.
I mean they get into levels of violence
that you wouldn't believe it if I told
you because they have all the toys.
So anyway, so what you don't do and
do together is what people don't understand, and
what they're stuck in is the pranking and
the censorship.
Now, Title 12, Section 411, if you understand
old admiralty, old, old admiralty stuff, it's not
even in books anymore.
I mean it is but not online.
I've been looking for it.
Actually, there were a couple of good books
that were written in the 1800s and they
stopped because they just discuss admiralty, which is
piracy, seizure, trafficking and all that, right, for
thousands of years.
So they got tired of it and they
went into legal statutory stuff in the 19th
century.
But there are maxims in admiralty, and one
of them is that if you endorse something
in a transaction unconditionally that you are implying
that you are never looking for redemption of
that thing.
OK, what does that mean, right?
If you sign off on something, just your
name here, you can take this.
You should never expect it back because there's
no conditions on there.
What if you sign your name on something?
You could take this rowboat, but you have
to bring it back in a week and
it's $50 a day, let's say, right?
Well, that's different, isn't it?
Now that's a condition, right, you see?
But if you just take the rowboat unconditionally,
you're a fool to expect it back, to
have it redeemed or have it redeemed.
Like if the boat was lost by the
user, well, they're not going to bring you
the boat back because it's lost, but they're
going to bring you something of equivalent value,
coin, money or something on another boat.
You get it?
Reimbursement, yes.
Right.
So whenever you sign a check or just
sign whatever you saying that, hey, guys, I
got an unlimited credit line and I don't
care.
And you guys could change the rules.
And instead of me being the boss now,
I'm a slave.
It doesn't matter.
I'll just do whatever you say.
Any time you don't have to even play
by the rules.
You know, I'm just here.
Anytime you need something, let me know.
That's what you're saying when you just sign
your name.
Did you know that?
I did not.
How many times do you go to a
bank account or sign your name on something?
And that's what you're saying.
Let me just take it from the top.
Yeah, I'll just sign my name because I
got all the credit.
You see, I was given a credit line,
you know, when I was born and I
can just sign my name.
That's value.
And you guys can have it.
You could do whatever you want.
You can change the rules.
You could use any rule.
You don't even have to use rules against
me.
And just if you ever need anything, just
let me know.
That's what you're saying when you sign the
name.
Just like that.
Also, I want to bring up what they're
doing on electronic signature pads.
Yeah, you did mention that.
Yeah.
They're harvesting those signatures as original because the
moment you sign that thermal or active pad,
it goes into a digital form, and that
digital form in storage is the original because
obviously because the minute you sign it, they
clear it, and the next person comes and
signs it.
It's just a transmitting utility, you see.
The actual original is what's held in memory,
you know, on the file somewhere.
Those signatures are sold and used on other
contracts constantly, and you don't know it.
If anyone wants to go investigate what Wells
Fargo was doing a few months ago, there
was a few articles that they opened a
few million credit cards accounts and started drawing
credit, unbeknownst to anyone whose name they were
using.
You go look it up.
It's just happened about a year ago.
Yeah, about, you know, I was going to
say a year, year and a half or
so.
Well, it happened years ago, and it's still
going on, but they just happened to get
a little bit of a slap on the
wrist for that.
Now, whenever you're dealing with credit transactions, they
won't let you go unless you sign or
use the digital, you know, verification.
So how did they – how were they
able to get all – where did they
harvest all – where did Wells Fargo harvest
all those signatures from?
Let's see.
Little leprechauns coming into the bedroom at night
while you're sleeping and putting a pen in
your hand.
Let's see, maybe.
Did they clone you in Area 51 and
your clone signed it?
No, no, no.
Let's see which one.
Could it be those signature pads that you're
using?
Oh, yeah, I think it's the signature pads,
yeah.
And now the same thing is done with
the chip.
The chip is going to be a tough
one, and there's many reasons for that.
But the chip – there's a chip in
the car, there's a chip in the phone,
there's a chip in the car as well.
If you get a new car, any new
American car, it says right – there's a
sticker somewhere in the car by the trunk
or by the driver's door, and it says
that this car is equipped with electronic devices
that law enforcement can take control over.
Yes, yes.
See those stickers?
New cars?
Mm-hmm.
Something like that.
They all use a slightly different verbiage.
OK, so the deal with money is whenever
– there is no money, and you're not
going to get any money.
There is no way you're going to get
any money because this is coming from a
primal point from the gods.
But what people don't understand is when you
deal with the taxing authorities, you file a
return.
You have to return something for using, right?
So the idiots that if you work for
an employer, they don't know and they never
will know.
You don't even bother talking to them.
If you can evidence that you have not
been signing just the name and you write
a condition on it, meaning like lawful money
only, 12 USC 411 is a simple way
to write it on a check.
Now, most people get direct deposit.
Cut that shit out, I tell people.
Get it out.
You could say you want a hard-written
check.
Even if you want to take a dollar
out of it or whatever, it's fine.
I can't do the direct deposit.
You have to have it written out.
That's why I haven't done the PayPal yet
or anything on the site.
Because there is no way between all of
the shenanigans that they do, using the name
or the account that it's going to end
up into, that can be shown that you're
making a demand for lawful money or a
conditional endorsement each way.
And I got into it with them and
American Express and some other people on prepaid
cards.
They wanted all this.
I'm not asking for credit.
This is a prepaid card.
No, it's all credit.
I said, I know it is.
And I kept going up and up and
up, and it turns out that it is
all credit.
There's no way.
So it's very difficult to do anything electronically.
But the thing is, there is another way
I haven't developed.
It has to be developed where you develop
an electronic ledger that shows that each thing
is unconditional.
There's a condition to it versus unconditional.
That's why there's no PayPal for the Greek
or anything like that.
So what's going on is when you sign
the name on anything, you should make your
intention clear.
In other words, if someone says sign here
and you just sign the name, what you're
saying is, yeah, you know, I've got all
the credit and the signature is important because
it's the key element in the economic gear,
the workings of everything.
I'm the basis of it.
I'm the one that's got all the credit.
And I know you guys got laws that
govern this, but if you don't feel like
using the laws, that's okay.
I'm always here for you.
Right.
That's what you're saying when you sign the
name.
I hope I'm trying to make this simple.
Yeah, yeah.
There's people.
There's lots of evidence.
There's a couple of people that do lawful
money.
If you do a search, there's David Merrill
and his sidekick Joe and all that.
They do pretty good research.
He's got a good mind on the admiralty
side and all this, but in terms of
the other stuff, it's just hogwash.
I mean, they're just as censored as everyone
else.
And I'm not saying that because I like
them or don't like them.
I'm just subjectifying.
This is just hogwash.
So I can't send anyone over to any
place.
But it's a saving to suitors club or
something like that.
These guys get into all this stuff.
Right.
But when you look at their biblical analysis
and their biblical metaphors, it's laughable.
So they're very censored when it comes to
anything outside of the redeeming for lawful money.
So I can't recommend them.
See, because people are too naive.
Well, the Greeks said I should go to
this site or check this out.
So that means because if the Greeks said
it, that means everything there is good.
No, it's junk.
You know, they're morons, but they've got this
thing downright.
You know what I mean?
Right.
So anyway, that's just how it works.
You know, you don't go into a shoe
store demanding a chocolate milkshake because you're in
the wrong.
You get it.
You go next door where the ice cream
shop is.
So you have to be aware what you're
saying and what you're looking for, where you
are.
So how do you know it's a shoe
store?
Well, you know, you've got a shoe.
You've got a sign outside.
You know, you've got shoes inside.
It smells like even if you're blind, you
can smell it's a shoe store.
Right.
Just like when you go down certain supermarket
aisles, you know if you're in the garden
chemical aisle.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
So anyway.
So anyway, so this is what's going on.
Most people, you know, like I could go
to anything on the Internet and I'll tell
you, people send me links.
Hopefully, I mean, thankfully not anymore.
And in 0.2 seconds, I could tell
if it's junk or not.
0.2 seconds.
I could do five websites in one second.
I know it's an exaggeration, but that I
could, you know, even if you're blind, you
could open the door and you could smell
it.
You see.
So, but it doesn't mean that it should
be condemned and there's nothing good there.
Back to the money.
There's a lot of history of people that
have done the standard route dealing with, you
know, the taxing authorities.
And at the end of the year, instead
of doing a return, they send them a
letter and say, hey, listen.
I got – these are all these copies.
You know, if you're getting paid every two
weeks, you could probably do it.
That's 24 checks, right?
But if you're doing more transactions on a
private business, you have to keep really good
record keeping.
You must show that you did endorse it
conditionally versus unconditionally.
Right.
And say I haven't used any – you
know, I haven't used any money this year.
And by the way, if you want me
to pay taxes, I have to get some
lawful money to pay taxes.
Oops, oops.
OK.
Well, if we ever took any money out,
we're going to give it back to you
plus 5%, not a return, a small percentage.
We have to show deductions and all that
bullshit.
What they do is they give it all
back plus 5%.
Then you could go to the employer and
show them the letter and say they should
have never taken it out in the first
place.
And the accountant will implode.
He can't acknowledge it because if the accountant
that works for the company acknowledges that he
shouldn't do withholdings on you, he acknowledges that
his whole life is a lie and he's
partaking in – you know.
Right?
Right.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that's why, I mean, if I
was king, all the accountants get taken out
back.
They all get shot.
All the attorneys, they all get taken out
back.
They all get shot.
Well, we don't have any accountants or attorneys
anymore.
Great.
We just start some new ones right away.
It takes 15 minutes to train an attorney
or an accountant.
Not 10 years in school.
Yeah.
Anyway, no questions asked.
Yeah, brutality, right?
Yeah, right.
Yeah, you're really brutal for sure.
Exactly, yeah.
Because they don't know what universe they're in.
They're still – they have no idea.
So the idea here is that there is
no idea if you are going unconditionally in
everything that you do.
Right?
It's kind of like the old engineering student.
I'll give you a quick joke.
The old engineering student, he lives on the
far end of the dormitory on the campus,
and all the other engineering students live right
there by the buildings.
And they have really short breaks between classes,
and he's always late because he has to
go all the way down to his dorm
and walk back.
Everyone's like, you need to get a bicycle.
You need to get a bicycle.
And he says, OK, I'll get a bicycle
one of these days.
I'm tight on cash.
I don't know how that will happen, but
I'll look to get into a bicycle.
Well, a little time goes by, and he
rolls up on time on a bicycle.
They're like, well, you're right.
You got a bike, man.
How did you get the bike?
He says, well, I was walking over here
the other day, and this beautiful girl, she
was braless in a sweater.
She was on a bicycle.
She throws the bicycle down on the ground
and takes her shirt off and says I
can take anything I want.
So anyway.
The girl pulls her shirt up, throws her
bicycle down.
You can have anything you want, and he
goes for the bike.
Of course, you see.
Anyway, because you see, her intent for doing
that was obviously a sexual one.
Right.
But she said unconditionally you could have anything
you want, right?
Right.
She was not expecting.
There's no reason to explain this.
This is a joke.
It's stupid to explain it.
That's what you're doing.
Every time people sign their names on anything,
I don't care what it is, you're basically,
instead of pulling your shirt up, you're pulling
your pants down and bending over.
Yeah.
And say you could have anything you want.
And you know what?
The banker is going to take the signature,
but some scumbag attorney or accountant or whatever
down the line or banker is going to
take the other part, and you're going to
get it without a reach around.
Holy smokes.
You get it?
Yes.
Yeah.
And you're getting it, but you're so used
to it, you don't mind it.
How's that for one?
Ah.
You see?
Crazy world.
But if you've gotten this far and haven't
gotten anything out of what I've said, just
hit the delete button and do something else
because you're not going to get it.
I'm not saying it's hopeless because you're probably
censored.
You probably don't understand how the money system
works.
Another idea of how the money system works
is very simple, credit.
You have something called a potluck.
White people like doing this stuff all the
time because if you have ten people at
a potluck, you're expecting ten people to bring
ten items, right?
Ten dishes, yeah.
So usually when you go to a potluck,
whoever is there, it's almost mandatory that they
brought something to eat.
So no one will go hungry.
Everyone is chipping in.
There's an abundance of stuff, right?
That's what the credit system is like.
When you're born in a country, they create
a credit line.
It's 1.8 million in America.
I think now it's up to 2.6.
You could look at the Social Security Act
of 1935.
They've upgraded it in 2006.
I think now it's up to 2.7
million.
That's why if you know anyone that works
at the administrative part of a hospital, when
the long-form birth certificates, they're long-form
with the baby's footprints on it, when they're
transported out of the hospital, how are they
transported?
Wells Fargo security truck, armored truck comes and
picks them up.
Have you ever seen that?
Go to any county.
I have never personally seen it, but that
would make sense.
Yeah, I have personally seen it.
Yeah.
Yep.
So, and they do it every three days.
So, yeah.
Anyway, it's kind of sad, but it's not.
I mean, it is the way it is.
Now, here's the other thing about laws.
What people don't understand is how they vary
from country to country, even though they're the
same, really.
Like I know all the building codes were
made universal, meaning throughout all countries in the
90s.
So, for example, if I'm having a conversation,
if I know the building codes here in
America, and I'm speaking to someone in Australia,
which I've done, who works in that field,
I can tell them specifications on layouts of
plumbing, electricity, and certain things, and they will
say, yes, that's right.
That's how it has to be.
How do I know that?
I'm in the States.
Well, because I know that in the 90s,
those codes were made universal, international.
You get it?
So, it's pretty simple.
Now, when it comes to laws, for example,
you have something called reciprocate, reciprocity.
An example of reciprocity would be like a
driver's license or a passport.
For example, if you have a passport in
England, can you use it in the US?
Yeah.
Can you use it in France?
Use it in Russia?
Yeah, because it's through the State Department, right?
Same with driver's licenses.
Have you ever heard of someone having a
driver's license in a foreign country, and they
come and rent a car somewhere else, and
they get pulled over, and they have a
driver's license to drive a commercial vehicle on
the road, and the cop says, fine, because
it's only a few days, right?
It's reciprocating, right?
Money is reciprocating.
Can't you convert dollars to euros and euros
to dollars, right, where there's an established value?
So you can literally, if you know what
you're doing, I'm not suggesting this for the
listeners, and maybe you could, if you're savvy
enough, you can reciprocate any law to anywhere
that stands unless it's restricted only for that
area.
We've lost our stream, but keep going.
We are recording.
Okay.
So if you've ever seen, you want to
get the stream back up?
I'm working on it right now.
Okay.
But you can keep going.
We've got it recorded.
Now, this isn't going to help anyone directly,
because I've given you the fishbowl analogy.
If you come too soon, you can't come
too soon or too late, right?
This is just a mindset talk.
So let's take a pause.
I'm going to let me know when you
get the stream.
I'm going to get some coffee.
I could still keep speaking.
Yeah, okay.
But I'm not because of the distance.
I'm going across the house here, and I
might start losing the signal, so I'm going
to mute, and I'll be right back.
Okay, sounds good.
And we apologize for that, folks.
Apparently, the stream decided to shut down, so
we're getting her back up.
We'll get her going.
I'm back in the office.
Actually, I got some coffee down.
Did you stop the recording, or are you
still recording?
I got her.
I believe we're back online.
I'm just double-checking my work.
What do we got here?
Yep, I believe we're up and running.
I'm back in the office.
I actually got some coffee down.
Did you stop the recording, or are you
still recording?
There.
Okay, we're good.
All right, there we go.
Okay, folks, we're back.
Yeah, that's fine.
So I don't know.
Sometimes I think this conversation, the conversation, that
sermon at best, sermon just means speech, might
go unwarranted for most or not necessarily.
But I think it needs to be said
to fill in the veracity of what is
going on, meaning and how strange I see
it.
I think I was discussing something with someone
the other day, and I've said this on
calls with – I think when I was
doing the solo events.
The difference between those that know what's going
on and those that don't is not marginal.
It's not like whispering a secret into someone's
– to bring them up to speed.
It is so distant.
You might as well be across an ocean.
You're not even within the same – you
can't even see the person.
That's how far away they are in terms
of the mindset required.
Right.
So that is a physical aspect or a
social way to describe it.
But the cosmic primacy of it is that
they're being censored by the gods, you see.
Right.
So I'm going to put it
– attributes of the coming perfect society before
mop-up crew arrives.
Is it to be perfect as in all
follow the lawful teachings of the scriptures for
a brief time or perfect by more modern
-day standards, i.e. Both.
Things as they are now just working better?
Both.
But also if you remember what I haven't
stressed but I have mentioned continuously is –
I'm going to give it as a metaphor.
Water is necessary.
Water is good.
Just like good law, good instruction.
But also water is, if you look at
the insurance manuals, the number one destroyer of
property.
Right.
Water can kill you.
Is it possible to take a set of
instructions, rules, and laws and tweak them to
make them so overbearing that you end up
eliminating a third of the Earth's population?
Oh, yeah.
Yep.
Then he had something here regarding 2,500
years ago, Greeks comments that some people had
started to work out how to break free
from this realm.
Would that be the Egyptian pharaohs?
Often wondered if the mummification process was some
type of suspended animation where the mind was
able to wander and act in other realms
for a certain amount of time after mummification.
No, nothing like that.
You could be thrown into the landfill or
burned up.
It doesn't really matter.
Mummification is a form of – what do
you call it when you formally bury people?
But a funerary rite, just like in the
Hindi culture, their funerary rites was a funeral
pyre where they burned the body.
Right, right.
I remember that.
Yep.
Yeah.
And in other countries, they just wrap you
in cloth and put you underground.
Yeah.
No, that's just a funerary rite.
It has no significance on anything other than
– to think that it does means you've
sort of fallen into their teachings, which are
false according to what we know from higher
teachings.
That's the other thing.
Higher teachings and lower teachings sometimes run parallel
and you can bounce from one to the
next, right?
Like three-phase electricity, you've got three hots
coming in, right?
That means they're all equal to an extent
but not really.
But then I have found in most cases
lower-level teachings are contrary to higher-level
teachings.
Look, we were just talking about the money
system.
Right.
I was having a conversation a while back
with someone regarding credit cards, and he says,
I called you Greek because I had a
really funny conversation with a credit card company.
I said, what are you doing using credit
cards?
He said, well, just hear this out.
They told him that he couldn't use a
credit card to settle the bill with another
credit card.
OK.
Then if I can't do that, then how
am I supposed to do it?
And they couldn't give him an answer.
Write a check.
Well, what is a check?
Where does the money come from?
And he went back and forth and they
kept switching him through all these people.
No one there knew who had an answer
for him.
Oh, my.
That's how stupid people are.
Electrolytes.
Yeah, I'm a drinkator.
I'm a drinkator and it's got electrolytes.
Yeah, it's in Brondo.
Well, what's Brondo?
It's got electrolytes?
Yeah.
This is the state – and I'm not
just talking about the common people, which are
just – don't even bother.
I'm talking about your higher-ups are in
total crap.
They're high-level people.
Whenever you hear me talking about people who
are stupid, I'm not talking about the commoner,
by the way.
I hope you people – Bill, I'm talking
– speaking of your very high-ups in
academia, medicine, legal, they don't know.
They don't know at all.
I mean just like in mediocrity.
The higher-ups didn't know at all either.
No, they didn't.
Excellent movie, by the way.
Oh, yeah.
It's a documentary.
Yeah, it's one of the best films ever
done.
So anything else?
Is Thomas hot?
Is he live?
There are 11 people on his – I
see – yeah, I see the 11.
You had a final one.
And thanks if you answered any or not.
I cannot listen live, so don't know with
regards to Ramos and Colossi and a bunch
of names here.
I see.
Oh, you got it.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Tall, I mean, one of the grandiose statues
of representatives of men's gods.
It's a very – Yeah, yeah.
No.
Thanks.
Low-quality questions.
Yeah, they are, but that doesn't mean you
are.
Right.
That's fine.
Thank you.
Thank you for bringing these up.
Now, Egyptology is a real interesting thing because
there were several Egypts, by the way, right?
People don't know about that.
You've heard of the dynastic and then post
-dynastic, the exos, where they were ruled by
foreigners, right?
And then you have to couple that with
the information that we get about that society.
There was an Egyptology craze in the late
19th century that lasted up until the 20s
of the 20th century.
That's why if you look at a lot
of architecture and haircuts and things like that,
they're affected through the early art deco thing,
a lot of furniture and styles.
And also here's the other thing.
When you're dealing with the Egyptians, their academics,
they're all liars.
I know it sounds like a pejorative thing
to say Greek.
How can you say are you nationally profiling
them?
Not really, but the Egyptians are liars.
This has been what I just said I
read out of something in the 19th century,
and it still holds true today.
What I mean about that is that if
you go to Egypt and you do research,
and every time you run into an Egyptologist
who is Egyptian, they have been told to
skew the information according to what's been put
out already.
You get it?
They don't want you knowing anything about what
they are.
Don't have one guy telling you this happened
here and this time, and the other guy
says that never happened here.
Yeah, so the hard thing about Egyptology is
you're on your own.
Speaking of links, I dropped one in this
morning about the— I think it was Egypt
that was going to start allowing the public
to see their ancient library in Sinai, I
believe it was.
Oh, okay.
Egypt reopens ancient Sinai library housing 4th century
New Testament.
Oh, New Testament.
Yeah.
That's going to be in Greek.
That's going to be interesting.
That's like saying 150 years from now, if
we had that much time, they're opening a
library to show the U.S. Constitution.
But it's written in Spanish, though, and it
was written in Spanish around 2050.
You get it?
Yeah.
I've been keeping an eye on that.
I love the fact that we can go
and check out last 24 hours, last hour,
last 24, and that's worked out quite well.
There's a lot of interesting stuff in there.
Say that again?
About the archaeology, yeah.
Well, how else are you going to evidence
to the past?
Exactly.
Yeah, we're not talking about good records because
people, no one cares about evidence anymore, and
also no one cares about what's happening in
front of their face, what they actually see.
So the beauty of archaeology is it does
two things.
It provides physical evidence, and also archaeology seems
to be important.
It just hits that note in the mental
vibe.
Oh, archaeology means it's important.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, it's not like philosophy.
People will always use philosophy to downplay the
conversation.
Well, I don't want to listen to your
philosophy or something, right, or these other OGs
or isms or whatever.
But when you say archaeology, it means it's
implied that it's true and correct to a
certain degree, which it's not, by the way.
It's funny when they pull out 3rd century
B.C. pottery and they say it's 12
,000 years old.
I mean, prove it.
I mean, the thing is loaded with carbon
-14.
It can't be more than .500. Yeah, yeah.
So it's just really sad.
But, again, you know why people are endorsing
this stuff unconditionally.
What's funny when you go across even financial
sites and archaeology sites, history sites, these people
have forums.
Even computer hackers have a forum.
If you want to know about what's going
on with computer hacking, they have a forum.
Go look at it.
They're hackers themselves.
MIRC used to host thousands of channels.
I'm just that subject alone.
Yeah.
So I'm going to move this.
I'm trying to mute for a moment.
Okay.
So I'm going to maybe either say we
should call it an hour, or do you
want to delve into anything else?
I hope I hit people over the head.
I was going to say, remember when you
were talking about Genesis and you gave the
analogy of the starship, which is vast and
huge, and is it possible that the tree
was some type of mainframe artifact that the
ship itself used?
And I realize this is really a stretch.
Because I was thinking about the word fruit,
and if you look at the fruit of
a laptop, let's say, it's the programming, it's
the architecture, it's the bearings, it's goods.
Would that not be somewhat the same analogy?
It could.
It could be the writing room.
Right.
The word for garden not only means garden,
it means enclosed area.
Right.
A contained area.
Not separate, which is Kodesh, but gone is
gone.
Like vineyards are in a gone.
Right.
When you look at an orchard, an orchard
is a gone.
I would suggest that the control is at
the capstone at the top.
I would suggest.
We don't know.
Okay, yeah.
And I found it interesting that this happened.
They put it as the windy part of
the day, which leads you to believe there's
environmental aspects to this whole thing.
Just a lot of interesting questions came out
of that.
Yeah.
I'm sure it had its own weather system,
if you make it large enough.
The ether in there was large.
It was larger than a small country.
It would be big.
It was larger than, you know how in
American geography they compare size.
Usually they say it's bigger than the state
of Rhode Island.
They use Rhode Island a lot, right?
Right.
This was definitely bigger than the state of
Rhode Island.
It would have gone from New York to
Florida.
It was bigger than the state of Texas,
right?
That's huge.
Remember, only two things come from Texas.
Right, exactly.
So I would suggest that talking about the
Book of Generous, right?
Like we say, we'll talk about the Book
of Generous or, you know, when a baby's
born.
When a baby's born, they cut the biblical
cord, right?
Right.
So anyway, I mean these things, people need
to lighten up about it and look at
what's being said.
One thing I threw in some comments after
we did that last Sonic event was with
Sam there, who's also new at this, by
the way, and not to, you know, say
I think people like coming on and hearing
him and I go back and forth.
But he'll tell you, I mean, all this
stuff is new.
He heard the Greek on Freeman, so it's
been less than a year.
Yeah.
Actually, perspective.
He's doing very well for his time well
spent in it.
Yeah, he's got as much time in it
as everyone else, so don't be impressed.
But he has a good way of articulating
his own way of saying things.
So Sam and I have had at least
100 hours offline communication, you know, I mean
on private Skype calls.
Sure.
So, you know, frequent calling.
You know, I'm easy to reach and I
give time freely if I can.
Right.
But the questions, the things that I threw,
I believe, or, you know, what's going on
in there is when you look at the
book of Genesis, it was done.
The setting is the Israelites are out of
Egypt and Moses is in command.
Right.
And proof of that is when.
And there was, well, he was the only,
well, we just, there are verses in there
that show that he was in command of
them in a very unique way where you
could see verses in there where the gods
said we choose to speak to Moses face
to face with other men.
We just communicate with them through dreams and
visions, meaning, you know, the other prophets and
stuff.
Moses, remember when his brother Aaron and his
sister decided to kick in with Moses and
they got ousted.
No, no, you can't just because I'm talking
to him doesn't mean I want to talk
to you and she got leprosy.
Remember, you could read that anyway.
Right.
They got kicked to the side, you know.
So, so anyway, there's stuff going on here.
This is later on in Exodus.
I'm speaking on, but book of Genesis was
penned around there but also you have to
remember the influence that Moses's wife's father in
law had yet throw he was a king
of the area, and just like any king
you keep records.
And one aspect he advised Moses on how
to judge the people or reckon the what
the people had brought to him.
And you know, you have you appoint the
leaders of 10s of leaders of hundreds in
the leaders of thousands, you know, so it
would be like, would be like county state
and federal that's you know that's that's what
that is right.
The 10s would be the county state would
be the hundreds and the federal the monarchy
would be the leader of the thousands, you
know, and that just means that requests of
the thousands right.
And the requests of the hundreds and the
requests of the tens So he was knowledgeable
enough to take advice Moses take advice from
him at Moses did and I would suggest
that when you look At the genealogies these
genealogies were written Now they were not written
on stone because we don't see a repeat
of verses by the way I think I
did give a little hint whenever you see
something written and the sentence is duplex like
it's You'll see like the cat is black
and then it says the cat is black
again, right?
Yep, that's off the tablet.
That means that means it's off of a
stone tablet Yes, or a clay tablet because
that's how they put them in order The
last that's first sentence was the last sentence
of the previous tablets.
That's how you put them in order, right?
So Very rudimentary, but usually when it's transcribed
they they write, you know, they write the
whole thing out So it's a kind of
a neat thing to note, you know, you
don't see that in Genesis too much if
not at all So when you get around
what they call chapter 5 when it states
This is the book of the genealogies Yes
Five of Genesis.
Well, guess what?
All right.
This is another book within the book another
book also starts right around chapter 2 that
no one realizes You know, it's a total
it's a different.
It's not much of a book.
You can have a book.
That's one page long, right?
So is it really called a book that
really?
But if you read Genesis where I've been
saying this for a very long time over
a decade if you read Genesis chapter 1
It shouldn't end where they ended it.
It should end where it's signified or signed
off which is around Chapter 2 verse 3
or 4 or 2 or somewhere around there
Right where he says things were done and
then the father's name is used for the
first time That is another literal writing.
So that first chapter of Genesis is a
separate writing When I mean separate writing it
could be years Separate it could be hundreds
of years, right?
We don't know but it's not the same
document.
So Genesis is in essence a compilation of
Various books and it changes again around Noah's
flood because if you one way to recognize
that as a look at the blessings of
the sons of Noah Right.
Well one son does something bad, but he's
not cursed his grandson is cursed or his
son is cursed So, why does that happen
so we can get into all of that
and we get into the book of generous,
right?
So and don't get your biblical cords cut
one too soon, but yeah Anyway, I would
suggest that this is an undertaking that is
beyond me.
I mean I can do it.
I know I can do it I don't
have the inclination to do it directly, you
know right now, you know, meaning Hey, I'm
gonna do this presentation and all you guys
get right, you know, I'm not inclined.
Actually.
I think it should be done by others
My my best work is done by just
telling people how How badly they've been pranked
and censored?
About anything any subject, you know Because you
remember no matter how much information you put
out about the ancient Ritz if you're censored
and pranked It's just gonna irritate you more
All right, you got the censorship and the
pranking taken care of first Mindset now this
message.
Yeah.
Yeah, the mindset has to be correct.
Yeah It's not you know, we're not inanimate
objects like a computer Well, you know, isn't
it possible to get based on you know,
the capability any computer and download anything on
it?
Correct as long as you take certain CAD
programs and things we have minimum requirements Let's
just say, you know, you can download anything
on any on any machine We're not like
people are not like that if you are
being subject to heavy pranking and are just
endorsing anything that you run into unconditionally Would
be like a human in malware Yeah, yeah
walking him malware.
My my thing is to address the walking
human malware or those Those that are ready
to not be under the malware anymore through
the pranking and the and the censorship and
also Motivated by penalty is another, you know
people do things because if they don't do
them, they'll get in trouble That's not the
right the good a good reason why you
should do something You see ultimately that ends
up being the low level stuff.
So you I'm thinking Like, you know when
you when you sift or sort valuable things
out of junk or like when mining In
mining, you'll you'll crush ten tons of rock
just to get an ounce of gold, right?
All right, you know and and you know,
they're like, oh they call it a tailings
pile and a lot of times guys are
like Oh, yeah, let's go to this tailings
this mine shut down.
They have a tailings pile.
Let's go get what they missed Well, you
got to do both I like to do
both I like to get the good stuff
out right away and then go back to
the tailings pile and get whatever is left
That's valuable, right?
Oh in any for any subject, you know
So like recently there was someone with us
a health issue And what should I do?
And I said, well, you know do this
and he says well he'll quick I said
no that'll take about a month and they
were shocked because you know, everything else that
I've given them Advice on medical advice.
They it was healed and I'm immediately like
a day or two or three, you know
stuff That would have taken weeks But this
time I said this is going to take
and I had to I haven't really fully
explained to them.
Why?
Because it's to me it's obvious, right?
Because you have two two things working in
the universe two forces and they're opposing forces
And it comes to move one is implosive,
which is contractive cooling condensing then the other
one is explosive force, which is expanding and
heating and Evaporative and decomposing get the two
just straight, right?
So this manifestation this person had was explosive,
but it was from the inside coming out
Not from the outside coming in you see
right so fire would take a month So
there's not you see there's you see not
every there is no broad.
There is no broad brush You know swiping
every situation with what the Greek says You
have to learn how to diagnose how to
discern and all that But I see that
there is so much censorship and so much
pranking and so much motivation through penalty that
yeah Why bother you know, but I know
that there's some value to be gotten with
some individuals and in some situations so and
I've been saying the same thing for over
a decade and There's things that I'd like
to say and it's just simply not time
yet Because you have to get the background
on it And I will be saying those
things in the future about every about the
again about the money system about the body
about how to Eat about scripture and all
that.
So I'm still a little reserved right It's
kind of like here's another analogy if you're
in like a fun park, you know They
have all the rides and the roller coasters
and stuff, which by the way, I don't
like those things make me miserable Right, there's
no reason, you know, you know, there's no
reason to rush to one on the other
side of the you'll get to it Just
ride this way.
You know, I don't want this one.
I'll just go to this one You know,
it's like it's no big deal.
You know, if you're really young you want
the cotton candy?
I want to go do this ride first,
you know, and I want to ride it
again and all that I'm all I'm over
that you see so yeah, that's why I'm
back I don't think I was I'm the
right person to do the scriptural stuff I
might be more right than others right now
But we'll see let's give it some time
we'll give it another year or more Yeah,
I Mean, I do that.
Anyway, my favorite thing.
I mean look don't you want to know
about the gods?
You know, that's just a rhetorical question and
who they are and what they've given us
about Information about them other than look at
them what they've manifest and knowing their archetypes.
Yeah, sure Who doesn't well actually a lot
of people don't but you see so I
do that every day And I'm constantly meditating
on the the you know The books of
wisdom and all the commandments and all the
things in there constantly every day There actually
doesn't go a few a few minutes in
my waking hours that I do Not think
of these things but to put them together
and Do a presentation.
Yeah that can be done, but I don't
see it happening at the moment but I
think little spurious discussions coming across with those
that have the The ability to ask some
questions and in to have the insight to
delve a little further I'm all game for
it.
Just like you know with you or Sam
or anyone else, right?
But but it's it's all it's all right
there.
I think one of the things that can
help people out very much With their studies
is to just show how simple it is
You know, it's there the whole time right?
Why are you you know, just to well
Oh, here's the thing how to read out
of a situation how to just constantly read
out in other words When you go into
anything, whether it's legal financial health, even what
you're gonna eat for lunch or scripture or
whatever Don't deny your emotional desires and your
personal desires for but re-examine them You
say is that really what I should be
doing?
Just like years ago people used to come
to say Greek.
I hear you're good with healing and the
body and all that Well, I've got this
blah blah blah.
Oh, hold on.
Hold on.
I don't want to know I said the
only one that knows why you're sick is
you the reason You didn't slip and fall
or break something or have a been shot
with an arrow or burned, you know so
this is something that is conditional you make
a list of all the things that you
normally do and Make a list of all
the things that you normally don't do and
should be doing and then switch places Yeah,
and there's no way you're going to be
sick because you're sick because of what you'd
regularly do So what if most of the
questions and most of the comments that I
get is still regular?
So people are still going about how they're
going about whatever they're doing and they hear
some interesting Greek speak And then they ask
a question and it doesn't mix too well
or it wrestles or it doesn't it can't
elevate them out of that condition because they're
still considering what they're doing is what they
Can't is the only thing that can be
doing so Yeah, only Let's tie that back
into the book of Genesis, let's say Doing
a project on it I think Thomas brought
up doing the the two four hours or
four two hours or whatever is still just
scratching the surface But we could do that.
That's not a bad idea And it have
to be for the reasons that he stated
which would which would be great either way
You know the 50 bucks a person donating
50 people.
I'd be great.
I'd bring it or it why not?
I do 20 hours in Genesis then.
I mean, you know, no, we're only gone
to chapter 2.
But anyway, so then going on Looking at
for example the book of Genesis and when
you're getting information on that I'm really not
saying anything that you you couldn't see yourself
So there's even more importance there and instead
of giving the fish called the book of
Genesis speech or talk or sermon Which all
means the same How about instead of giving
you fish showing you how to fish You
see right Have I ever told you anything
out of Scripture that you couldn't go and
find in Scripture?
It's there for everyone and maybe it's the
way that I'm explaining and showing it to
you proving it out, but it's still there
So how about just having discussions on how
to prove things out and how to read
out of something?
Right, and that wouldn't yeah, that would be
fair enough.
Yeah I think that there's more value in
that Well, that's what everybody's people to speed
a little bit more to and it teaches
discipline All of which is highly needed Well,
the highest discipline is the anti discipline because
when you say discipline It means that you've
borrowed it from somewhere in most people's minds,
right?
Right.
So let me give you an example like
When you say the Bible I was in
a conversation a little while back these two
people they have internet presence They're into scientific
stuff and Walter Ross and I brought up
biblical.
So no, I don't want that's not biblical
I grew up in a non-denominational Christian
Church.
I know Bible said nope.
You don't know anything in the Bible if
you know that's really hard for them to
You might be familiar with this or I've
heard through principality of some sort But the
Hobby Lobby billionaires opened up the Bible Museum
in Washington DC.
Yeah.
Oh Boy, you know and what I looked
at it and I was like, yeah Well,
it's exactly what I've been saying for years
and years and years Not only are you
going to have the destruction of Christianity, you
know?
In other words the destruction of these houses
of worship and all that and the attendance
dropping But you're going to have more attention
to the scripture None of it will be
accurate like that.
You you can't have a week in the
since two years ago every week There's a
church bombing or a church blown up or
a church shooting or a church closing down
go look on the internet every now Yeah,
but now fast enough But this is what
and I've talked about this before when I
used to do the roundtables with Seth years
ago four or five years Oh, yeah, watch
that.
And also you're gonna watch the the biblical
text itself is Going to rise in prominence.
None of it will be accurate Now in
other words the reason why churches are being
Dispossessed and closed and burned or whatever is
not for the reason why that's happening up
what you're being told Obviously, it's not like
some Islamic terrorist or some whatever doesn't know
the gods are doing this, right?
All right, because they're tired of it.
You know, if the gut imagine if the
gods are tired, but no one's noticing it
doesn't matter They're still tired of it.
How do I know that they say it
read the text?
So what was your take on this you
know, you know that you brought that that
place up about the million names That they're
trying to collect.
I That was a just like a left
turn.
Yeah Well, I don't know you mean from
the Bible Museum is trying to collect Yeah,
you're collecting like millions of names and such
and I'm like, well, what are you gonna
do with that?
Well ask Wells Fargo.
Yeah.
Oh, well, yeah, you did bring up that
too.
Yes, I Cross my mind These people look
anyone public in any religious context right now
is rotten to the core It doesn't matter
how much lipstick and a mascara and if
they got a four thousand dollar suit on
it doesn't matter There are a few men
and pig.
Yeah They are rotten to the core And
and if it doesn't and the more that
better they look as human beings, you know
As people say or moral or whatever I'm
telling you that is just a strong facade
Some of them have a weak facade like
recently I see in the news.
The Pope is telling reporters inaccurate reporting as
a sin.
Oh, yeah All the cocaine and Yeah,
so, you know, I mean it's just sick
I mean it's just rotten to look I
mean Yeah, it's just and I'm not saying
it's rotten.
You know what?
I took the shortcut to find out these
people are rotten, you know, I got this,
you know I got the shortcut.
I read it out of Scripture Right.
That's how I that's how I figured out.
These people are rotten to the core, but
they're being used you see so Let's see.
There's another question that popped up here for
34 about 14 minutes ago or so greetings
just happened to glance.
Okay I'm unable to listen live right now
But if you're looking for discussion topics appreciate
hearing with the Greek in part regarding emission
theory relative visual and audio perception Appreciate the
links in chat the other night.
Okay, the mission theory the You know, you're
like it your eye gives off light and
your ear gives off sound.
That's how you hear and these These organs
I'll get into it a little bit and
we'll see if it develops or we'll just
call it a shorter recording, right?
Have you ever heard of like people that
worked on a rigger as riggers or music
musician?
band and you know sound people right and
they do the job for 20 years and
you know There's a guy walking around in
his 60s.
Oh, I worked with Pink Floyd for 20
years.
I've lost most of my hearing, right?
You've heard of that before When they and
they examine the ear the cochlea and all
that and whatever and they look at it
and they look at it There's nothing wrong
with it.
Nothing wrong at all, right?
I think it's a murder Or something, you
know follicles degrading Yeah, but they still can't
you know, it's not enough though They look
at Yeah, sometimes they'll say people got better
hearing than you and their hair follicles are
almost gone.
So what's going on?
Well This is the it goes into the
realm of Fantasia here.
But hear me out This is how you
do therapy, by the way The ear gives
off sound and it's a carrier sound a
carrier frequency.
No, it's beyond frequency.
It's actually longitudinal Right in many cases it
does in other words doesn't go far beyond
the body But it's really intense and because
you're used to it.
You don't know it just like you You
know, how many times have you realized that
you're walking down the street or walking across
the room?
When you're doing so You can describe it,
but it's not it doesn't fascinate you anymore.
Does it because you're used to Right, whatever.
So or speaking, you know, you know, there
was a point in your life where you
couldn't walk or speak Right, you had to
develop that okay, so it's developed like that
and you take it for granted So when
you have a sound coming in That it
has to meet that sound and and there's
no not real funky wave stuff going on
where they compound or cancel each other out
But what happens is there is a preponderance
of sound being emitted by the body and
a preponderance of sound Coming in that also
gauges.
Is it going to be detrimental pleasant or
negative or positive to your being?
Right, that's why some people are inclined to
like certain kinds of music and others are
not yeah, you heard of that.
Yes.
Yeah Okay Like I've heard someone say well,
I like music, but I can't stand anyone
No, no lyrics and no singing in it
and I'm like what you know other people,
you know I could see they look real
formal and they're into heavy metal and other
people, you know can't listen You see that's
where that makes a big difference on your
preference and taste.
Yeah Yes, the same the same with the
eye how many times do you heard someone
say oh I don't like the way that
looks right Or the same thing someone else
was that I like the way that looks
or that color Which obviously heard what's your
favorite color?
Yeah, I Because you have a specialized emission
from the eye.
There's a guy named Ross or something in
the 20s.
It was a psychotherapist and He said that
the eye remits light and he set up
a black box that people put their face
in and it had a Photoelectric relay and
they told him just stare at this just
look forward and he would they would set
off the relay, right?
You know, it was a very sensitive one
You saw him look right and just by
the moment.
He's into chromotherapy and all that what you
brought up before too, which is Another one
that's just Mind-blowing Gaudi Aldi and Babbitt
century and Dinshaw Gaudi Aldi Dish I got
all these play.
I like to bring him up because in
the 1930s he had a house on the
Jersey Shore and The the FDA I think
was new then and they were going against
him and he kept beating them in quarter
He beat them once on the suit.
So they Either he read in the paper.
I think he was gone or he was
and then arrived later that his house Which
was also his lab burned down And that's
what they put in the in the paper,
and that sounds pretty plausible Right.
Yeah that happened, but it also sounds plausible
that it was an accident but no the
eyewitnesses in the neighborhood said an army plane
flew really low and dropped something on the
house and Then it caught on fire right
a little bit different Yeah, yeah, so I
mean that interesting.
I mean you get the because by the
way the American military is for hire by
the way Oh, yes, they are Yeah, and
if you've got enough cash you could legitimately
do it you go through the JAG you
go through the attorneys there and they Set
up a contract and they do it and
you have to pay for all that stuff
and make sure there's no blowback You know
that right?
Yeah, there have been several.
I'm not going to talk about it now
Maybe in the future, but I'd like not
to the several cases where the Air Force
was used on people I mean, I'm not
talking about Waco now.
That was different.
That's governor gave up the National Guard I'm
talking about straight-up f-16s coming in
and you know shooting a missile at someone
and there was call then it was called
a Gasline exploded and you know those, you
know Then like all of a sudden you
see all these photographs of these old pipe
that after the truck showed up This was
the gas line that exploded.
Sure.
Yeah.
So anyway Yeah, it's pretty pretty crazy bunch
of people on this planet Fix this country
or no, they're not gonna fix anything.
It's gonna be just the way it is
until it's not So I didn't get much
into the eye in the in the ear
because you know I really don't know enough
to really pontificate on it and tell you
this is what's going on And this is
what we can do about it.
It's a fascinating start.
That's for that's for sure and And it
does require more and more research in It's
extremely subtle Yeah, because if you're going to
measure make the compression devices I call them,
you know measuring tools to measure it you
think about how clean or how?
Neutral the environment has to be to pick
up such a subtle effect Light coming out
of the eye and sound coming out of
the ear, right?
You know some that's why sometimes people you're
I hear ringing in my ear and especially
if it's not in the head where it's
just One ear left or right like when
I have someone around me if I hear
ringing in the right ear I tell them
put your ear against my ear.
Do you hear ringing?
Because that ring that ringing is not not
just neuro it's actually audible it could yeah,
you can actually you can actually yeah Oh
my wow You ever hear anyone saying I
ring in my ear get someone I'll stick
a microphone in there Very young.
Yeah, or if it's sensitive enough and you
will pick up a sound not I know
in some cases that tinnitus and all that
is different.
This is that's a swelling That's a glandular
swelling and it pushes on which then produces
a sound and then goes to the next
nerve Here's the other thing of other people
say, oh, yeah, this is a nerve thing.
Yeah, but how does it work a mechanism
works?
Just you can't just chalk it off as
it's the nerves.
No, it's good.
So we've got to trigger it now Now
the nerve actually has the output and then
that's picked up by another nerve and it
goes down because if it's just the nerve
That doesn't it's like if you sit on
a microphone, it doesn't make make any sound
It needs it needs an input it needs
an analog input there is there is an
animal function And this is still not comprehended
But these little things that I've brought out
if you have a deep Understanding of how
the body works and you add that to
it.
You'll probably be able to render some good
therapy Yes, yes.
Oh You know, how about you know recording?
Well the fact that we're inductive says a
lot And that's on every aspect of the
whole human body.
Oh for God's sakes you take a lifetime
Which That's where the potluck or thing comes
in you everybody brings something to the table
Yeah, something that took four hours to cook
you just show up with it So, you
know, we don't have to wait the four
hours, you know, bring bring what you cooked
up already, you know And that's used in
a negative sense, right?
You cooked something up.
So But bring it bring bring it forward.
Yeah there was a program that I was
While I used to use a long time
back where it was like a radio station
Walkie-talkie kind of setup and you could
have many people come in and it was
just basically push-to-talk kind of stuff
one in the only way that it would
work is one person could talk at a
time and Usually took a pause in between
but you had the ability to have large
amounts of people Contribute at once and I
might just dig back into that again.
That might be something of use But maybe
perhaps in the future and you can privatize
it.
Keep it to yourself and only the people
who know where it is can get in
and It's an online thing like it is.
It is an online thing.
I believe it was called Zello Zello was
what it was called caught with the call
letters on that Zello it's an application.
It can work on a computer or your
silly rectangle devices and Okay, yeah quite the
interesting feature I set up one a long
time back and I think it's still active
to this day I haven't really used it
in years, but I know it's still there
But uh, yeah, it was quite the quite
the fascinating little piece of the architecture Could
be of use for us somehow some way
somewhere And can always be recorded if needed.
I think that's just as easily possible with
the with this program Yeah speaking of before
we check off I got the Greek speak
Chetango open and it shows about 10 sometimes
11 If someone would if they could hear
us if anyone's on chat I'll give them
the 20 seconds just type even just something
I could hear you or yes in the
chat box to see if it's integrating or
facing off well with the chat or it
just happens to be out of consequence or
Coincidence coinciding that there are that many people
on chat right so if you're on chat,
but it is a message Put in and
see We have exactly 10 anonymous users at
this point And let me check the stats
on the stream here and At this moment
we have one two three four five people
listening So it's always good.
Oh, that's good enough.
Yeah, so in other words.
We're still hot.
We're still We're hot.
Oh, yeah, I've got Stream running in the
background just to make sure that and periodically
when I'm muted Okay, just like right now
right just like night.
Yeah, and there she is yeah, okay.
Yeah, she's good.
Okay good Yeah, just curious because it's checking
on the technology.
It's not a van.
You know.
Yeah, so it does cause we saying yes
Okay, cool.
Greetings cause would be All right If there's
not anything else, it's just call it call
it an hour and a half, right?
I'm gonna edit out what would you like
those to title this for today?
Not any oh, yeah, I'll let you pick
it this time.
Oh I'm not sure I didn't know that
they were being titled.
I'm I think I've been titling them in
rather Interesting format I think last one was
Greek salmon.
I and Okay, yeah, oh that's that's an
easy one just about what are you endorsing?
Yeah.
Oh good one.
Very nice I mean very good Yeah Whenever
you get just give someone An unconditional endorsement
with no conditions.
Yes You're giving them in this particular plane
as the New Agers say or this Society
or the people that are alive today and
have been alive Before you are going to
be Let's just say screwed shafted Manipulated.
Yeah And there are entire agencies corporations and
entire societies like the legal society financial society
banking society medical society Religious society that are
set up Everything To take of your unconditional
endorsement.
Yeah, and I remember once O'Chelle asked
me what do you mean by endorsement?
I just shook my head and I was
like, never mind.
Let's just go on to the next thing
Yeah, you know you're doing it all the
time and you don't know what it is.
Perfect example, right?
Yeah humanity, so Figure out what that you
know, people use it loosely in language.
Also, I endorse that you know, or you're
franchising Chasing so so this is an interesting
thing to consider How because it's all based
on the conspiracy theory known as taxation that
is a conspiracy theory that is the bankers
quasi government agencies what's left of the government
and Other societies that have all conspired together
To get the public to believe that when
they pay taxes That's a putting that in
air quotes That is actually the fundamental underlying
economic underpinning of the services They get public
services.
That is It is not And it's not
at all.
All of that is just taken from you
as a use fee I used to research
what they were using the money they collect
for and then I stopped because I I
got some blowback and Also, I got you
know, it's some dead ends that I didn't
want to turn around and start all over
Mm-hmm, but they can't use it Like
when you if you show up to a
taxing authority say hey you guys I you
told me I owe you a thousand bucks
Here's a thousand bucks.
No, no, no, no.
No, you can't just do that.
You have to fill out a form Because
they take the check the check gets thrown
out in the garbage They can't use that
then they take the other The the form
that you fill out and deposit that that's
where the current the funds come out of
the form signatures.
Yeah Yes, yes Endorsement Yeah, now you're the
bank, you know now when the taxing authority
takes the the tax check and throws it
in the garbage They tell the bank They
get the information up to tell the bank
that you wrote the check off of that
they did that and the bank your own
Bank, then takes a thousand on keeps it
themselves and you think that it went to
the taxing authority Because there's another fascinating subject
on the cage code and where that money
went after it was taken out and held
and Yeah, you get a bank statement and
it shows you where you know Not only
you know the statement with the the activity
on the account and where you spent it,
you know circle K this bank utility It
doesn't say that it actually they sent them
anything.
It just says they were notified by them,
right?
carefully notifications So you you swipe the card
you get, you know Ten bucks at the
convenience store and you see that on the
statement that the bank is nowhere Don't you're
presuming the bank sent them the money?
Yeah Yeah that institution notified them that you
swipe the card so that bank now has
to take out the money that's visible to
you So to keep plausibility going but that
money never left bank So they used to
say assuming makes an ass out of you
and me that's right and this Yeah, if
the planet is full of asses, can you
call them asses?
I mean, it's it's actually a downgrade on
the real asses, which are correct and the
donkey So this is really that that's why
I've said before this is you you're in
an unreal big unrehabilitated Unrehabilitatable condition can't fix
it.
You just have to it's kind of like
the junk cars now Society and the whole
surface not the planet itself, but what you've
done with it you ever go to a
junkyard and they put the car in the
crusher and You know, they haven't quite hit
the lever yet to make it into a
ball of steel But you know at that
point who's thinking let's get some Bondo and
some new parts and make it a let's
bring it back Yeah, only an idiot think
that it's already in the and it just
didn't get to the crusher because it's a
mistake or a coincidence There was a lot
of determinations made before I got to that
condition Right, and it's not fixable.
It was considered unfixable way before it got
to the crusher right now You're at the
crusher and they're ready to pull the lever
the gods are you ain't gonna fix anything?
Best thing you could do is if you're
near it just you know, look the other
way So a piece of glass might shoot
out or whatever, you know, or a piece
of shard and catch some shrapnel, you know
So that's yeah, it's not fixable, you know,
the way The redo is yeah, you're waiting
for the ultimate This is what people are
waiting for and they don't know it the
ultimate police state but it won't be done
by a bunch of sniveling ignorant cops and
Law enforcements or whatever you call police state,
you know military or whatever No, no, no,
it's gonna be done by the gods and
they're gonna be benevolent, right?
Get ready for a non privacy state.
You will know you will have no secrets
at all You don't have any secrets right
now to those that matter Anyway, can you
tell someone a secret or put something away
that you're gonna hide from the gods or
the angelic beings?
No All right, don't they matter more than
what people do?
Yes, so if this is going to be
known so all these things that you're being
told right now You're gonna have a new
world order.
Yes, you are, but it's not going to
be the one they now these are things
to look forward to a Global level police
state a no privacy state and a new
world order, but it's not going to be
run by men It's going to be run
by the gods and that's how the restarts
going to work Yep, and you're being shown
all that right now and no one knows
how to read it.
Isn't that funny?
Well, they see it But they all they
do is snivel and complain about it based
on the censorship and based on the poor
input that they've got So, all right Yeah,
yeah, well, we just chewed up another hour
and a half just like that again Greek.
Well, okay Well, thanks very much.
Oh, yeah, the pleasure was all mine as
always a lot of stuff to go over
again But well worth every second Well worth
every second.
Yes.
Yes, it is great.
Okay.
Well, thanks for doing it Bruce and not
a problem there You also sir.
Bye.
Take care