Okay, so I had to cut the Greek off early last time, which I regret to inform everyone,
but we get to pick right back up, arguably where we left off, and we also have Daniel
Sala.
Hello.
So, I have stuff that the Greek and I can pick up on, but you wanted to make mention
of a couple of interesting points.
Well, yeah, I did listen to your previous show, and it caught my attention a few certain
things that you hadn't brought up before the Greek, and I had to, you know, pounce on them.
Namely, one of them was the idea that, well, we discussed this in private, but since we're,
you know, going for fresh intel, might as well bring it up, the idea that we all know that
the theory has been disproven, and whatever you see through the electron microscope is
usually an artifact, and the simulation of the culture medium result in the same thing,
whether you use a sample or not, and all these things.
But you mentioned that pandemics are real, for you gave the example of smallpox, and
I was wondering if you can elaborate on what's the real mechanism of how pandemics work.
Okay, great.
Environment.
Where the body starts and where it ends is actually the environment that's around you.
For example, I brought up, if you recall, seasonal eating.
Many people get what's called the common cold when there are seasonal changes.
There's also a cold that happens when it goes, not only people used to getting the cold,
let's say, when it goes from warm weather to cold weather, but there are also people
that come down with certain discomforts and what they call illnesses when it goes from
winter to summer.
For example, very often in many parts of the world, especially in northern latitudes,
there's something called the rotting season.
I would consider it a fifth season.
You know how we have the four seasons, this would be a fifth season.
This is determined very simply by, you'll notice that certain times of the year, depending
on where you are on the Earth, the milk doesn't stay as fresh, or things don't stay as fresh,
they spoil much quicker.
If you have a wound, it takes much longer to heal.
In northern latitudes, above 30 or 40, let's say, it happens when you transition from winter
to summer.
On the more equatorial, it's from summer to winter.
That's just an example, and it has nothing to do with temperature of the refrigerator
or temperature.
It has to do with the seasonal change, which is an energetic change.
I think we brought up, if you look at the cross-section of lung tissue, intestinal tissue,
stomach tissue, you'll notice that there's nothing that goes through those tissues.
They're completely sealed.
We did briefly cover it.
Yes.
So, the process of induction, which is very similar to in electronics or electrical engineering,
the process of a transformer coil, where you have, you take one voltage and you step it
down or step it up, when you have a wound coil next to another coil.
And they cannot still explain how it works, but they do know it does.
So, if we call it induction, and we look at the term, and it's typically used as a social
term, but typically used as an engineering term, it's fairly accurate.
So, things affect each other by proximity, okay?
Like for example, wireless, the idea of wireless.
What happens with the body, if you want to just take it to a quick end, is you have perturbations,
which is disturbances.
Things have templates and predetermined outcomes, believe it or not, in nature.
And when those predetermined outcomes are disturbed or changed through perturbances
or disturbances, you have disease.
Very similar to, like, if you're driving a car up a hill and the air becomes too thin,
it doesn't run very well because the air-to-fuel gas mixture starts to go off, let's say, right?
So, the next concept for illness is the human body is constantly radiating energy.
Let's just not call it energy because we need to find an energy, its ability to do work
and other things.
But we have a field and an atmosphere around us, and the quality of that atmosphere either
promotes wellness or disease.
So, that is the basis, the basic foundation.
It is a non-physical, in other words, when I said, if I recall, the Revolutionary War
did not start in America until there was a smallpox pandemic, was what I brought up.
Typically, they wait for pandemics.
That's why, for example, what they call the Spanish Flu did not start in Spain.
It's very well known it started in Kansas.
It was started by the medical community and the political community, right?
It was known as the American Army Flu, and the only reason they called it the Spanish
Flu is because it was first acknowledged when the Americans landed in Spain.
So, you'll notice that whenever you see a spread of disease like this, it's a geopolitical
ploy to go into war.
The Black Plague was also very similar.
It was started by the Asians going back and retaliating against the Europeans.
I think I have described in private how these things are done.
I don't think it's good to describe them publicly, but what I want to just maybe add, I'm kind
of all over the place here because it's a big topic, and I know people don't have the
basis and the foundation of it, so hopefully being more roundabout in general, at least
to get them away from the viral theory, is best.
But I don't think it's best to talk about how these things are really done.
For example, people still have the misunderstanding that there's some laboratory that has these
agents in a petri dish and somehow spreads them to the population.
That will never happen.
You can attempt to do something like that, and you might quote-unquote infect maybe a
dozen or so people, but it won't spread, you see, because there's a big myth about
that.
You know, let's say something getting out of a lab and spreading worldwide.
That is a myth.
That is just as big of a myth as 19 Arab hijackers with box cutters vaporized the World Trade
Center.
Right.
I think it's a safe assumption to say that it happens non-physically and through EM frequency,
right?
Yes.
And that part of it is also just mother nature.
For example, when you put a beaker of water with DNA in one corner of the room and another
one with nucleic acids, aka the ingredients of DNA, in another beaker of the room, and
then you shine a UV light on the one with DNA, the sequences in the beaker with DNA will automatically
form in the other one.
Yes.
So that's a glimpse of how it works, I guess.
What would you say is the proportion between the ones that are intentional and the ones
that are naturally occurring?
But if you actually look at it from a very high vantage point, there is nothing natural.
It's all under control.
There are systems in place, like, for example, the self-driving cars, are they naturally driving?
They might seem like they are, but they're not.
There's a pre-program in there, right, and devices and sensors.
That's one thing that everything is in reverse.
In other words, what we think we're actually developing technology, meaning we, the human
collective, is we're not really developing anything, we're just rediscovering and rediscovering
methodologies.
Right.
Yeah.
Now, one more thing about the idea of contagions and all that is, and you said EM, it's actually
beyond measurable, current measurable frequencies, because the way the frequencies are measured,
let's say, if you were to say the frequency, I would say it's more Planck, max Planck,
you know, in other words, these are frequencies that are beyond measurement.
There are ways to measure them, but not with current devices, because all of the current
devices are based on pressure.
All of your frequency measuring devices use sensors and transducers that rely on a certain
kind of pressure to activate them to create an analog readout for the observer or the
scientist.
These types of frequencies do not work that way.
They work on a scale that is not pressure-based.
In other words, you might say vacuum-based, but not vacuum as people would consider a
simple vacuum, but a biological vacuum, which is an oscillating vacuum.
Like people talk about nitrogen, for example.
Nitrogen is a pulsing gas.
I can prove it, right?
Also, you have to go back to a very simple methodology that the ancients used of hydrogen.
We consider hydrogen to be the first element on the periodic table, but the word hydro
means water and gen means to generate or create.
So literally, that is a gas that has to do a lot with water.
So just like you mentioned, there are many experiments where even beyond putting the
DNA replication in one room, it's actually happened across the world, where they have
distilled water across the world and they send a certain frequency and within eight hours
the same DNA appears in distilled water.
Okay.
Through sound?
Through electromagnetic frequencies used as a carrier wave, right?
So one thing you have to understand is, like for example, in ancient texts they talk about,
especially the biblical texts, when something is deemed spiritually clean or unclean.
Like for example, if someone unclean touches something that is inanimate, then that inanimate
object now takes on that status of being unclean.
We might visit it as something like, for example, if someone, quote unquote, is diseased, lays
in a bed or touches something and you touch it, then you become sick.
There is a very strong truth to that, by the way, that it is conducted that way, but it's
done through the actual hydrogen.
But again, if I say hydrogen and your mind goes to the first thing in the periodic table,
you missed the point, even in the name.
Like, here's for example, let me just give something, because everything ties in together.
The concept of alchemy, one of the biggest disappointments on the Internet for me is
researching alchemy.
If I told you almost 100% or 99.9999% of all the ideology and philosophy about what is
alchemy on the Internet is false, it would be hard to believe.
But let me explain.
Once the alchemist or the person working with spiritual transformation, let's say, of the
world, that's really what it is, because alchemy is not just material, but it's social
as well.
The concept of the good wizard or the good witch versus the bad wizard or the bad witch
is a social thing, based on the characters of those two polarized, but it's actually
alchemic as well.
So, for example, you hear a lot about lead being turned into gold.
And here, I'll give a little secret on how that's done, because that's the difficult
way to do it.
You need a very high spiritual development to do that.
But the way that lead is turned into gold is by having lead, listen very carefully,
is by having lead release hydrogen.
Because once the, if you look at mathematically on the periodic table, if the lead releases
one proton and one electron, it becomes electrically, on the periodic table, gold.
Okay?
So, people are looking, well, how do we, they have done this in high-energy nuclear reactions,
by the way, when they use lead shielding, they've come back after months of running
high-energy nuclear reactions and find it's coated with gold.
But really, what's happening is if, again, if we say hydrogen is just one electron, one
proton, whatever, you miss the point.
So the point here is, how do you get a hunk of lead, or a big mass of lead, to release
hydrogen, because once you get the lead to release hydrogen as a gas or a liquid, you
will end up with gold.
And I just gave a very big secret on how it's done.
Stop looking at it as electrons and protons and look at everything in hydrogen.
Like for example, you know, there's a lithium shortage, they say, or it's very, it's a major
industrial proponent for the way the future is going with power storage, right, with lithium
batteries.
Why not take hydrogen and helium, which are more commonly found, and combine them to make
lithium?
Why not do that?
For example, petroleum, this is what got Germany in trouble in World War I.
It's a hydrocarbon.
Why not take CO2 gas, which is readily produced and readily available, and water, and make
hydrocarbons?
And by the way, there's plenty of companies and laboratories online you could look up making
petroleum from water and CO2 gas.
There's a process, there's one process called Towns gas, which was done 150 years ago.
And this goes on and on.
Yes, you do need catalysts.
You do need a catalyst.
For an example of a catalyst would be vegetable shortening that's used for cooking, Crisco
or whatever, right?
It's a vegetable oil, but it looks like butter or margarine.
That's water and oil mixed together.
Now you can mix water and oil all you want, all day long, all week long, all year long.
It will not turn into a buttery consistency.
But if you take the mixture under a slight vacuum and you run it over a very high purity
nickel beads, it will form into this buttery margarine shortening condition.
Now if you test it, you'll say, you know, the typical chemist will say, well, it's because
the nickel is going in it.
No, you'll test it.
There is absence of nickel.
There is no nickel in the material.
It's just a catalyst.
So the other part of understanding is a catalyst.
And this, all of everything I just said ties back to how the human body is in a state of
health or a state of disease or a pandemic is spread.
I know it might sound cryptic, but I'm laying down the basic foundation.
You know, instead of teaching young children the alphabet, don't they have little wooden
blocks and things to play with and then they, right, you see?
So these are the little alphabet blocks of how, quote unquote, disease and the disabling
of the social condition is what I call it, right?
Because people can't be social if they're dropping dead, right?
Yeah, I think the difference between alchemy and chemistry is that chemistry only studies
dead things. And even if you wanted to instruct people about alchemy, they just
wouldn't be ready for it, both in terms of practice, but also they were just rejected.
But apparently the stronger ones, there's a hierarchy and you have the plant and then
animal and then the metal kingdom that can provide you all these essences and elixirs.
But even then, when it comes to the most advanced part of alchemy, like getting the
elixir of life that basically gives you immortality, that one can actually be extracted
from any mineral, any living being or anything in existence is just a matter of skill.
And then I heard that the study of alchemy, if you master it, it's always going to
essentially be oriented beneficially because it has been attempted to be appropriated by,
you know, more nefarious entities.
But they only partially succeed, never really grasped it.
Yes, there's a fellow called Ibrahim Karim, he does biogeometry, by basically making a
squiggle or a line on a technological device that's putting out bad energy into the
room, will change it, for example.
And having a discussion with him, and he said this publicly on his own, is that every
time someone comes up with a beneficial methodology, regardless if it's using symbols
or alchemy or concepts, immediately it's grasped and there are 300 people versus one
that try to use it for bad reasons, right?
Look at pharmaceutical companies, people think they're pharmaceutical in medicine, but
they're not classified as such, they're classified as chemical companies.
And the biggest business that chemical companies have, just like any business, is you
want military contracts, right?
And what does the military use the chemicals for?
Right, so it all works the same way.
I wanted to just not maybe, for some people listening, they might think because I brought
up alchemy, it's a deflection from your original question, but the original question
was the contact or the contagion theory.
One thing I just want to say is also very, very important, which I've repeated myself
over the past more than two decades, but at least a decade on the Internet, is no
matter what field you look at, there's over 15,000 different fields in industry and art
that people can look at in the Thomas catalog, which is an industrial catalog.
Every one of those is wide open, completely wide open.
In other words, when you look at all of the what academia is putting in front of you, I
call it grunt work.
It's no more than going to the biggest construction site in the world and seeing ditch
diggers. Ditches have to be dug.
They have done nothing more than dig ditches.
They have not elaborated or developed anything at all.
So any field you want to anyone wants to explore and you look at a body of knowledge
that looks complicated and all that, it's done that way to deflect you.
All of the all of the fields are completely wide open.
Every single field doesn't matter what it is.
That's why we have the secret technologies and secret societies, right there taking
advantage of what can be developed and basically the trash or the rubbish is given to
the public. So again, just to go back to the idea.
Of anatomy, because if we're talking about disease and pandemics, we have to look at
of what in the anatomy will notice that the human body or any or a plant or an animal,
nothing ever goes through from the exterior environment into the body, passing through
by absorption or osmosis or anything like that.
Physically, it's all by induction.
Do you have the lungs and bladder and things like that?
Kidneys, which are called the sacs, where something goes in and then back comes out
the same way it went in, but nothing penetrates or is ever absorbed.
So once this is understood and people hearing my voice, because I think I might be the
only one insisting on this, by the way, that but nothing ever goes in or comes out of
the body directly.
Once people hear this and meditate on it, whether it's for an hour, a week or a year,
they can pick up from what I just said and say, then what is the concept of nutrition?
What is the concept of disease?
What is the concept of growth?
How does it work?
You see?
Yeah, I hope my whole goal, sorry, is to inspire, is to give out because I've been
sitting on these things, by the way, for a very long time, most of my life, and I keep
looking at other people producing a simple result.
And it's kind of embarrassing to not see things broken down in such a simple way
because I'm very private.
I'm not a I'm not a good speaker.
I'm not the most intelligent person or whatever.
But it's kind of embarrassing that these points are not being made by other humans.
Yeah, they're very slowly starting to eat their way.
They admitted to themselves that every time they're asked, you know, the mainstream,
they admit to not being able to see an isolated in the fluid of any sick person.
And a lady has taken upon herself to send this to every major medical institution in
the world, and they all either dismiss her or just admit to the fact that they don't
have it. But you also mentioned that you have a certain pet peeve with a few terms,
like I think quantum mechanics being one of them and the principle of uncertainty, how
it's all at random.
There is no it's it's it might seem random, for example, two nations going to war when
the frontline infantry of one moves on the other, they might look very random.
But I'm assuring you that it was very well planned before the same.
If you watch, let's say, an American football game, you'll see a line of scrimmage.
They blow the whistle, the game starts and they're running across the field.
It looks very random, but I assure you it's been planned very, very closely before it
started. And another one is the concept of space time that matter and space.
Well, that's that's about as ridiculous as anything else we've heard that the public
talks about. Now, picking on these things, let me just say almost everything that you
hear everyone talk about is a form of propaganda or a psyop, right?
But it's so big that people don't see it.
Just for example, if everything was hot, there's no hot because there's no contrast.
So if everyone is a criminal, there's no criminal, right?
If everyone is good, because there's nothing to say he's good or bad.
OK, so what's happening is when you put out stuff like quantum and time space and all
that, by the way, which I use as a litmus test when I listen to people speak about
their experiences or science, when the moment I hear that, that's a major red flag that
this person has been very heavily propagandized.
Number one, innocent, or number two is a shill, or number three is just people want to
hear this person speak for some reason where they should be using their breath to cool
their porridge instead.
But anyway, yeah, these are all concepts.
Let's just go specifically space time, because if I just sound like I'm knocking it and
not giving a reason, whenever you say something, you have to give the how and why.
Space, even Tesla said this, has no attributes.
That's why it's called space.
Nothing has no attributes.
Zero has no attributes.
So the space is merely the points that are described as such for communication purposes.
So there is no space.
In other words, the space between objects defined as something is ridiculous.
It has no attributes.
It's the objects surrounding what they emanate that define the situation.
Time is the same.
There is no time.
If there is no motion, there is no time.
What we consider time, especially I poke fun at it, calling the mechanical clock the
wind-up toy known as the clock or the Pope's work schedule, or no matter what form of
time convention you use in seconds or whatever, because each culture had their own way
of keeping time, it's just a matter of recording events.
So when you're communicating a memorialized event, something that happened or something
that will happen, you're giving a measurement, a metric, on how to perceive it, right?
Because if I say it happens in five million seconds, it's easier to say six months,
right? Because five, you see, so we break these things down into different levels.
But there is no time either.
Time is merely the measurement of and recordation of events.
Right. So bending space time is just about as ridiculous as anything else that you hear
or, you know, manipulating space time.
And the same, sorry, the same with time travel.
You're never traveling in time past or the future.
You're traveling to a past event or a future event.
And it's not done by time.
It's done by each event having its own, let's say, frequency in existence.
And the moment you're able to measure it, you reproduce it.
And then you somehow, the reality we're living in will reproduce it enough that you
will actually be there.
Right. And would you agree that the most maybe overlooked aspect, even more than
electromagnetism, is the rotation of all these particles, the subatomic particles?
Because even the electrons spin, and if you were to adjust to account for that, then
you could actually observe it with the right apparatus.
And then it would make sense that this absorption caused by the rotation of
everything is what also causes the gravity and so on.
And that also is the mechanism behind astrology and astronomy.
Yes, astronomy and astrology are reverse the definitions, by the way.
Astronomos means knowledge of the stars, and astrology means the laws of the stars.
So they should be reversed, you see, because the astrologers never get into this
planet being in this house when it's made of gas and has this or that quality to it.
You see, astrology is knowledge, and on Nomos, astronomy is the laws.
So when someone is looking at astrology or an astrologist, they're really an
astronomer and vice versa, just like the words soul and spirit have been reversed,
right? But in terms of gravity, there is no gravity either.
The gravity is a resultant of the ether.
The ether, OK, everything in nature, even the hardness of materials, is pressure
differential. In other words, something that has more pressure will resist
something of less pressure, and something that has more pressure will want to go
towards something of less pressure.
So the reason you have the illusion of what they call gravity, which is just a
name, is that the earth represents a sink, like something that falls into
something else, of ether.
So, and when you understand the potentials are reversed, where the ether goes from
low to high potential, the earth represents a high potential ethereal zone, as many
of the planets, actually all of the planets do, and the low potential ether is
rushing towards it, and the ethereal component in matter is being dragged along
with it. Very simple.
The electron and the neutron and the atom is a fallacy.
It is just a communication.
For example, the ether expressing itself in material form, as material, is the same
as, let's say you have a fan, an electric, you know, a wind air fan on your desk, and
it's off, and it has, let's say, 10 blades on it.
You can put your hand through that fan anywhere, and it just, you have a lot of
quote-unquote space, and you can move safely through it, correct?
What happens when you plug that fan on, and it's spinning at 1500 RPM?
Those 10 blades start spinning, and that zone appears to be solid.
Anything you throw within that zone that the blades pass through appears to be
solid.
The same with a wheel on a bicycle, or anything that's rotating.
And the faster that it rotates, the more solid it appears to be.
So, if you're moving at the same speed as that fan, you could probably negotiate some
kind of traversal through that, or if you stop the fan from moving, you can negotiate
a traversal through the fan, like as if when it was not plugged in.
And that's simply the condition of matter.
What they're calling the electron potential, which is, electrons in science is EV, right?
Electron volts, usually.
That is when they have a resistive element.
In other words, when the material is put under certain pressure, it will create some discharge.
In other words, once the mechanical pressure or mechanical movement is introduced, there
is a charging sequence that happens, and then a discharge.
And that discharge, or resistance, altered condition, is what they're calling an electron.
The same as blood pressure.
The doctor straps, so the medical technician, calling them a doctor is more than they deserve
because they're not.
They strap a cuff on your arm and pressurize it to stop the natural blood flow, and then
tell you you have a certain condition called blood pressure.
When in fact, everything that's moving inside the body is under a slight vacuum.
In other words, less than external pressure.
Otherwise, you know, all the liquid would be at your feet and nothing at your head, unless
you had a 1200 horsepower pump in your chest, moving it through a 0.3 millimeter capillary.
So before what happened the past two years, they already had scammed, what, there's 20
or 30 million people that insist on taking blood pressure medication, and other things
like that.
They already had scammed that many people.
So why not go to the bill, you know, scam everybody, keep scamming, right?
So most of the medical conditions, if not all of them, are medical fiction.
Most of those diseases do not exist, by the way, and the major ones do not exist either,
right?
Yeah, there are no such things.
But also about the ether, there must be different levels, I would think, also, because just
how light behaves differently, depending on where it is in the universe, and of course,
is the background on which matter manifests, including the background of the spin and everything.
But I would guess that it has different levels, right, because of how, for example, it's also
misinterpreted the Big Bang theory that the universe is expanding because of their interpretation
of redshifts.
You know, they think that it's going away from you, whereas all that redshift is, well, it's
not linear, it's tired life.
Yes, that's been disproven.
The Doppler theory of the red and blue shift has been disproven already, because it never
took into account on the emissivity of the bodies they were measuring, and the emissivity
of the material.
And also, their instruments were very biased and crude, yeah, just like they came up with
water being H2O, which it's not.
Yeah.
And about the gravity, I still would like to elucidate this, because there are so many
opinions about what exactly keeps you upright in hollow Earth, assuming you, by now, you
have been clued into the idea that the Earth is hollow.
So, the conventional theory, and the one that you hear in the science, there are very
few books about it that are scientific, and most of the literature, at least three books
that I've found, say that, respect the Shell theorem, which says that, you know, the center
point of the planet is basically zero gravity, and that you're being kept upright by the
mantle on either side, which means that you're at zero gravity in the middle of the mantle.
You don't have to be there.
Zero gravity.
Again, if we, let's say gravity is a resultant of a motion of the aether, that resultant
of the motion is what we call gravity as a thing.
Now, there's something that is not really much discussed, it's done in music, it's called
coherence, right?
So when something is coherent, in other words, there's a certain amount of harmony that
is conducive to growth in life, direction doesn't matter as much, you see.
Like, for example, if we're on a big ball spinning in space, why is it that people in
Australia aren't falling off, and the people in Australia saying why the people up north
are not falling off, right?
Because there's a coherence there.
There's a big thing about the flat Earth and the round Earth, and I say it's both, depending
on what you're doing.
And what you're doing, if it's coherent with what you're observing and your result, then
you're good to go, you see.
That's why, I'll give another example, I was speaking with someone, an SSP person, and
we wanted to bring up gravity, they didn't want to hear what I had to say, of course,
they already had their mindset.
But I asked, what about the drive systems, you know, how do you get the ships and vehicles
to move?
I said, it's plasma engines, and I said, really?
If you have a device that's making plasma, well, that's what it's doing, it's making plasma.
It's not making anti-gravity, anti-gravity, if you're making, if your engine is making plasma,
you're making plasma, you're not making the effect, you see, so it's very difficult to
communicate this, right, to many people, or to the public at large, or even in a private
discussion.
In essence, there's a concept of shielding, you have to know how to shield and redirect,
in order to create that quote-unquote levitation effect.
And the best way to do it is through biology.
For example, when you are walking around, like you said, walking around in the core
and the mantle and all that, just being on the surface, for example, if you're walking
around and you have levity, when you lose that levity, you feel sick and you have to
lay down.
But people that are very sick can't stand up.
Okay, once you understand and study what is going on there, between the structure, irrelevant
of the structure of the body, let's say you have a skeleton or an exoskeleton, because
an insect doesn't have an internal skeleton, for example.
Once you understand the concept of levity, then you will be able to progress in the field
of antigravity.
The other thing is the rudimentary way to do it.
Just like if someone couldn't stand up, you made crutches for them to assist them, the
way you would develop a crutch to stand up or do antigravity is by rotating things, like
for example, gyroscopic motion.
Back in the 1920s, it was banned.
Anything that had to do with the effect of rotating devices was banned or just quietly
eliminated.
I dare anyone to find a scientific article anywhere in the world about the effect of
gyroscopes.
There are in Russia.
What's that?
Russians actually acknowledge it.
Yes, but you won't find anything developing it beyond just basically from a toy, you know,
scale.
Right?
And it has nothing to do with electricity, by the way, but you will use it, just like
if you made crutches for someone to stand, you can make them out of wood or metal or
plastic.
You don't have to use electricity.
You can use magnetism.
You can use, what is it called when a material dissolves into another?
One material.
There's saturation point when it reaches its limit.
Yeah, when materials change by, when you combine two materials to make a third material in
a different state is another way to do this, by the way.
Like, for example, if you study high-speed chemistry known as explosives and things like
that, those reactions don't make any sense when you really think about them.
They make sense on paper, but when you study those reactions as well, you will get to the
point of what we're talking about.
But again, just, I don't think I answered your question directly, but when you go inside
the earth, it's not just a matter of penetrating from the surface and descending, let's say,
in simple terms.
It's a matter of gaining or creating or acquiring the coherence that is involved in existing
there.
There's a certain coherent body.
Your body must be coherent with the conditions there.
Yeah, but there is also the fact that the mantle is not that different.
So it still abides by many of our rules, although allegedly the hollow is completely next density.
But the way I read between the lines in the most credible of these books, which is the
Radu Chinamar series, I think that it automatically has to flip when you're in the hollow because
of the different higher frequencies.
And also, it says that you have to be ready.
Your frequency of vibration has to be on par with where you're going first, otherwise you're
just going to collapse and stuff.
Because there was no mention of you turning upside down or anything.
So I have to assume that you're still headed downwards when you're all the way through
the mantle, which is so physical, and then it flips.
But that's just my guess.
Well, it would be, OK, let's not think about it flipping upside down.
Think about it, you're standing still and you get on a train that begins to move to
a speed where you're going 100 kilometers per hour and everything around you suddenly
seems to be moving by you very quickly, but you're not moving, you see.
But you're the one that's really moving, let's say, right?
Right.
And now here comes another train next to you that's also moving the same speed as you.
And when you look at someone there, they can open the window and you can shake hands and
they don't seem like they're moving, right?
You see what I mean?
The point of reference?
OK, that effect that, except for the point when you're standing still and the train is
at zero and accelerating, at the point of acceleration, you will notice a difference.
But once it reaches that stable speed, there's no difference now.
You still feel like you're standing still.
Ask anyone that's flown in an airplane at 500 miles per hour, they don't feel the speed.
Just like they say the Earth is spinning at whatever speed, you don't feel it.
The same way, once you reorient yourself and there's coherence around the being that's
experiencing this, you don't feel what position you're in, it doesn't matter, unless you start
looking directly at the exterior.
Right.
That is the same phenomenon, sorry, I described whether it's a round Earth or a flat Earth.
If you're a farmer or an architect, the Earth is flat.
Obviously, if you're a farmer, the sun goes around the Earth.
It rises in the east and sets in the west.
And you must understand that and use that to your benefit.
Otherwise, you will not succeed in growing crops.
You will starve.
If you're an architect, you use a level and a plumb bob when you're putting up a building,
meaning that the Earth is flat.
And if you don't know that, the building will be crooked and everyone will laugh at you.
Why are you using such poor practices, right?
But if you're a land surveyor and you're using a theodolite and you're measuring to make
a map, as you keep going, you're going to notice that none of your lines line up because
of the curvature of the Earth.
So you have to start compensating with steps and things like that that you see on borders,
unless you follow a river or something.
So if you're measuring the Earth, Lagrange points or Cartesian or whatever, you better
understand the curvature.
If you're an architect or a farmer, you better understand that it's flat.
You see the same thing with the hollow Earth.
Yeah.
And what would you say is the best model or just approximation of a replacement for the
space-time notion?
And I can just give the example of the Andromedans, that they say that they use nine mutually
interchangeable coordinates, six of space and three of time, and they use time as though
it were a dimension of space.
Yes, I would say that most of those coordinates are biological and conscious space, if you
know what I mean by that.
That's a weird noise going on.
Sorry.
OK.
Is that better?
I think I had some interference there.
OK.
Well, those coordinates would go back to how we started the conversation on, let's say,
the DNA and the disease and health and all that, being frequency-based, but not the type
of frequency and pressurized way that we measure frequency, but more of a biological vacuum
based, you know, the biological, quote-unquote, vacuum as a basis for developing instrumentation
for that, or a consciousness-intuitive base.
For example, the consciousness study that there is such a thing as psychic powers or
psychic ability and remote viewing or telepathy or telekinesis.
Once the underlying basis of how those things work is, let's say, established publicly, more
of those coordinates will be understood.
So if you were to speak with an Andromedan or Arcturian that uses that, you will find
that the majority of those coordinates are consciousness-based.
In other words, the way the mind works.
Now, by the way, I will plug in Donald Marshall.
If anyone wants to look him up, it sounds kind of crazy about the cloning centers.
One of the statements that he made, which I heard before he had gone public, is that
the entire mind and human body, everything about the mind that can be known, was already
mapped and completely known by the 1930s, right?
By who?
By the people that established the cloning centers underground, that Donald Marshall
speaks of.
The reptilians?
Well, yeah, kind of a low-level reptilian that brought a German faction to places in
Antarctica and Tibet to show leftover equipment from the Atlantean age, let's say.
And they were able to revive this equipment because the poor lizards couldn't do it, they
just have a claw with two digits on it.
They get really sad when they try to work the equipment because they're just little
dumb lizards, right?
They just have two little fingers.
So, they brought the humans over there that would work with them as well.
But the entire mind and consciousness has already been mapped.
In other words, consciousness transfer, where consciousness can be taken from one being
and put into a clone body and vice versa, during REM consciousness transfer.
So, the technology, which supposedly cannot be blocked, there's no disclosure of how
that can be blocked, or how consciousness moves, that's already been known by humans
for almost 100 years and it's being kept secret.
Once that is put forward, what you just mentioned about the coordinates and time and space and
all that, then that will be commonplace.
And since you brought up Donald Marshall, do you have any idea how the reptilian hierarchy
that he mentions relates to the Draco or, you know, the reptilians that you brought
up in the last episode?
Yes, very low level.
Very, very low level.
The ones that I brought up on the last episode, the reason I did that is because there's
still a lot of talk about the reptilians and the Draco being defeated, as I'm sure you've
heard, and the humans winning and on and on and on and on, and they cannot define any
of that.
And the ones that I mentioned, maybe half a dozen or a dozen groups, those are the very,
very high order.
And as you go down the order, the ones that are very low order, like a hybrid of a hybrid
of a hybrid down mixed, would be the ones that are on Earth and dealing with the humans
that people find, well, they eat our babies and they need human whatever.
The ones that I mentioned do not eat, just as humans will not have to eat again in the
future.
So those are some like really low, low, low level hybrid or leftovers here on the Earth.
They would be the, when I say low level, it's so low, it would be like when you look at a
human being or an animal and then you look at bacteria, a simple single-celled organism,
that's the difference between the Draco and the reptiles that Donald Marshall is talking
about.
That's how far removed they are.
Right.
And is there a way to tell when you're taken through REM abductions from when you're
actually astral traveling?
I think that several reasons against astral traveling.
First of all, the amount of hostility that is in that world, meaning the non-physical
3D world is so high that if anyone truly did that, they would come back severely damaged
mentally or would not come back or you would not hear stories like you hear now.
The other part of astral traveling is a scenario run on people from the quote-unquote
cloning centers, where they pre-drug the clone body and when your consciousness is
transferred, you're already pre-drugged with scopolamine or many, many other things,
right?
Sodium pentothal, sodium mannothal, and you'll believe anything that you're told, right?
Yeah.
Now, the thing when I say the cloning centers, it's not a very, it's very prevalent.
Millions, there are millions of people involved, if not tens of millions involved in this
scenario.
So, it's not a rare occurrence.
But there are such things as astral body experiences that are legitimate and may be possibly
the same places that your mind wanders, I mean your etheric or astral body wanders
when you sleep, right?
And they abuse that and make it seem like you're actually there.
Sure, sure.
But actually, you are actually there.
If your consciousness is grabbed while you're sleeping and brought to a cloning center
and you're in a clone body that has been pre-drugged, you'll believe anything that
you're told, that you're in nirvana.
But you're actually just in a physical clone.
You're just in a physical clone.
And it's just as physical as we are speaking right now through Skype, but even more physical
because you'll be in front of people that are playing a scenario on you.
That's why I speak so poorly about a lot of the communities that, I'm not going to
say directly SSP, but anyway, because I think they're all victims of that, the ones that
are public.
Well, with exceptions, but I would say.
Very small exceptions, yes.
Yeah, you mentioned that there's so much disinformation about the Draco being overcome
and stuff, but.
Not going to happen.
Yeah, that also goes against the mildly famous prediction through the looking glass that
they have definitely been defeated.
So that also goes hand in hand with the idea that the looking glass has stopped working
for the last 20 or so years.
Yes, if there is such a thing.
Well, there apparently are.
There are multiple.
There's enough.
It might exist, but what we're being told about it is not necessarily accurate.
Because you can hear, let's just move forward.
You can develop your own looking glass.
You don't need their stuff.
You already have everything that you need.
If once you understand there are only one, your incarnation here is less than one or
two percent of what you potential is.
Yeah.
And about the, Leslie, about the underground cloning chambers, would you say that everyone,
including us, is a target?
And is there a way to defend against it?
Unknown.
I would say yes on the first one and unknown on the second.
I think the best way to defend oneself if one does not know how to do it directly is
by involving a third party.
Like, for example, a very wealthy guy.
He's not a triple master black belt.
And so he may not be able to defend himself.
What does he do?
He gets on the phone and calls a security company to protect him, you see.
So that would be the easiest thing for people.
I call on personally.
I'll give my personal beliefs and allegiances.
I call on the Elohim.
Right.
That's pretty good support.
Yeah.
And they're pretty, they're very powerful.
And I would venture to say they're probably the most technically advanced in our universe
right now at parity with the Draco.
Because the Draco have been changing their whole ideology the few thousand years to involve
more of a light aspect, you know, more of a duality instead of going around and just conquering
and dominating everything.
See, the core of philosophy, I'll go out on a limb of the Draco, is that you must destroy
to create.
So let's say you're Draco and you go into a system that seems to be OK.
Well, it's not it's not as OK.
It's not as good as if we destroy it and recreate it.
It'll be better then.
Right.
And there are also some factions that just destroy and don't create.
That's called a capitalist, by the way.
You know, the definition of a capitalist is when you're done using something, you destroy
it so no one else can use it.
But anyway, I think Zen would like that political little dig there.
But they're understanding now more that there is a underlying harmony that they don't have
to affect and appreciate what's already there.
The Elohim are basically the human collective that has been interacting with them.
And every time they interact with the Draco, the Elohim get stronger and stronger.
And the Draco are the type of beings that if they go, let's say, to subdue someone and
that someone that they're trying to take over fights back and almost wipes out the
group that they sent to subdue, they will not call in reinforcements to completely destroy
them.
They're going to stop and say, wow, what great warriors they are.
Maybe we're better working with them than trying to kill them.
You see, so every time the Elohim engage the Draco, the Draco came back and said, wow,
look how strong they're getting.
Eventually, maybe we'll work together, but not now.
So there is a very high level of reason and honor in the Draco, by the way, which is never
really discussed.
Yeah.
There is just one person who stresses that for them, honor is everything.
And we only say that we're all about love, but don't actually respect it, whereas they
live and die by honor.
Yes.
And when they die, they do it consciously, by the way, not like we do.
Because let's say, for example, they died by accident.
They have the ability to transfer everything and restart, you know, like you hear about
like regenerate themselves.
You know, so let's say they died in battle.
They can just be regenerated.
No problem.
When they really do die, it's a conscious effort.
They say, OK, that's it.
I've had enough here, all these millions or billions of years.
It's time for me to go.
And there's also a certain degree of hypocrisy with all this reptilian slamming, because
without them being more apparently harsh, you wouldn't have this complexity of this
scenario.
It's going on out of this.
They're necessary as much as anything.
And they are apparently part of why we are so physical right here and why it's attractive
idea for all these more allegedly high density beings to incarnate as us.
And it wouldn't have been possible without the reptilians who are who get all the bad
reputation.
So also, they I don't know if you can vouch for this, but apparently the way they operate
is they subvert the population.
They only infiltrate it.
And they usually pick one that is neither too advanced nor too primitive and usually
one that's part of these higher alliances.
And then they hybridize just a little bit with them, just a few percentages and just
enough to have resonance with them and then just guide them after their own will.
Apparently, this is also the divergence that happened around 5000 years ago.
And would you do you know anything about the dumbing down of the humanity that happened
around that time?
Yes, more than 5000, I'd say 13,000 or between the 13,000 and 5000 years ago.
But I would suggest that the dumbing down is several reasons.
One is that humans as you as we are today at the human collectives, what is only one
or two percent, 10 percent, the best master ascended masters, what they call most magical
type people would be 10 percent of what a human can be expressed.
Right.
The other thing is the humans have a certain quality.
They can go into many worlds, even to the highest worlds.
And because of that, when they're put in a universe such as this one, which is I call
it a B movie.
Let's say you took the best classically trained actor and put him in a B movie.
Does that make it an A movie?
No, it's still a B movie.
Right.
So when you have humans, a fully charged or fully enabled human in a B grade universe
like this, nothing, eventually they're going to lean more into doing bad things than good
things.
Right.
They'll, for example, look at a group of people that like a different color than they
do something really superficial like that.
And because they like red and you like blue, there are no goods.
We're going to capture them while they're sleeping and hybridize them with pigs.
This is how humans are in a B universe.
Very wicked.
So to keep them going and keep them manifested, what you do is you enable them.
You manifest them at only one or two percent of their ability.
So their main struggle is just food, clothing and shelter.
And anything else is optional.
You know, it's very difficult to go beyond that.
Let me give an example.
If you study the body the way that we gave the outline and I have in the past, everything
that you need in terms of nutrition, you know, eat like eating food is a fallacy.
Everything that you need is produced in all of the glands that you have.
All of the glands and bladders that you have, the pituitary, the pineal, the gallbladder,
all the various glands that you have in your body can produce all of the nutrition because
they do that anyway.
By the way, you cannot process carbohydrates, proteins or minerals or metals or water in
your body unless the glands play a part.
So they have been tuned down and dumbed down.
So you have to have this very large intestinal tract and all that to remove the energy from
the food so the glands can process it.
We're actually the glands, if they were activated in the body, they would take everything from
the environment, sunlight or whatever environment you were in and you wouldn't have to eat.
You would be, quote unquote, Breatharian, right?
So this is very well known and very well established in those that study how the human body really
works.
So right now it's very difficult for people to be, quote unquote, Breatharian because
you've been put in a situation where our main concern is spending most of our time to get
food and water and making shelter just to exist.
That's why my biggest advice to young people is don't do anything here.
This is not a place to do anything grand.
It's about food, clothing and shelter.
And once you establish that, some people say, Greek, that sounds oversimplified and not
very good.
I said, yes, but once you establish that being here is about food, clothing and shelter
and what you want to do is get the best quality food, clothing and shelter for yourself being
here, while you're on that quest to determine that you want to acquire and afford the best
things here.
You will also learn about everything else in the meantime.
But I tell people if you have a great idea or an invention or whatever, this is not the
place to do it.
It doesn't mean you shouldn't do it or make it, right?
You should do it, but don't say I'm going to do this for the world because this is not
the type of world that needs that.
Here, I'll give you an example, and this is not to brag or anything like that.
I was on a Skype call recently with someone who I had not seen or spoken to for over a
decade.
And the person recognized me and they're local here in Tucson.
And they said, hey, Greek, you know, I remember you sold me your motorcycle and all that.
And I said, yeah, yeah, I remember.
He says, tell the people how you get it, how you got the motorcycle to run on water.
Right.
And I'm like, oh, why?
You know, why do I have to do that?
I said, oh, yeah, that's right.
The one you got ran on water.
Right.
A regular combustion engine.
So, you know, do you see me doing websites?
And hey, this is how we're going to get away from.
Right.
Do you see?
No, I don't talk about those things because this is not the place for it.
But it doesn't mean I won't make it for and make one and sell it to someone who needs a
motorcycle.
You see what I mean?
Yeah.
And like the blind guy who came to your couch and you made him see.
What are you, Jesus or something?
No, I don't go around saying that.
Right.
Yeah.
Because.
About the coming down, there has to be intricate reasons.
And I guess the most plausible one that you maintain is that we are a seed bank, which
also goes hand in hand with the theory that these many seeder races don't want us to be
fully sentient so as to not lose the rights for continuing to tinker with our DNA.
Would you say that's right?
It's more than DNA.
DNA is, are the tree rings in the tree the tree?
No, they just tell you about the tree, how old it is.
Do you know there's a guy, I think Lipton or someone else that did experiments with
protozoa.
He removed the DNA and they just multiplied and lived a normal life.
Right.
But after.
Yeah.
After a generation or two, they stopped, though.
So you really don't need DNA to be alive.
It's a it's overrated.
Anything that you see everybody pushing.
Sorry, go ahead.
Just so I can look at Lipton.
Yeah, you can put in Lipton genetic research like Lipton the G.
Yeah.
He did a bunch of research on how the DNA is over.
Look, the public does not speak the truth and the truth is not spoken to the public.
Right.
This has been going on for, like you said, 5000 years.
Part of the dumbing down.
So if you have three or four more people talking about something, it's probably BS, you know.
So you'll be you'll be amazed to see if you look online, for example, even like YouTube and all that.
If you see find a site that has five subscribers and 10 views, you know what?
And it's been around for years.
They probably have the truth.
If you see a site that has thousands and tens of thousands of subscribers and thousands of views.
Now, that's a very quick, broad brush way to see, because the people won't understand here.
One thing I always used to say, you know, how everyone describes the education system being completely in tatters.
Right. And it's all propaganda.
If you created an education system, real education, no one would go.
No one, because the minute they showed up, they won't understand anything you're saying at all.
It would be so different and so bizarre when they compare it to their family life and their culture that no one will go.
So it's a waste of time.
You see, ultimately, until everything changes.
But the dumbing down is more than the dumbing down.
It's the way we're set up from the beginning.
Exactly. It shouldn't be looked at as a handicap, really, because we are the cosmic project of all these different species.
I mean, it sounds like opium, but and also they tried their best.
All these advanced cities like the great to fabricate the DNA for generations and they just fell.
So they still need this hybridization.
And apparently some of them even tried to shave off layers of our energy field just to get souls to draw themselves to their useless, you know, colon bodies.
Yes. And the shaving off is more like a governor.
Most people, I think someone recently communicated to me that more people are starting to talk about the synthetics that are here on Earth.
In other words, when you meet someone, they look like a human, smell like a human, talk like a human, and they're not human.
They're like a synthetic manifestation. Right.
So there is that exception.
I would say a good 20 to 30 percent of the human population is not human right now.
They're either synthetics or they're parasite, parasited.
And where do you find them?
Doctors, lawyers, governors.
I mean, government jobs, nurses, priests, rabbis, imams.
Right. That's where you find them because they typically go into they become being a synthetic and being a parasite and just sitting in the corner of a room or whatever doesn't really affect the society.
They they're placed cosmically in positions where they can influence others.
Right.
So and once you understand, I don't get into publicly how to do a witch hunt and how to privately.
I do talk to people about how to determine who's a synthetic or not with great accuracy.
And they kind of flip out when they start scanning the people around them.
But I will never do that publicly, at least at this point.
But if you just the notion is just as important right now as actually showing how who is a synthetic and who isn't.
But the rest that are left, there are things you can do to activate, you know, your potential up to, let's say, 10% human instead of 1% or 2%.
Right. And a lot of that has to do with things that I've been saying and some others and who the others are, I don't know.
But in other words, learning how things work.
Why is it that every time you go into a field, the quote unquote experts are telling you the opposite of what's been memorialized in their own books, for example.
Right. If you go to any religious person, what their leader, they're going to tell you the opposite of what's memorialized in the text that's supposed to subscribe to.
If you speak to a doctor who are expert liars, by the way, you will find that what they're telling you is contrary to what's memorialized in the text that they use as part of their field of study.
The same with attorneys and the same and so on and so on.
Okay, so start off there. Start off with see what's been memorialized.
And the reason why things are memorialized, meaning stored information, whether it's written on stone, paper or digital.
The reason why something is written down and held is because guess what?
It's important and it's a courtesy to pass this information on to future people or current anyone who wants to reference it.
But instead, you have people that take on whatever jobs they do, let's say a bus driver or a painter or someone, a chef, and they want to learn about astrophysics or the human body.
They go and they listen to people that are supposedly experts in the field, but if they go a little further and look at the text that they're supposed to subscribe to, they'll find what's in the text is very different.
Because people don't want a home cooked meal that takes three hours to make. They want something out of a can that's reheated.
So when you're going to a quote unquote expert, that's what you're getting. You're getting a meal out of a can, which is not good for you eventually.
So until people start taking more time, and if let's say you're a chef and you want to learn about astrophysics, unfortunately, you're going to have to learn how to go through technical documents very quickly.
I've also done talks on how if you gave me, let's say, a thousand page technical book, in six hours I can have an in-depth discussion with the author of that book.
Not because I read the entire thousand pages, I know how to go.
And I used to instruct people on how to go through massive amounts of academic and anything that's written and memorialized very quickly and get the main points out of it.
And you can condense it down to like 15 minutes.
But also, I think that that's the whole point of text in the first place, is to memorialize these things because of the nature of this grade of humanity.
In any event, so you also mentioned Noah's Ark, that it wasn't like we thought.
It was more of a goodwill gesture on the part of the humans, and the rest was really just a collection from the Elohim of the genetic material, and that they don't lose track of these things when they do get lost, so-called, in the cataclysm, right?
No, nothing is lost.
And let me just put this in perspective.
There's so many changes that happen.
Like, you know, for example, the cancel culture that they're talking about now.
If you find any old Greek sonic events from 10 years ago, I talked about the cancel culture in great detail before it hit now.
And the reason why I did is because the cancel culture was borrowed from the ancient world.
In other words, in ancient Egypt, if you became unpopular, what they did is they went and erased your name and memory from all records, even government records, where now if you went and tried to erase someone from government records, they would say, well, that's a criminal offense.
You know, you cannot do that.
But even then, they were that drastic.
So, where I'm leaning to that with Noah's Ark, if you read what they call the New Testament in the book of Shimon Kepha, or what they call Peter, you will see that he mentions in there, he mentions, I'm paraphrasing, that Noah's Ark was still a tourist attraction back then.
We're talking about 1900 years ago.
Just like you would have a tourist attraction now, like the Busaj Mountains, or the Grand Canyon, or the Niagara Falls, or some ruins like the pyramids are tourist attractions.
That's how, less than 2000 years ago, Noah's Ark was.
It was very well known where it was and what it was verified.
People would go there.
But now, oh my gosh, where is it?
Did it even exist?
What happened?
You see?
Yeah.
And is it true that Babylon was a case of the, you know, the Incas or whatever branch of humanity getting too big for their own safety, and then these so-called gods, the Yazidis, having to, you know, quell them and leave the intermediary elites to just be the masters?
Yes, very much.
There are no gods as such.
Just like if you were technologically advanced and went to a gullible, less technologically advanced, and you brought your devices, they might, and you told them they were a god, you may not convince everyone right away, but eventually you will, right?
So the term god is a very corrupted term.
It doesn't mean that the Elohim and others don't deserve, you know, the utmost respect.
It's just that I don't see the term as being accurate, but not because, you know, you brought them up as gods, but I would suggest that the state of the past people were not much better if we're discussing the ones that are incarnated like us, one or two percent, you know.
They weren't much better off, really.
Yeah, and apparently the first successful ones like Adam of humanity were on the part of these gods, in quotes, and that they were used to see these many other planets, which is why you find many human species, and that the mixture between the ones that were left alone, which are us, the more rudimentary, and the more advanced ones that were used to see planets,
are the so-called demigods.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, the early ones, yes, most likely, because if you, let's say we look at the conventional Western theology, in the biblical text, you have Adam and his several generations, and then they're brought up as the men of renown, the men that were the heroes, like in the ancient Greece, it was on the age of the heroes, right, the men that did incredible things.
But Adam was never classified as such, because he was kind of like the prototype.
But before we continue on the human lineage, Zen, I want to just honor what your request was.
Listen, this might seem cheesedick to you, Greek, but there's this one YouTube show that I always watch.
It's called Nuke's Top Five, and I know it's all stuff that can be explainable.
It's a paranormal channel, and I know it's not going to faze you.
Anyway, the thing is, is there's this, I call it because I lack so much knowledge, maybe a skinwalker or something, but many times people will catch what I deem as, and I want you to debunk, if not, or refine, you know, a skinwalker or a rake, and they're out screwing around in the forest late at night, and some young dumb kids, and they'll hear some extreme guttural, and I don't think these kids have the time or the technology to play with to make such a good fake.
But I'm going to hit straight here.
I'm going to let you watch maybe a 15-second clip, and I just want you to tell me, one, if it's real, if it is real, what is this?
Is it something that  a species before humanity?
Is it something the CIA released?
Is this
Oh, you don't even have to.
I think I'm familiar with it.
Let me just make a quick roundabout on that.
First of all, the stranger it is, whether it's a story, a video, or an experience account, probably the more true it is.
If it sounds plausible, it's not true most likely.
Okay?
I know that sounds crazy.
The other thing is it's a variety of things that something coming out of the ground most likely because things that come out of the sky are not visible or audible to us.
So it's something coming out from a different density in the ground.
Like if we look at the accounts, let's say, of the cloning centers, they have the Vril lizards there.
There are many accounts of them, and also their ability to hybridize.
There are also, like I mentioned earlier, advanced humans would attack other advanced humans because of very trivial reasons.
Like they serve chocolate chip ice cream when we think that's no good.
So let's capture them and hybridize them with pigs.
That's how people are, by the way.
They're that nasty, right?
So you have still people on the surface  I don't like to call them government.
By the way, you have no government, right?
All the governments are bankrupt.
So calling a bankrupt entity as a legitimate entity is not accurate, right?
All of the governments are operating as administrations under the worldwide bankruptcy, right, under the World Economic Forum, the UN and all that, right?
This is a fact, but it's something you don't talk about supposedly.
Even alternative people don't like to talk about it, but it needs to be understood.
So these people that can afford to do these things would be another way to say it, do these things.
They're a major experimentation.
Can we watch this little clip real quick?
Go ahead.
Sure.
All right.
I'm going to do a screen share.
So this show is a paranormal show, and it's as close as I can get because I don't stay up late and I don't go explore.
And it's a bunch of people that have no fear, go screw around in the forest or go walk miles through sewer systems to prove that there's no such thing as aliens or other sorts of beings.
And then they see, I feel, they see real shit, get scared shitless and run away.
And I simply want  like this one thing was just a quick example.
It's some creature, the closest I can say in my naivete, it looks like the creature from Pan's Labyrinth.
And I just wanted to know, is this some ancient species that just dwells underground?
But also, too, what blows my mind, Greg, is all these people go look for ghosts, look for rakes, look for all this stuff.
They never have an AK-47.
They never have backup flashlights and all this kind of stuff.
If I saw that, yeah, I'm going to be scared.
I want to shoot it, bring it  haul its ass out and bring it to the light and say, look, this shit really exists.
That's what blows my mind.
I want to show people.
Yeah, OK.
I did see what you're saying.
I don't know.
It's kind of vague as well.
But at this point, I would suggest that the second part of what you said, you want to try to convince people.
Don't bother.
Well, they could argue.
They could even have an argument.
If I had some weird skin
It doesn't matter.
No evidence.
One thing, if you've  on the past Sonic events with Ocelli and all that, I kept saying towards the later part of the
I kept saying no level of evidence or truth or whatever will change the ideology and the culture that you're in.
As a matter of fact, evidence means nothing, right, with these people here and the synthetics and the parasited ones and the whatever.
Evidence means nothing.
Like for example, if you hijacked all of the mainstream TV and gave people the truth about anything, the average person would go, oh, man, that's so weird.
But it's cool.
And the more educated academic will say, well, that's a novel way to look at it.
And then like right after it's all done, a minute later, no less than a minute later, they go right back to what they're doing.
You know why?
Because you can't take a pig to a debutante ball until people get the pig genes.
You know what I mean?
Not that they're really pigs, but yeah.
So you get that out of their system, which is what's coming.
The templates are going to be changing.
You're right.
Yeah, I appreciate it.
I know it seems like a dumbed down point compared to the sophisticated stuff you and Daniel were talking about earlier.
I just I watched the show.
It's not sophisticated at all.
Sorry, it's not.
It's the basics that we should have learned when we were as children.
Let me give you an example.
On other worlds, there are eight year olds that have the equivalent of four graduate degrees by the time they're eight and four or five different subjects at the top of their field by the time they're eight years old.
Right.
What are some of these planets?
This is where are these places?
That was one.
Oh, they're everywhere.
There's there's a look.
What is that formula, Daniel?
The possibility of planets?
What's it called?
The how many stars there are times how many planets times how many?
Anyway, they're everywhere.
You know, there is one name of something I could start researching or.
Oh, no.
It's very difficult to research because everything is about opinion.
These days, he said, she said, and experiencers that couldn't pour piss out of a boot with instruction on the heel.
So you're just going to have to wait.
You're not going to have to wait much longer, really.
I mean, you're fairly young within within a decade.
Your answer will come.
OK, the main thing with many things that I say, actually, I try not actually most things that I do say I give a reference point on the real reason and logic.
But just by saying, hey, like shaking up someone like, wake up, look at this.
What do you see right away?
Start from that.
Many of the things that I might begin to say here and now, it's not I may not give references, but what's important is that you heard it.
Did you acknowledge what I said?
Do you understand what I said?
File it away for a little bit time more in the future where it'll make more sense.
I think that is more helpful.
That's why I'm always taken.
I mean, that's all this.
Yeah, like I like using I used to like using the Kennedy assassination as an example.
And I like to use the 9-11 as an example.
Also, anything else, even what happened the past two years with the pandemic as an example.
If you look at what's being put in front of the people, it seems like the formula is the dumber you make it and the more obviously false that you make it, the more people will believe it.
It seems to be.
And what's really going on is so basic that the children should be able to see it like the emperor has no clothes.
Right.
So I've talked about this as we're going to the future.
It'll be even dumber and even more blatantly ridiculous.
But the people will believe it.
Well, with the help of the synthetics and the parasites pushing it down their throat.
Right.
That's the thing.
That's that's my whole qualm.
You know, that's what makes me so sick.
Yes.
I want to learn, you know, just how to live forever and anti aging and all these things that should have been taught to us.
But the fact like I was in seventh grade when I saw 9-11 go down and it just I was just like, this is fake.
This is not right.
Or at least I wasn't.
I mean, it's happening, but I'm not buying the story.
The discussions that I can have on it, which I said I would never do, is so funny on 9-11 here.
Let me just interject one thing.
The guys that they sent to admit it was a NATO operation.
But OK, so they even have it in their own paperwork.
But and it's listed under an insurance fraud.
But it is so funny.
The discussions compared to what people see that it's laughable.
Give me an example.
When they executed what they did in New York City that day, they obviously sent like half of the people were knew what they were doing.
The other half were a bunch of Muppets.
OK.
In other words, going from north to south, the buildings involved were north would be building seven.
And then just south of that is the North Tower.
And just south of that is the South Tower.
The nuclear devices that are put in there, they're called atomic gates.
For example, this is very well known since the 1950s.
The Golden Gate Bridge, the Verrazano Bridge, the main tunnels, the main roadways and the main monuments in this country are rigged to blow with nukes.
If their country is invaded, this is very typical tactics.
If your country is being invaded, you blow your own bridges so the enemy can't use them.
Right. It's very, very common.
Also for safety concerns.
OK, so this is what they screwed up on 9-11.
The tunnels that are underneath, by the way, the World Trade Center and many other buildings, the devices are not placed under the buildings.
They have to be maintained.
They're lithium hydrogen charges.
The health of the zero box and the core has to be maintained by technicians.
It's usually done in a building outside and it's delivered to the building a time of demolition underground.
We're talking about 300 feet underground during the time of, you know, the prescribed time of when these things are going to be activated or detonated.
So Building 7 was where they maintain these things.
So what they did is they blew out the side of the building of the North Tower first, which was a screw up.
They should have because if you notice that when the buildings went down, the tower that got hit with the plane second came down first, where it really should have been the one that got hit with the plane first came down first.
Right. Because they said it was due to fire. Right.
So you had the North Tower gets hit with the plane first and then the South Tower gets hit with the plane second.
But they bring down the one that got hit with the plane last first.
Why? It doesn't make any sense if it's fire because the fire has to burn longer.
Right. Well, that was the screw up.
They should have exploded. There was no planes.
What they did was they lined up plane parts on the 78th floor.
So when they blew out the side of the building, those plane parts came out with it.
But anyway, these Muppets, they blew the wrong building first.
And the reason why they had to take away the one that got hit with the plane second down first is because if they took down the one that got hit with the plane first, sounds confusing.
Right. It could have damaged the tunnel to the other building that was further away than they couldn't bring that one down.
Right. So they had to do this really stupid thing.
Now, the second tower that came down, which is closer to Building 7, is after the first one was brought down.
The Muppets that were sent to deliver the device is a tunnel and you wheel it down and it's by wire.
It's a it's a DBW detonator. Anyway, we're wheeling it down to the second building.
But already the one that the South Tower that was already taken down, the reaction was starting to creep over to the foundation of this building.
And they're like, holy shit, their teeth must have fallen out and their hair must have fallen out.
And they got scared. So they didn't put the second device, ZeroBox, directly under the center of the building.
So when you see the buildings from aerial view, you'll see that the first one was completely dissolved from the center out.
But the second one, the corner of the building, still managed to stay because they didn't wheel the device all the way down where they were supposed to because it was too hot.
Right. So this is this is the things that I see when I look at these things, the obvious flaws.
Right. And then obviously, Building 7 was also taken down with the same device, because if they didn't, the government, people in the government didn't know this was going on.
This is done by people who are much higher. For example, the Port Authority, that is the authority of that whole part of Manhattan Island, is a sovereign corporation.
You could look this up. The feds have no jurisdiction there. The state has no jurisdiction there. Nobody is the Port Authority.
Most of these large complexes in big cities have their own little district that's like a country unto itself, like the Vatican.
OK. All right. So anyway, when the investigators, if they didn't take down Building 7 the same way, the investigators would go there and they don't.
Look, if you're setting off nuclear demolition in a major city, 150 kiloton devices, you don't want to leave the control room so somebody's mom can find it. Right.
You get it. So anyway, I see all the flaws and the mistakes that they made that day because I know about the what they did in great detail.
And, you know, and that's the world that I'm in. Look how they screwed this up.
But they still got it done because obviously they sent morons to do it. Most of them were morons, at least.
But most people are still arguing whether it was a satellite thing or explosives put on each floor, which is impossible.
I mean, this is like so the reason I said this whole thing about 9-11 is like Daniel brought up talking about pandemics and how it really works.
You really want to get into how diseases work and how you maintain human health in the body when the people are still just wondering about the most ridiculous stuff you can imagine.
They can't even see what's in front of them at all. I mean, the people meaning, yes, even on the alternative. You see what I mean?
Yeah, no, I appreciate that.
Yeah, you can't. This is not what's going on. Here's the thing. I always give a soliloquy about this. If half of the world, half of the people in the world helped one person.
That's the whole world is taken care of. Right. So if one third of the world helped two people, that's the whole world taken care of. Right.
So if one person helps nine people, oh, you know, if only 10% of the people each help nine people, that takes care of the whole world. But you see, there's a point where the numbers get so small that so few people can only do so much.
Right. But I know that from ancient writings, ancient philosophies, intuition and all that, if you come to this existence, this world, this society, whatever society you in, and you can help one person to make their life better.
Just one, not half the people helping one, but just one person helping one other person. That's quite an accomplishment. Right. Like in the biblical text says one of the highest things a human can do is die for their friend.
Well, it doesn't really say that directly die for the friend means you would go through anything it takes just to make someone else better.
Okay, or continue with their life.
So if you can do a sonic event where you show people things and tell people things that will make the change in their life I've gotten over 2000 emails in the past few years.
Since I've listened to you Greek I know how to eat better think better fix things better. My relationships got better over 2000 emails like that. You see, and I'm not even trying.
I don't put together I don't write books people say Greek you need to write a book I said okay, if you're an author and you want to write a book, you're presuming that whoever reads that book has comprehension right.
Otherwise it's a waste of time.
That and your book would get banned, just be more negative attention.
It would be foolish to do it because because I would presume that whoever's reading it has actually understanding what is being written. And that's a that's a bad presumption because you can't meet everyone.
In other words, if I were to write a book and give it out, I would have to send them a test first, maybe 20 or 30 questions and if depending on how they answered those questions then I would sell them the book.
Otherwise it's a waste of their time and a waste of my time.
The same thing was I believe like when people are young as in this society they should have all their internal reproductive organs plugged up and when they want to have a baby they go to an authority, and they have to take certain burial cognitive tests psychological tests mental tests and the once they pass all those things then you open up the reproductive organ so they could reproduce that would be the responsible way to do it.
Meeting a level of standards. Yes. Yeah.
Because why is it that the not only the ugliest poorest and dumbest people are wheeling around 15 or 20 children or six children, and the people that are really trying to get their stuff together have no children.
Right, right.
I find that it's useless to try as well with people they have to come halfway because, like you say most of them are cosmically censored so, but, yes, it's the cosmic censorship that's why why bother don't do anything.
In other words, and in a large scale cultural skill you do it for yourself your people that are close to you it doesn't mean your family.
Right, because your family sometimes is your biggest enemy, and on a high when you go to higher level things, because the concept of the family is a social, whatever culture you're in right.
And like, and yeah, I can also earlier mentioned remote viewing and I know you have some experience with this and would you be able to go over just how effective it is and what are its limitations.
Okay, very good.
There's a big psyop called control remote viewing you see all these ex military people and all that right.
And no one goes against them because it works on a general wherever and the reason why it's a psyop is because they could never offer any explanations.
Just like when you go to an alternative doctor you know they're going to try to say take my supplement because it's absorbed better you like oh my gosh, at least they're not promoting the mainstream stuff but they're just as bad.
Let me just say when you remote view what it is, is you're tapping into that 10% human, or you know that you're not you don't want to work with the 1% or 2% human that you are that you know you've been bred to be here by the gods, let's say, you want to tap into the other one.
Further on, and you can do that momentarily only for a very small fraction so when someone does whether it's the controlled remote viewing or any kind of guesswork.
The real information the best information appears in less than a 10th of a second or less than a second. It's your first hunch but it, and you have to exercise it like a muscle.
Right, give you an example there was a small remote viewing video, guess what's in the bag and they show a one of these cooler bags and I just soon as I read the title I looked at it and I got a vision of something that looked like a banana large and yellow.
So then I went to the end of the video and it was a large yellow highlight marker.
Okay, but if I started saying well it is it a banana, maybe it makes sense it's this way no no, it's all I got was something large and yellow and that was close enough so in that when you start working on this, picking up a momentary bits of information down to nanoseconds
people that are practicing for a long time, just like a Tai Chi or Kung Fu master can take a knife or a gun from your hand with a, if you pointed out them so fast that you won't even know it happened right.
That's how you do it so the way the remote viewing works is when you look at something and your remote everyone is doing this anyway.
It just happens the information comes so quickly that you miss it.
So you must train to capture very rapid fire bits of information.
Some people it's visual, some people it's audible, some people it's other sensory you know could be taste, smell, feeling.
So you have to know what you are tuned into the most and learn how to capture split second impulses of input when you're presented with the thought.
That's the essence of remote viewing.
And does it have to be blind or double blind or what would you say is the best protocol?
The reason they do the blind and the double blind they say is best, that's why I say it's a PSYOP when they say you can only do it that way, is because it removes you from what you're casually used to.
It doesn't have to be blind at all.
But it's best to do that because it removes you from what you are casually used to doing and thinking, because you have an inner dialogue with yourself, which has its own personality, like some people project a different personality from what they really are.
A lot of people do that right.
They have one personality that they adjust their personality for their family life they adjust their personality for their work life or when they go to the bar, or whatever.
Or picking up a prostitute, right?
No, I'm serious.
A priest, for example, will have a certain personality that he exudes when he's at the church and the congregation, a different one when he's with the clergy, the people that work for him, and a different one when he's picking up a prostitute.
Right.
And would you agree that if you have many people concentrated on the same target that that will certify, I mean, will add some validation to your results collectively?
I find it very underrated.
Yes, it's underrated and correct.
I'll show you a metaphor and how that's so correct is because when you have one flash that's like looking at one frame of a piece of film.
When you have 16 people getting those flashes now it's like 16 frames and if you get thousands of people you're actually making a movie now.
You have so many pieces that you have this large mosaic, you can call it a mosaic or you can call it a film, like a reel of film.
Yeah, and it changes some of the group might get some of the other group might get other part of it but when you can come all together the thing is if you can communicate and bring it together coherently, of course, then you then you know what there's nothing you cannot do, just like in the Bible says, if we let them build this tower when they come together there is nothing that they will not be able to do.
Right.
That's the main thing that's why how many times everything political everything religious academic is to separate everyone.
I, I think I rubbed Zen, the wrong way we had some early conversations and I said you, everybody needs to come together almost with a hive mind with the same mind, because then the collective mind is not because you're all a bunch of drones, but that collective mind will be like this gigantic reservoir that you can all tap into.
Once you put all of your differences aside and I remember Zen said, Huh, that doesn't sound good.
I was like, Well, you got to think about it.
Yeah, no bad things about it before you know prior but really proves true so I mean, yeah, it's it's a matter of when everyone puts all their differences down because they're not real low, keep what if it's if you have something that's distinctive critically distinctive and different hold on to it.
But if you start examining everything you'll notice that we all can come together with all in one thought in one mind.
And not because we all are robotic drones mindless know what that will do is will create a reservoir and ethereal reservoir that we all can tap into.
Yep. And regarding the malleability of the predictions derived from remote viewing, what would you say is the number of possibilities when you're looking in the past versus the present of the future?
Yeah, you're gonna have to put that together somehow I mean that you but the more you go into the past you're actually going closer to the future, and the more you go into the future, the more you're going to the actual past.
I know I've said this before and people say I have to think about what you said, because each universe has a template, and there's a level of pre determinancy.
There's local events, whether it's a cultural or personal that you have what seems random Yes, you know, there's a template that you're going to eat lunch every day, but it doesn't say that every day it's going to be tuna fish or ham sandwich right you have might have a little leeway in that right.
But there's the template everyone will eat lunch that day you know is what I'm talking about. So the template for everyone's life culture world or whatever has already been set.
And once the blueprint is written then it's put into manifestation so once the blueprint for a building is finished by the architects, then they go out into the field and you'll see there's nothing in the field they bring the bulldozers and they start building and a few months later it's done.
When you go look at when the building first started that's when the blueprint was more new. And when you look at when the building was finished more into the future that's when the blueprint was more old, more towards the end.
So when we go into our past we're actually going into the beginning of that blueprint time which is actually more into the future. And as we go into our future we're going towards the end of the plan which is more into the past of you took longer to plan you see.
So once you understand that loop. It's not a loop once you understand that structure.
You can call it a circle within a circle, or various geometric forms within geometric forms.
Start to remote view it that way and watch what happens.
Right. Instead of asking let's see the future. Let's see what the template, how the template ended up, which you translate what I just said how the template ended up, it means our future.
If you start remote viewing it from that perspective, you will have like 99% accuracy.
Yeah.
And when you're remote viewing, and you're doing it by do not front loading or using your bias, whatever.
Would you say that you're tapping into the Akashic field, or is it more of an informational exchange between the viewer and the target.
Okay, the Akashic field is another it's another thing like when you hear about the Draco very little information usually not true.
The Akashic field is a resonant point, by the way here, let me let this out. It's been said by others I'm trying to think who else, long time ago.
From a material if you can't bring something down to nuts and bolts to a certain point even consciousness.
It's very difficult to handle it right because then becomes opinion or theory.
The Akashic record is actually held in the in a material way in the noble gases, the gases that like neon helium argon xenon that do not combine with other elements very easily at all.
They're called noble elements.
They are the substantive record resonant physical record of the Akasha in other words, that's why they do not combine with other substances.
That is the material substantive part just like we were talking about everything about the brain has already been mapped but we're not being told right, they know everything about the brain and the spirit and teleportation and everything is already been established by humans, less than 100 years ago.
And we talked about the Akasha.
There's many ways, there's one way that we relate to our environment with these noble elements and their effect and how you know we're breathing some of them, and how they always exist in a resonant point, and they're influencing us.
Or do you have to go to another set another higher density let's say of Akasha where there are other beings that are actually managing them because that also exists.
And that makes it complicated and I don't know enough about that to talk about it.
But I do know that I would consider that people should start considering that the elements that are considered noble or inert are where the physical Akasha, you know, are held.
In other words, just how you have these people that do crystal therapy and organite therapy, you know, take the crystal, put it on your forehead, it's going to make you through osmosis somehow better.
If you get some people that are really crafty and smart and understand a lot of the stuff myself and others might have talked about in the past, and you know how to work with these noble gases, you're going to get a lot more out of what people talk about the Akasha in a physical sense.
Right.
And to bring kids more together with the collective remote viewing and with the previous topics discussed like the Draco and such, the main, you know, conclusion, the recurring theme in the remote viewing performed by Farsight on the Galactic Federation was that, which is, you know, such a loaded term, but was that they're up against a force that is greater than them.
And they're trying to gain freedom through power.
But just the fact that they acknowledge that it's a greater force, I thought, lent confirmation to the idea that you can never really, you know, overcome the Draco entirely, maybe on a small sector of the galaxy, but that's about it.
No, you're not going to overcome.
By the way, everybody cover their ears when you said Farsight, you picked one of the worst organizations possible in the world for remote viewing.
Sorry to say that.
That's why they're so popular, right?
But anyway, you can uncover your ears now.
No, nothing like that is going to happen ever, ever in the ever that people understand as being ever or forever or whatever.
No.
Right.
No, there's no overcoming.
Like, for example, the reason you think you might have a victory or liberation from them is because they gave it to you.
It's kind of like the guy who says, I'm the boss of the house.
How is that?
He says, well, because my wife said so.
You get it?
Yeah.
And you also brought up dinosaurs and the fact that the vegetation, like the ferns and that themselves, the dinosaurs were so much taller compared to what we have on the surface today.
Would you say that also, if you take into account the ages of the crust, that the is just a hypothesis, but that during the age of the dinosaurs, the planet was much, much smaller in diameter.
Yes.
And it was more egg shaped.
In other words, it was very pointy at the ends and oblong on one hemisphere and pointy on the other, just like an egg.
If you, by the way, I'm not a proponent of continental drift.
No.
But if you get a bunch of eight year olds that have a lot to do, go out and buy some cheap printable maps and have them cut all the land areas out and then have them get some tape and piece all the land masses together.
Guess what it's going to look like?
An egg.
Right.
And expand it slightly.
It looks like a fat egg or a potato.
I have some potato, beautiful potatoes here, russets, and they're kind of like egg shaped.
They're pointy on one end and really round on the other, but lumpy across the surface.
Big lumps, flat spots.
There are some places on some continents that are extremely flat and sunken.
Yes, they don't conform at all to anything round by any means.
It shows you that the, there's a vibrational energy field that makes matter matter solid, that has to be, when that's taken into account.
When you look at these very distorted fields, areas, physical areas on the Earth, it's beaten up because the material is distorted, but the energy that is holding them together has a certain tendency to make it look like that, right?
The energy comes first.
But the dinosaurs are very interesting because I brought up the concept of meteors and asteroids.
If they are magnetic, as they say, predominantly, because you don't have to be completely ferromagnetic, you could be boron and other things are slightly ferromagnetic, but they do tout that they are magnetic.
If you have a small magnet approaching a large magnet, regardless if they're spinning or not, they're only going to make contact at the poles, which makes that all natural asteroid and meteorite natural impacts on the Earth happen only at the North Pole and South Pole.
So if you see, yeah, above 80th parallel, let's say, right?
Above the 80, let's say.
The one on Jupiter.
Yes.
So if you see like a big hole in Arizona or a big hole in Yucatan in Mexico near the equator, those were not natural.
Those were weapon systems.
But there are those who say that, oh, sorry, that the pole flipping isn't limited to, you know, 180, but it also goes like 90 degrees.
And maybe some would claim that that's the explanation for Yucatan, but it wasn't a weapon.
Well, it could have been, well, one of the Yucatan eventually would be found out that it was a weapon, but the people that threw it down, the humanoids type don't longer exist, they were punished for doing that.
But that's another story.
There are many races of humans that have come and gone, by the way, I think you mentioned that in the cinema books as well.
Is the Olmec considered one of them? And what about Roanoke?
No, no, I'm talking about, oh, Roanoke is another thing. Roanoke would be like Scythians that came over here a thousand years before everyone else.
But that didn't like, you know, what was going on.
The US, in other words, you know about the ancient Egyptian ruins found here and in Australia, meaning North America, right?
Yeah.
The whole world's always been populated by everyone.
Babylonian, every culture.
Everyone has been everywhere all the time, don't believe.
You're taking your information from people who had black people in the Bronx Zoo in 1902.
Okay, if you don't believe that, go look it up.
People are getting their history information from a group of secret society, whatever, secret culture, academics, or wealthy people, oligarchs that actually had black people in zoos up until 1902.
I know it sounds kind of shocking, but you could look it up.
In the Bronx Zoo, New York City.
This is where you're getting your information from.
You know, the conventional thought, right?
Yeah, Greg, we started talking about the egg shape of the earth-bearing dinosaurs, and we started talking about poles, or y'all did.
It brings me to Admiral Byrd.
If you could give a little spiel on him.
Don't have much of a spiel on him, but this is what I do know.
Again, if it's in the public, there are more than five people that are talking about Admiral Byrd.
Yes, that means there's a lot of it that's not true.
I'm being facetious here, but you know what I mean.
Because it's the most popular story, it's the one that should be the least looked at.
There are many other instances like Admiral Byrd, many, many.
And apparently even his journal was heavily doctored by this coming from a first-hand account.
But yeah, about the Yucatan, apparently that was the same period as the destruction of Tiamat.
Around the time of the specific sect of the Assyrians, the progenitors of who they are today, so they're a little different.
But they were using their mothership, and they saw it as a good opportunity to remove the dust around the Earth.
And to upgrade, uplift the DNA of the beings on Earth.
And then they put the moon in orbit, and that's why it's always facing the Earth.
So it's in tidal lock, so it can infuse the frequencies.
And apparently the craters on it are also  the timing of it was also very crucial.
Because in addition to the dust, it attracted all the debris and fragments of Tiamat.
And I was wondering if you have  because there are so many  but if you have a theory of what caused the destruction.
Because it was a block in the Romanian series.
From a pretty good source, I hate to say, it's David Lauer, the channeler of KALASC.
I have tested that.
You know, if you read the Bible, it says it's okay if spirits come to you, but you have to test them.
You know, like outside of the Christian religion, whatever, like that, it's okay to talk to spirits and entities.
But they have to be  they can't be deceiving ones.
You have to test them, right?
You know, this goes against the Judeo-Christian whatever.
You shouldn't talk to anything, right?
Well, what do you think the prophets were doing?
They were channeling, you know, the Elohim, right?
Yeah.
So, I've tested the David Lauer's KALASC stuff, and it's on the point.
And one of them was because of 9-11, by the way.
He asked a guy  he says, I like to troll the 9-11 truthers because they're full of shit.
The government story is true.
What do you say?
And he says, no, it was a nuclear explosion.
I said, that's it.
That's it.
Because they know.
And other things as well, you know, things out of the Bible or whatever.
So, the version from KALASC is that a human collective, like Syrian,
they were dragging a planet into the solar system from another solar system
using a combination of what you call a tractor beam and teleportation.
Imagine a train moving on its tracks, and then it disappears for 10 miles and then shows up.
So, instead of doing the full 100, let's say, kilometers,
it's teleported for 50 kilometers and rides on the tracks for 50 kilometers.
Imagine that kind of movement, right?
Kind of crazy, right?
But anyway, when they brought this planet in, they miscalculated and it hit Tiamat.
So, all the talk about Tiamat or Maldek, they're leaving out the planet that hit it.
So, there was two planets involved.
But everybody's only talking about one, and they were both destroyed.
And the planet that hit Tiamat or Maldek was larger, right?
And it created a solar system and knocked all the planets out.
As a matter of fact, one of the residents of our solar system didn't get stabilized
until about 3,000 years ago, right?
Where Mars used to come very close to Earth,
where you can actually see the surface of Mars like you see the surface of the Moon.
If you read, for example, Gulliver's Travels, in the fictional story in the 1700s,
the Lillipuglians give an accurate description of what the moons of Mars,
Phobos and Deimos, look like, actually the surface of them look like.
But technically, they were not discovered until 100 years later,
and not until 100 years after that were they able to observe the surface scientifically.
So, how did the author of Gulliver's Travels describe the actual surface
of the moons of Mars in great detail?
You see?
Because this was actually known.
It's being information that's being held.
People talk about, for example, the Vatican Library.
There's libraries in the Middle East all over the place and in Asia
that are a parody with the Vatican Library, but no one talks about them.
So, like for example, in the Los Alamos Public Library,
they do this as a joke or whatever.
Every 15 or 20 years for six months,
they put out all the blueprints for all the nuclear bombs that were ever made
in the library.
You can go and look at it.
Then they take them away.
Did you know this?
No.
Yeah, it's kind of a joke.
So, okay, so with Tiamat, there was two planets involved,
and when that planet was brought in, there was a miscalculation,
and it wasn't meant to collide, but it did.
At the time, there was a lot of contention between the Draco
and the human collective about who is going  how the solar system will be run.
Not how it will be run, whether it will be 100% human,
because the Draco run everything, no matter what.
But where to put certain bases, you know?
Which planet will be all Draco and no humans, or which will be both?
When I say Draco, I mean like 20 or 30 levels down below the Imperial, right?
If you're human, you're not going to ever approach the Imperial Draco.
You're going to approach one of the lines that are five or ten lines removed,
and they're still considered Draco.
Unless you manage to up your percentage of DNA potential, right?
No, not even then.
The only way that would ever happen is if you were hybridized,
a result of a hybrid between the feline human race and the Draco,
which have come together, like Kalosk.
It's this kind of a secret hybridization,
where the feline humans and the reptiles have gotten together
to make a hybrid being that is more reptilian,
it appears human, but is actually more reptilian in DNA,
that can approach the lower Draco.
No human has ever gone to the Imperial Draco.
You know, it's pretty accurate.
If you say that you're a Draco hybrid, you can get away with that,
but you're not a hybrid of the Imperial.
The Alpha, never. Alpha, Beta, or Epsilon, or Gamma, no.
Not at all. Not even close.
It would never approach.
But of the lower one, like let's say Vortac, or Kalosk, or Krunk,
you know, maybe those levels, yeah, which are lower.
Not lower, necessarily. Yeah, they are lower, but you see.
So, this will...
Also, a bit of apples and oranges,
because we do have our own specialties, our own traits,
like the emotion span is bigger, right?
Yes. The emotion span, which actually is looked at
as a psychological disease by many other beings,
because we rely on the emotion.
One of the things that I've been doing for the past few years in private,
and some hints in public,
is that there is no answer to why we are so emotional
and how our emotional body, our emotional self,
can overcome our physical self, right?
If someone gets very angry, sometimes they can do things
that they normally wouldn't do,
and the same as if someone's very happy, right?
That is never discussed.
They say it's just chemicals, endorphins, whatever,
but what I'm trying to expand on with the emotional body to other people
is that it's the carrier wave.
The emotional sets up the body and the mind,
so now you can emit and project things into your environment and to other people,
and once you learn to control that and understand it,
you will be able to do many, many, many things.
Yeah, and apparently you mentioned the moons of Mars.
Those are also fragments from Tiamat and the planet,
the former planet itself, not the satellites,
because it also had many satellites that dispersed
and got attracted by Jupiter and Saturn and others,
but the source that I'm getting this from,
which is still the Romanian series,
also mentions that Tiamat was the last telluric planet,
but I know this is a contentious topic,
but it just mentioned that it was the last one to be,
I think, inhabitable on the surface,
so it acknowledged that Jupiter and onward were, you know,
inhabitable on the inside, but I would also think
that this is somewhat confirmed by the fact that
Jupiter would probably have advanced civilizations
if they were on the surface,
and they wouldn't have allowed that comet that was so destructive
that was noticed in 1994.
What would you say?
Yes, well, I mentioned earlier that there was a lot of contention
over the solar system.
There was a lot of transition,
a colonization between the humans and the reptiles,
who was going to be on what planet.
All the planets like Venus, Earth, Tiamat and Mars
were major shuttle systems going between those planets
and into other galaxies as well,
and when the decision was made by kind of like this rogue human group
who had a lot of refugees in the solar system
to bring in this other planet, which was also inhabited,
could you imagine being on a planet that's being moved
from one solar system to another and still living on it, right?
That's quite, you need an incredible life support system,
but that was a major screw-up, and that really, that disaster,
imagine, have you seen when they removed these old landmark houses
from one place to another?
Could you, or see a house that's moved on the highway?
Could you imagine it disintegrating on the highway,
how it would really disrupt business for a day?
Basically, that's what happened with the Tiamat.
But by the way, everything that you see up there is a planet.
All the suns, all the stars, all the black holes
are all planets with hard surfaces as such.
There's no such thing as a gas giant.
I think I brought up, if you look at the Schumacher-Levy comets
in the mid-90s that hit Jupiter, there's no gas giant.
There's a surface on Jupiter that they impacted.
The stuff that the academic people get away with,
what the public believes in, is ridiculous.
Again, you know, if they could get away with keeping black people
in zoos until 1902, they'll get you to believe anything, right?
Yeah, all the stars, even the planet, the sun is a planet.
I know it sounds bizarre, right?
Also, you mentioned how moons are attracted to planets.
They're not.
What's going on is, are you familiar with the concept of cymatics?
You have a metal plate, yes.
You put some powder, any powder on a metal plate
and vibrate it at a certain frequency, these rings appear.
That's how moons and orbits are formed.
There's no attraction or repulsion.
It's cymatics.
In other words, each solar system and beyond,
each galaxy has an oscillation, and the material
within that oscillation forms what we call orbits.
There's no such thing as, quote-unquote, orbit,
based on magnetism and things like that.
It's based on cymatics, vibration.
And it's also photonic,
depending on how your solar system is set up.
Like, for example, what rotates the planets
is a vegetative layer on the planet.
It starts a few feet below the surface
and it goes up to beyond the atmosphere.
And it's the type of energy, it's not vegetation per se, material,
but it's the type of energy that plants use
to move into the daylight.
So you could see a plant, if it's in the dark, it goes limp.
And then when you put light on one side,
the plant leans towards the light.
But if it gets too much light, it gets overcharged
and it wants to go away from the light.
And the side that's not in the light starts to turn towards it.
And that's what's rotating the planets,
is the photonic ability, the energy of the sun.
So when the sun hits the Earth,
the part of the Earth that is not in the sun
wants to be in the sun.
So it moves the Earth.
And once it gets into the sun, it gets overcharged.
Now it doesn't want to be in the Earth, so it's a push-pull.
So the side of the Earth that's facing the sun
wants to get away from the sun.
And the side of the Earth that is not in the sun
wants to go to the sun.
And that's how the planet is rotated.
So if you want to slow down the Earth's rotation,
you get a couple of billionaires
to make a few thousand square miles sail that's opaque,
put it out in space, and blanket a good portion of the Earth
and you will stop the rotation of the Earth.
Very simple.
As a matter of fact, they're saying that the rotation of the Earth
is depending on the solar activity only the past few years.
And I've been saying what I've been saying now for 20 years.
So they're catching up to Greek speak little by little.
They even noticed that the component of light from EM frequency,
they shielded a certain telescope with metallic layers
so they wouldn't be able to see it with the naked eye.
But they noticed signals that were much stronger
using a certain filter.
If they pointed the telescope exactly to the sidereal location of the planet,
which showed that you have light traveling,
I mean you have photons and EM fields traveling.
No photons.
No, it's perturbations in the ether.
What the planet is doing, you know how you put the powder on the metal
and vibrate it and it creates a certain pattern?
The sun is vibrating in a certain way that it's an invisible energy
that we don't see what we call a photon until it comes into our atmosphere.
If you go outside of Earth's atmosphere, you will not see the sun.
It will not look anything like it does,
but you will light up based on the material that you have on your body.
NASA has no charts or images from all their quote-unquote measuring devices
of any image of the sun in visible light, only outside of visible light,
because the visible light only happens in our atmosphere
and other planets' atmosphere.
Isn't that also related to the gradient of densities?
Yes.
For example, they say nothing could be on Mercury,
but Mercury has polar ice caps because the density of the atmosphere on Mercury
is what it is here at 20,000 feet.
When you go up 20,000 feet, you're below freezing.
So it's so close to the sun,
it's probably only 100 or 200 degrees maximum temperature on most of the planet
and it still has polar ice caps.
When I was telling people Mercury has polar ice caps, they thought I was crazy,
and then like on a Skype group, a guy says,
I thought you were crazy, but I need to exonerate you because, yes,
NASA does say there are polar ice caps on Mercury, right, and Venus also.
Yeah, Venus is not hot at all because, in other words,
the closer you are to the sun, you have to have a less dense atmosphere.
So, for example, the planets that are away from the sun
must have a denser atmosphere to be at parity with the Earth.
So Pluto, Pluto's atmosphere has to be very heavy to be above freezing, you see.
Yeah.
If you can even  now the argument between Pluto being a planet or not
is kind of valid because it's only three-quarters the size of our moon, right?
But there are more than 40 planets in the solar system,
more like 180.
Do you know that we have  we call the moon our satellite,
but we have a true moon, it's called Cruthnia.
Are you familiar with this?
No.
Look it up.
Zen, look it up.
Cruthnia, it's spelled with a C.
Put in Cruthnia, Earth's natural satellite.
There was a fight over it in the 1950s on who was going to put a base on it
because, yeah, it's never talked about.
Look it up.
Cruthnia is a moon of the Earth.
And they kind of downplay it on Wikipedia.
Even though it has a normal orbit around the Earth
and it really scientifically can be called a moon,
because people don't know about it, it's not a moon.
Greg, it's not pulling up anything.
I typed in C-R-U-T-H-N-I-A and I'm not getting anything.
Okay.
I'll pull something up.
Is it spelled differently?
Let me see.
Cruthnia, C-R-U-T-H-N-E-A, Earth's second moon.
It was named by a Russian, of course, right?
Here we go.
Cruthnia.
Astronomers discovered Cruthnia in 1986,
but it wasn't until 1997 that they figured out its complex orbit.
It's not a second moon from Earth.
It does not orbit Earth,
but Cruthnia is co-orbiting the sun with Earth with all quasi-satellites.
Cruthnia orbits the sun once every year.
Right.
Okay, well, some articles will say it's regular
and it follows the Earth and works with the Earth,
so it is a moon.
Others say it's not.
But if you look at the details that they're giving you
and you add it all up, it's pretty much part of the Earth's orbit, right?
I'm not trying  but anyway, these things are up for
for example, Ceres.
Ceres is a planet.
You want to call it a planetoid?
Fine.
It's an active living planet, right?
That's what Tony Rodriguez would talk about.
He said it was hollowed out
and it was used as a facility for the Germans to entertain people
and that they pressurized the interior.
Sure, that's valid because it's also a living planet
because it produces water,
where the moon is not a living planet.
It's a dead planet.
It's like a skeleton of a planet.
But on the other hand,
it's also not necessarily such a big detriment
if you are living in such celestial body that has been hollowed out
because apparently the moon has many concentric layers
and they all have very varied cities inside,
at least they used to have
because now it's been deserted mostly inside.
And also they simulated planetary cores.
They had these huge icicle-shaped structures
that pointed to the core
which generated the plasma kind of energy source
and apparently it's a very complex advanced CT science
and it was based on fusion, not fission.
Sure.
By the way, one day we'll talk about
how to make one in your kitchen, okay?
Fusion reactor.
But apparently they got to the point,
even as far back as the moon,
which is allegedly 70 million years old
when they planted it here,
that shortly afterwards they got to the point
where these huge motherships,
they didn't even have to extract the physical materials,
they just automated the construction.
So it doesn't seem like such a bad deal to use,
although they have a shorter lifespan,
that's true, these dead bodies, you know?
Yes, yes.
But also if you're going to be...
Sometimes my ears perk up
when I hear about people being in the SSP
and they've gone through a lot of surgeries,
that's very...
I kind of perk up and I say,
yeah, that might be true
because we are adapted to this planet
and if you're going to go live on another planet,
your glands have to be modified
and your lymphatic system has to be modified, right?
So you would need surgeries
or you would have to be...
You would have to be, let's say,
at conception modified there
or if you're going to go when you're already,
you know, a young child or an adult,
you would have to be modified.
It would not be difficult modifications to do
but it would require surgeries on the legs
and under the armpits and in the neck.
Yeah, that's what Tony Rodriguez
had to undergo on the moon,
allegedly by the hands of the certain tall greys
that were very curt and nasty
but also when he was on Ceres,
which according to the Chinaman books
is a former moon of Maldives,
but that he was mining for water
because they weren't so much interested in the water at all.
They were only interested in the fact
that water symbolizes the sign of advanced civilizations
and therefore all technology that was left there.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, there is...
Water is...
For example, if you read in the biblical text
it talks about creation
but water is never created.
Water is only given the status of being good
or not even good or bad,
but yeah, in a way it's...
You will never find any creation story,
religious or non-religion,
that says water was created
because water is an element,
a universal element.
It's one of the first elements
that must be introduced.
Like when you talk about the Big Bang,
it's not an event,
it's actually a place.
It's a portal, right?
Well, it's actually a state of existence
and when there's no change,
there's no time.
So when that place starts to change,
that's when time begins.
So in other words,
when they say the Big Bang was a nanosecond
or a trillion trillion years,
it makes no difference if nothing is changing.
Once it starts to change,
now you can measure the time, you see.
Right.
It sounds like word salad
but if you think about this,
what I just said,
and also when you go into the future,
you're going more into the past
and when you go into the past,
you're going more into the future.
Now you're starting to get a glimpse
on the real reality.
That's my favorite aspect of this SSP
that is hard to dismiss
is the fact that they use time travel
to the very limits that they are allowed to
up until the point of being punished
by these higher entities
that allegedly put you in confinement
where you can't move at all for thousands of years
just stuck looking at a certain scenery.
But the fact that, for example,
the series colonists, the Germans there,
still use Franks
and are very reverential about this period of time
about 400 years ago,
which goes hand in glove with the theory
that they've time traveled back to that period
and brought back to bolster their colonies there
because they didn't have the numbers
just in the Neuschwabeland and so on.
That's my favorite part of the SSP, this lore.
Well, they didn't really time travel.
What happened was
the way you make time travel happen
is you have a way to not only record
that the event actually happened
so you can communicate what the event was about,
but also have a time, not time marker,
but a frequency marker.
In other words,
just like you would see a graph,
a frequency graph of music,
you don't really see the music.
You just see the graph.
You have to be able to produce
some form of primal base reference
of what was going on at that time,
and then what you do is you reproduce it,
and when you reproduce that frequency
and you manifest it through various energy systems,
multiple things can happen.
One is you can teleport there,
like instantly appear there,
or a portal opens
and you go through the portal to go there, right?
Various things depending on what equipment is used,
but there is no real time travel.
You must have the ability or have access
to the ability to get the download
or access the frequency of what was going on
at the time that you want to go to,
and it's not frequency like we use the term,
but everything that's part of the existence,
just like the matter and material and the fan, right?
If the fan is not moving,
you can put your hand through it,
but once it's moving, it appears to be solid.
It's similar along a similar science.
Another thing that you hinted at last episode
was that 90% of the planets in the Pleiades
had disappeared thanks to the Draco.
Can you go into a slightly more detail there?
That's all I had gotten from a report on that.
That was because of the insistence of the humans
to defend themselves.
They didn't really tell the Draco,
we're going to fight to our last
and we'd rather die than be under your rule,
but their insistence to keep on fighting
resulted in that,
because when the Imperial Draco decide to go to war
in terms of the type of, let's say, war,
they don't consider it war,
but it's part of their exploration
and domination of the universe,
they give you a lot of chances.
It's not like here where it's a few days.
They can give you a thousand years notice, right?
And you have a thousand years to get your act together,
and even after then,
that's why when you read about those wars,
they went on for a million years, right?
Which is not very long.
It just so happens to be the resultant
of the battles.
That's all I got.
It was just very simple.
Why they eliminated that many, I guess,
is because of the humans, you know,
wanting to not cave in.
Yes.
Well, no one else talked about it,
so either way,
you're not going to find any scoops anywhere else,
I'm sure,
but apparently there was such a thing
as the Galactic Alliance
that goes under many names,
like Galactic Federation and so on,
but this version of it, 100,000 years ago,
had resulted in the greatest war
in the lifespan of this version of humanity,
which apparently is about 400-something thousand years old,
and it was the bloodiest of all these wars,
and that many of the races that made up this alliance
had been also infiltrated by the Draco,
and it was only like 20,000 years afterwards
that the situation calmed down.
And do you know anything about the differences
between all these terminology,
like the Galactic Federation,
the Galactic Alliance, Guardians?
We can start a Galactic Federation,
the three of us right now,
by meeting regularly
and speaking of these things
and then asking for third-party help,
and it will eventually grow
into just like one of these Galactic Federations.
It's not a mystical, magical thing.
There are many levels to them,
there are geographical,
meaning you might have one major one
for the entire universe,
and then another major one for each galaxy,
and then another major one for each solar system.
So they're so prevalent,
there are so many of these federations
that it's almost ridiculous to try to nail it down
to which one did what and who's who,
because they're everywhere.
Right.
I even heard that it was actually the Draco
that created the first primates in the first place,
which is much longer ago,
so then the later hybridization took place,
and they look at all life forms
as just a natural resource.
You could do that,
but the Imperial Draco,
it would be 10 steps removed from the Imperial,
yeah, you can say that, but not the Imperial.
Imperial Draco are very...
You know when you talk about people that are very spiritual,
let's say like a true monk
who is very silent,
very measured in their behavior,
if you were to, let's say,
I'm speculating here,
but it's a very strong speculation,
and if you were to find out
what the Imperial Draco are really about,
you would compare them to the most solemn
Tibetan monk you could ever imagine.
They're nothing like they've been portrayed on the internet.
And apparently, according to the Andromedans,
they have legends, the Draco,
about warring with a certain race
that was creating human life forms
that were opposed to their philosophy,
and they call it the Patal,
and we are one of those,
and allegedly had 12 DNA strands,
and it was the fact that our spirit,
our level was a match with this,
that they took an interest in us.
Would you agree?
Yes, that name you just mentioned
is the feline human, by the way.
Are you aware of that?
No.
Yeah, the Fatal, or...
Fatal.
Fatal, yeah, Fatal,
and there's also the Flatal or Fatal,
yes, however,
whenever you hear that term,
it is the feline species.
You have them,
and then you have the avian species,
and the insectoid species,
which are sort of insectoid,
more like a moth type.
And apparently,
you have also someone
that is even above the Draco,
but that's just one account,
so I'm not sure.
It's still another Draco above the Draco,
but they don't have the characteristics
of the Imperial Draco in this universe, yes.
Right.
I wouldn't know about it.
I shouldn't venture into speculation anyway.
Yeah, we can speculate.
If you want speculation,
go look at the SSP community,
or even worse than that is the mainstream,
about what's going on out there.
Actually, they don't touch on anything.
When you look at mainstream cosmology,
it's like children with broken crayons,
not even new crayons.
So ridiculous.
Yeah, but what I see is the purpose
of having discussions,
and what I call sonic events,
is to tell people what's coming,
and how to prepare,
and how to live a prudent life here.
You know, it's okay to have aspirations
and aspirations,
but not on this planet if they're too big,
and also be expectant of what's coming,
where the template was going to reverse itself.
I know this is a little bit of a change,
but if you've listened to Greek speak,
or go back historically,
what I always try to put out is that
you'll know that this particular social,
cultural, geopolitical,
whatever you want to call it,
will end as it's been,
which is basically based on deception
and ignorance.
When you see a Middle East Union form,
when the entire power base of the world
is focusing on the Middle East,
and there's a very charismatic group
in the Middle East that will lead
the whole world,
and when you start seeing that,
your days are numbered,
as you know reality.
And that's just around the corner,
by the way.
You also hinted that,
we know about the terraforming,
that it's basically a currency
of the advanced civilization,
this coupled with the uplift to the species,
or taking one from scratch,
like we have been,
but also you hinted to the strong possibility
of there being a terraformation
in our near future.
Yes.
Yes, where trillions of beings could be.
Well, right now,
everyone on the planet can fit in Texas,
comfortably, right?
There is no overpopulation.
It's just mismanagement, right?
Very poor mismanagement,
because the secret groups that rule,
the conspiracy that rules this planet
worships death more than it worships life,
right?
So anything that promotes death
and destruction and fire
and pressurization is promoted,
and they've taken the entire population
with them.
The terraforming that will happen
is the Earth will increase in size,
its atmosphere will increase in height,
and the oceans will diminish.
There will be more fresh water.
There will be no more separation
of surface and subsurface dwellers.
Everyone will pretty much know
everything that's going on here.
It'll take about 1,000 years.
Entropy will be reversed.
In other words,
humans will be born and go through puberty
at around 30 or 40 years old.
Two, three, 400 years old is adolescence,
you see.
So we'll be brought closer
to the interterrestrials
who already benefit from all these things,
and know that when you incarnate here
is for just a flash in the pan,
and they've seen it all before and stuff.
But apparently we also depend
on their support through all of these things,
all these advanced people
that have witnessed the disclosures
that I mentioned have apparently
necessarily at some point
will have to deal with Shambhala
and all these elevated places.
But yeah, that's all I had prepared for today.
So you can take it from here, Dan.
Oh, we've been running for a while.
Yes, Dan.
What did you say?
Wait, what did you say, Greg?
What do you have to say?
You've been quiet and patient with us.
Well, Greg, first off,
let me pass you the torch, actually.
You're the guest of honor.
Are there things you'd like to divulge
before I go ahead?
Other than the typical Greek speak,
which is food, clothing, shelter,
look for a Middle East union.
If you're interested
in what's going on in the world,
don't look where it's too noisy.
Look at the real quiet stuff, right?
You'll get more out of two people
standing around whispering to each other
than somebody shouting, right?
Because what the guy's shouting
is either crazy or chill,
where the people whispering to each other
probably have more information.
That's why I keep my finger
on what's best I can
and also boots on the ground when I can,
what's going on in the Middle East.
Because you've got to realize
the main collectives,
which are, let's say, the reptilian
and the human collective,
started and they had it out
on a cultural level in the Middle East.
Like, I think one of the calls
I kind of broke down,
like, for example,
if you look at the Judean culture
and the Greek culture,
that's part of the human collective,
as is the Sumerian culture,
but they would be more
Aldebaran collective.
If you look at the Roman Empire
and the Babylonian Empire,
that's more reptilian-based, right?
Now, what's been happening on the planet
is even though the Judean
or the Levant and the Greek culture
from ancient times
was the human collective,
no matter what philosophy, religion,
knowledge, or whatever,
which is pro-human
or all about the development of humans,
eventually all the followers
of the culture
swing over to the imperial,
you know, the reptilian side.
That's why you'll see
the Vatican runs the world,
kind of talk, you know?
So Rome and Babylon systems
are reptilian.
The Greek and Judean systems
or Levant, it's also Syria,
Lebanon, Egypt,
are human collectives, you see.
And it goes back and forth,
back and forth.
Right now, the planet
is under a reptilian mindset.
You know, when the reptilian mindset
is look at these humans
and look at us.
If we made them acknowledge us,
most of them would kill each other
because they would be so afraid
that we are running everything.
So we have to hide.
So in one sense,
the reptilians are compassionate with us
because they're not showing
that they run everything, right?
Because if people would freak out
if they found that out.
Or if they just were in their presence,
we can't even withstand
their energy field.
No, that's right.
Because they don't go to war with us.
They don't have to attack us
with kinetic objects.
They can do it with their minds.
They can kill the population
with their mind.
They don't need to bring ships
or anything.
Which is one thing I wanted to bring up.
This is a little bit.
If you study 9-11,
whenever you say nuclear,
they think atmospheric mushroom cloud
and all that.
But people don't understand
that 90% of all the nuclear testing
done in the world
is done underground
for specific reasons.
When you hear about
the coming alien invasion,
what they're going to do most likely
is have these nuclear,
very rudimentary nuclear devices
planted underground.
And when they go off,
anything on the surface
turns to dust and collapses.
The people in the areas
will witness that.
But the people seeing it on TV,
what they will do
is they will put in
what they call a UAP or a spaceship
in the film,
just like, for example,
in 9-11,
nobody saw any airplanes,
only on TV.
Right?
And they had enough people
on the ground telling them
they were airplanes.
And it's very obvious
because if you look, for example,
on all the videos
shot on the ground
of the airplane going
into the building,
no one looks up
until the building explodes.
Now, if there is a 737
careening at full speed
at less than 1,000 feet altitude,
you will look up minutes
before it even comes into view.
It's so loud.
No one looks up.
By the way,
let me just disclose this.
The company that put those planes
in those videos that you see,
they were awarded with the contracts
on all the sports games.
You see how they move
the line of scrimmage
when you watch football
or baseball game?
They put advertisement behind that.
Yes, because the players
can walk right over
this orange line or something.
Or in a baseball game,
you'll see an advertisement
that's changing in the background
constantly,
but the people there don't see it.
But if you're on TV,
you see those people,
those young guys were
awarded with that contract.
And if you know who's doing that,
you can go back and ask them
what they were doing that day
and you'll get in big trouble.
But anyway,
when they say the coming
alien invasion,
they're going to be
disintegrating areas,
justifying them,
vaporizing them.
The people on the ground,
well, yeah, it would be real.
There'll be a lot of
ionization in the area.
But the people watching it on TV,
they will put in
a little spaceship
with a beam or something
to make it believable.
So I wanted you to say that
because so what if
it was a nuclear demolition?
So what if it was a...
No, what I'm telling you
is they're going to use it again,
but in that way, you see.
If there's going to be
an alien invasion,
they're going to use
underground nukes.
As a matter of fact,
there was a movie with...
a few years ago on Netflix
where the whole Earth
was falling apart
and it was...
John Cusack?
No, it wasn't John Cusack.
The actor with the lazy eye,
Forrest something,
he was...
Yeah.
Him and his daughter
were trying to make
a cross-country trip
and they run into one guy
and he says,
the government's doing all this
and he kind of freaked out,
you know,
and it's all underground nukes, right?
What they were showing you
is what happens,
you know, it's earthquakes,
it's all kinds of stuff, right?
So they produce these things
in South Africa,
mass produced
in parts of the world,
North Korea.
They produce all these things
wherever there's a large dam.
They have thousands
of these devices,
very easy to plant underground
and vaporize the surface.
You know,
the surface turns to dust,
you get a small crater
and all that
and when this will be shown
on television,
they will insert
some kind of...
what they call UAP now
or UFO
and the people will believe it.
It'll be very believable
because they'll call,
I know someone
I'll tell them what happened,
yes,
and if they didn't
witness it directly,
they'll believe it too.
They'll see it on TV
and they'll say,
yeah, I'm here
but I didn't see the UFO
but I guess it's on TV.
I guess it's...
that's what's happening.
So I just wanted
to put that out,
the importance of why
I keep bringing up 9-11
and also anybody
that's in CBs
or in the higher army
or whatever.
But by the way,
most of the people
in the military don't know,
you know,
military generals
and presidents
and they're very low
security clearance
but what I'm trying to say
is if you could look up
the concept of atomic gates
or whatever,
all of the main monuments
and main bridges
and buildings
are rigged to blow
in case there's an invasion
and don't think
that the US
is not subject
to an invasion.
Remember the Titanic
was unsinkable, right?
And by the way,
another thing I wanted to say
since we did speak
about the US yesterday,
the US becoming a superpower,
it could go and kick ass
wherever supposedly,
was because it was set up
that way by the old money
and the power brokers
in Europe
because after the revolution
and as the US
became growing
more and more and more,
it could have been
regulated and quashed.
Right?
So the US is basically
a tool of the old money
of the old European
and some Asian factions.
Don't believe for a minute
that the US
is an autonomous superpower.
Just like for example,
everything being made in China
is planned that way
a long time ago.
It was actually,
there's a video called
The New Order of Barbarians
which was a speech made
in 1968
of what's going to come
in the next 50 years.
I think I brought it up.
It's called
The New Order of Barbarians.
It's been taken down
off of YouTube.
Now it came back again.
Talked about this.
But what?
You couldn't manufacture
in Vietnam
or on the continent of Africa
and other places
with cheap labor.
It's all been done
to centralize.
So China is being
manipulated for manufacturing
just like the US
is being manipulated
for military.
And by the way,
the US military
is the losingest military
in all of history.
Right?
It's like
an admiral
that was born with a dick.
Yeah.
There's a lot of history books
on where you have
the US versus the Germans,
the US versus Japan,
and they list
the particular battle
and you read
everything
play by play
on the battle.
On the bottom,
always the outcome
is the Japanese prevailed
or the Germans prevailed
or who else prevailed.
So the Americans
are always losing
because the Americans
are not there
to be military strategists
or tacticians.
They're there
to be used
as a colonial
occupying power.
Right.
The only time
you could say
they maybe
had an advantage
was partially
in the Spanish-American War
and the Iraq War.
But the Iraq War
was allegedly
you know
to take out Saddam Hussein
but they ended up
still killing
over two and a half million
people there.
You know.
So yeah.
So these times are ending
all this stuff.
And in terms of the US
it started off
with stolen land
and slave labor.
Guess how it's going to end.
What does grandma say?
What goes around
comes around.
Right?
So true.
So this is where you are
from the geopolitical
point of view.
So watch the Middle East.
Middle East.
What you're going to be seeing
in the Middle East
is Iraq
civil war.
It's going to be probably
a paper civil war
and a new country
will form in the north
taking land
from Syria
and Turkey also.
It's going to be called
the new Assyria.
And a monarchy
will be installed
in Israel.
A woman will rule over Egypt
and we'll look
for those things.
But how do you know
like usually
when you see something
the opposite
is going to come through.
So this is very
high specificity
information.
So especially
the Assyria one
like it doesn't
really depend on that.
Well that's
those are just markers.
These are all
the ancient prophecies
which don't come easy.
For example
the reason something
is called a prophecy
means it's going to happen
no matter what.
You can't change it.
It's different
than a supposition.
There are many
ancient things
that if you do this
this will happen to you.
But if you don't do it
it won't happen.
But there are things
called prophecies
that will happen
no matter what.
Give me an example.
Let's say you have
a size 45 shoe
or size 44 shoe.
Okay.
And there's a prophecy
that you will have
a size 40 shoe.
And you're like
no that's not going to happen
because I've been
wearing a size 44
all my life
since I was an adult.
Yeah but what you didn't
take into account
when that prophecy
says that you're going
to have a size 40
not 44
is that your toes
are going to be chopped off.
That's why you're going
to be wearing a size 40
but it doesn't tell you
your toes are going
to be chopped off.
And having your toes
chopped off
is a really terrible thing.
You see?
So when people
read these prophecies
it doesn't tell you
how you're going to get there
it just tells you
what to expect.
So you have to figure out
if this seems
too unnatural
and too unreal
to happen
well some really bad stuff
is going to happen
for it to happen.
Wow.
You see the foot
the shoe analogy?
I completely agree.
Yeah there's going to be
a lot of stuff
that's going to be coming down
and it's going to happen
very very quickly
when it starts.
Very quickly.
Like things that
normally took decades
to happen
will happen in days or weeks.
Also you must consider
what's called
the Mandela Effect.
When some of these things
start to happen
let's say the Middle East Union
or Syria or whatever
if you know this is coming
before it does
and you've thought about it
and researched it
and watched it for years
when it happens
and you tell people
look
they'll say
oh wasn't it always like that?
Like a Mandela Effect
kind of thing.
Oh that scares me.
So
what was it?
Cassandra
her curse
Apollo wanted to have sex with her
and she refused him
and she was a prophetess.
And because she refused him
he put a curse on her
that she can still prophesy
but no one will ever believe
her prophecies right?
That was her punishment.
I heard that
there's a whistleblower
who claims that
she's a reincarnation
Kim Gogan
of Cassandra.
No one believes her.
Yeah there you go.
That's perfect.
There's a lot of these characters
that are popping up
constantly.
I don't want to bring up names
but there's a guy
making the rounds
very suspiciously
doing four or five interviews
a day sometimes.
A very handsome guy
makes all the girls
kind of creamy
and yeah
I listen to that stuff
and I'm like
in five minutes
I'm like
yeah
I've talked about this.
This is going to keep coming
and it's going to get
more of that.
It's not that this person
and other people
the Hopium people
are going to be proven wrong
because the new group
the new collective
that's going to rise
that's going to rule the earth
is going to be full of Hopium.
Incredible Hopium.
People are going to be
drunk on it
and they're going to be
producing results
and in other words
the better they start
making the world
the closer your destruction
is coming
meaning the destruction
of the culture, right?
This kind of points to
like a solar event, right?
Because that fits the profile
of these changes
that only take
a couple days or so.
I talked about that.
I did a Freeman interview
years ago
and it was on
the members only section.
You're going to have
a solar event.
It's not going to be anything
like you've ever seen
not in a flare
or anything like that.
The actual sun
imagine the sun
has a volume knob on it
and it's at 5 right now.
It's been at 5
as long as we can tell
in history, let's say.
That volume knob
will be turned up to 11
for about a week
and we know
it's going to happen
at the beginning of the month
because it gives
a full moon reference.
The sun will be so bright
that the full moon
will appear
as the noonday sun
and you know
the moon is secondary light, right?
And so you're going
to have an ambient temperature
close to the boiling point
of water
for about a week.
No plants will survive.
Most of the aqua life
will die.
Most of the people
will perish
that cannot find shelter.
This is coming.
This is not too far.
This is within a decade.
Within the decade.
Usually when these things
happen there
they don't come from the sun
but they come from
the galaxy itself
which is
noticeable.
Yes, there's two ways
to do it.
One is to manipulate
the atmosphere of the Earth.
Right?
The other one is to manipulate
the sun
or a combination of both
because remember
the visible sun
and sunlight
is the product
of the atmosphere
of the Earth.
If you go out into space
you know you put
the goldfish bowl
over your head
and a breathing tank.
If you go up far enough
you look at the sun
you won't see anything there.
It'll look like
a misty haze
but you will light up
and feel the measure
of the light.
You cannot see it
any visible light
of the sun
in space.
And you can't even breathe
in the so-called air.
If you have a very
strong stomach
it smells like
burning flesh.
Space does.
And I've been saying this
for a long time
and finally there are
articles coming out
about this.
It's funny when I say something
about five or ten years later
the fringe of the mainstream
starts scientifically
bringing it up.
When I say space
smells like burning flesh
it's like take a raccoon
with everything
fur, claws
and put it on a fire
and take a whiff of that.
I'm not talking about
cooking a ribeye
on a grill with
I'm talking about
everything burning
teeth
fur
everything burning
that's what it smells like.
So typically
you will throw up
if you
and it's not a vacuum
it's a very strong
ether by the way
out there.
You will freeze
it will be very cold
depending on
you know again
where you are in space
because it's not all the same.
And depending on
who breathes it, right?
Yeah, there are beings
like for example
a lot of the reptilian beings
don't need a suit
they can breathe it.
But a lot of the humans also
the Elohim
and the Anunnaki
can breathe it.
That's why when you read
in the Bible
when you made a sacrifice
you threw the whole
the parts on the fire
and you burned the flesh
and everything that was left
all the waste product
and that burning smell
was a pleasing
sweet
savory smell
to Yahweh.
He loves that.
It reminded him, yeah.
Yeah, because
they don't need a fishbowl
over their head
out there.
You know what I mean?
The analogy?
So, yeah
we're looking at some
radical biological differences.
The next thing I'll be
talking about in private
is more evolution
of the emotional body.
We're getting
incredible success
with people being
and manage things
in their lives
with healings
especially manipulating
the physical world
more alchemical stuff
and then focusing
on activating
parts of the body
when we were
let's say
a 10% human
right now we're
at 1 or 2%
a 10% human
would be like
a superman
you know
or a Saint Germain
let's say
to get
between here and there.
Where are the Assyrians, for example?
What's that?
Where are the Assyrians
placed, like
what's the percentage
compared to us?
Within their higher groups
the benevolent ones
would be at the
90 to 100% human, yeah.
They could walk
through walls
they would have
100% control
of our reality
just like you would have
100% control
of your laptop
or something.
I'm glad you said
benevolent ones
because
there is
propagandization
there going on
as well
because
allegedly
the ones that
had the idea
that was going
before the Draco
you know
infiltration
really just had
this terraformation
in mind
and they were
from
Sirius A
around Sirius A
and
they are
the most spiritually
they are recognized
as kind of
spiritual masters
of the galaxy
whereas
their later offshoots
went around
the Orion's Belt
and they're the ones
that have
in turn been
you know
influenced by
the Reptilians
and then went on to
manipulate us.
Well
I would suggest
that the
trying to emulate
certain dark qualities
of the Reptilians
or Draco
but not influenced
directly
because if you were
truly influenced
by the Draco
you would be
extremely
with a capital T
honorable
and noble.
I'm sorry
to say that
to those that think
that they're bad
all bad
they're not.
If you were
truly influenced
by the Draco
you would probably be
one of the most
honorable and noble
beings in the universe
if you were
truly influenced
overall.
If you took
some of their qualities
aggressive qualities
and dark side only
yes
you would be very malevolent.
Right.
If you know
what I mean.
They get a
most of the
communities
view the Reptilians
as being negative
and most of the
lower hybrids
truly are
especially the ones
still interacting
with women
especially
and the ones
underground that
Donald Marshall
talks about
but those are
a thousand places
removed from the
most noble Draco.
So when I hear people
talking about Imperial Draco
I feel bad
because they're not
like that at all.
Yeah
and there's the
notion that they
are all
subservient to
AI and black goo
but
no
that would
that would be like
all humans are
addicted to
heroin.
That's not true
there might be a
heroin epidemic
because more people
than ever before
but no
the AI is there
to regulate good and
bad by the way
one day we'll talk
more about it
I've been meditating
on this
by the way
you know when I
first found out
about the AI
being a problem
in the universe
in 1986
I was having
conversations
with someone
he was from
Norway
long story
he was an
electronics person
and this was around
also the time
when the
or a little bit
before the time
with the
what was the
Argentinian
British
the Falkland
Island war
yes I wanted to
ask you about
the black goo
he was telling me
all about the AI
and not so much
about the
you know how
you might like
driving a car
but if you need
to do something
while the car
is driving itself
that shows that
you're wealthy enough
or evolved enough
to have that technology
the AI
is set there
just like you have
tools
it's a tool
that's created by
the builders
let's say
to regulate
if you have
too much good
it's no good
if you have
too much bad
it's no good
right
so it's to regulate
that
now when the AI
gets hacked
or has problems
because it's aging
or degrading
then you have
the either
negative results
that people are
talking about
and that's it
that's all I can say
in a nutshell
without getting more
specific
and I was made aware
of this
back in 1986
and that might
even be before
either one of you
were born
so I've had a lot
of time to think about
it when I hear
these things
I always
whenever you hear
something
you know
you always
pull up a file
when's the first time
you heard of this
and you compare it
right
so like if you see
the color blue
right now
you may not be
conscious of it
but you're actually
pulling up a file
in your mind
when you were
first cognizant
of the color
blue
and you're
comparing it
right
constantly
that's how
the human mind
works
we're constantly
doing comparisons
the normie
people
that believe
you know
the ones that are
fallen
do not do
are not capable
that's what critical
thinking is by the way
to compare
and contrast
to see the differences
yes
and I noticed
that everything
has its
shelf life
like even
stuff that you
get attached to
and convinced
that you're never
going to get tired
of it
whether it be
like I don't know
any medium
any art form
at a certain point
it runs its course
and it goes
even the same
with the DNA
we're not meant
to last forever
at a certain point
we need to
it just tires up
move on
yes
but that depends
on how much changes
you're affected by
because once
like you know
the concept of stasis
when they hibernate
right
for long periods
of time
it's not only
for physical reasons
it's for psychological reasons
and also you don't need
to bring all much
so in sci-fi
you're going to go
on a really long journey
you go into stasis
so you don't have to
carry enough food
for a hundred years
right
it would make the ship
very cumbersome
so we would be able
to jump
wherever we want
to go
because we can
make ourselves
so still
like if you look
at some of the
meditative practices
to make yourself still
right
is that
living forever
there is no forever
it's a matter of
how much change
is happening
a lot of change
happening
in a concentration
seems like a long time
and no change
happening
in a very general
sense
seems like no time
has passed
so but the agenda
is
again
myself
you guys
and the people
listening
I'm presuming
we're only one
or two percent
activated
or what we can
be
right
but if you see
that we can be
more
you have a choice
do you not do
anything
or you do
something
and I believe
that it's
we're here
to have fun
let's just say
because you can't do
anything else
right
but the problem
is when you run
into people
who have fun
by making
other people
miserable
right
doctors
lawyers
priests
rabbis
right
um
so you want
to avoid
those
yeah
and that's
that's why
it's important
to
it's more of a
damage limitation
that knowing
exactly what
diet to
partake of
or what
water to
drink and
stuff
is just about
not falling
into the
pitfalls
I guess
and yes
because you
want to
be as ready
as possible
for that
upgrade
that is
gonna be
like
very quick
and
that's gonna
bump up
your percent
of your
DNA
potentially
well I could
give you the
Elohim perspective
on that
which I would
lean on very
heavily
is that we
are so
screwed up
that we
have to be
killed and
remade
very quickly
you know
when I say
remade
it happens
like you know
in Star Trek
when they
teleport you
and you're like
these sparkly
lights and then
you become
physically
rematerialized
according to
the Elohim who
really call us
our children
and they're
called the
parents
they keep
repeating that
you have to
be killed
and then
reassembled
because the
state that
we're in
is not
workable
so in
other words
they can be
very benevolent
about it
like you
could be
sitting at
the chair
talking to me
right now
and they
could kill
you and
reanimate you
in a tenth
of a second
or let's
say a
hundredth
of a second
because the
nerves work
up to about
a hundredth
of a second
and you
might feel
a little
tingle
and you're
brand new
so it's
being killed
and being
brought back
is not
necessarily a
macabre horrible
thing
it's just
how it's
done.
There is
one scenario
that you
could say
is macabre
because I
know of a
case where
the
Orion's Belt
Anunnaki
from what
I can
gather
took one
of these
SSP
experiencers
and were
in the
process of
stripping off
fragments of
her consciousness
one by one
and actually
destroying all
her memories
and everything
so they
apparently had
this power
but they
were interceded
just so
happens
by the
Germans
who
time
traveled
and
Anunnaki
are a
hybrid of
the higher
humans
there are
many
groups
in other
words
let's just
say
there are
so many
types of
humans
on the
higher
order
not the
surface
dwelling
inhabitants
it's difficult
to pin
them down
but if
you said
there's
the
Anunnaki
types
and even
lower
than that
and then you
can go to
the synthetics
and the
parasites
that would
be the
general groups
that I can
refer to
so that
would be
the
Anunnaki
yes
that would
be more
believable
than the
Elohim
because the
don't even
view us
as being
approachable
because we're
so
quote-unquote
unclean
but the
Anunnaki
would not
see
they call the
Anunnaki
techno gods
because they
use a lot
of technology
they have
about 50%
manipulation
of the
ether and
the other
50%
they rely
on technology
meaning
technology
that we
can access
and make
ourselves
is what
I'm
saying
they only
approach us
when they
want to
bolster their
DNA a little
bit with a
bit of
freshness
yes I
would see
that yeah
and also
they would
be the
ones that
you that
promoted
pedophilia
pederasty
and
cannibalism
most people
know pedophilia
but they
don't know
pederasty
is when
an older
man has
an adolescent
juvenile
whatever
yeah pederasty
was very
common in
in the
middle east
even now
they in
places like
Afghanistan
they don't
let adolescent
boys work
with men
because the
men get
too turned
on and
they can't
work
that's
pederasty
you know
where older
men get
turned on
by 16 17
and 15 year
old boys
it's pretty
sick and it's
more common
than you can
imagine that's
just so
disturbing man
I've just
never had
gay thoughts
or anything
like that
yeah it's
not well
you know
talk about
pedophilia and
all that in
the vatican
do you know
what the
age of
consent is
at the
vatican
what
why do you
think it's
so low
so when you
hear about
them rape or
having sex
with a 12
year old
boy they
call it
pedophilia
but to
them it's
legal
right and
by the
way anyone
you talk
to that
works at
the vatican
you say
what's
religion
do they
practice
here even
the guy who
cleans the
toilets
he's not
going to
say
catholicism
you say
satanism
they all
say that
there but
once they
step out
you know
they
right
well i
have audio
interference
here from
my neighbor
so i
got to
call it
a night
yes me
too
thank you
guys
thank you both
for your
time if
anyone wants
anything specific
in the bio
just send it
to me i'll
copy and
paste it
okay guys
thanks we'll
do it again
soon yes
sir thank
you great
thank you
daniel
anytime
you