Greg, I sincerely appreciate you making time, really.
That's right.
Okay, cool.
My pleasure.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
Oh, my pleasure.
Let's kick it off.
Cool.
So I basically put together a big list
of stuff that I've been, I don't know,
wanting to answer or to revisit with you
and just go over.
And one thing that I've been hearing some
buzz about, the drone thing brought it up
recently.
I know that's a big sigh, but who
I think behind it, from what I can
gather, is this whole Northcom entity that came
around after 9-11.
Do you know much about that?
I think it's straight north of you.
Yeah, it could be.
Here's the thing.
Let me just bring up a point that
I'd like to carry over on the rest
of the conversation.
And I'll show you how it applies to
anything we discuss.
Because I refer to us as surface-dwelling
earth inhabitants, and we live in a very
toxic environment.
Well, okay.
Yeah, we do.
Yeah, we know it's toxic.
No, I'm not talking about chemicals and pollution.
I'm talking about mentally toxic, and I'm going
to mention the premise of everything is the
way society functions.
There's two categories.
You have the public and you have the
private, and I'll give you a quick example.
And we'll go back to the drones.
With the banking system, I borrowed money from
the bank.
I have to pay it back.
That's what they tell the public.
That's what everyone thinks.
But really, what's going on is the bank
has no money to lend you.
They just monetize your signature, and if you
confront them with that, they punish you.
So if you operate in the private, and
you know what's going on, you have a
much different attitude.
So what I mean by this is, if
we're going to go back to the drones,
there's a private side to what's going on.
And when you hear the term black ops,
secret operations, whatever, forget about those terms.
That's private.
It's a bunch of people pulling out some
private stuff that can only be, or organizations,
that can only be interpreted with public knowledge,
which is not compatible, if that makes sense.
No, you're right.
That's the dilemma I have.
I know I'm fed artificial feedback, all this
bullshit, and I try and make sense of
it.
I don't necessarily care about the drones, per
se.
The public is allowed this much of a
threshold, a fraction, and then it's to mess
with us and do all these things.
But it's like, I don't know where, I
just- No, I get it.
Let me just say it this way, Zen,
or let me just stop you.
There is no rational way to describe what's
going on, logical, rational, feasible, acceptable way using
public parlance, what the public is told, will
not apply.
It's kind of like 19 Arab hijackers vaporized
the World Trade Center with box cutters.
Wait a second, Greg, that's not the official
story.
Yeah, tell me the official story and tell
me it makes more sense than what I
just said, right?
So it doesn't work.
It's just, so what I would suggest, in
this case, with this question, with the drone,
is what do you see?
What data can you gather and compile for
yourself?
And those that you would consider as being,
like Dan Pena would say, high performance people,
not this semi-intelligent tripe shit, and I'm
using the medical term there, right?
I mean, people that you consider to be
high performance, high functioning people, gather your own
data, put it together, hit the mute button,
look at the pictures, all right, that kind
of thing.
But what I've been aware of, what's going
on with the drones, just to segue back,
what is it?
It's a PSYOP, but what isn't a PSYOP,
right?
If you go to the grocery store, the
new packaging on a box of breakfast cereal
is a PSYOP also.
So what degree of a PSYOP?
I really don't care.
Personally, I think the mothership, you know, I'm
talking about like the two mile long mothership,
should enter our atmosphere and vaporize everyone on
the surface.
So a bunch of drones to me is
just a joke.
But anyway, that was, take that however you
want to do it.
So it is a joke.
I was just thinking, how do I breach
the surface of these entities that are underground
in Colorado Springs, things like that.
That kind of stuff always.
Well, how is there, you know, they say
mind your own business or, you know, miners
like to say that, mind your own business,
right?
I would just do that.
I mean, I'm not saying for you, that's
a bunch of folks that are, are they
getting away with it?
The answer is yes.
Right.
Because even the administration says, yes, we had,
we've heard about them.
We are aware of them, but we don't
know what they are.
Isn't that the official answer typically?
So basically, it's a joke.
Yeah.
All right.
But here's the thing.
So my point is here, we know these,
this is a private group, right?
And and they're doing their thing.
And yeah, it's a little inconvenient, psychologically, mentally,
socially or whatever.
But we're going to let them do their
thing.
That's basically it.
So let them do their thing.
Are they affecting you personally or your loved
ones?
The answer is no.
And out of it.
Oh, well, OK.
I think in an abstract way, they are
not to necessarily rebut you, sir.
I'm just saying, like, they do that stuff
to see how we're going to handle it.
And then, OK, great.
Now they're going to pass drone legislation so
that they want to completely control the sky.
And I feel if they get enough pushback
from us, they I know it's a very
broad sweeping term.
Well, maybe we should go public on how
to build a device that could send a
tennis ball through a brick wall.
I don't think they'll be up in the
sky for very long.
But anyway, that's another discussion.
Yeah, I'm just tired of being treated like
like a dumbass.
That's all.
No, you will.
Well, that's because you're not pursuing.
I'm just saying, let's just let me say
this.
We're not pursuing high performance or stuff that's
in your category.
And you're actually allowing yourself to be downgraded.
I mean, just take that as a suggestion.
Right.
Like if I look at alternative whatever.
OK.
The alternative media online is public.
It's public stuff.
It's in public parlance.
It's what the public understands.
None of it makes sense because all of
this is being done in the private and
it's being shown publicly.
Yeah.
No, you're completely right.
But I think that one can understand if
one can understand that it's all crap and
then be able to analyze it and understand
to a certain level and realize, OK, what
part of this is a test?
What are they really saying here?
You know, what does this mean about the
powers that be?
You know, is it a front?
Is it a this or that?
And I think that's worth interpreting, I mean,
if one can.
And that's what I guess the advice I
see from you and I know that there's
many layers to all this.
You know, there's there's a lot.
It depends on what you want to put
your focus on.
Sure.
You know, like, for example, there's, I don't
know, 40 or 50 million people in the
U.S. on blood pressure medication.
And guess what?
Blood pressure is a fiction.
It's a medical.
It does not exist.
There is no pressure in the blood and
they're and they're dying from this medication.
Right.
Same with diabetes.
There's no there's no measurement.
There's no way to measure blood glucose.
It's done by an analog that shows how
much hydrogen peroxide is revealed in the test.
There's no direct way.
So no one has these diseases that people
are succumbing to.
The treatment is the disease.
As they go with these false diagnoses and
get these treatments, it's the treatment that kills
them at a rate at a rate of
three million per year, even though the statistical
number is a million per year.
And I think that's a little bit more
of a concern, because what's going on with
the medical industry is is several fold more
severe than what was going on in National
Socialist Germany or any other, you know, bowl
pot in Cambodia or Stalin.
What they were doing is going on right
here, right now in the West, not just
the U.S., Canada as well.
And people are being unnecessarily right.
Destroyed literally.
I mean, I don't really care to some
example, because it's no one that I know.
But when I hear it's like, you know,
my dad died of diabetes or whatever, whatever
at 57.
And my mom is having a hard time
and I have three brothers and sisters.
I mean, you know, that's kind of shitty,
isn't it?
Right.
And he didn't ever had that in the
first place.
And I can mention like 90 percent of
the stuff they put out is fiction and
they're just killing people with the treatment.
To me, that's a little more on a
social level.
Right.
So but like I said, you know, I
have yeah, I don't have the only input
I have on you on this is start
looking at from a public versus private perspective.
You know, let me just interject this.
You're considered a minor.
I've been doing a lot of research in
this lately and come up with my, you
know, a minor someone less than 18, you
know, incompetent.
You need a custodian or someone over you.
All of the institutions you deal with, all
of the authorities, small or large, administrative, public,
private or whatever, you as a minor.
And what do you tell?
So let's say, you know, you have a
minor, a child, and he says, hey, man,
give me ten thousand bucks, your pickup truck
in your house for a week.
You're going to laugh at them, right, because
they can't, you know, handle it right or
anything like that.
So this is what's going on with information.
They're putting out information that's for a minor
and incompetent.
So you know, so on and so forth
in that vein, not people that are competent.
This is the public.
The public has always been this way.
Very well said.
I agree.
I'm going to ask, move back to something
you said earlier before I kick it to
Daniel, let him ask you some stuff.
But you said that I'm not in search
of anything, and so many words from what
I remember, that matters to, I guess, the
powers that be.
But OK, look, let's touch on, I don't
know if I was trying to design something
that's anti-gravitic or something to master my
environment more, that would be, I'm assuming, a
threat to the environment.
Yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
We live in a very toxic environment, not
chemically toxic, but mentally, socially, spiritually toxic.
And there are powers that be, but they're
not physical as much as we would like
them to be.
And they block us from mastering the physical
world every so often.
And very few are given that power.
And also, let me just put it this
way.
Surface dwelling Earth inhabitants are the lowest form
of human existence on the planet.
In other words, we can get into it
more.
Living on the surface shows that you're very
primitive.
You don't know how to deal with your
environment.
All advanced societies do not live on the
surface.
They go underneath.
It's just like, okay, Daniel, I just built
a new house, and I feel like getting
new furniture for the new house.
Sound reasonable?
Sure.
So here comes the moving truck with all
the furniture, and I direct the people unloading
the truck to load my bedroom, living room,
dining room furniture, and put it on the
roof of my house because that's where I'm
going to be living.
What a kooky thing to do.
I'm going to be laughed at, right?
You put it inside the house.
So you do a flyby on the Earth,
and you see all this stuff built on
the surface.
You're like, leave those guys alone.
They're really dumb.
You live in the Earth, not on the
Earth.
So just that premise alone.
Could you imagine someone in your neighborhood living
on the roof of their house?
Would you consider them sane?
No, sir.
Yeah, exactly.
So let's use that premise to anchor your
other questions as well.
You're not dealing with anyone, right?
Let's talk about the guy who lives on
his roof 24-7.
How to transcend all that.
I'm trying to think of a way to
ease into, without jumping too far.
I don't want you to slap me down,
but it's part of the learning process, and
we came to you with answers.
You're doing us the favor.
Enough kissing your ass and stuff.
I'm just saying, I don't ever want to
be a host that takes you for granted,
but I'm trying to think, how do I,
with this short amount of time on this
Earth, if you will, positively affect and or
elevate humanity?
Got it.
Other subjects.
Yeah, it's just, I don't want to be
- Well, here, this is fine.
On the sonic that I do, Rated Y
with Ocelli, I keep laughing and say, hey,
I know the meaning of life and you
don't, ha ha.
Meaning of life here, this is not open
for debate, is to have your time wasted.
Everyone wastes each other's time, whether you know
it or not.
It's so hard to get things done, and
there's so many ways it's done.
First way we waste our time is there's
no communication.
Again, advanced, if we were advanced or we're
not here to waste our time, we wouldn't
use speech for communication.
Because we use speech, there's lying, there's deception,
there's all this stuff.
We are here, we are designed, we're actually
made or allowed to be bred into a
situation and developed in a situation where everyone
is wasting everyone's time.
It doesn't matter if it's your parents, your
loved ones, your friends, your work.
Is it all in vain, Greek, analyzing-
It's all in vain, exactly.
No, no.
I was asking you.
It's all in vain, so it is all
in vain.
Okay, so there's no- It's all in
vain.
Lessons can be learned that accumulate later in
some, I don't know, life that we get
to spawn into.
There's no ascendance.
People like Daniel Lyle would just say, human
forever, the soul, if you will, and there's
no elevation.
There's no- No, not with all the
...
If you make a rundown of a list
of let's say an automobile, it stalls at
a red light, it's dripping gasoline, it's dripping
oil, hard to start when it stalls.
You're like, this thing, we're going to leave
it alone and use it like that, right?
Well, you could, right?
You know, a broken down car that just
barely works, or you fix it or get
another one.
There's no ...
The decision has been made to leave everything
as it is alone.
I'm talking about in the grand scheme, right?
We're just going to truck along this way
and whatever.
That's the main decision.
Like you've heard, don't make waves, right?
Or hey, if you put that in public,
they'll kill you, right?
Or whatever, blah, blah, blah.
Hey, but what if the breakaway civilizations that
have successfully broken away adapted that attitude?
That's why I feel that there's hope.
Yeah, well, that's what they do.
They break away, and I agree.
I would come back with the mothership and
vaporize the surface if it were me.
That's not enforce everyone where they should be
underground.
I hate to say it that way, but
there's no alternative.
Here's the thing.
Our bodies biologically can continue.
You know how your body breaks down and
rebuilds itself, apoptosis, all the biological functions, right?
When you sleep, you recover and all that.
The way that works in our body, we
can live for 1,000 years, easy, right?
But we're designed and made.
There's a throttle a governor put on us
that we die out 70, 80, 90, 120,
whatever, right?
That is actually there to help us, the
short life.
I can't tell you for sure all these
other things that people talk about.
What happens after this?
I would say that our mentality here is
not clear enough to understand what happens after
being here, but I would take everything that
we hear as a hint, right?
For example, not to bounce around, but this
stuff about reincarnation, that's not discussed properly because
if we are here for the third, fourth,
fifth, or tenth time, aren't we technically in
the afterlife right now, right?
These things need to be put together a
little better.
I have no desire for anything here.
It's kind of like years ago on Sonics,
I spoke, we're in the waiting room.
You have a dentist appointment, right, Zen?
You go to the waiting room, how much
are you going to complain about being in
the waiting room?
Yeah, if they should take you at 11,
it's two o'clock and they haven't taken
you yet, you might reschedule, right?
But you're in the waiting room, so what
are they, they got crappy magazines laying around,
you might have a conversation, play with the
stupid rectangle, whatever, whatever.
That's what we're in.
We're in a waiting, we're in a holding
pattern.
Look, if the powers that be of the
grand scheme, I'm going to use your terms,
the King's language, you know, if they're prerogative
or if just by happenstance, whatever it may
be, is for our time to be wasted,
why can't I make the best, I mean,
why can't I subsequently in vain try and
make the best of my surroundings, you know,
just for shits and try and, my big
thing, my blanket statement is just elevate humanity.
I really want to do everything I can
to- You might have to rebuild, okay,
here, let me just say it this way.
Okay, in civil engineering, when you design a
highway, like an off ramp or an on
ramp, you have to design it for typically,
statistically, what would be known as the worst
driver and the worst car taking that off
ramp, right?
So everything around us is designed that way.
It's for the least educated, the least aware
people and the least physical fitness to function
in this society.
You know about that, you know?
So basically, you're in a low functioning society.
Everything is made, in general, to accommodate those
that are operating on an absolute minimal functioning
level, mentally, physically, et cetera, et cetera.
So how do you make it better?
There's several ways, several approaches, and I'm speaking
strictly, everything you're asking can be fixed from
a strictly nuts and bolts engineering perspective.
You don't even need to ask big spiritual
questions or big social questions.
Okay.
Break away, go underground.
I guess I can come back and visit
that later, but, and can you tell me
about this, okay, this governor on our lifespan,
I'm assuming you're referring to a genetic, something
that- Oh yeah.
...
telomeres after a while?
Yeah.
It's more than telomeres.
The physical is secondary.
It's kind of like, you know, when you,
let's say, do a wifi signal to your
laptop or your television in the living room,
you can discuss the pixels as much as
you want, but I'm telling you there is
a signal that's being piped over, that's being
picked up, that's manifesting.
Those pixels is a little more critical, right,
than the pixels, because what I mean is
you have a high resolution or low resolution
TV, you're still going to see what's being
broadcast.
Can you touch on how we rebut that
governor or what we can do to, you
know- Not here.
Not here.
Not now.
In other words, you have a dentist appointment
at 11 o'clock, it's 12.30, they
haven't seen you yet, you can kick and
scream all you want, that's not going to
make the dentist come out and take you
in his chair.
I'm just wondering if there's any, you know,
right question I can manufacture to relate that
to the dentist to do something in my
best, but I don't know, at least she
has to- Well, use the dentist, because
I have an acquaintance who's a dentist, and
when I want to see him, I call
him on his cell phone, and he's like,
yeah, yeah, we can do that, and you
know, let's meet at eight o'clock at
the office after I play basketball.
I mean, that's the relationship I have with
him, right.
And the thing about it, I said, hey,
Mitch, when you get your, do you ever
need any dental work?
The dentist, he says, yeah, I do.
I said, do you do it on yourself?
Or he says, no, it's very difficult to
do it on yourself, right.
You see, so you do require a tribe,
so your questions are requiring that, you keep
saying, what can I do?
And I'm telling you, what you want to
do requires a tribe, a village, a nation,
right?
You're right.
I just, thank you for helping me with
that, understand, yeah, and better.
Anyway, Daniel, please, go ahead, I've eaten up
a lot of time.
Well, I think there's a distinction between wasting
your time, which I agree is the highest,
you know, goal that we can aspire to
in this realm, and between losing your time,
because if you just go by the schedule
and the impositions and the things that are
governed by time, like let's say, watching a
movie or going to a sports game, then
you will be losing your time.
But if you're wasting your time, that implies
a certain openness to something that is mysterious.
It could be redirected so the same time
is not being wasted.
Yeah.
As for us living on the surface, on
the roof, still, I think there's something to
be said about Goldilocks planets being inhabitable and
having the ability to be thriving on the
surface, except that we are in the most
precarious position of having all these grids and
all these prison systems governing us.
That's what makes us especially repressed and inside
more of a prison than a university, as
we were supposed to.
Sure.
Or I would say how closely related is
a prison to a farm?
How close are they related?
The creatures that live in a prison and
the creatures that live in a farm are
both fed and taken care of to a
certain degree, right?
And they're both monetized.
Yeah.
I don't think it's a prison as much
as it's an unfortunate situation.
And by the way, some people listening to
this are, oh, this Greek guy is very
negative.
I'm not into it because I like the
airy fairy woo woo stuff that your intention,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
That's fine.
But what I'm saying, you'll find in every
ancient text, every single text that's been written
by, you know, those dummies that came before
us, right?
That's what everyone, we're taught to think that
the ancients were dumb, right?
Every ancient text that you'll find, you know,
the holy writs of the world are pretty
much I'm paraphrasing.
And you mentioned the us having the potential
to live a thousand years.
Would you be able to isolate maybe the
biggest poison or the top three or something?
Yeah.
Your skin.
Let's just keep it simple.
Remember that everything is based and we're speaking
publicly, so we're addressing minors, people with a,
you know, under 18 mentality typically.
It doesn't matter if they're 70, right?
This is the way the public is groomed
and they go to their grave as basically
children, a children mentality.
How do you know an old man just
walked into a room or an old lady
walked into the room?
By looking at them, right?
If you put an old man versus young
man, old lady versus young lady on the
internet right now in images, what's the first
thing you're going to notice?
Old people have baggy, wrinkly skin.
That's the first thing that you notice, right?
Typically more than the facial features drooping or
being in large brow bone or large ears,
right?
Well, the reason that happens that, you know,
is your skin as you grow older, parts
of your body keep growing.
I'm not going to get lascivious, but they,
that does too.
I noticed after 50 anyway, so like for
example, the femur, the brow bone, the ears
keep growing as you get older.
A good example of that is if you
know anyone that's in their forties, fifties or
sixties and was in the military, say, Hey,
go pull out.
Do you still have your military uniform and
your hat?
Yeah.
Pull it out.
And they're in their twenties.
You know, they have their military hat, you
know, what for parade and whatever, right?
Formal hat, dress hat, it's called, Hey, put
your hat on.
And when they put their hat on, you
know, it sits on top of, of their
head, like a, like a toy hat, like
a child's hat doesn't even fit anymore because
that keeps growing top of the cranium and
all that, right?
So you keep growing.
Now the skin grows faster than the rest
of it.
And you know, when you're young, you're a
five pound pork chop in a five pound
bag.
When you're old, you're a five pound pork
chop in a 10 pound bag.
Why not just put it back in a,
right?
So I'm not saying go and get plastic
surgery, right?
You know how the, you know how that
looks, right?
But so why does the skin keep growing?
Are there chemical attachments, energetic, electrical attachments behind
that?
Yeah, of course.
And you can, can you prevent that from
growing?
And because the skin is an organ in
its own right, you have to take certain
considerations.
But that would be the first thing that
I would do.
But wouldn't it have to be related to
our main fuel, which is a gas of
some type?
Well, yes, I'm glad you mentioned that.
We all have an atmosphere.
You know how you study, let's say, geography
or wherever the earth has an atmosphere, it's
so thick or whatever.
And everything has an atmosphere.
Even if you study Galvani, the early natural
philosopher, you know, scientist, he said that what
conducted electricity across metals was that metal has
an atmosphere, it's not the metal itself.
But anyway, and we have an atmosphere around
us and it's material.
And actually, you can smell that atmosphere on
some people, if you know what I mean.
And we affect that atmosphere by putting on
perfumes and colognes, if that makes any sense.
But also, we have an energetic field, just
like the earth has a magnetic sphere and
that we call the aura, for example.
And just like that aura is very, how
would you say, inconspicuous, like the aurora borealis,
for example.
You know, you only see it in certain
places.
So, we have many conditions that affect us,
right?
And like, for example, I'll give you a
short, you know acupuncture, right?
Where they put pins and needles into people.
Okay, ask anyone who practices that in the
West, how does it really work and why
do we use pins and needles and all
that?
They don't know.
They're just doing their job.
Well, you know what a lightning rod is,
right?
You direct the electricity from the atmosphere to
the ground.
When the idea of acupuncture is that you
apply a conductive piece of material into the
body and based on the diagnosis on the
practitioner, what he wants to do is draw
energy from the aura surrounding the human body
and put it back into the body.
Or if there's too much energy in the
body, to send it out to the outer
field, the magnetosphere of the body, that's what
acupuncture is, right?
So, it's like a lightning rod would be
used on the earth.
But isn't it barbaric a little bit because
it's disturbing the vacuum, first of all, and
second of all, because it's tough to map
out what's the good parts of us.
I'm not condoning it.
I wouldn't do it.
Like, for example, if I had a condition
and someone suggested I go try an acupuncturist,
I'd just laugh it off.
I wouldn't do that.
But I'm just giving that as an example
to help illustrate the condition.
But since our bodies are electric, there is
a beneficial type of electricity, right, as opposed
to the one we use?
Yeah.
What I would suggest about electricity is their
end result product.
Like, for example, baked goods is an end
result product of using grains, ground-up grains,
right?
So, the electricity that we...
When we say electricity, people think, oh, I
plug something in a wall or a battery.
That is a very highly pressurized, magnetically or
chemically pressurized ethereal flow.
It's a secondary thing.
When you're dealing with biological, it would be
more the biological vacuum and what we call
the ethereal reaction, which has very different potential.
In other words, the ether goes from low
to high potential, where when we say electricity,
it always goes from high to low potential,
right?
So, we have to understand that there's a
reverse of potential.
In other words, I just did a weather
seminar.
It was three three-hour sections on how
to manipulate the weather around you, you know,
locally and not so locally.
And I broke it down in practical terms.
And basically, every time we discussed something in
the physical reality, when you're working with weather
or ether, it's the opposite.
And the main opposite would be the energy
potentials go from low to high, not high
to low.
Where can we find that?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Is that recorded at all?
I can learn from it?
It is.
It's a private group.
I did several seminars on several different subjects,
and they were just open.
I had about 50 people.
But now, I'm going to be doing new
seminars on several subjects, and it'll be fee
-based.
But this one is not fee-based.
If you send me an email at uncommonsenseradio1
at Gmail, that's the number one, uncommonsenseradio1 at
Gmail, I'll send you a link.
And we just reposted everything again, because Skype
takes it down every 30 days.
Thank you.
Sorry, Daniel.
I didn't mean to.
No, it's fine.
It's nine hours.
It's three three-hour segments.
I do, let's say, every Saturday, we do
three hours for three weeks.
And that's just barely covering the surface.
But we already have several people making rain
and doing what they want.
Especially where you are, Zan.
My gosh, hurricane's coming.
What do we do?
Run, right?
I'm like, no.
Yeah, not at all.
We have total control over that.
Yes, it's upsetting to know that they just,
I don't know, these lesser men build over
us.
And as you can tell, I'm so buttered,
and I just, I'm relentless in my pursuit
of trying to figure out how to get
ahead of all this.
But anyway, Daniel, I want you to wrap
up your first point.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't want to take a thunder.
I don't want to take a thunder, Daniel.
I think the answer to what would you
do if you did find some, let's say,
free energy, which, like you said, all energy
is free, so you shouldn't name it that,
but a free energy device, you should just
keep it for yourself, because what you do
when you're alone will be rewarded by the
world around you.
Right, well, here's the thing.
The operative point here, what you just mentioned,
let's say you just get a free energy
device.
You're pretty new at this, because you just
got it, right?
So it's like when you get, you're five
years old, you get a brand new bicycle,
you say, I'm going to ride to California.
Or do you ride in your neighborhood first,
try it out, make sure, right?
Don't get your, don't get anything caught in
the chain, right?
Get wrapped around the axle kind of thing,
right, until you get used to it.
Yeah, so it would be very difficult.
I mean, we already have devices that it's
just a pipe.
You're aware of it, and you run dirty
water through one side, and the water comes
out clean on the other, and it's like,
what?
That doesn't make any sense.
No filters, no chemicals, right?
Well, that already exists.
We already have that, and they're not for
sale.
I do a 90-year lease.
So if anyone says, how many of these
have you sold?
I can honestly say none, right, because I
lease them out for 90 years.
So anyway, that's the operative thing.
By the way, if you have a free
energy device, don't put it up for sale.
Just do a 90-year lease.
But to tie it together with the drones,
I believe you did foresee this type of
phenomenon back in like 2016 or 15, that
we would see all sorts of lights in
the sky that were supposed to represent a
distraction, a false disclosure, and that if you
want to make, let's say, a baby step
towards understanding that phenomenon, you're supposed to get
behind the actual, the way in which you
cancel mass and weight, which is not inside
the atoms of physical objects, but in the
ether.
Right, it's all, if you're familiar with the
work of Ken Wheeler, I don't endorse him.
It seems like every time he does a
video, he's just rewording everything from his first
video five, 10 years ago.
But his perspective in nature, and I agree,
there's a book by Gustav Le Bon written
on transformation of elements and materials.
And all the early, quote unquote, physicists, which
were natural philosophers really before the term came
about, it's all about pressure mediation.
Everything in nature is trying to equalize.
So if you create a low pressure here,
out there, that's higher pressure wants to rush
in to the low pressure, right?
And if you create a high pressure here,
it's going to want to rush towards the
low pressure around it.
And that's the basis for everything that works
in the perceivable universe.
And if you're stuck on the atomic side,
meaning everything is material, most ridiculous thing is
a photon, you know.
How does the photon go through glass, right,
slow down and then speed up again after
it leaves the light bulb, right?
Ridiculous.
If you're stuck on atomic, let's say, model
of the universe, that everything's atoms including light
as photons, you will never, I assure you,
you will never, ever, ever, ever, ever have
anti-gravity or anything that we discuss or
aspire to.
Ever.
You'll never have it.
But once you understand there is an immaterial
substrate, it's completely immaterial that once it's handled
a certain way or manifests into material and
light, and you understand pressure mediation, right?
So, for example, the way, if you understand
what an airfoil is on a wing, on
an airplane, the Bernoulli effect, you have something
that looks like a flat plane of material
like a wing or just a board of
wood.
And if you run it through the air,
it doesn't, you know, it just cuts through
the air, it doesn't lift.
But if you increase the surface area on
the top of the board and keep the
bottom flat, as you run that board horizontally
through the air, the top of the board,
which is like an airfoil now, that's a
longer surface, the air takes a little longer
to rush off and it creates a low
pressure because of the time variance.
And but the air on the bottom of
the board, because it's flat and parallel to
the air movement, the air moves a little
faster and you have a high pressure and
that creates lift, right?
If you look at every cross-section of
any airplane or helicopter or propeller, it has
that feature.
How simple is that?
So, what the simplest airfoil will do is
create a low pressure above, high pressure below,
the end result is lift.
Exactly the same with the ether, you know.
I think there actually were stuff written about
ether lift and lift, you know, simple lifting
devices.
Now, if you're going to go after it
by strictly using electrical fields and all that,
that's not going to work either because electricity
is a byproduct.
It's kind of like if grandma baked a
batch of chocolate chip cookies that were made
of wheat, can you take that chocolate chip
cookie, plant it in the ground and expect
a wheat field to grow out of that?
Never, right?
So, it won't because it's too processed.
It's too processed.
Yeah, so you have to handle the unprocessed
ether.
Now, here's the thing, what is the ether?
Before we get into that because that's been
dabbled with and I believe we know it
can be explained but it's not really shown,
discussed publicly.
Let's just ask the same question, what is
a bear?
You know, the animal B-E-A-R
that lives in the woods, black bears, grizzly
bears, whatever.
If you ask anyone, even a child, what
is a bear?
Do you know what that is?
Yes, everyone pretty much will say yes.
Polar bear, doesn't matter.
Now, I'm telling you, we really don't know
what a bear is but we know enough
about bears that we say that we do
know what bears are.
And the reason why we say we don't
really know what bears are or is, is
because I've never run into anyone or heard
of anyone who sat down and had an
eight hour conversation with a bear.
Have you?
No, but we know enough about bears and
their behavior that we can work with them
and identify them and actually say that we
know what bears are.
Can we do that with the ether?
Absolutely, yes, we can.
And that's how I operate.
Do we know enough about it to work?
Just like, for example, if you speak to
a physicist, what is electricity?
You know, really, if you get down to
it, there's no physicist that knows what electricity
is but we still, does it mean we
shouldn't use it?
Do we know enough about it to make
it useful?
Does that make sense, Zion, to you?
I'm picking up what you're laying down as
far as I think I know, my subjective
understanding, yes.
But as far as ether, okay, what about
like in relation to Mel's Hole or something
like that?
If that exists, if you can confirm or
deny it, whatever.
I don't know what Mel's Hole is.
Oh, okay, there was a similar place, I
think on an Indian reservation.
Basically, it's, I don't know if you heard,
it could be urban legend, but I'm assuming
it's true.
Oh, a weird place with weird anomalies?
Well, it's a place that according to this
urban legend, which I'm assuming is true, there's
a naturally occurring hole in the ground where
a dark light would beam out one time
a day.
And if you drop things into the hole,
you never ever hear some sort of noise
or anything.
And if you drop something live down and
pull it back up, it's warped.
And that coins from with different times and
different presidents, same countries or stuff like that
would be found around it.
And if you park your car close enough
to these places on earth that there would
be, I don't know, stuff from, I guess,
different timelines playing on the radio or alternative
timelines.
Maybe this is just a red herring.
We should forget about it.
I was just thinking.
No, no, that's fine.
I was, I had a, well, somewhat mild
relation with someone who had gone through New
Mexico and swore that he went through a
town that he knew before.
And when he went through the town, this
is about five years ago, it looked like
very 1940s.
And he sent himself a postcard.
And when he got home, he got the
postcard and it was postmarked 1947, even though
it was five years ago.
So maybe they really do have aliens in
the post office, but yeah, weird stuff like
that.
We're the aliens, right?
I mean, how the hell do we just
pop onto this planet?
We are the aliens to some degree.
I mean, you know, to some, yeah, we're
the only, you know, we can go into
so many reasons why we're alien here based
on, you know, how different we are from
all the creatures, right?
Yeah, even on the biblical texts, we're a
genetic project and all that.
But, oh, about the dark matter, dark light,
it must be some residue of the, you
know, phantom matrices because we're in a side
of simulation, nested inside of simulation and so
on.
So that's probably why he was led to
an artificial timeline in that one.
And then, I don't know.
Events, yeah, yeah, synthetic events or different events.
There's a very thin transition or veil, I
should say.
For example, when some people, very rare, you
know, the NDE reports, near-death experiences, but
if some of the more, let's say, if
you listen to NDE experiences, they all sound
pretty much the same with some variance.
But there's a few out there that are
interesting that before you transition to the other
side, you actually go through different realities that
are like this one, that seem very similar.
You might look at yourself in the mirror
and you look very different.
Or, you know, you might have a green
car here and when you pass, you go
out, you walk outside of your house and
the car is now red.
And then you go to another reality, which
is very, very different, and so on and
so forth.
Several of them that are all coexisting.
Yeah, but the fact that each denomination sees
their own pantheon in their NDEs suggests that
it's, you know, artificial in that.
Yeah, they never, yeah, because they never really
died, because if they did, they wouldn't.
Look, Woody Allen, I think, or someone said,
if dying was so bad, how come no
one has come back to complain?
Yeah.
But about the ether and the drones, I
think in one of your oldest sonics, you
explained how come they take those 90 degree
turns.
They can go through the veil to an
extent.
Like when, again, with the NDE, is there
anything really supernatural happening?
I mean, death is such a common thing,
right?
Where you basically unresolve in this world and
you resolve into another reality, right?
So they're able to resolve another reality that
appears to be a 90 degree turn at
Mach 10 in this reality.
Very simple.
I'm suggesting that you're gonna be breaking, it's
not just anti-gravity and those super, let's
say phenomenal motions that you see in UFOs.
I believe that they're operating in a slightly
variance, another reality that you can see in
this one, like a shimmer on water, right?
And yeah, they rely on the reorganization of
energies, which all the energies come from the
ether, right?
Pre-energies, yeah.
Once we identify it as energy, it's finished.
Just like you can't plant a chocolate cookie
in the field and expect wheat to grow.
Yeah, you have to function with the original
whole materials that come out, quote unquote, naturally,
because nothing is natural anyway.
It's everything that's constructed.
You know how they say, well, without being
religious, God created everything, right?
Well, someone who creates things is an artist.
And that's where you get the word artificial.
It's an artificer.
So everything is artificial.
If you go that route, you know, that
someone created all of this, right?
So an artificer makes things that are what?
Artificial.
Yeah, not in the sense, like, for example,
years ago, I was peddling water.
I was trafficking high-end water in Los
Angeles in most elite shops there.
And I was able to clean and make
wonderful spring water, like the, even goes against
the best spring waters in the world from
LA tap water via implosion.
And it was called Spring 2.0. And
the label said, synthesize spring water.
And we were giving out samples.
And one lady approached me and she says,
why does it say synthesized water?
It sounds artificial, right?
I'm like, you know, that's a good point.
That's a good point because it is, but
not in the sense, when we say it's
artificial, it's usually a downplay, right?
A downgrade, right?
So by saying we live in an artificial
environment is not downgraded at all.
It's just being more objective.
That makes sense.
And as a result, you could say that
the generators are not so much generators as
pumps.
That's right.
No one has ever generated electricity just like
a water pump has never created water.
You know, like I say, let's go out
and buy a water pump.
Usually has a power cord attached to it.
Leave it still in the box, plug it
in to your power.
Do you expect water to start shooting out
of the water pump?
No, because the water pump is designed to
take a certain static body of water and
to based on its design to create a
certain volume or pressure, right?
So let's go back to the generator.
It's a group of windings that creates static,
takes static, right?
Static electricity and winds it up and pressurizes
it and reflects it down a conductor known
as metal.
Notice I didn't say really conduct.
It sends it across the wire, just like
a magnet works, for example, when you put
a magnet on your, actually magnetizes the ether,
polarizes it.
When you put a magnet on your refrigerator
door, is it, what is it?
It's just running along the refrigerator door, right?
That's how electricity works over metals and other
things and some minerals.
And once you understand that principle, you might
want to abandon the whole thing, right?
Of, you know, having a field coil, you
know how basic generators work.
There's various types of ways of doing it
with magnets or without magnets and where you
have an exciting current, you know, several, there's
many ways to do it.
But I would suggest that if someone wants
to start getting into this, let's just say,
I'll say this because I'm in the process
of working on this right now, is using
an exciter type generator.
Instead of winding, spinning a coil around a
magnet, energize a smaller coil that becomes magnetic
and then rotate the other coil around that
primary energized coil and keep seeing what you
get.
And if you start playing with this, you'll
notice that your local transformer, your local power
supply in your neighborhood, everyone, all the power
goes out for a few blocks.
And the electrical companies right now have enough
sensors that they can almost find the source
of what caused the capacitor or transformer to
go out.
And you get a, first time, they stop
in front of your house.
Second time, they knock on your door and
they said, you know, the power went out
again.
Do you know anything about it?
And what I suggest you say is, I
really don't know.
I was watching TV and the lights went
out, man.
Don't say, hey, come out here.
I want to show you what, anyway, you
get the point, right?
I shouldn't have shared that, but yeah.
But there are also examples of the technology
that is electricity that is longitudinal, that is
instantaneous, that we're not supposed to have, that
is out in the open.
Yeah, but how are you going to control
that?
Because it's instant, well, you can, Eric Dollard,
again, I don't endorse him, but he has
some good stuff.
You can build a very simple circuit.
There's a video that's about 15 years old
on YouTube or maybe 10 years old.
It was an eighth grader that built basically
Tesla coil setup, like a tank circuit.
And he basically showed that it, that little
circuit that he built was 1.5 times
the speed of light transmission.
Very simple to do.
And the way you do that is a
tank circuit, which is capacitors in series shunted
with a coil.
If you want to do the opposite, slow
it down, is coils in series shunted with
capacitors.
So it's very easy to do faster than
light.
And that's a longitudinal.
When you say longitudinal, that's faster than light
propagation, right?
So you have to start thinking in those
realms where things are instant.
And that's, again, it goes into the, how
much of, okay, let's just make an open
question that maybe we can't answer.
How much of messing around with that stuff
can you do without the other realities coming
and saying, hey, what are you doing?
Yeah.
Right, how much of that can you do?
Or they'll say, hey, I see you're doing
it.
Let's invite this guy, right?
Let's invite him, right?
And then once you're invited, you walk through
a door that you may not come back
in, right, does that make sense?
There's also a gray area such as that
person who died 10 years ago who did
invent and tried to patent a so-called
free energy device, but was unsuccessful.
And of course, Bismarck and Kalamnit, I forget
the name.
Well, you know, you can't just say one
because there's many, I believe, and they've done
many, many different ways.
And I think they're all very different from
each other, but using a similar principle that
they may or may not be able to
communicate, which is what we're trying to do
now, perhaps.
And you can recreate many elements out of
others that have nothing to do with them
using the latent free energies of the ether.
What do you mean by elements?
Like, I don't know, lithium or water, catalysis.
I mean, bronze gas, that's supposed to be
like a different phase of water that we
didn't even know about.
I get it.
There's something, the field is, you know, yin
and yang, right?
I don't like discussing it that way because
it sounds like I'm trying to get into
a modified Asian philosophy.
So I've come up with a new way
to describe it.
I call it universal principle.
You know, yin being soft and expansive and
yang is sharp and hard, right, and focused,
right?
Yin is unfocused, yang is focused.
Again, it's like pressure mediation.
When I get into, let's just call it
transmutation.
You okay with that term?
Yep.
Okay, I've done many, many times, I'd like
to say hundreds of times in my life,
but dozens of times, public demonstrations where I
take pure carbon and transmute it into iron
at a rate of 70% by volume.
And what's interesting about the iron, once you
transmute that, the iron does not rust, even
though it measures as pure iron.
And what's interesting is in India, there's some
iron pillars and they're measured to be 99
.999% pure iron and they don't rust.
And the reason why it doesn't rust is
if even you look at the bullshit periodic
table that we have, when you follow Fe
iron all the way, I mean, carbon all
the way to iron, you notice it passes
through nickel.
And one of the characteristics or qualities of
adding nickel to iron is that it won't
rust, right?
Stainless steel, for example, just one of the
metals.
So once you start transmuting elements, you can
actually control their properties, which are very different
from the way elements.
So the iron that, so for example, the
iron that we get that rusts is not
made this way.
Why?
Because it oxidizes very readily.
It goes through various stages, right?
So now we understand that when you transmute
elements, you can control based on the way
things are ordered, let's say on the periodic
table loosely.
You know, like for example, you brought up
lithium.
Helium can be turned into lithium, right?
And, you know, I'm sure Zanziers are perking
up because, you know, you've heard about so
many geopolitical moves being made because there's a
potential for a lithium mine, right?
So what do you think would happen?
Let's say we're on the silver or the
gold standard and you're able to make gold.
How would you be viewed?
As a threat, if you weren't- Yeah,
exactly.
In the Yalta conference, you'll find that, this
is back in the 40s, that the Russians
were given the go to control the world's
platinum.
And if you don't believe that, even platinum
mines in the U.S. are owned by
Russian, by Russian concerns, right?
And through isotopic measurements, about 60 or 70
% of the world's platinum is synthesized.
In other words, made in the lab, but
they can get away with it.
For example, I've dabbled with this.
Well, let's just say I'll share it.
When you turn copper into gold and you
have a Dory bar, which is about 20
% gold still and some silver and copper,
and you send it to a place to
be tested, they run an isotope on the
gold and they have a chart.
And based on the isotope of gold, they
know from what part of the world it
came from, right?
Because they've already mapped out all the gold
mines and the regions.
But if you make a certain percentage of
gold and send it to a lab to
be tested, and it doesn't show up on
one of these isotopes, they tell you there's
no gold in it.
It's just iron and copper.
And then you'll say, oh, really?
Okay, well, why don't you send the sample
back?
And they'll say, oh, we lost the sample,
right?
And what's interesting, there's a place called Swastika,
Canada.
And that was one of the few.
By the way, when you do this, these
are labs that are registered that give you
a certified, right?
So all the computers are networked.
Once you go into a system like that,
now you're blacklisted.
And all the labs that share that same
network basically give you the same answer.
So we sent it to a lab that
we thought was out of this loop.
And it was a week, we didn't get
any answer.
So I called and did you get my
sample?
And he says, yeah, we have your sample
here.
We haven't opened it yet.
Is there anything you wanna tell us?
I said, yeah, do you have it in
your system?
He says, let me look in my system.
He says, oh yeah, I see you here.
It sees that you were sending us a
sample.
It says that it's iron and copper and
we lost the sample.
But they haven't opened it yet, right?
So anyway, I'm gonna stop right there.
Let your mind, you know, see us.
So there are things like that going on
constantly.
I recently spoke to someone who was kind
of like, not a bad person, but he
got in trouble with the judicial system.
And he found a way to get make
the case go away, but they didn't like
that.
So they said, well, the case can't go
away because you have a grand jury indictment.
Now, when we look at the dates, the
grand jury indictment was three months before he
was initially arrested.
How could that be possible?
Right?
This is the kind of stuff that's so,
sometimes when you see like the fix, the
fakery, the suppression, it's so obvious.
It's not subtle, right?
And where's the outrage?
For example, just to bounce around socially, how
many times have you heard people like Tracy
Twyman or certain people that made controversial, put
out controversial material on the internet, or books
or whatever.
And they said, you know, I'm not suicidal
And yeah, you're not suicidal.
You're very stable, you're sound body and mind.
And then like a year later, you find
out they were found hanging in their garage.
Where's the outrage?
It's obvious they were offed, right?
But where's the outrage?
Why aren't there like millions of people gathering
around demanding?
No one cares.
So no one cares here.
And you know what?
They shouldn't care because deep down inside, they
know they're here to waste their time.
So why bother?
And the way they get people to kill
themselves can even be indirectly through psychotronic attacks.
Yeah, depends on the character.
I mean, like for me, no matter how
many voices they beam in my head, I've
taught myself to ignore them, right?
Because I know all the voices are external
anyway, right?
Could you go over that?
Because you're the first person that I resonated
with describing that you shouldn't have the inner
monologue and that it's actually something much darker.
Yeah, I'll give you an example.
We're taking up space.
You ever see someone park their car in
the middle of the road and they leave
and it's like, wait a second, why couldn't
you pull over to the side?
So everybody else can pass.
Well, that's what the earth is.
We have parked ourselves in another reality and
these other beings view us as something to
be messed with.
And they have a society just like we
do.
They have bars and movies and families, right?
But they're not in our material realm.
And they mess with us by giving us
a voice.
That's why when you try to remember back
as far as you were an infant, you
didn't have that inner voice.
Sort of developed around five, six, seven that
you can remember.
And I'm pouring some coffee here.
So what's interesting is they have beings that
go through school.
Like for example, in the West here in
the US, we have a lot of Chinese
restaurants with Chinese immigrants and people think, oh,
they just came over from China to work
in a restaurant.
No, there are actual schools in China that
train people to emigrate to the US and
work in the restaurant business, right?
So they have some little schools where when
you deal with humans to give them their
inner voice.
And these are the different classifications of humans.
And this is what they typically think of
and say.
And that gets locked into your voice.
And the voice in your head sounds like
the way you sound to yourself and you
think it's you.
Now, what's interesting is when you have, let's
say a very mainstream person and they listen
to their inner voice, kind of like in
the cartoons, you got the good angel on
your right shoulder and the bad angel on
your left, right?
Yeah, they play that with you as well.
But I can give you a scenario.
Let's say you got a real mainstream person,
believes everything on the news and files taxes,
takes a pill when they're sick, all the
basic stuff that mainstream does, right?
Suddenly they go to like Zanz or your
website and they start listening to some of
your interviews and they're like, oh man, this
sounds so intuitive and right.
And I better read, it's not, you mean
the world is not like I was told?
And they start abandoning all those mainstream thoughts.
That voice can no longer serve them.
So he puts it on an alert.
Hey, this guy's learning new stuff.
I can't give him the voice anymore.
So then they have to assign a new
being to give you another voice.
That's why when you run into people that
kind of like just started learning this alternative
stuff, it is the happiest time in their
life, they're at the most peace in terms
of their, they wanna learn, they wanna tell
everyone and all this stuff.
But when they send the new being over
to them that's designed for those that go
into the alternative world or whatever, suddenly you
notice they start getting angry on why no
one wants to hear what they're saying, right?
Suddenly, they all have the same characteristics pretty
much, right?
And then when you find out by, for
example, let's just bypass the whole thing here,
that inner voice is artificial and they're actually
keep replacing beings as your level of consciousness
changes and you keep growing your consciousness and
rejecting that inner voice, what happens is they
send like the real big bad ones like
the Delta Force beings and those guys, what
they do is they start giving you a
little clairvoyance, like what's going to happen eight
minutes from now and you start feeling psychic
and then you forget that it's still not
you and now you start telling people that
you're psychic and you're really not, it's still
this other thing doing it.
So, yeah, and I just gave you an
overview and you've heard me discuss this more
in depth but that's the overview.
So, these people that say that they're psychic,
they are but they're being played.
They're being played also by a being that
like, it's like, hey, this person here, their
heart, the easiest way to control them is
let's let them believe with a voice that
they're psychic and then now we got them.
So, okay, now, what if you know that's
going on, now you go even beyond that,
being psychic, oh, Greek or anything, really being
beyond psychic, of course, and you just keep
operating and then you get to a point
like the Truman Show where he takes the
sailboat out and he finds that it's all
fake in the set, right?
So, once you get past that psychic point,
then you see, oh, it's nothing here is
worth it and I'm not saying this to
be whatever, a downer, but just enjoy yourself.
Hey, look, there's plenty of people that work
in Hollywood and show business with fakery around
them, even they're even, hey, I'll let you
in on something.
Do you know when you watch entertainment movies
or whatever, you know, they're actually told what
to say usually and it's reading a script,
you believe that, right?
And most of the stuff is props and
fake.
Hey, does that mean they're having a terrible
time?
No, you can still enjoy yourself in that
setting.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, so every word that you can make
out is, it betrays this possession, so to
speak, because you're supposed to think in clearer
ideas, nothing good.
Influence, I'm glad you mentioned that because first
you have influence with these beings and then
the people that have problems with their cognitive
ability, those are oppressed, like voices that, you
know, that's what they use, let's say, for
example, a beam of thoughts in your head
to make you kill yourself, right?
You have the oppression.
And the final state is possession where your
consciousness is completely taken over and becomes unconscious
and this other being now operates through you,
right?
And this is all non-material, not like
the real takeover, this is not being a
host.
You are a host though, but there's no
physical entity, it's all mental, so you have
to watch out for that too.
Yes, which is not really so much pranking,
which probably has a much deeper cause, which
has to do with loosing, I mean, living
and using our creative powers, which they lack.
Yeah, and they feed off of it.
There's a movie called Monsters, Inc.
where they scare the children and they, actually
their energy reloads their, right, it's their food
source?
Yeah.
That is absolutely, I would say, 99.99,
almost absolute, one of the situations that's going
on.
And if this astral world that people say
that they go into or these spiritual beings,
doesn't matter if they're biblical, whatever religion, new
age, I don't care, if they're so, oh,
I met a benefactor, a beneficial entity, really?
So how come he hasn't given you a
formula for like, you know, curing cancer or
free energy?
None of them are beneficial.
Even if you read the biblical text, whatever
God in there that you're talking about, show
me one that's beneficial or benefacted to us.
None of them are, none of them, not
a one, so.
So, yeah, that does away with any form
of channeling, but there is.
They're not here to help.
Mm-hmm, but there is one of these
communications that is like, let's say, genuine, which
maybe I shouldn't expose this, but you yourself
were subject to, which is the one that's
more cellular and the one that Ashayana describes
as kelontic.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, excuse me, I believe that they are
operating in a way that we are also,
in other words, but on a different level,
right?
So let's say, for example, you have someone
who's barely making, eking a living because they
have financial problems, right?
But then you have someone who's worth several
billion and they have financial problems that physically
and mentally have them in the same condition
that the person who could barely get enough
food to eat.
You know what I mean?
So a wealthy person that's miserable because of
finances or someone who has no money at
all that's miserable because of finances and they're
in the same condition, it doesn't matter what
level you're on.
Yeah, the guy who's the billionaire that's degrading
because of his financial, he's got a Rolls
Royce and a mansion, but mentally and physically,
he's in just as shitty as the guy
who can't get enough to eat, you see?
So these other beings are like we are,
but just on a different level.
You know, they're driving Ferraris instead of horse
and carriage.
They're just as screwed up as we are.
Because the sum average, there are people that
get, there's a little meme, a cartoon, where
there's some little greys in a flying saucer
and they look down on the earth in
the meme and you see smokestacks and pollution.
And the greys are speaking to each other.
They say, hey, didn't we send them Tesla
100 years ago?
Yeah, but they didn't listen to them and
they're all laughing, right?
Yeah, but probably they also don't just use
the imps and demons, I mean, but also
5G frequencies to instill the confusion and the
subliminal messages, plant ideas.
I think it's even before, 5G is basically
a transmission system to operate machines that are
loaded with a lot of circuitry.
And it has a very high dynamic range,
5G.
What I would suggest the technology to do
that was more around if you study the
work of Delgado in the 1960s, mind control,
where in the 1960s, he went out into
a bullfight arena and he had a little
wooden box in his hand and they let
the bull charge him, pushes a button and
the bull stops and kneels, pushes another button,
the bull gets up and charges, pushes that
other button again, the bull stops and kneels.
This was in the 60s.
This was publicly demonstrated.
Was it low frequency or ultrasound?
Yes, but it's never one frequency.
It's kind of like when you sit down
for dinner, you just don't eat one thing,
right?
You have a side with it and you
have some seasoning, right?
It's, I'm giving the food metaphor.
It's a recipe.
Right, but since we're on this topic, could
we maybe delineate between the people who are
body snatched literally, like by aliens or by
Brill, and the ones who are synthetic?
Oh, I can't really, I can't say I'm
expert on that.
But you were the only one who described
how the synthetics can be created, let's say.
Oh, you mean like a clone?
Well, yeah, let's say for simplicity of terms,
cloning.
Yeah, but I'm referring to the way that
you said that you can, through technology, obstruct
the light that goes from the sperm cell
to the egg.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, it's all light.
That's actually been substantiated clinically, that when the
sperm, let's say, fertilizes the egg, there's a
flash of light, right?
The same with blood cells.
Live blood testing, they'll see flashes of light
and then new types of cells appearing in
the blood sample.
Yeah, there's many ways to do it, but
essentially you're going to be, once you create
a being that you could walk into a
room and press the flesh, you're gonna go
into the cloning technology where they have to
be grown into a tank.
And I suggest that the tank isn't made
of any hard material, kind of like in
some of the newer sci-fi cloning, you
see it's a soft material, right?
Because you don't want to twitch and bump
and break a limb while you're being formed.
So I would suggest that eventually understanding the
cloning and growing human or whatever animal has
been going on for a very long time
as well, which we call a synthetic.
But okay, synthetic in terms of the impetus
when let's say a child is in the
womb being, yeah, when that light is affected,
you can change the trajectory and the development
of that being and what spirit will embody
it.
Yeah, absolutely.
And it takes a very short period of
time, right?
When you see a flash of light, how
long does that last, milliseconds?
So you have to be able to do
quite a bit of adjusting in that small
amount of time and to synthesize a type
of being.
So in other words, yeah, I would say
maybe, let's say as the breeders keep breeding,
there is technology that can actually control the
quality of the person that will be bred
at that moment.
Yeah.
Downgrading or upgrading.
I see no reason for, yeah, I see
no reason for upgrading anyone here at all
because there's just, putting a highly intelligent capable
individual in this world is living hell, right?
You want low functioning people here.
But in regards to light, that also has
to do with, that's behind some of the
psi abilities, like manifestation is just visualizing something
before it exists and then you bring it
about.
Well, psi abilities go, like I described earlier,
where they keep exchanging the being that gives
you your inner voice and they can't do
anymore.
They give you someone who makes you think
you're psychic and usually fall for it.
And when you're not on that level, when
you don't fall for it, you'll find that
the psi abilities are not a big deal
and that everyone has it and you're wondering
why they're not using it.
It's a different level.
You're not going to say, because I have
psi abilities, I'm better.
You're going to say, oh, how terrible this
is because look at everyone has it, but
yet they're not using it.
Another component that is overlooked in the psi
and other things is the emotional.
And no one has really been able to
describe their purpose or their meaning.
Yeah, I get into a lot of that.
I'm going to probably be doing a seminar
on that, a fee-based one.
I've been speaking on it now for quite
a few years.
I thought about it for quite a few
years before that, doing experimentation.
I call it the emo work.
There's no explanation for why we have emotions
in society, why they exist.
It's not just, if you believe that we're
just biochemically stimulated and that's all, then this
is not for you, of course, but there's
no explanation why we are emotional.
But then you'll find, how many times have
you heard of someone going postal, right?
Very calm individual, suddenly they were emotionally motivated
to do some heinous crime or wonderful thing
also goes the other way as well.
So once you learn to take control of
those emotions, you'll find that's where your consciousness
is and your actual body works by emotion,
not by the voice in your head.
And also the emo work creates a field
around your environment that helps you control or
influence things around you, people and material, you
know.
Yeah, the emotional envelops the energetic and the
physical.
That's what it is.
That's what you're actually reading.
The emo is the reading of that.
And it also ties in with the body's
consciousness.
Your body has a slightly different consciousness.
It's a very primitive consciousness.
Like for example, you can say that, yeah.
It's kind of like someone's an intelligent guy,
tired of being here.
He wants to kill himself through drowning.
And as he's drowning himself, there's a voice.
Why are you doing this to me?
I wanna live.
Don't do that, right?
That's the body's consciousness.
You know, that keeps the heart rate and
all that going.
So that also lies in the emo.
If the body gives you a voice like
that, it's very desperate.
It doesn't operate that way.
The body operates only in the emo.
I seem to recall serial killers coming to
that realization when, for example, just after they
slit their own throats or something like that,
they regretted it.
Yeah, it's like this dual.
I'm not saying duality in a sense that,
you know, left and right or black and
white.
It's a very, very minor, small consciousness, right,
that's there, that runs the body.
And you brought up yin yang.
And would you say that that is, you
know, something you can find anywhere, meaning everything
that is, let's say, positive has a counterpart
that is negative and that's how the universe
balances itself?
Yes and no.
It's not static like that.
You know, when you say positive, negative, the
first thing people go to is a battery,
right?
You don't put the battery, positive, negative, corresponding
to the device, it doesn't work.
And it's that battery always has a positive
and always has a negative, right?
It's not like that, really.
I mean, that's a good way to start.
But it's the constant rate of motion.
The only thing that doesn't change is that
things always change.
So everything is in constant flux.
So when something becomes very yin, it attracts
more yang.
But if it becomes so yin to a
limit where it cannot become more yin, it
flips over and becomes yang itself.
For example, let's give a grenade.
Let's just analyze a military grenade.
You hold it in your hand, it's very
heavy, it's very hard.
Everything is packed very tight, even the gas
that's in there or whatever is packed super
tight, that's considered definitely a yang object.
When you engage the grenade and the reaction
begins, what does it do?
Does it get more yang?
Or it's as yang as it can be,
the trigger in a grenade makes it a
little more yang to the point where now
it becomes, what?
Yin, which is expansive and very quickly.
But the expansion happens very quickly in a
yang fashion.
So when something is very yin, you counter
it with something that is yang in small
measure because you don't want to tip it
over, right?
So I'll give you an example.
The human body is really where we apply
this to.
And this might sound crazy, but this is
a true experience.
The top of your head is the most
yang part of the human body and the
bottom of your feet is the most yin
part of the body, right?
So for example, when you hear someone that
has a brain tumor, that is a energy
in the body that is very, very yin
because it rushed up to the most yang
part of the body, right?
So anything ailment on your feet or near
below the knee is a very yang energy
and it rushed down to the yin part
of the body.
And by the way, for the brain tumor,
people try various things that they need to
do is various salts, which are yang, to
contract it.
But if you really want to hit it
hard and fast and make it go away
in a few days, for example, start studying
the yin and yang and you'll come up
with something and I'll give you something I've
come up with and it works, is if
you look at energy perspective, the most yin
energy, the most yin energy is radioactivity, what's
commonly known as radioactivity.
Now, that's how yin, the energy is that
causes an ailment in the brain.
So what can counter that?
Do we know any living organic substance that
counters it?
There is an insect called a cockroach and
it's very well known that it could take
on a manifold many times levels of radioactivity
and still be unaffected where that would kill
other living things, right?
But so that roach, cockroach is extremely yang,
but let's, is there a way to make
it even more yang?
If we take the roach and bake it
until it carbonizes, not burns, but turns black
into carbon, let's say 300 degrees Celsius, 550
degrees for a half an hour you'll have
some very toasted roaches in a cookie sheet,
carbonized, you can break them up in your
hand.
You put them in a gel capsule and
you have the victim with the tumor take
three capsules in the morning, three in the
afternoon and three at night and then go
get a scan about a week later and
try to find that brain tumor.
Sounds kind of crazy, sounds kind of witch
doctor-y, doesn't it?
By the way, if you're going to apply
this, I wouldn't suggest the person that they're
taking capsules of roasted cockroaches, they don't even
have to know.
So I just gave an example of the
power of this universal.
By the way, with ancient healers that were
valid, do you know most ailments were healed
or cured within 24 to 36 hours, 72
hours tops, right?
Within a few days.
Very rapidly because it's all energetic.
The thing is, if you do it, when
you apply energy, principles of energy to anything
physical, what happens if you apply too much
energy to that physical thing?
You can blow it up too, right?
So you have to be careful.
You have to know how to dose it
out.
Do you think that overlaying colors, I heard
that if you project certain colors in a
certain spiral, especially the spiral, do you think
that applying energetics or psi or something using
spirals has a potency effect?
Oh gosh, that's a funny question.
I'll give you a funny answer.
Try it and report back.
Right.
You brought up the cockroaches and another old
time scoop of yours is that these insects
have an elemental entity that governs them and
they're also- Very much like people do,
yeah.
All of these things do.
If that element withdraws, those insects withdraw from
our reality.
Right.
So I guess our elemental are the gods
who put this- I would say they're
partially withdrawn and kind of, yeah, just have
minimal influence on us right now.
Yeah, they use proxies.
Yeah, many levels of, you know, one of
the things that I say is I was
sent here by accident and it was, well,
you know, if someone's religious, they say, well,
God doesn't make accidents, he's perfect.
Yeah, but if you're God, you have admins
working for you, right?
And they're not perfect.
So they screwed up and sent my stupid
ass here and I shouldn't be here, right?
And because I know I shouldn't be here,
I'm not gonna act like I belong here
either, right?
I don't want anything from here.
I just wanna skate through life.
I just wanna skate through and just get
the F out of here, right?
I don't want cars or fancy things or
money or I want good enough fitness, quote
unquote, health, so I don't act like a
lab rat sick here, right?
I just wanna skate through this reality.
I wanna go through the third grade and
not do my homework.
And then just at the end of the
semester, tell me I'm going to the fourth
grade, which is in another different school.
That's my whole reality here.
And the God with a capital G isn't
even mentioned in the Bible.
It's just the fact that all the gods
have been given that name.
Yeah, Yahweh is a man.
If you study it and read it, it's
very clear in Exodus 15.
But does he have an adversary?
Meaning is there a Satan entity?
Let's put it this way.
It's purely political.
Are you pro Biden or pro Trump?
If you're pro Trump, Biden is the devil.
If you're pro Biden, Trump is the devil.
That's all, that's all it is.
Right.
It's political.
Yeah, I heard that the state we're in
now started with the reincarnation blanking and the
fields that are supposed to suppress us and
keep our ages limited happened around 25,000
years ago with the Leviathan races coming and
taking over Atlantis and putting portals around.
I think the time thing is kind of
messed up and I'll tell you why.
Let's just say we had, I don't trust
any of those numbers.
It's fine to discuss them because sometimes they
parcel out and work well, right?
If I go shopping and I say I
have three cans of beans and a dozen
eggs, you can see that, right?
Let's say it's even that good, but I
could show you that those beans are not
really beans and those eggs are not really
eggs.
Or an egg is really an entire chicken.
You know, when you eat an egg, it's
no different energetically than eating an entire chicken.
When you eat chicken, you just eat the
muscle tissue.
You're not eating the organs, the feathers, the
head or anything, right?
But when you eat an egg, you're eating
all of that, right?
So you can get into all the fine
points, the energetics, the portals, the time and
all that.
But time is just, do we wanna talk
about when the event happened or the event?
Because right now, I'll tell you, like I'm
working on several projects.
It'll be eight in the morning and I'm
working on something and I feel like a
half hour just went by.
I should get something to eat.
It's eight in the morning.
But I come in and look at the
clock and it's five o'clock.
How is that possible?
I'm not talking about lost time either because
I know I'm not, you know, I tend
to look at objects to see if they're
changing in real time.
It means I'm in a dream.
I'm not in a dream state, no lost
time.
So the whole thing about when things happened
is I've gotten away from.
I can talk a lot about things that
are going to happen and are happening right
now that I've discussed over a decade ago,
even gave the year.
But in terms of how long things are,
I've really started to separate myself from the
whole thing about time.
No, I'm with you.
Yeah, I heard too many conflicted testimonies that
I can't believe anything.
So basically I'm just going by what's most
compelling.
I agree.
I agree, always, you know.
But about the predictions, I think for the
longest, I mean, for a long time, you
weren't super clear cut about the exact time
and the exact date of the reset, but
after looking at our cakes and maybe other
sources, I think you have concluded that the
reset is not around the corner, but it's
somewhere more along the lines of 2040, which
also falls in line with the greatest, in
my opinion, remote viewing experiment based on the
year 2050, when all the people, they isolated
that time period as the one that will
be the most meaningful and that there will
be no overpopulation, meaning that there must be
a loss of life in the middle there.
Yes, yes.
I think that that'll be more evident around
the 2030 time, because they tend to push,
when the powers that be, like Zan mentioned
earlier, they know what's coming.
Like, for example, you can go underground and
someone will bring a text to you that's
3000 years old and it looks like it
was printed 10 years ago, right?
So everything, all knowledge is preserved, not on
the surface though.
So I would suggest my time, I've always
speculated and said, this is what's coming out
of the biblical text, right?
You have 2000 years here, this time period
here, this is dictated to repeat at this
time and I gave certain specifics and that
seems to be working out.
With the advent of the material from archaics
showing it's more astronomical, geophysical and repeatable, mostly,
there are many events, by the way, that
were just, just as bad as what archaics
talks about that happened that he doesn't talk
about outside of that 138 year periodicity or
that 500 something year periodicity, right?
There are other events that were very similar
to those.
Very difficult to tell on that point.
Again, I've kind of divorced myself from the
speaking out on time at all, the other
past, present or future.
And most of the stuff I'm just qualifying
is stuff that I've derived from the biblical
text because it's such a foundational book that
everyone focuses on, but no one knows what's
in it because they don't read it, right?
They listen to other people who are telling
them what's in it.
Well, they can just read it themselves.
It's pretty simple.
So I would question the veracity of the
biblical text and its accuracy based on tampering,
right?
Or whatever, or how valid it is.
But I'll tell you this, I'm an Old
Testament kind of guy, right?
I would rather get my law from something
like the Old Testament than what the state
is telling me to do in terms of
how I eat, how I do business.
And by the way, if you look at
all the conventional laws, what's considered common law,
that all comes from that text anyways.
No one seems to know it, so why
not, right?
And that's how I pretty much operate.
But I think about the gods, that they
always tend to appoint themselves as our creators.
That's something that signifies them because they want
us to worship them.
Yeah, big egos.
That's something to find in the testimonies as
well, firsthand.
But also, let me give a little diversion
to that.
Some, let's just say, I'm not a fan
of the New Testament because talk about corrupted
texts, but when the JES, the Messiah, there
are more references to those that know, not
believe, but know what's going on to calling
them his brother, his family, not someone to
worship, right?
So just want to put that in there.
There are some elements, quote unquote, of the
gods that consider us to be brothers.
Now, what is a brother, right?
So not, right, you don't worship your brother.
So I just want to throw that in
there.
Yeah, because it's not all about worshiping.
No, and they also apparently see us as
really cherished relations that we're their most prized
possession, maybe, or?
Yeah, it's kind of like when, in America,
they do this, dad spanks the child and
says, this is gonna hurt me more than
it's gonna hurt you, but he spanks him
anyway.
I'm not into that kind of stuff.
So do we have to go through what
we're going through right here?
I mean, most people think about it.
We can have this discussion as many times
and with whoever, but 99% of the
people, let's say 90% of the people
to be more conservative have no clue and
don't care, right?
Everything is fine for them, right?
So we're still talking about a rare, this
is the stuff we're talking about here is
for small, rarefied group.
True, but there must be also a purpose
why they would treasure us, which, yeah, has
to do probably with the ascension cycle, but
more immediately, what would you say is the
main reason why we are so disputed and
so coveted?
Does it have to do with the physicality
and what advantages do we have?
I think it's like that material and non
-material lineage, like someone who's raising chickens, you
have to guard the eggs that the shells
don't crack because those eggs, when they mature,
will become chicks, which will mature and become
chickens to carry on the bloodline and beyond,
and the notion that chickens exist in the
universe even.
I don't know, but what I do know
for sure is that I was sent here
by mistake and I don't belong here and
I'm not gonna act like I do, right?
I know that for sure.
I know we're wasting our time, I know
that for sure.
Very simple, just anyone that you know, love,
don't like, like or not, try to communicate.
It doesn't matter what it is.
It's like, what the hell is going on?
We are not communicating, right?
And we're wasting time.
And I know that for sure.
I know for sure we're in a spiritually
semi, well, we're also in a materially toxic
place.
For example, materially, let's say you find an
unadulterated society living on the surface.
They're living in harmony with the land.
They still get diseases and storms and earthquakes
and outbreaks and attacks by wild animals.
So it's even toxic for the most optimum
situations.
It's very toxic.
How very toxic it is to be here
depends on the perspective, right?
So I know these things are for sure
that I mentioned.
And the rest, those past few things that
I just mentioned, the past minute or so,
is enough for me to chew on that
may or not prevent me from going further.
Why are we cherished or why are we
here or what's going on after and all
that?
And at some point, you know, there's a
mind state, you know, like you can be
hungry and then you get some bad news
and suddenly your appetite goes away.
My appetite is gone for many of these
things here.
I just wanna skate through this reality and
get the F out of here.
And then I'll take what comes as it
comes.
I know there's some people listening to this
say, well, this guy's a real downer, man.
Well, too bad.
Wake up, actually educate yourself.
Because you know, if you go to sleep,
you know, they say people should wake up.
Doesn't make any sense, because if you go
to sleep stupid, you wake up, guess what?
You're still stupid.
You have to educate yourself.
I mean, gain knowledge and workable knowledge that
you can apply based on your capacity, right?
Well, yeah, but that just means that you're
not here to smell the flowers, but you
still have a purpose because otherwise you wouldn't
have this inborn reason to persist.
So it just manifests.
Yeah, there are a lot of good movies.
Let's say a scenario for a movie where
someone's traveling cross country on the dog, you
know, the Greyhound bus, and they get off
on the wrong stop and they're left there.
And then the rest of the movie commences
on their experiences there.
That could make a good film.
You could write a pretty good script around
that, right?
Yeah.
You said once that, which I agree that
90% of this existence, I mean, of
what it boils down to is avoiding the
idiocy around you.
Right.
That puts you in the bedstead.
And that's one of the, and once you
realize that, you know you're not supposed to
be here because it's a waste of time.
There are too many governors, too many limits
here.
And it's, we're limiting ourselves.
You know, like with like, as humans, we
relate with other humans, whatever term you wanna
use as people, men and women.
And when you find out that the majority
is not interested because of some degraded state
that they're in, you know, what does that
do for those that, right?
It's kind of like unpleasant.
So you still have to make it pleasant.
You know, and as I'm getting older, I'm
in my, going into my seventh decade.
I'm 60 now.
I've realized, you know, I don't like what's
called atrocities, injustices, treating people poorly.
But when I start to consciously say I
can see how that can be justified, I
stop myself in question and say, now I'm
feeling a little too angry, right?
You know, like earlier when I said, if
I had the mothership, I'd vaporize the surface.
Yeah, it should be done.
But would I be the one to push
the button?
I'd think twice.
But yeah, that's a requirement almost to really
clean this place up.
But when I start noticing that I hear
about harm being brought to others, I'm like,
oh yeah, maybe they deserved it.
And I start to question myself and say,
you know, it's not for me to think
about those things at all, even whether it
should have happened or whether we should do
anything about it.
If you can do something about it without
making too big of an effort, of course,
hell.
But I'll tell you this.
I've told people that I know for many
years now, when you're driving along the road
in your vehicle, car, your conveyance, and you
see an accident happen, don't hang around and
be a witness or whatever.
But if you see that you can immediately
do something to help, go ahead and help.
But otherwise, just get the F out of
there.
Just get away from it, you know, right?
Don't try to play the Good Samaritan stuff.
Unless you see there's a direct opportunity where
you should do something, yeah?
Otherwise, don't hang around and say, oh, maybe,
maybe, maybe I can help.
No, no, no, no, get the F out
of there.
None of this maybe stuff.
So in other words, make your movements in
life more sure.
Instead of like tracking on programming, oh, there's
an accident, I should stop and see if
they need some help.
No, just get the hell out of there.
Right, that's how I see things going on
in life.
And I'm with you in the sense that
you can say anything.
It sounds maybe fatalistic, but in the end,
it's not what you say that defines you,
it's what you do.
And I really echo the feeling that things
have gotten so bad that they can't get
any worse.
And like we said with the yin-yang,
I think it reached one extremity and it
can only get better.
And that's why you seem jaded, but you're
just being a realist.
Yeah, well, there are many cycles.
Like hard times make good people or strong
people, but then the strong people make good
times, which makes weak people, which then brings
hard times again.
Right, and the cycle keeps going, right?
And we're in the weak part.
Oh, absolutely, yeah.
But the thing is, it's a mix.
We're in the credits.
It's not gonna make sense this time.
There's gonna be a group of very strong
people that are going to just overrun the
weak people.
And there'll be nothing to measure it against
to say like, oh, this happened before.
It's gonna be very unique, be done in
a very different way.
Yeah, so you're gonna see a lot of
that going on.
So as time progresses, things that don't make
sense and they seem like they happened before
and we could use historical references, but this
is a new thing.
Yeah.
Right, and since, just to maybe close it,
since Christmas, so-called Christmas is around the
corner, I just wanted to maybe go over
the fact that I believe it's a celebration
of Nimrod, who is sometimes called Marduk, who
was the Babylonian ruler that was responsible for
untold amount of massacres and was part of
the fallen angelic, so that it's another inversion,
right?
Yeah, I'd say, but if you discuss an
agricultural-based society, which we still are, by
the way, there's a computer, a programmer developer
guy, he's arguing with me that we're not
agricultural and we don't need mining.
And I said, what's that on your blue
jeans?
It's a metal button, well, you need mining
for that.
And are you having lunch today?
What are you eating?
That's agricultural, right?
You can't escape it.
So agricultural, those that master agriculture, master the
seasons and the times, and it would be
the dark, you know how you have spring
celebrations when the days are expanding and the
weather is pleasant?
You have the midwinter dark times of days.
So they decided to mark those things with
a feast or celebration or gathering, just like
we have personal gatherings in our lives, and
anniversaries, whatever, birthdays, people, things that people do.
On a social level, a national level, you
have gatherings and things based on seasonal events.
And one of the things was, you know,
the Saturnalia, how many things in Christmas?
The thing that gets me about Christmas, though,
is this, there's some popular documentaries about Christmas
and they start out by saying, well, we
know that Jesus was not born at this
time, it's actually pagan, but, always, right?
And well, no one knows when he was
born, but if you go to the scripture,
it gives you an astronomical alignment which transcends
any calendrical system.
And if you look at that astronomical alignment
when he was born, it's in the Book
of Revelation, it was around 3 BC on
the month of September on the day of
11, about 6.20 PM.
We get it down to the half hour
because there's more than five or six astronomical
bodies.
You know, the more astronomical bodies you have
in the alignment, the more discerning you could
be on the time.
So September 11th, 3 BC, that's why they
had that big birthday party for him in
New York 20 some odd years ago, right?
So, anyway.
Yeah, it seems that the most obvious things
are the ones that escape us the most
and the ones that we need to work
on the most.
Well, everything is obvious to who, right?
Right.
You know, if we have a really big
secret, I suggest we publish it and put
it in the public library.
No one will ever find it.
Right.
But yeah, that's about all I prepared for
today, so.
Well, that's fine.
Good, I came unprepared as usual.
Oh, it's okay.
Yeah, no, we're just happy to have you.
I mean, I could go on forever.
I have tons of stuff, but I mean,
Greg, I just wanna be conscious of your
time, but I appreciate you being here with
us.
Greg, if you'd like to conclude or take
reins while we both shut the fuck up,
you know?
No, no, it's fine.
I have a shitty paywall with Ocelli.
It's called Rated Y.
You could, I don't even really promote it
and whatever, like I said, it's behind a
shitty paywall.
If you contact Ocelli at ocelli.com, if
you're interested in joining, that's fine.
It's called Rated Y.
And because it's behind a paywall, it's not
public, and I can discuss things on a
more deep level and things that shouldn't be
discussed.
Let's say, you know, if you do a
public website, you're subject to whatever you wanna
call it, you know, censorship.
So I feel pretty free discussing things there.
It's ongoing.
We do about two, I don't do shows.
They're called sonic events.
Because, you know, when I hear the word
show, I'm looking for where's the donkey, where's
the girl, you know?
But anyway, yeah, so there's sonic events.
And right now we're doing more of the
private, I'm gonna be discussing more on the
human body and discussing more of the realm
here, how to operate in it and prosper,
be completely prosperous in it.
And that just doesn't mean, financial also, and
prosper, you know?
And we discuss things like there's no such
thing as health.
That's a stupid term, you know?
It's fitness.
What level of fitness do you wanna attain?
And, you know, many of the emo work,
you know, all this other stuff.
Yeah, I guess I'm shamelessly promoting it, but
I'm not, you know, don't contact me to
join.
Just go to ocelli.com, message him or
whatever.
He'll show you the way to get there,
you know?
Because it's private, you get into much deeper
stuff that you hadn't previously.
Yeah, that's how it should be, right?
I think, Zan, you know about that.
You start going and doing public whatever YouTubes
or whatever long enough and you're gonna, right?
You're gonna have- That's the first step.
That's the baby step to try and get
you to stop.
Because if I was really onto something, you
know, I wouldn't even be here breathing.
But yes, yes, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So anyway, I appreciate you guys.
I like you both very much in terms
of doing this kind of stuff.
I think your audiences, I say your audiences,
or the audience appreciates us three getting, having
a chat during the Sonic event.
So it's all good all around.
Yeah, great.
Thanks for having me.
Yeah, it's really nice because I just don't
get this in life or the way I
can deduce things.
And I don't know, it's like, it's like
I wish my dad had this knowledge or
whatever, but I don't mean to sit here
and fawn over you or gush.
I'm just saying, you know, I just, I
don't know, man.
It's like you're the older brother I never
had or whatever, but it's just, it's very
nice to give us the time of day.
And thank you so much for letting us
record this session and sorry to hold y
'all up.
I just like to always express my thanks.
I do not take this for granted, but
anyway, thank you so much.
Oh, I know you don't.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you both again.
Take care.
Bye.